All right Jim your
quarterlies look very good.
How the thing is
going at the library ?
Oh I told you
couldn’t close it so…
So you’ve come to the
master for…guidance ?
Is this what you’re
saying grasshopper?
Actually you call
me in here, but yeah.
All right, well let me
show you how it’s done.
Yes, I liked to speak to
your office manager please…
yes hello this is Michael
Scott, I am the regional manager
of dundler Mifflin
paper products.
Just wanted to talk to
you manager à manager.
All right done deal,
thank you very much sir,
you’re a gentleman
in the scolar.
Oh I’m sorry, ok,
I’m sorry, my mistake.
That was a woman I was talking
to... she had a very low voice.
Probably a smoker.
So…so that’s the
way it’s done.
I’ve been in Dundler
Mifflin for twelve years,
the last four as
regional manager
If you want to
come through here,
so we have the
entire floor,
so this is my kingdom,
as far as the eye can see,
ah this is our
receptionist Pam.
Pam, Pam Pam! Pam Beesly.
Pam has been with us for…
for ever, right Pam?
Well, I don’t know!
If you think
she’s cute now
you should have seen her
a couple of years ago!
What?
Any messages?
Yeah, just a fax
Pam this is
from corporate.
How many times have I
told you that there’s
a special filing cabinet
for things from corporate.
You haven’t told me!
It’s called the
wastepaper basket.
Look at that !
Look at that face!
People say I’m
the best boss.
They go, "God we've never worked
in a place like this before,
you’re hilarious, and you
get the best out of us.”
I think that pretty
much sums it up
I found it at
Spencer Gifts.
My job is to
speak to clients
on the phone
about quantities
and type of copier paper.
You know, whether
we can supply to them
whether they can
pay for it and...
I’m boring myself just
talking about this.
He still loves that
after seven years!
What?
Nothing
Ok, all right.
See you later
All right, take care.
Back to work.
Corporate really doesn’t interfere
with me at all, Jan Levinson-Gould
Jan, hello!
I call her Hillary
Rodham Clinton, right?
Not to her face because,
not because I’m scared
of her, because I’m not
but...
yeah.
All right, was it anything you
wanted to add to the agenda?
Me no get an agenda.
I’m sorry, what?
I didn’t get any agenda.
Oh I faxed one
overdue this morning.
Really? Cause I didn’t…did
we get a fax this morning?
Yeah, the one…
Why isn’t it in my hand?
Because a company runs on
efficiency of communication, right?
So what’s the problem
Pam, why I didn’t get it?
You put it in the garbage can
that was a special filing cabinet.
Yeah, that was a joke, that
was actually my brother's,
it was supposed to be with bills
and doesn’t work great with faxes.
Do you want to
look at mine?
Yeah. Thank you.
Ok since the last meeting,
Alan and the board have decided
that we can’t justify Scranton
branch and the Stafford branch
Oh ok…
No, Michael don’t panic
No no no no this is
good, this is fine
Michael listen,
don’t panic
We haven’t made
any decisions yet,
I’ve spoken to Joshua in Stanford
I’ve told him the same as you
and it’s up to either you or him to convince
me that your branch can incorporate the other
Ok no problem
This does however mean that
there is going to be downsizing
Me no wanna
hear that Jan,
because downsizing
is a bitch,
it is a real bitch,
and I wouldn’t wish
that on Joshua’s men,
I certainly wouldn’t
wish it on my men,
or women present
company excluded...sorry.
is Josh concerned about
downsizing himself?
Not downsizing himself but is
he concerned about downsizing?
Question: how long
do we have to …
Oh, Todd Paker, terrific
rep, do you mind if I take it?
No, go ahead
Pac man!
Hey, you big queen
Oh, that’s
not appropriate
Hey, is old god zillary
coming in today?
I don’t know
what you mean
Look, I've been meaning to
ask her one question
Does the carpet match
the drapes?
Oh my god!
That's so
horrifying! Horrible
Horrible person!
So do you think we can keep…a lid on this for
now I don’t want to worry people unnecessarily.
No, absolutely. Under this regime,
it will not leave this office.
So what is downsizing
actually mean?
Well
You guys gotta update your
resume, just like I’m doing.
I bet it’s gonna
be me, probably.
Yeah, it’ll be you
I have an important
question for you.
Yes
Are you going to Angela's
club party on Sunday?
Yeah, stop.
That’s ridiculous.
Am I gonna tell them? No I’m not going to
tell them, I don’t see the point of that.
As a doctor you would not tell
a patient if they had cancer.
This is Mister Scott.
Ryan Howard from
the temp agency
Deniqua sent me down to
start today
Howard, like Moe
Howard, Three Stooges?
Right here, my vibe. Oh
Pam, that’s a guy thing Pam.
I’m sort of a
student in comedy
I’m Hitler, Adolf Hitler
I don't think it would be the
worst thing if they let me go.
Because then I might
It’s just, I don't think it's many
girls dream to be a receptionist.
I like to do
illustrations,
mostly water color,
a few oil pencil.
Jim thinks they’re good.
Dundler Mifflin
this is Pam.
Sure, Mr. Davis, let
me call you right back.
Yeah, some just came up, two
minutes. Thank you very much.
Dwight, what
are you doing?
- What?
- What are you doing?
Just clearing my desk,
I can’t concentrate
- It's not on your desk.
- It’s overlapping.
It's all coming
over the edge.
One word, two
syllables : demarcation.
- You can't do that.
- Why not?
Safety violation, I could
fall and pierce, and organ.
We'll see
This is why the whole downsizing
thing just doesn't bother me.
Downsizing?
I have no problem with that. I have been
recommending downsizing since Halpert got here
even brought it
up on my interview.
I say, bring it on!
You just still have messages for
yesterday. Relax everything is under control
Yeah, yeah, yeah oh
that’s important, right.
Oh, this is so important,
I should run to answer it.
What?
Come on. Six million
dollars man, Steve Austin,
actually that would be a good salary for
me don’t you think? Six million dollars?
Memo to Jan: I
deserve a raise
Don’t we all?
I’m sorry?
There’s nothing!
If you are unhappy with your compensation,
maybe you should take it up with HR,
ok? Not today, ok? Pam
just, be professional.
I think I’m a role model here, I
think I garner other people respect.
Attention on Dundler Mifflin employees, please
we have a meeting in the conference room ASAP
People I respect, heros
of mine, would be Bob Hope,
Abraham Lincoln,
definitely,
Bono,
and probably God
be the fourth one.
And I just think all those people
really helped the world, in so many ways,
that it’s, it’s
really beyond words.
It’s really uncalculable.
Now, I know there’s some rumors out
there, and I just kind want to see….
I’m assistant regional
manager, I should know first.
Assistant to the
regional manager.
Ok. Can you just
tell me please?
Just a whisper in my ear.
I’m about to
tell everybody.
I'm just about
to tell exeryone
Please, ok.
Do you want me
to tell them?
You don’t know
what it is!
Can you tell them,
with my permission?
I don’t need your...
Permission
granted. Go ahead
Corporate has deemed it appropriate
to enforce an ultimatum upon me,
and Jan is thinking about downsizing
either the Stanford branch or this branch.
I heard they might be
closing this branch down,
That's just...
That's just the rumor going around this
is my first day I don’t really know.
Yeah, but Michael what
if they downsize here?
Not gonna happen
It could be out of
your hands, Michael
It won't be out of
my hands, Stanley, ok?
I promise you that.
Can you promise that?
On his mother's grave.
Well yeah it is a promise, and frankly I’m a little
bit insulted that you have to keep asking about it.
It’s just that
we need to know
Hold on a second, I think Pam
wanted to say something, Pam?
You had a look that you wanted
to ask a question, just then?
I was in the meeting with Jan and she did said
that it could be this branch that gets the axe.
Are you sure about that?
Pam? Maybe you should stick to the ongoing
confidentiality agreement of meetings.
Pam, information
is power.
So you can't say for sure whether
it's gotta to be us or them.
No no, no Stanley, no you did
not see me in there with her.
I said, if corporate wants to come in here, and
interfere then they’re gonna have to go through me, right?
You know, you can go a
mess with Josh’s people,
but I’m the head
of this family,
and you ain’t gonna be
messing with my children.
If I left, what would I do with all
this useless information in my head?
You know, tonnage
price of minal folders?
Pam’s favorite flavor of
yoghourt, which is mix berry.
Jim said mix berries?
Yeah he’s under me
Watch out for this guy Dwight
Schrute in the building!
This is Ryan,
the new temp.
Nice to meet you.
Introduce
yourself, be polite
Dwight Schrute, Assistant
Regional Manager.
Assistant to the
So Dwight tell him about the kung
fu, and the car and everything.
Yeah, I got a 78-2-8 , I’ve bought her
for 1200, fixed it up, now worth three grand.
That is his profit!
New engine, suspension
I’ve got some photos
Damn it!
Ok, hold on,
Judge is in cession.
What is the problem here?
He put my stuff
in jello again.
That’s rough
professional, thanks
That's the third time and it
wasn't funny the first time.
It’s ok here, but people some how is
taking advantage because it's so relaxed.
I’m a volunteer sheriff's
deputy on the week ends,
and you cannot
screw around there.
It's one of the rules.
What is that?
That’s my stapler.
No no no, do
not take it out!
You have to eat
it out there,
because there are starving
people in the world,
and which I hate, and it is
a waste of that kind of food.
Ok, you know what?
You can be a witness.
Can you reprimand
him please?
- How do you
know it was me?
- It's always you.
- Are you gonna
discipline him or not?
Ooh discipline, kinky!
All right, here’s
the deal you guys
the thing about practical jokes, is that you have
to know when to start, as well as when to stop!
And yeah, Jim, now is the time to stop
pulling Dwight’s personal effects into jello.
Ok, Dwight I’m sorry because,
I’ve always been your biggest Flam
Nice, that’s the
way it is around here
You should have put
him in custard-y!
Yes, new guy!
He scores !
Ok that’s great, I guess,
what I’m most
concerned with is...
damage to
company property.
That’s all.
Pudding…
I’m trying to think,
another desert to do.
Do you like to going out at
the end of a week for a drink?
Yeah!
Oh, that’s why we all going out, so
we can have an end of the week drink!
well then when
are we going out?
I don’t know,
tonight, hopefully.
Ok, yeah.
Hey man!
Hey!
What’s going on?
Hey baby!
Roy is my fiancé, we’ve
been engaged about...
about 3 years, and we were supposed
to get married in September,
but I think we’ll gonna
get married in next spring
Do you mind if I go out
for a drink with these guys?
No, come on. Let’s get
out of here and go home.
Ok, I will be out in a
few minutes so it’s lame
twenty past five I’ve
still to do my faxes.
You know you
should come with us,
because you know we are going out and
it could be a good chance for you to
see what people are like outside
the office, I think it could be fun
No, it sounds good but
seriously we gotta get going
Yeah
What's in the bag?
Just tell her i'll
talk to her then
No definitely all right
dude awesome, we’ll do
Do I think I’ll be
invited to the wedding?
So, have you
felt vibe yet?
We work hard,
we play hard.
Sometimes we play hard when we
should be working hard, right?
I guess the atmosphere that I've
created here is that I am a friend first,
and a boss second.
Probably an
entertainer third.
Just a second
Right?
Oh, hey do you like the
Jamie Kennedy Experiment?
Yeah
Punk'd, and all
that kind of stuff?
You are going to be my complice,
just go on with that ok?
All right
Just follow my lead,
don’t pimp me all right?
Come in!
So corporate just said
that I don’t want to…
…you got a fax
Oh thank you Pam
Pam? Can you come
in here for a sec?
Just have a seat, I was gonna
call you in anyway, you know Ryan?
As you know, there is
going to be downsizing
and you have made my
life so much easier,
in that I’m going to
have to let you go first
What? Why?
Why? Well, theft,
and stealing
Stealing?
What am I suppose
to have stolen?
Post-It notes.
Post-It notes...?
Worth of those
like 50 cents?
You steal a thousand Post-It
notes at 50cents a piece,
then you know you’ve
made a profit margin.
Resell of business Pam
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
I can’t believe
this, I mean,
I have never even stolen as much as
a paper clip and you're firing me.
And the best thing
about it is that
we are not gonna have to
give you any severance pay,
because that is
gross misconduct, and…
just clean out your
desk. I’m sorry.
You’ve been X'd punk'd!
Surprise it’s a joke, we
were joking around, you see?
Ok, he was in on he
was my accomplice and
It was kind of a morale
booster thing, and
we were showing the new guy around the
kind of, giving him the field to play, so…
God, you were, we
totally got you…
…you’re a jerk
Well, I don’t
know about that
What is the most important
thing for a company?
Is it the cash flow?
Is it the inventory?
No it’s the people.
The "people".
My proudest moment here was not
when I increased profits by 17%,
or when I cut expenses without
losing a single employee.
No, no, no, no.
It was a young
Guatemalan guy,
a first job in the country,
barely spoke English,
came to me and said
"Mr Scott,
would you be the
Godfather to my child?"
Didn't work out in the end. We
had to let him go. He sucked.
Hey
Hey how are you?
Good I thought you were
going out for a drink with…
Oh no
How’s your headache?
Better, thanks.
Good
Are you
Walking out?
Yes
Yes do you wanna?
Yeah
Great, let me just
Oh Roy
Yeah, listen have
a nice week-end!
Yeah definitely
you too! Enjoy it
Come here
The World’s Best Boss