Where is my desk?
That is weird.
This is not funny.
This is totally unprofessional.
Okay. Well, you're the one
who lost the desk.
I didn't lose my desk.
Calm down. Where was
the last place you saw it?
Okay, who moved my desk?
I think you should retrace
your steps.
Okay, I am going
to tell Michael
and this entire office
will be punished.
Colder.
Warmer.
Little warmer.
There you go.
Ooh, warmer.
Warmer.
With enthusiasm.
Warmer. Warmer.
Cold. Cold. Cold.
Back up.
Ooh. Ooh. Warmer.
Hot. Red hot. Hot.
Very hot.
Dwight Schrute.
Hi, Dwight.
Um, what sort of discounts
are we giving
on the 20 pound white?
Jim, I've given you
this information like 20 times.
I know.
It's by the ream?
Uh, yeah.
It is now 9.78.
So it's a discount of 7%.
Okay, thank you.
Gotta get back to work.
Wash your hands, Kevin.
Right.
Oh, well, let me just
check the pricing list.
Hold on one second.
Sensei.
Hello, it's sempai.
You know what, let me
give you a call right back.
I'm going to find it
and then I'll call you back.
Thanks.
Yes, I just had a ques...
Yes, sensei.
Arigato goazai mashta.
Hai.
Was that your mom?
No. That was my sensei.
Oh, thought it was your mom.
I am now sempai,
which is assistant sensei.
Assistant to the sensei,
that's pretty cool.
Assistant sensei.
Okay.
I am a practitioner
of Goju-Ryu Karate
here in Scranton.
Huh!
- 2.
- Huh!
Dwight,
stamp and kick back. 3.
Huh!
My sensei, Ira,
recently promoted me
to purple belt
and gave me the duties
of a sempai.
Not that a lot of people
here in America
know what a sempai is.
But it's equally as respected
as a sensei.
I don't want to stay
until 7:00 again this year.
I don't really have
any control over that, Stanley.
Michael tends
to procrastinate a bit
whenever he has to do work.
Um, time cards.
He has to sign these
every Friday.
Purchase orders
have to be approved
at the end of every month.
And expense reports.
All he has to do
is initial these
at the end of every quarter.
But once a year, it all falls
on the same Friday.
And that's today.
I call it the perfect storm.
Did you ask me here
for any specific reason?
Ah, yes. I did.
Here's the bizzle.
I have a very top secret
mission for you.
I want you to update all the
emergency contact information.
Why is that secret?
Hello. Oh, God.
Busy work. Get away.
Get away.
Ah, cretin.
Um, I put stickers
so you know where to sign.
Yes, thanks.
I know where to sign.
It's just that last year, you...
Last year,
they were out of order,
weren't they, Pam?
Well, the last pickup
for overnight deliveries
is at 7:00, so you need
to have them signed by then
or much earlier.
Chillax, Pam.
Stop Pam-MSing.
That's pretty good.
Um, actually, I'm sending Ryan
on a top secret mission.
Tell her what it is.
Updating emergency contacts.
Well, is that really a priority?
Is it a priority?
Oh, I don't know.
Um, what if there's
a tornado, Pam?
People's legs are crushed
under rubble.
Please, would you be so kind
as to call my wife?
No. I can't.
Because we don't have any
emergency contact information
because Pam said
it wasn't a priority.
Think.
Think with your head, Pam.
Okay, well, she walks out.
That's the problem
with being a boss
is that when you are tough,
they resent you
and when you are cool,
they walk all over you.
Catch-22.
Catch-22. Yes.
Why don't you give me
your contact information
to start with, okay?
What's your cell?
Uh, Larissa Halpert.
What's her address?
Uh, Vonburgen Street.
Hello.
Hey, Ryan.
This is Michael Jackson
calling from Wonderland.
You mean Neverland?
This is Tito.
What?
Your major and minor lines
cross at a ridge.
That sucks.
You're making this up
as you go along, aren't you?
I am just following
the web site.
Well...
at least I don't have cavities.
Yes, you have very nice teeth.
Thanks.
Who's your emergency contact?
Stacey.
Pick up.
Hello?
This is Mike Tyson.
Hey, Dwight.
As sempai, do you ever think
there's gonna be a day
where humans and robots
can peacefully coexist?
Impossible.
The way they're programmed...
You're mocking me.
No, I'm not.
Well, let me offer you
a little piece of advice.
I am not afraid
to make an example out of you.
Well, that's not advice.
What advice sounds like is this.
Um, don't ever bring
your purple belt to work
because someone might steal it.
Okay, give that back to me.
Okay, say please.
No. That is not a toy.
Please.
Good. And it absolutely
is a toy.
Arigato.
This is not a toy.
This is a message
for the entire office
so that everyone
could see that I am capable
of physically dominating them.
And this is more
of a yin yang thing.
The Michael is all cursive,
Scott all caps.
Left brain, right brain.
Or a duality of man.
Could you practice on the forms?
No women or children
unless provoked.
Okay. Roy.
Warehouse guy.
Doesn't count.
Okay. Michael.
Could you beat up Michael?
Yeah, I don't think
that would happen.
Cause we're friends.
Because I would kick his ass.
Well, Dwight's purple belt.
So? I've beat up
black belts. Yeah.
How'd you know
they were black belts?
They told me after.
See, I used to run
with a very tough crowd,
street fighter types.
Real, real bad people.
I'm just lucky I got out.
Is your wife still your contact?
Uh, ex-wife, yeah.
Uh, her last name is Becker now.
Okay.
You don't need to write "ex".
And after that,
nobody ever messed with
the damn rascals ever again.
Sounds tough.
When you're a Jet,
you're a Jet all the way, right?
You're a Jet?
Have you signed
the expense reports yet?
Yes, in theory I have.
I just need to cross
some Ts and dot some Is.
All right.
I am going to be in my office,
if anybody needs me.
Hoo! Ha!
Oh, wow.
Michael.
Sleeper hold.
Bed time for vato.
Oh.
Stop it.
Oh ho ho ho.
You are the weakest link.
Ow!
I'm friends with everybody
in this office.
We're all best friends.
I love everybody here.
But sometimes your best friends
start coming in to work late
and start having dentist
appointments
that aren't dentist
appointments.
And that is when it's nice
to let them know
that you could beat them up.
Just hit me.
You'll see.
I can't.
Cause I just got a manicure.
Oh, queer!
Eye. Queer Eye.
That's a good show.
Important show.
Go ahead. Do it.
Just have Dwight punch you.
Oh, yeah. Well, that would
be kind of worthless
because I know
a ton of 14-year-old girls
who could kick his ass.
You know a ton
of 14-year-old girls.
Look. Dwight is a wuss.
When we rented Armageddon,
he cried at the end of it.
No, Michael, I told you.
That was because
it was New Year's Eve
and it started to snow
at exactly midnight.
Bruce Willis.
They're going to leave him
on the asteroid.
Okay, I'll punch you.
Oh, okay.
Here we go.
All right. Come on.
Gah!
Oh!
Did I want to harm Michael,
the one man
I've been hired to protect?
No, I did not.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Thank you.
I come from a long line
of fighters.
My maternal grandfather
was the toughest guy
I ever knew.
World War II veteran.
Killed 20 men
then spent the rest of the war
in an allied prison camp.
My father battled
blood pressure and obesity
all his life.
Different kind of fight.
Okay, he has to be stopped.
Please, please, please,
please, just ask Michael.
I don't know.
Ha.
Okay. I'll buy you
a bag of chips.
French onion?
Obviously. Why are
you spinning around?
Okay.
Yes.
Take this pen.
Go away.
I just have a quick question.
I haven't signed them yet, okay?
No, it's not that.
Um, I was just wondering,
since I'm probably going
to have to stay late,
could you ask Dwight
to stay late too
so he can walk me to my car?
Come in.
Uh, Pam,
but Dwight can't stop you
from being mugged.
He's just not tough enough.
He's a purple belt.
That's really high.
Oh, I could beat up Dwight.
That's ridiculous.
I can murder him.
It's just that out there, you...
Oh, is that what they're saying?
Yeah, kind of.
Okay. All right.
Where's Dwight?
Uh, kitchen.
Okay.
Try it again. Here we go.
Hi-yah!
Good.
Wow, it was actually
pretty good, right?
Excellent. Now watch.
Let me take you from behind.
- What?
- Watch out, Kelly.
Might sucker punch you.
I didn't sucker punch you,
Michael.
In case you didn't remember,
I was defending my honor.
Like a samurai.
Really?
Yeah. Well, the offer, Dwight,
was for one punch,
which I absorbed.
I had no idea that there'd be
a second punch.
So catch-22.
Okay, fine. Tit for tit.
Give it your best shot.
Two punches. Go.
Look. If we were in a bar
right now,
there would be two punches.
Me punching you
and you hitting the floor.
No, I'd block your first punch
rendering you ineffective.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
You know what,
you're just lucky
that we're at work right now.
Ooh, what about Dwight's dojo?
No, they just have classes.
It's free during the day.
It's fine.
I've got the key.
Hey, Michael.
Hey, Toby. Any word
on those time cards?
Hey, you know what?
I have an idea.
Why don't you leave right now?
Why don't you walk
away from the room, okay?
Fine.
We'll go at lunch.
Pam, make an announcement.
Figure out carpools.
Um, well, we're all
getting excited
to see this fight.
The Albany Branch is working
right through lunch
to prevent downsizing.
But Michael, he decided
to extend our lunch
by an hour so that we could
all go down to the dojo
and watch him fight Dwight.
Fight. Fight.
Fight. Fight. Fight. Fight.
Fight. I'm coming. Fight.
Sorry.
I recognize that.
That is Japanese
for California roll.
Uh, no, it's not.
I think it is.
A guy told me about that.
Actually, it's a symbol
for eternal discipline.
Oh.
Wow. That is really
interesting.
What?
Your love l...
I'm just kidding.
I can't see anything.
Look closer.
Okay.
One point for me.
Tied up.
Oh, you're dead.
What? What are you
going to do?
Bring it, Beesly.
Bring it.
Ooh, yeah. Good move.
Ooh, not such
an ultimate fighter now, huh?
Oh, put me down.
Put me down.
Oh my God.
Hey, put me down.
Hey.
Okay, gentlemen, listen up.
After a clean strike
to the chest,
stomach, or kidneys,
I will separate you
and award a point.
First person
to three wins, all right?
Yes, sensei.
Lot of rules.
Lot of rules. On the street,
we didn't have any rules.
Maybe one. No kicks
to the groin.
Home for dinner.
Hajime!
Ha-yah!
Whoa, hey!
What the hell was that?
Dwight.
Yes!
No way.
One point.
All right. That's the way you
want to do it?
Two more! You want to play dirty, huh?
Okay, game on, man.
Sweep the leg.
I'm coming at you, man.
Ha!
Okay, purple belt.
Okay.
I got it.
No.
I got his pants.
That was my pants.
No points for pants.
Dwight, you have...
No, look.
No, you have something.
You have something.
God, you look like such
an idiot.
Hoo! Ha ha!
Clean technique, gentlemen.
Come on. Do that again.
Do that again.
I dare you.
Ha!
Okay, break.
Break. No holding.
Oh, you can't see?
You can't see?
One point. Two points.
Three points.
Break.
I win. I win.
No, you didn't.
No you...
Eight point.
Nine point.
Stop it. No.
Come on. Michael!
Open your mouth.
No, Michael!
You talkin' to me?
Raging Bull. Pacino.
Oh, I want that footage.
I want it.
I need it.
Oh, I have to get back to work.
I have lots of work.
Oh, oh, oh.
Check this out.
Come here.
There he is.
Mr. temp.
Having lunch by the car.
Let us play with him.
See what we can learn.
Oh we're playing phone tag.
Seven new messages.
First new message.
Hi, Ryan. This is
Saddam Hussein.
Next message.
Hey, Ryan. This is
your girlfriend.
And I'm mad.
My emergency contact
is Todd Packer.
Todd F. Packer.
You know what the F standings for?
Fudge?
Uh, come in.
Oh, hey, Karate Kid.
The Hilary Swank version.
Hi. How are you?
I need to change my emergency
contact information
from Michael Scott.
Okay, to what?
Just put... the hospital.
Contact number, just put 911.
He is such a sore loser.
You heard obviously
that I mopped the floor
with him this afternoon.
You know what,
um, do yourself a favor.
Just leave me as his contact
and I will call the hospital.
Cut out the middleman.
Later, Jim.
Later, Kev.
Have a good weekend.
Yeah, you too.
Yeah.
Have the emergency contacts.
Just lay 'em on the chair.
I'll take it from here.
So what you up to this weekend?
Uh, hanging out
with some friends probably.
Well, if you do anything crazy,
give me a shout.
Yeah. All right.
I will, um, see you Monday.
All right. Bye.
Dwight.
Michael, did you finish yet?
This close. Dwight, may I
speak with you for a minute?
Uh, I'm busy.
Well, busier.
But I'm making the time.
Michael, can't your
conversation wait till Monday?
Well, you don't even have
anybody to go home to, Toby.
The shipping place closes
in a half hour.
I know. But I've been carrying
the load on my back all day.
And if everyone would just
chip in a little bit,
might help me out.
What do you say?
Let's gang bang
this thing and go home.
Good? Dwight.
This is illegal.
I don't care.
I have been testing you
the entire day.
Did you know that?
Of course.
And I'm happy to say
that you passed.
So effective immediately,
I am promoting you
from assistant
to the regional manager
to assistant regional manager.
Michael...
I don't know...
I know. I know. I know.
I know.
I wouldn't be offering it
if I didn't think
you could handle it.
I can handle it.
I can.
I know. Okay.
Wow.
So I guess this'll
just be my office.
No.
No. Title change only.
I'll have Pam send out a memo.
No. No. Three month
probationary period.
Let's just not tell anybody
about this right now.
Just a formality?
Absolutely.
But not really.
Michael...
I have so much
to learn from you.
Yes, you do.
Thank you...
sensei.
And ditto.
I told Dwight
that there is honor in losing,
which as we all know
is completely ridiculous.
But there is however honor
in making a loser feel better,
which is what I just did
for Dwight.
Would I rather be
feared or loved?
Um, easy. Both.
I want people to be afraid
of how much they love me.
And I think I proved that today
at the dojo.
Typewriter torture.
Sensei, help.
No.
Typewriter.