I am actually looking forward
to take your daughter
to work day.
I am not great with kids.
But I wanna get better
because I'm getting married.
So I put out a bunch
of extra candy on my desk
so the kids
will come talk to me.
Like the witch
in Hansel and Gretel.
Bribery.
Nice.
Oh, I have more.
It's Pam.
Ms. Beasley
if you're nasty.
Janet Jackson.
Hey, you having
a wardrobe malfunction, or...
You can't be nasty today.
Oh, God.
Is that today?
I reminded you last night.
Listen, I like kids.
But this is not
a kids environment.
This is like HBO.
No limits.
Who knows what I'm gonna say?
Crazy stuff.
And it is R rated.
It is not rated G.
I am like Eddie Murphy in Raw.
And they are trying
to make me into
Eddie Murphy in Daddy Daycare.
Both great movies, but still.
Well, I'll be in my office.
Don't you think
you should say something?
They're cool.
Michael, I think
that as the boss, you should...
Fine fine fine fine fine!
Hi, children.
I'm Michael Scott.
And I am in charge
of this place.
Uh, how do I make you
understand?
I am like Superman.
And the people who work here
are like citizens
of Gotham city.
That's Batman.
Okay, I'm Aquaman.
Where does he live, guys?
The ocean.
I work with a bunch of nerds.
Mmm.
Hello, tiny one.
Come on.
You are the future.
This is my file cabinet.
Um...
Oh, this is the partition
between my desk
and Angela's.
Abby's my fiancé Stacy's
daughter.
I think she'll have a good time.
I just hope she doesn't
look on my computer.
Actually, I'd better go check.
Michael, you remember
my daughter Melissa.
Oh, yes.
Hello, how are you?
Good to see you.
Wow, you've really grown up.
You know what?
Don't mind me saying so.
She is turning into
a stone cold fox.
Better keep the frat boys
away from her.
I'm in 8th grade.
Oh...
She's in middle school.
Yeah, middle school's amazing.
It is extraordinary.
An extraordinary time.
It's not that children
make me uncomfortable.
It's just that, why be a dad
when you can be a fun uncle?
I've never heard
of anyone rebelling
against their fun uncle.
They want how many spiral pads?
Uh, well, 50.
I over ordered because
they had a back order.
I got permission
to bring Jakey in to work.
Which is great because
he got suspended this week,
and now I don't have to
pay for a sitter.
Can you pull that down there?
Okay, tell 'em
what you wanted to say.
Do you need any help?
No, thanks.
We'd have to explain everything.
It's probably just easier
if we do it ourselves.
All right,
I wasn't expecting that.
Let's go draw.
Oh, my God.
She is so cute, I wanna die.
Don't you just
love kids, Angela?
I guess I wouldn't mind a pair
of small, well behaved boys.
God, I cannot wait
to get pregnant
and have babies.
Kelly and I both agreed
that we would just have fun.
And I'm learning
that fun for Kelly
is getting married
and having babies.
Immediately.
With me.
Just compare last year's orders
with this year's.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I'm looking
at it right now.
Yes.
We...
Yeah, they're very...
They're different.
Yeah, we can stick
with last year's.
We're just gonna have to
supplement it somehow.
Hey, Abby, do you wanna help me
shred some old documents?
It's actually pretty cool.
No, thanks.
I only have one goal today.
To make one kid like me.
Just one.
What are you reading?
From the Mixed Up Files
of Mrs. Basil E. Frankweiler.
Oh, best book.
Yeah, but I read it before.
So have I.
Hey, question, if you had
to spend the night in the Met
or the aquarium,
which would it be?
Definitely the aquarium.
Definitely.
Yes.
Glad you said that.
You don't wanna help me
with some of my sales, do you?
'Cause I'm kinda swamped.
Sure.
Really?
Mmm-hmm.
Yes.
And you're Abby, right?
Yeah.
I'm Jim.
Let's sell some paper.
All right.
Let's start with your mom.
Yes.
Well, we can...
Um...
Hey, you know what?
Can I call you back?
I'll call you right back.
Yes, I promise.
Hello.
Can I help you?
You can pick that up
if you want.
That's all right.
Wanna bring it over...
Here, I'll make some room.
My name's Michael.
What's your name?
Sasha.
Nice to meet you.
Ooh!
Oh, you know what that is?
That is a train whistle.
Like I'm the conductor.
But I'm sort of the conductor
of the office here, right?
You wanna try?
Sure.
All aboard for sales!
Next stop,
Cook... camonga!
Ow ow ow ow, you broke my hand.
There is no way that hurt.
Really? 'Cause she's
pretty strong, Dwight.
Little girl, come over here.
Shake my hand.
Come on, I don't have all day.
I didn't feel anything.
Nothing.
You're so weak.
Excuse me, these are
expensive collector's items.
Okay?
Do you have any computer games?
No, I don't have computer games
on my work computer.
That would be inappropriate.
Yeah, Meredith doesn't
have any either.
It's so lame here.
You call your mom Meredith?
That's very disrespectful.
Whatever, okay?
You can refer to me
as Mr. Schroot.
That's your name?
Mm-hmm.
Mr. Poop?
Schroot.
Mr. Schroot.
Sure, Mr. Poop.
Schroot.
Are you Mother Goose?
I drink, like,
100 iced macchiatos a day
and practically nothing else.
Wow.
There's a really
cool coffee place, Jitters,
at the Steamtown Mall.
You ever been there?
No.
You've never been to Jitters?
Ryan, you are so dorky.
Give me your number
so I can text you.
Um...
Come on.
Can I have your email address?
I just thought
you should know...
Mmm-hmm?
I think something
a little fishy is going on.
A little fishy?
Yeah.
I mean, I've been
noticing them all day.
And I was thinking...
That little girl is a child!
I don't wanna see you
sniffing around her
anymore this afternoon.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Boy, have you lost your mind?
'Cause I'll help you find it.
Whatcha looking for?
Ain't nobody gonna
help you out there.
Jesus can come
through that door,
if you don't stop sniffing
after my child. Okay.
Stanley yelled at me today.
That was one of the most
frightening experiences
of my life.
That was Greensleeves.
A traditional English ballad
about the beheaded Anne Boleyn.
And now, a very special treat.
A book my granmutter
used to read me
when I was a kid.
This is a very special story.
It's called Struwwelpeter
by Heinrich Hoffmann
from 1864.
The great tall tailor
always comes to little girls
that suck their thumbs.
Are you listening, Sasha?
Right?
And ere they dream
what he is about,
he takes his great
sharp scissors out
and then cuts their thumbs
clean off.
Dwight, Dwight.
What the hell are you reading?
These are cautionary tales
for kids, Michael.
Yeah, you know what?
No.
No no no no no.
The kids don't wanna hear
some weirdo book
that your Nazi war criminal
grandmother gave you.
What's a Nazi?
Nazi was a fascist movement
in the 1930s.
Don't talk about Nazis
in front of...
You know what?
They're gonna have nightmares.
Why don't you just shut it?
I was gonna teach the children
how to make
corn husk dolls.
Why don't you just leave, okay?
Bye, Mr. Poop.
All right,
there goes Mr. Poop.
Now, who likes Dane Cook?
I do!
Children cannot lie.
They are innocent,
and they speak the truth.
And out of the mouths of babes,
Michael Scott is freakin' cool.
You know, I never misbehaved
in front of my father.
Because he was a very strict
disciplinarian.
I can only hope my mate
has some of those
same qualities.
This is where the magic happens.
Right over here,
let me show you this.
See all these?
You know what that is?
That's paper.
This is where paper comes from.
Any questions?
So, you cut the paper
and dye it and stuff?
No, we don't actually
cut the paper.
That's a good question.
The paper is sent to us
cut and dyed
from a paper manufacturer.
And then we sell it
to a business
for more than we pay for it.
That's not fair.
No.
Yes, it is.
It's... well, you need someone
in the middle to facilitate...
You're just a middleman.
I'm not just a middleman.
Wait, why doesn't the sawmill
just sell the paper
directly to people?
You are describing Office Depot.
And they're kind of
running us out of business.
We have better service
than they do.
There's Creed! Let's take a look
at what he's doing, everybody.
This is Creed.
And he is in charge
of... something, right?
That is correct.
Say hi to the kids.
Hi, kids.
You ever seen a foot
with four toes?
Eww!
What are you doing?
Stop it, stop it!
Just no no no.
No, no!
Would you cut it out?
What is your problem?
No no no.
We're not gonna see
the four-toed Creed, okay?
You know,
there's something interesting
about me that you
might wanna know.
I used to be the star
of a kids show.
No way.
It's true, I did.
You serious?
I am totally serious.
There was a show
called Fundle Bundle,
and I was the star.
What?
It's true.
I can prove it.
Watch this.
Ryan, can you
come here a second?
I would like you to go
to my mother's house
in Dixon City.
And if she's at the pool,
the back kitchen window
should be unlocked.
I want you boost yourself up.
I want you to go
down to the basement.
In the basement is a tape
labeled Fundle Bundle.
I want you grab it.
I want you to get my guitar.
I want you to get a tambourine.
Do you know how
to play the tambourine?
I'm already getting the pizzas
from Brenetti's, so...
I can go with him.
No, I will go.
Okay!
Thank you, Ryan.
Good attitude.
Hottest in the office.
All right, now what kind
of pizza do you like?
I don't get why parents
are always complaining
about how tough it is
to raise kids.
You joke around with them.
You give 'em pizza.
You give 'em candy.
You let 'em live their lives.
They're adults, for God's sake.
I am going to give you
a little blast from the past
of Michael Gary Scott
when he was a child star.
And a show
that you might remember
called Fundle Bundle.
Okay, without further ado, Ryan?
Bundle, are you read
to come on in?
Yeah!
Let's have some fun!
That is Miss Trudy.
Can't tell from her costume,
but she had an amazing body.
Okay, you can fast forward.
And, I want you...
It's coming up... stop!
Stop stop!
Stop.
Yes!
That is Edward R. Meow.
That's pretty funny.
Yeah.
Hey, what's your name?
My name's Chet.
Well, hi, Chet.
Is that Chet Montgomery?
I don't know.
Yeah, that is!
He's the meteorologist
from channel 4.
Checking in with Chet.
Doppler 7.
That guy's legit.
What do you wanna be
when you grow up?
I wanna be on TV.
And he is on TV now!
Everybody please shut up.
Please.
So you don't miss it.
Okay, next.
So, what's your name?
That's me.
Well, what's your favorite
subject in school?
Recess.
So, tell me,
what do you wanna be
when you grow up?
I wanna be married
and have 100 kids
so I can have 100 friends.
And no one can say no
to being my friend.
Uh...
Oh, okay.
Well, nice talking with you,
Michael.
Back to you, Miss Trudy!
Hi, everyone,
it's one of my favorite..
Could have sworn there was...
Did you get married?
Uh, no.
Why not?
Uh, it just never happened.
So do you have any kids?
Uh, nope.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I do okay.
Was Chet Montgomery
cool back then?
Yes.
Even I have a girlfriend.
Okay.
All right, okay.
So you didn't get to be
what you wanted to be.
I guess not.
You know, I have
a load of work to do.
So I am going to grab a slice
of this delish pizza.
And I'm gonna go do my work.
Bye.
He's not coming out.
He won't pick up the phone.
I can't believe his mom
dressed him like that.
That's the real tragedy.
Pam, Pam!
I love this guy.
So, Melissa, I met
your mom a couple times.
She's so nice.
Who, Terry?
Mmm-hmm.
That woman is not my mother.
That is my stepmother.
Mr. Poop,
I have to tell you something.
Uh, okay, but first
that's not my name.
You're ugly.
Well, at least I'm not
a horrible little latchkey kid
who got suspended from school,
so...
Meredith!
Yeah?
I think these belong to you.
Oh, that's okay.
She can keep those.
Believe me, she has enough toys.
She doesn't need your watch.
Thank you.
Is everything okay?
You have to ask me that
because you work for
human resources.
That's true.
You know, sure,
playing the field is great.
Don't get me wrong.
But there's more to life
than notches on my bedpost.
Tell me something honestly.
Do you think that it is too late
for me to have kids?
Well, you need a wife first
or at least a girlfriend.
What about...
Not Jan.
Jan.
Okay.
If you really wanna have kids,
I guess you could somehow.
Foster parent or something.
Or biologically.
Somehow.
Thanks, that's...
No, that really
means a lot to me.
Hey, does Sasha
have a godfather?
Because...
Yes.
Okay.
Is it okay if I take one?
Sure.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Is your job hard?
It's not too bad.
I get to shred things sometimes.
Do you wanna see?
Yeah.
Really?
Okay.
Um, here it is.
Don't put your fingers in there.
Cool, huh?
That's so cool.
Yeah.
Yeah, I get to do this,
like, every week.
That's so awesome.
Yes, it is true.
I, Michael Scott, am signing up
with an online dating service.
Thousands of people
have done it,
and I am going to do it.
I need a user name.
And I have a great one.
Littlekidlover.
That was people will know
exactly where
my priorities are at.
Go ahead.
Do you wanna come over
for dinner tonight?
Oh man, I would love to.
I can't tonight, but can I
come over some other time?
What are you doing?
You never have plans.
Thanks, Kev.
Um, I'm actually going
on a date.
Nice.
Hey, uh, no, please.
You can't leave yet.
There's still one more thing
we need to do.
Why does he own a guitar
if he doesn't
know how to play it?
I think he thought his ukulele
skills would transfer.
My theory is that...
And they do.
Your parents love you very much.
One more time.
The Schroots considered
children very valuable.
In the olden days
the women would bear
many children
so we would have enough laborers
to work the fields.
And if it was an especially
cold winter
and there weren't enough
grains or vegetables,
they would eat
the weakest of the brood.
No!
They didn't eat the children.
It never came to that.