So...
I'm happy to be here.
It's very nice
to see all of you.
You're all looking well.
Today's a Women
in the Workplace thing.
Jan's coming in from corporate
to talk to all the women
about, um...
I don't really know what.
But Michael's not allowed in.
She said that about five times.
Women today, though we have
the same options as men,
we often face a very different
set of obstacles...
in getting there, so...
Hey, what's going on?
Michael, I...
Yeah, you know what?
I thought we agreed...
I thought about it.
I just have few things
I wanna say.
What are you doing?
Just hear me out.
What is more important
than quality?
Equality.
Now, studies show
that today's woman,
the Ally McBeal woman,
as I call her,
is at a crossroads.
Michael...
And... no, just, I...
You have come a long way, baby.
But I just...
just wanna keep it
within reason.
They did this up in Albany...
You are not allowed in... And they
ended up turning the break room
into a lactation room,
which is disgusting.
Now you're really
not allowed in this session.
Well, I'm their boss,
so I feel like...
I'm your boss.
Anybody want any coffee
or anything?
We're fine, Michael.
We just need you
to leave, please.
Women in the workplace.
Yeah, translation:
I have been banned
from my own conference room
so that Jan can talk in secret
to all the girls.
Oh, sorry.
"Women of the Workplace."
About what?
I don't know.
Clothes, me...
Ick.
Ladies, I am so,
so sorry.
Can we... start again?
We were on such a roll.
I-I really apologize for that.
Jan.
Yes, Pam?
Michael's still at the door.
Michael!
So one obstacle
is how assertiveness
is perceived differently
in men and women.
Men who are assertive
tend to be admired.
They're called...
anyone?
That's a terrible idea.
What is?
Them in there all together.
They stay in there too long,
they're gonna get
on the same cycle.
Wreak havoc on our plumbing.
Everyone, guys...
Circle up, please.
Come on over.
Bring your chairs.
Toby, come on over.
You're a guy... too.
Sort of.
Let's do this.
Well, first of all,
I, uh, just wanna
warm up a little bit.
Let's just clap.
Ready?
Yeah!
Yeah! That's what
I'm talkin' about!
I don't know what you're
doing here, Michael.
Just having a little
guys in the workplace thing.
Why can't boys play with dolls?
Why does society
force us to use urinals
when sitting down
is far more comfortable?
Can you please do this
somewhere else, Michael?
We have nowhere else, Jan.
This...
We could do it in the warehouse.
Dwight, excellent idea.
Go to the warehouse.
Okay, fine.
Be actually perfect.
Perfect!
You know what?
There is another side
to this place, gentlemen.
And I know we all love
our cushy jobs and our fun,
exciting office.
But do you realize
that underneath us
there is another world.
The warehouse world.
A world that is teeming
with sweat and dirt
and life.
Life.
The bowels of the office.
These guys are down there.
They are real men
doing real man's work.
We are going to learn
how a warehouse works.
Oh, I think this is gonna
work out great.
Because managing the warehouse
is a very important
part of my job.
And I haven't been there
in months.
Remember on Lost,
when they met the Others?
I'm so sorry about that.
Um, so where were we?
Pam, are you okay
taking notes then?
Mm-hmm.
Please?
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
So let's meet the warehouse!
Let's get some shots.
Pan around there.
This is Darrell,
one of our warehouse staff.
Darrell, what is
your biggest fear?
My biggest fear is that
someone will distract us
from getting all
the shipments out on time.
You know what?
Darrell is actually
the foreman here,
and not Roy, which is cool.
There's Roy, ridin' the big rig!
Um, so Roy is actually
going to be marrying Pam
sometime this summer.
And, uh, she's our receptionist.
Sort of a BrAngelina thing.
Why?
BrAnangelina is
the Brad Pitt and Angelina.
I don't understand.
Roy... Roy and Pam.
It's a Ram.
It's a Ram thing.
I bet Roy heard about
you liking Pam.
I bet he'll try
to beat you up.
Thanks for
the heads-up, Kev.
I got your back if he does.
But try to stay out of it.
Just in case there's
somebody down here
who shouldn't be.
A little Good Will Hunting
situation.
All right, troops.
This is... an important day.
A big day.
Now, you may
look around and see
two groups here.
White-collar, blue-collar.
But I don't see it that way.
And you know why not?
Because I am collar-blind.
Why don't we go around the table
and all say something
that we know we're good at.
I will start.
I am good at public speaking.
Hi, I'm Meredith,
and I'm an al...
Good at supplier relations.
Great.
Phyllis.
Um, I'm good at computer stuff.
E-mails, um, spreadsheets,
all that.
Really?
I don't know.
I thought that...
No, okay, stop.
You know, I've seen
some of your spreadsheets.
And I almost always...
Really?
I thought they were pretty...
I don't know how I fit in
with these women.
Here.
Or with Jan.
Um, I mean, we get along great.
Fine.
Um... I guess the person
I have the most in common with
is...
Jim.
Halpert.
Hey, uh,
I, uh, you know.
Heard there's a rumor
going around about,
you know, you used
to have a crush on Pam.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no.
No, it's cool.
'Cause I know you're a good guy,
and I know that that crush
ended a long time ago,
so, you know.
We're cool, right?
Yeah.
No, yeah, definitely.
You know, it's great with me,
'cause that way...
I'm glad she has
a friend at work
she can get through
the day with.
That way she's not all,
"Bah, bah, bah, bah,"
you know, when she gets home.
Yeah, I like talking to her too.
So, uh...
we're cool, right?
Yes. Yeah.
Good.
All right.
Cool, man.
Sweet.
Hey, Mike, look.
How about we go
upstairs, too, you know?
Learn how an office works.
Oh, well... We can both
switch places for the day.
Okay, yeah, you know what?
I don't... you're...
My job sucks compared to this.
I don't think you'd like it up there.
Good experience.
Guys! You wanna start
unloading the truck?
Okay, let's go.
Step up.
Check this out.
Look at that.
Ba boop!
"Hello, how are..."
Okay.
That's great.
That is good stuff.
In five years, I'd like
to be five years sober.
That is an excellent goal.
4 1/2.
I'll tell you one thing.
I am not gonna be
one of those women
schlepping her kids
around in a minivan.
Great. Uh-huh.
I want an SUV
with three rows of seats.
That would be great.
Well, I'll be honest.
One of the goals
of these women's seminars
is to feel out if there's
any standouts.
Women who could be a valuable
addition to our corporate life.
Michael wants us to bond.
So we need topics
for conversation.
Ponies.
No.
How about rainbows?
Flowers.
That's dangerous, Michael.
Come on, get down from there.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
Mike...
Stand clear.
Mike, get off
of the lift, please!
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Come on, now.
I'm fine.
Would you... look.
Oh, oh, oh!
We'll get somebody
to clean that up.
We're the ones that
gotta clean that up!
Damn it, Michael!
We have to have
this thing serviced.
So, guys' gripe session.
Here we are.
Now, we definitely live
in different worlds,
but we have a lot in common.
We even like the same girls,
some of us.
And that's gonna happen.
You know, we're guys.
So...
Hey... do you
want me to go?
No... why would I...
You could...
I'll go.
Stay or...
And a big,
walk-in closet.
Oh, that's part of my dream too.
Oh, me too.
Great. Okay.
And, Pam, what about you?
What is your dream?
Well... I always
dreamed of a house
with a terrace upstairs.
Plant flowers on it,
stuff like that.
Since I was a girl.
Um...
More seriously, though,
a husband that I love.
Roy.
And...
I love to draw.
And I did a little in college.
And I'd still
love to do something
where I could work with art
or graphic design in some way.
She's real good.
You know, the company
is offering
a design training program
in New York.
Well, I have a job right now.
So I can't really take time off.
Well, it's...
it's only on weekends.
And then a few weeks
in New York.
But I'm sure that I could
ask corporate to help you out.
Well, it's just that
the weekends aren't good
because, um...
There are always a million
reasons not to do something.
Let's start with the warehouse.
What bothers you as guys?
You know?
My priority is safety.
Okay.
So it really bothers me
when somebody
comes in here speeding around
on a lift,
playing with it like a toy.
It kind of gets
under my skin, okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Shh, shh.
Uh-uh, don't...
don't shush me.
I... that was just...
That bothers me too.
I was breathing.
Pam shushes me.
It drives me crazy.
I hate shushing, you know?
That's the thing.
What b... okay.
What is our...
beef as... human men.
You know, that's a good
question, Hasselhoff.
Okay.
What bugs us?
All right, good.
Guys raggin' on each other.
That's what guys do.
And we love it.
All right, let's talk about...
clothing.
I'm excited about today.
I love girl talk.
Dress for the job you want,
not the job you have.
All right, you can
use your clothing
to send a message
about your ambitions
by wearing clothes that reflect
what you aspire to be.
I'm not gaining anything
from this seminar.
I'm a professional woman.
The head of accounting.
I'm in the healthiest
relationship of my life.
I just think it's insulting
that Jan thinks we need this.
And apparently...
judging from her outfit...
Jan aspires to be a whore.
I hate it when girls insist
on taking them out
to restaurants
every weekend night,
and then they're like,
"When are we gonna
go on a date date?"
Oh, I hate that, too, man.
Exactly!
That sucks so hard.
And then they make you drive 'em
to church the next morning.
Like, gas ain't free!
Yeah, on our salaries, man,
what do they expect, you know?
What, "take us
out every weekend"?
You know what I mean?
We're not millionaires.
I feel you.
No, you don't.
You don't feel us.
How can you?
You... you know what?
Not literally.
You say we're the same,
but we get compensated
very differently.
Yes. We work the
same hours as you,
and you just said
we work a lot harder.
Uh, you do, so...
But we get paid a lot less.
Nn... yy...
Word.
Like, next to no benefits.
I know.
God, what is that?!
Exactly!
It blows, it blows, man!
You know, this would not happen
if we had a union.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah... no. Absolutely,
that's what we need.
Man, see, that's what
I been sayin', man.
We need to do this finally.
You know what?
Is that necessary?
'Cause you already sort of
have a union of guys.
It's more than necessary, Mike.
We need this.
Roy... you still have that card
from the dock worker's union?
Dock workers?
Man, hook him up.
Come on, man!
Yeah.
You know what, I think, uh...
Problem is the chicks.
Union, yeah! The
problem is the chicks.
And you gotta blame them.
Are you with us, Mike?
Yeah, s...
Welcome to the warehouse.
Mi-chael!
Mi-chael! Mi-chael! Mi-chael!
Another issue
is inequality of pay
between men and women.
I'm sure that all of you
have dealt with that before.
This is important.
Ladies, take a breather.
Jan, I, uh...
wanted...
Can I help you?
Um, I wanted to say
that the guys downstairs
are thinking about
forming a union.
And they have some good points.
What? A union?
Don't get hysterical.
I'm not.
Part of my job
is knowing how to talk to women.
Let's... be...
rational... here.
What are the pros,
what are the cons?
The cons are that everyone
will lose their job, Michael.
Everyone.
Office, warehouse.
What do you think
the... pros... are... here?
Don't talk to me
that way, please.
Just... they're gonna
wanna hear this from you.
Oh, you got yourself
into this, Michael,
so you get yourself out. Well,
we're bonding down there.
I just don't wanna
have to tell them something
they're not gonna wanna hear!
Now who's getting hysterical?
Okay... Come on Jan.
After all we've been through.
Michael, Michael...
We have history.
We have a history.
Michael.
Between us.
Don't say another word.
Get... yourself...
down... stairs.
I'm just saying
that we have something...
Okay, whatever.
You know what?
We could get this done
a lot quicker
if we formed
a type of assembly line.
This here is
a run-out-the-clock situation.
Just like upstairs.
Sports metaphors
are one of the ways
women feel left out
of the language of the office.
Now, I know this
might sound silly,
but many women
ask to go over it.
So... fumble means...
Mistake. Slip. Right.
Par for the course
is a golf term.
It means right on track.
Uh, below par means worse.
Wait, that should mean better.
That doesn't make sense.
What about second base?
Like if Michael said
he got to second base with you?
Does that mean you
had closed a deal?
Excuse me?
I mean, that's
a baseball term, right?
I don't know what...
Michael was...
talking about, I don't know.
Like, you went to Chili's,
and he got
to second base with you.
Excuse me.
Kelly, I don't know
what Michael was talking about.
He just told everybody,
and I just wanna know...
Hey.
Hey!
How's it going down there?
It's a complete d...
Well, actually,
it's exactly
what you'd expect, so...
Right.
How are the girls?
Good.
We watched a video about
our changing bodies.
Did you really?
No.
Oh.
Almost.
Um, but, hey, um...
something kind of cool.
There's this internship
in graphic design
that Jan was telling us about.
She made it sound, like,
really great.
Nice.
Well, what's it all about?
I think you should do it.
That's great.
It's really cool.
Cold front comin' in
to the warehouse!
Uh-oh!
Better put on your ski boots!
Wooooow!
Happy New Year, Darrell!
Hey, Darrell!
You ever done this?
Are you married?
I'm divorced.
That must have been hard.
It was.
Yes.
You were probably feeling
really depressed and sad,
and that's why you
did that thing with Michael.
I think you should all spend
a little more time
thinking about your careers
and less time on personal stuff.
Mmm, I think we're all okay
with the balance we've struck.
At least you don't have kids.
You have no kids, right?
Thank God.
Okay, let's take five.
I think we could all use five.
How can someone
so beautiful be so sad?
Hi.
Did you take care
of the situation?
Yeah, yeah.
Yes, I...
I have... essentially...
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Yes, I've take...
I'm told that there's
been some interest
in forming a union,
and that Michael supported it.
Obviously he's not
a friend of yours,
because he didn't
tell you the facts.
So let me.
If there is even a whiff
of unionizing in this branch,
I can guarantee you the branch
will be shut down like that.
They unionized in Pittsfield,
and we all know
what happened in Pittsfield.
It will cost each of you
a fortune in legal fees
and union dues,
and that'll be nothing
compared to the cost
of losing your jobs.
So I would think
long and hard before
sacrificing your savings
and your futures
just to send a message.
If you have
any further questions,
you can direct them to...
To Michael.
Dreams are just that.
They're dreams.
They help get you
through the day.
Like the thing
about the terrace.
It's nice.
But, um...
I don't know.
It was just something I read
in this book when I was 12.
Uh, the girl in the book
has a terrace
outside of her bedroom.
And she planted flowers on it.
And I just loved that.
Just always kind of
stuck with me.
So you're not doing it?
How did you know?
Why not?
Just not...
no big reason.
Just a bunch of little reasons.
Come on.
Roy's right.
There's no guarantee it's
gonna lead to anything anyway.
Roy said that?
What? You have
something you wanna say?
You gotta take a chance
on something sometime, Pam.
I mean, do you wanna
be a receptionist here, always?
Oh, excuse me!
I'm fine with my choices.
You are?
Yeah.
It's impractical.
I'm not gonna...
try to get a house like that.
Um, they don't even make houses
like that in Scranton.
So I'm never gonna...
Just gonna push this over there!
This is not a good idea
right here.
Easy does it. Okay.
Pizza.
Great equalizer.
Rich people love pizza.
Poor people love pizza.
White people love pizza.
Black people love pizza.
Do black people like pizza?
Hey... um...
Look, guys, I'm sorry.
Sometimes, Jan...
can be such a bitch.
Hey, watch it.
Watch it.
We have a relationship.
Thank you to our hosts.
Hey, Michael!
This ain't over.
Excellent.
Is it good to be back?
Yeah.
I mean,
I love the guy stuff, but...
to run an office,
you need men and women.
You know why?
Because you need to have
that crazy sexual tension
to keep things interesting.
Dunder-Mifflin.
This is Pam.
Uh, hold, please.
Snow angel!