Lords of the Ring trilogy, if you see it back
to back, it's really long, but it's good.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Pam! It's Michael.
Help me.
I need help right now.
Michael, what's wrong?
I'm hurt.
I have hurt myself!
- Ohh, my God!
- Okay, wait, wait, wait!
Oh, this is not
looking good, Pam!
Michael, do you need me
to call an ambulance?!
No, I want you to pick me up.
- Ohh! - Okay.
- What's going on?
Wait a sec, I thought
you said that you were hurt.
I am hurt.
I hurt my foot.
Pam, what's going on?
I want to come to work,
but I need you to
come and pick me up.
Ohh, God!
Hey, whoa!
Michael!
Oh, God!
It's okay.
It's Jim.
Just say again,
really loudly, what happened.
Okay. Buhh!
I burned my foot!
Very badly, on my Foreman Grill,
and I now need someone
to come and bring me into work.
You burned your foot
on a Foreman Grill?
I enjoy having breakfast in bed.
I like waking up
to the smell of bacon.
Sue me.
And since I don't have a butler,
I have to do it myself.
So most nights
before I go to bed,
I will lay six strips of bacon
out on my George Foreman Grill.
Then I go to sleep.
When I wake up,
I plug in the grill.
I go back to sleep again.
Then I wake up to the smell
of crackling bacon.
It is delicious.
It's good for me.
It's a perfect way
to start the day.
Today I got up,
I stepped onto the grill,
and it clamped down
on my foot, that's it.
I don't see what's
so hard to believe about that.
Pam, could you come get me?
Uh, I have to stay here
and answer the phone.
Okay, could someone come
and get me, please? Ryan?
Michael, you should
stay home and rest.
There's no toilet paper here.
Could Ryan...
Tell Ryan to bring toilet paper!
Could you tell him that?
Can you hop?
I tried hopping, Kevin,
and I bumped my elbow
against the wall,
and now my elbow
has a "protruberence."
No one wants to pick me up?!
What is going on?
Michael is, um, sick,
and he wants one of us
to rescue him.
- I'm not sick, I'm...
- I'm coming, Michael!
I'm gonna save you!
Don't! Is that Dwight?
I do not want Dwight.
Hold on, Michael, I am coming!
- Wait there!
- I do not want Dwight!
Michael, why don't you
call your girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
But you said you went out
with her this weekend.
It was all made up.
Just... someone come, okay?
Anyone.
Anyone but Dwight.
- What was that?
Ohh.
Ohh!
He hit the pole.
It's broken, right?
He can't...
Oh, Dwight. Dwight.
Ohh!
Oh, my God. Oh, my gosh.
Is he okay?
He's still driving.
Dwight...
You forgot your bumper!
Hello?
Please don't send Dwight.
Morning, everyone.
Don't freak out.
I forbid anybody to freak out.
Clearly I have had
a very serious accident.
But I will recover.
God willing.
I just wanna be
treated normally today.
Normal would actually be good.
Considering the trauma
that I've been through.
You missed two big
conference calls today.
One with corporate.
Oh, did you
explain... why?
No, I didn't mention
that you cooked your foot.
Burned my foot, Pam.
Please stop popping my cast.
Thank you.
So where are you
shipping your foot?
Ha ha ha.
So where are you shipping...
Your foot.
Thank you.
Pam, messages, please.
You didn't have any.
Really?
Well, seemed very important
to you earlier
that you needed to stay and...
- Do my job?
- No.
Your job is being
my friend, Pam... and...
Ow!
God!
It slipped.
- What did...
- Sorry.
It's just that before, you said
you didn't want
any special treatment.
I don't want
any special treatment, Pam.
I just want you to treat me
like you would a family member
who's undergone some sort
of serious physical trauma.
I don't think that's
too much to ask.
Do you want some aspirin?
Because you seem a little fussy.
No, I don't want some aspirin.
Yeah, I am fussy.
Aspirin's not gonna
do a damn thing.
I'm sitting here with
a bloody stump of a foot.
Pam, I am
Assistant Regional Manager.
And I can take care of him.
Part of my duties are to...
What?
Part of your duties are to what?
You just said that part of
your duties are to something.
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
What is wrong with you?
Where is my cornbread?
Here you go.
Thank you. Did you get
all dark meat like I like?
Yes, I ordered three full
rotisserie chickens worth
of all dark meat.
Where are the yams?
They were out of yams.
I got you creamed spinach.
Did you go to the one
in Stroudsburg? Yes.
- And they had no yams?
- They had no yams.
How strange.
Because they always have yams.
Oh, man, is that
a Prism Duro Sport?
You've seen one of these?
Yeah, they're like an iPod,
only they're better.
'Cause they're chunkier
and more solid.
Roy gave it to me for Christmas.
I'm trying to figure out
how to put songs on it.
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't go there.
I know this Russian website
where you can download songs
for two cents apiece.
Really? Yeah, I'll write
down the address for you.
Only the only thing is...
is that all the songs
are in Russian.
Kidding!
Oh... oh!
Why would they all be...
Okay, see you later, Pan.
Pan?
Pam!
Pam?
Oh, God.
What?
Come here, please.
Tell me before I come there.
I want you
to rub butter on my foot.
No.
Pam, please.
I have Country Crock.
No.
Ryan!
These covers...
are totally indestructible.
Really?
Yeah.
Throw it.
I promise it won't break.
Chuck it.
Oh, no, it's broken.
What?
No, it's fine.
I told you it wouldn't break.
You could throw it all day long.
That is so cool.
Thanks, Dwight.
You're welcome.
So I guess Pam and Dwight
are friends now.
Oh, God, no.
Dwight isn't my friend.
Oh, my God...
Dwight's kind of my friend!
No, no... no one is helping me
out at all, Mom.
No, I'm not gonna call Jan.
She'd just worry.
Drive down here
and make a big thing.
Who told you that?
No, it was mutual.
What is Pam doing
chatting with you?
Hmm.
Do you like candy?
It's all right.
'Cause you're
sweeter than candy.
What is wrong with you?
Hey, cut...
Wow, you just dive right in.
You know, around age 12,
I just started
going for it, you know?
Help!
Oh, help! Help me!
What... what happened?
I fell off the toilet.
I'm caught between
the toilet and the wall.
What do you need?
Not you.
Someone else.
Get Pam.
I don't think Pam's gonna wanna
come into the men's room.
Get Ryan.
He needs to lift me!
And he needs to
clean me up a little bit.
Bring a wet towel.
Ryan is, uh... dead.
No, he's not.
I just saw him.
No. He's...
Can you just get up yourself?
I... you only
grilled your foot.
Oh, forget it.
I'll just get up myself.
Ohh! Oww!
Ow! Ow, God!
Do you think Dwight's
being a little weird today?
No... he's actually been
really nice and helpful.
And that isn't weird?
Well...
Can I have everyone's
attention, please?
Phyllis... Oscar...
Ryan, who is supposed
to be dead.
Can I ask you all a question?
Do you know what it's like
to be disabled?
Um... I had scoliosis
as a girl.
Never heard of it.
No... a real disability.
Not a woman's trouble.
When I was a teenager,
I was in an iron lung.
Wha... how old are you?
No, it...
Look, the point is...
I am the only one here
who has a legitimate disability.
Although I'm sure Stanley has
had his fair share of obstacles.
I'm not disabled,
and neither are you.
Okay, what does this look like
to you, Stanley?
Mail Boxes, Etc.
Shut... it.
Okay.
Well...
Well, you know what?
Disabilities
are not things to be laughed at
or laughed about.
You people are jerks.
Imagine if you had
left Stevie Wonder
on the floor of that bathroom
instead of me.
Oh, we wouldn't.
We love Stevie Wonder.
I burned my foot!
Okay, 20 minutes,
conference room.
Everybody's in there!
Dad?
While we are waiting
for our special guests
to arrive,
I wanted you all to take a look
at a few of the many,
many disabled icons
who have contributed
so much to our society.
Quick question.
Yeah?
Why is Tom Hanks on the wall?
- Twice.
- Good question.
Forrest Gump,
mentally challenged.
Philadelphia...
AIDS.
I think that's from Big.
I don't think so, no.
Yeah, he's dancing on a piano
with Robert Loggia.
He grew into a man overnight.
A rare disability.
It still works.
A crossword puzzle, Stanley?
Seriously, are you learning
nothing here?
Mm-hmm.
What do you mean,
"Mm-hmm"?
I mean I'm learning nothing.
Okay.
Michael Scott.
I'm looking for Michael Scott.
Yes, right in here.
- Good.
- Come on in.
Great.
This, ladies and gentlemen,
is our special guest.
Sorry I'm late.
Somebody parked in
the handicapped parking space.
Oh.
Hey, everyone.
I'm Billy Merchant.
You may have seen me
around here before.
I'm the properties manager
of this office park.
You are so brave.
Thank you.
Actually, I've been meaning to
come by here for a long time...
But it's hard for you, right?
Because you're in a wheelchair.
No, I just have a lot
of properties to manage.
Let me ask you something.
How long does it take
for you to do something simple?
Every day, like... like brush
your teeth in the morning.
I don't know, like, 30 seconds.
Oh, my God.
That's three times
as long as it takes me.
How did you
get in your wheelchair?
This morning?
Just like every other morning.
Just climbed on in.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Not funny, not funny!
Hey, hey, relax just, uh...
joking around here.
Well, that's good.
He still has a sense of humor.
Listen, I've actually
used a chair
since I was four years old.
I don't really
notice it anymore.
Well, they do.
They notice it.
Don't you?
You notice it.
It's the first thing you saw
when he rolled in here,
isn't it?
I wanna clamp Michael's face
in a George Foreman Grill.
So there are just
a couple things
I wanted to remind everybody of.
First is parking.
You can't block
the freight entrance
with your car,
even if your blinkers are on.
Does anybody have any questions?
Yes?
Yeah?
Dwight, you have your hand up.
Ignore him.
You know what?
We're not that different,
you and I.
When I clamped
my foot
into a non-stick...
You know what, Michael? Yeah?
Let me stop you right there,
and leave.
Did you see
Born on the Fourth of July?
I was under the impression
that Billy would be
more like that guy.
What's wrong with that guy?
You mean today?
He stepped on a George Foreman
Grill and he burned his foot.
No, not Michael.
The moon-faced kid
who crashed into the pole.
He looks like
he has a concussion.
Hey!
I found the pudding cups
you wanted
at a gas station in Carbondale!
You did it.
Look at you.
And with the plate
and the napkin.
Very nice.
Thank you, Ryan.
- You're very welcome.
- Did you get the yams?
No, the gas station
in Carbondale
did not have fresh yams.
Okay.
I'll just have the pudding.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Okay.
You know what?
I feel better.
Ryan brought me
some chocolate pudding,
and his kindness healed my foot.
Yeah, baby!
I am feelin' better.
My body's literally
healing itself.
It is amazing what
the human body is capable of
when you have a powerful brain.
I ground up
four extra-strength aspirin
and put them
in Michael's pudding.
I do the same thing with my dog
to get him to take
his heartworm medicine.
Ohh, finally feel the blood
coursing through my foot veins.
Ohh!
Oh! Okay, I think
we need to take him
to the hospital, because...
I'm pretty sure
he has a concussion.
Oh, now you feel
some compassion for him.
He needs to go right now.
And you're his
emergency contact.
I think you should go with him.
Why don't you go with him?
- I... barely know him.
- I want Michael to take me.
I can't take you.
I don't have my car.
- Please?
- And yours is all vomity.
You can take my van!
Oh, okay.
That's great.
No, I can't drive.
Jim, why don't you drive?
Fine. We'll go. I'm
still recovering.
So let's just... Ryan,
can you get my coat, please?
Slowly. Let's just
get to the elevator.
What are you doing?
Vietnam sounds.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Tired.
Can't lay down.
- Just take a rake...
- Wake up!
Ahh! Wait, here, let
me help you, Dwight.
Come on.
Get up.
Thanks.
- You're the best.
- Yeah.
It smells like chicken soup.
I know.
I have to go to the hospital.
Where are we going?
I just wanna
say good-bye, okay?
- I'll be back, I mean...
- Yes, I know.
But it's gonna be different.
Why?
It's just hard to explain.
Oh, Pam, you're adorable.
Oh, my goodness.
Come here.
Ohh.
Huggy hugs.
Shotgun!
You don't think you should
sit in the back with Dwight?
The rules of shotgun
are very simple and very clear.
The first person
to shout shotgun
when you're within
the sight of the car
gets the front seat.
That's how the game's played.
There are no exceptions
for someone with a concussion.
Oh, God, a minivan.
What is Meredith's problem?
Well, I think she has a kid.
Yeah, she has one kid
and no husband.
She's not gonna find one
driving this thing around.
Where are we going?
Come on.
- Get inside.
- Where are we going?
We're going
to Chuck E. Cheese.
Chuck E. Cheese?
Oh, God.
I'm so sick
of Chuck E. Cheese.
We're going to the hospital,
Michael.
I know.
I'm just sayin'...
Dwight, what are you drinking?
I found it under the seat.
Oh, my God.
Dwight.
Put that down.
I'm thirsty.
Noo! Give the bottle to Michael.
Noo! Just give the
bottle to Michael.
- Just give it to me...
- I'm thirsty!
Just keep your eyes on the road.
Give me the bottle,
or you're fired!
You can't fire me.
I don't work in this van.
Give it to me, Dwight!
- No, stop.
- Give me the bottle!
- Will you stop?
- Give me the bottle, Dwight!
- Michael, stop!
- Just give it!
- Just... stop it!
Stop spraying!
Give me the bottle!
- Stop!
- Stop spraying me!
Give me the bottle!
Dwight, what is
your middle name?
Danger.
Something with a "K."
It's Kurt.
Wow, I'm so sad
that I know that.
What do I write under
reason for visit?
Concussion.
What did you write?
Ahem, nothing.
I wrote "bringing someone
to the hospital."
So you thought they meant
your reason
for coming to the hospital.
No, no.
You know what, Jim?
This isn't about me anymore.
I made a miraculous recovery,
which is more than
I can say for him.
Come on, Dwight.
Hi, Michael.
Hi, Dwight.
Ahh.
Uhh.
Doctor, what is more serious,
a head injury or a foot injury?
A head injury.
Well, you don't
have all the information.
The foot has been
fairly severely burned,
and, uh, healed quickly.
Very quickly.
Actually, like,
suspiciously quickly.
So I'm ordering a CAT scan.
What is that?
Look, since you have
the machine up and running,
can I just stick my foot in?
- We can take a look.
- Well...
For a burn, you really just need
to look at the outside
of the foot.
Okay, what kind
of machine is that?
Does the skin look
red and swollen?
That's what she said.
That's my joke.
Damn it, Dwight.
Okay, no electronics
past this point.
Camera, sound equipment.
It's okay, they're with me.
No metal of any kind.
All right, well, I guess
this is where we leave you off.
I don't wanna do this.
Uh, well, you should have
thought of that
before you crashed your head
on your way to pick me up, so...
We'll... see you
when you get out.
Oh.
Fine. Fine.
Dunder Mifflin.
This is Pam.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Jim.
Oh, my God, what's going on?
Is Dwight okay?
Mm-hmm,
he should be fine.
But they brought him in
for a CAT scan.
I can't believe he's
getting a CAT scan.
Michael went in there
with him too.
It's pretty sweet.
Really? Michael went in
with him? Wow.
But they shouldn't
be much longer now.
So we'll be back soon.
Okay, that's... good news.
Um, uh, yeah, no.
I'll let you go.
Okay. Bye.
Bye.
Hey, Oscar?
What's up, Pam?
Um, I just wanted
to let you know
that Dwight's gonna be okay.
The doctor said there's
a really simple treatment
for a concussion,
so he'll probably even
be back at work tomorrow.
Okay.
I just, uh, thought
you'd wanna know that.
Okay, Mr. Schrute.
Inhale with me
on three.
One, two...
Sir, stop that.
Stop...
Stop that.