Tonight is the Dundies,
the annual employee awards night
here at Dunder Mifflin.
And this is everybody's
favorite day.
Everybody looks forward to it.
Because, you know,
a lot of the people here
don't get trophies very often.
Like, Meredith or Kevin.
I mean, who's gonna give
Kevin an award,
Dunkin' Donuts?
Plus, bonus,
it's really, really funny.
So I... You know, an employee
will go home,
and he'll tell his neighbor,
"Hey, did you get an award?"
And the neighbor'll say,
"No, man."
I mean, I slave all day.
Nobody notices me.
Next thing you know,
employee smells
something terrible
coming from
the neighbor's house.
Neighbor's hanged himself.
Due to lack of recognition.
So...
So you ready for the Dundies?
Ugh.
You know what they say
about a car wreck,
where it's so awful,
you can't look away?
The Dundies are like
a car wreck that,
you wanna look away,
but you have to stare at it
because your boss is making you.
Hey-hey-hey!
It's Fat Halpert!
What?
Fat Halpert!
Jim Halpert.
So why don't I take
you on a tour
of past Dundie winners?
We got Fat Jim Halpert here.
Jim, why don't you show off
your Dundies to the camera?
Oh, I can't
because I keep them hidden.
I don't wanna look at them
and get cocky.
Oh!
That's a good idea.
Mine are at home,
in a display case above my bed.
Yeeaacck! TMI.
TMI, my friends.
TMI?
Too Much Information.
Uh, it's just easier to say TMI.
I used to say "Don't go there,"
but that's lame.
And here we have
Stanley the Manley.
Now, Stanley is
a Dundie all-star.
Aren't you, Stanley?
Why don't you, uh,
show them some of your bling.
I don't know where they are.
I think I threw them out.
Oh, no, you di-in't.
Uh, think I did.
Mm... Why did...
Say, we gotta order some more
appe-teasers this time
We ran out last year, remember?
Yes, we should.
I... You know what?
I wanted one of those
skillets of cheese.
But when I got off stage,
someone had eaten all of them.
To Oscar Martinez,
it's the
Show Me the Money award.
Michael has taped
every Dundies Awards.
And now he's making me
look through
hours of footage
to find highlights.
For the ladies.
Hit it, Dwight.
Oh, yeah.
This is the part where Kevin sat
in front of the camcorder
all night.
It's great.
It was you.
It wasn't.
I swear.
Yeah, it was.
So what's the joke?
You're not perfect either.
We're not laughing
at you, Dwight.
So who are we laughing at?
Um, just something
somebody wrote.
Who? Dave Barry?
No, no.
Just something that was written
on the ladies room wall.
What is it?
Who wrote it?
Um, it's kind of private.
It's about Michael.
That is defacement
of company property.
So you'd better tell me.
Kelly, if you tell me,
you'll be punished less.
Okay, now I'm laughing at you.
Will her highness
Jan Levinson-Gould
be descending from her corporate
throne this evening
to visit us lowly serfs
here at Dunder Mifflin Scranton?
It's a two-and-a-half-hour
drive from New York, Michael.
Well, you could take the bus.
You could work on the way here,
sleep on the way home.
No.
Come on, Jan.
This is important.
I mean, this is,
this is validation
to my employees here
that you and corporate
approve of this.
Well, we don't
approve of this, Michael.
W... I mean, you only
have the budget
for one office party
a year, so...
we're not paying for this.
Um...
Can you...?
Are you there, Michael?
Yeah, yeah, I'm here.
I just wanted to, uh...
talk to you for
a second about that.
Um, what, uh, what is...
I mean, come on!
Jan.
What's... You're droppin'
an A-bomb on me here.
Really? I'm dropping
an atomic bomb on you?
Well, yeah.
I mean, what is...
Right.
You already had a party
on May 5th for no reason.
No reason!
It was the 05-05-05 party.
It happens once
every billion years.
And you had a luau.
And the tsunami relief
fundraiser,
which somehow
lost a lot of money.
Okay, no, that was a fun raiser.
I think I made that
very clear in the flyers.
Fun, F-U-N.
Okay, well, I don't
understand why anyone
would have a tsunami
fun raiser, Michael.
Well, I think a lot of people
were very affected
by the footage.
It's a little character
I like to do.
It is, uh,
loosely based on Carnac,
one of Carson's
classic characters.
Here we go.
The PLO, the IRA,
and the hot dog stand
behind the warehouse.
Name three businesses that have
better heath-care plans
than Dunder Mifflin.
Here's the problem.
There's no open bar
because of Jan.
And it's the reason why
comedy clubs have
a two-drink minimum.
I mean, it'll be fine, I just...
wish people were gonna be drunk.
Dwight, get out of here.
What are you doing in the ladies room?
It's not what you...
No! Why were you in there?
What were you doing in there? I am not.
You are in there...
The Dundie award
for longest engagement
goes to Pam Beesley.
Pam, everybody!
Yoo!
When is that girl
gonna get married?
That's what I have to say.
Aha, Roy's accepting.
Thank you, Roy, are there
any words you'd like to say
on Pam's behalf?
Uh, we'll see you next year.
Yeah! Oh, hope not!
Hope not.
I'm not changing that.
That's the best one.
No, it's hilarious.
You're right.
I just think, um,
World's Longest Engagement,
um, we're all expecting it,
you know?
That's why it's funny.
Every year that Roy and Pam
don't get married
it gets funnier.
Well, I think if you use
the same jokes,
it just comes across as lazy.
Oh. Lazy.
Uh-huh.
Excuse me, everyone.
Can I have your attention,
please?
I just wanted to say
that the women in this office
are terrible.
Especially the ones
who wrote that stuff
about Michael
on the bathroom wall.
Having a bathroom
is a privilege.
It is called a ladies' room
for a reason.
And if you cannot behave
like ladies,
well then, you are not
going to have a bathroom.
You're taking away our bathroom?
We are going to have
two men's rooms.
But where would we... go?
Be prepared to hold it, folks.
Okay, okay.
From 9:00 a.m...
Look.
Michael...
Yes?
Dwight's banning us
from our bathroom.
Okay, well, that's ridiculous.
So just don't...
I don't have time
for this right now.
There needs to be repercussions
for people's behavior.
Stop it! Stop it!
Okay.
Look, I know there have been
a lot of rumors flying around
about the Dundies this year.
How there is no money,
and how there is no food,
and how the jokes
are really bad.
But, what the hell, everybody?
I mean...
God, the Dundies are about
the best in every one of us.
Can't you see that?
I mean...
Okay, we can do better.
So tonight, for the first time,
we are inviting all of your
friends and family
to attend the awards with us.
Yes.
Yeah, not bad, right?
So let's make this
the best Dundies ever.
Best Dundies ever.
Welcome to the eighth annual
Dundies awards.
Before we get started,
a few announcements.
Keep your acceptance
speeches short.
I have wrap-it-up music,
and I'm not afraid
to use it, Devon.
Card!
Come on.
The Dundies are kind of like
a kid's birthday party.
And you go, and there's really
nothing for you to do there.
But the kid's having
a really good time.
So you're kind of there.
That's... that's kind
of what it's like.
The waitress tripped
on the cord.
All right.
Joke landed.
So we are here.
Thank you all for coming
to the 2005 Dundie awards.
I am your host, Michael Scott.
And I just wanna tell you,
please, please,
do not drink and drive.
Because you may hit a bump
and spill the drink.
I'll just put these
on the group tab.
Nope, actually,
this year, no group tab.
We're gonna be doing
separate checks.
You said we could bring
our families.
I did, and why didn't you,
Stanley?
I did, and my wife's
name is Teri.
Well, I'm looking forward
to meeting Teri.
It's this person whose hand
I'm holding, Michael.
Oh, yeah.
Shut it.
Um, good.
Speaking of relationships
of all...
all waves, shapes, and forms,
um, I was out
on a very, very hot date
last night
with a girl
from H.R., Dwight.
Really? We don't have any
girls from H.R.
No, uh...
F-for the sake
of the story.
And things were getting
hot and heavy.
Yeah?
And I was about to take
her bra off,
when she had me fill out
six hours worth of paperwork.
Like an AIDS test?
No.
God.
Ahem!
All right, so let's get
this pahty stahted!
Hey, let's go to Poor Richard's.
Yeah, let's get out of here.
Um...
Guys, where are you going?
Pam, show's
just getting started.
Sorry.
And now to celebrate...
You staying?
Yeah.
Gotta eat somewhere.
The Busiest Beaver Award
goes to Phyllis Lapin!
Yeah!
Way to go, Phyllis.
Nice work. Per usual.
This says Bushiest Beaver.
What?
I told them busiest... Idiots.
It's fine.
We can fix it.
We'll fix it up.
You don't have to display that.
Because that's what happens every time!
He's a jackass!
Every year.
Come on, we're going
to Poor Richard's.
No, I don't wanna go.
I don't want to!
Pam, no. If you would've asked
me that, then you would know.
Herro, everybody!
Hey... how are you?
I thought you left.
Um, no, I just...
I decided to stay.
Oh. I'll just get a
ride home from Angela.
I going to call the next award!
Oh, good, I'm just
in time for Ping.
Oh, that would be where?
Uh, me so horny, right?
You know what I'm talking about.
Can I get a drink?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This next award goes to somebody
who really lights up the office.
Somebody who, I think,
a lot of us, cannot keep
from checkin' out.
The Hottest in the Office Award
goes to...
Ryan the temp!
Yeah!
Here you go.
There you go.
There you go, whoo!
What am I gonna do
with the award?
Nothing.
I... I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
That's the least
of my concerns right now.
And the Tight-Ass Award
goes to Angela.
Not only because she is
everybody's favorite stickler,
but because she has
a great caboose.
So, come on down.
No.
I think those might be empty.
No, no, 'cause the ice melts,
and then it's like,
second drink.
Second drink?
The Spicy Curry Award
goes to our very own,
Kelly Capour.
Get on up here.
There you go.
"Spicy Curry," what's that mean?
Um, not everything means
something, it's just a joke.
Yeah, but why'd you
give it to me?
I don't know.
I just...
This is a bowler.
I know.
It's... they didn't have
any more businessmen.
Yeah, but I don't...
Just sit down, Kelly.
It's so freaking hot in there.
Now I know what Bob Hope
was going through
when he performed
in Saudi Arabia.
Man!
I got Dwight sucking
the funny out of the room.
But, you know, you do
what you can do.
Here we go,
he's early with the cue.
Gotta go.
Ow! Sing it, Elton!
Hey, thanks guys.
Hey, where're you guys from?
We just came
from your mama's house.
Are you guys gonna finish that?
Oh, right, yeah!
Sing another song, Dude.
Uh, you know what, guys?
We're just having a little
office party.
So if you wanna...
Hey!
You know, cool it guys, really.
You suck, man.
You suck.
Let's cut it.
I had a few more Dundies
to give out tonight.
But I'm just gonna cut it short.
And wrap it up
so everybody can
enjoy their food.
Um, thanks for listening,
those of you who listened.
This last Dundie is for Kevin.
This is the Don't Go In There
After Me award.
It's for the time that I went
into the bathroom after him,
and it was really,
really smelly.
There you go.
Yay, Kevin!
Whoo hoo!
For Kevin!
For stinking up the bathroom!
Yeah, all right, Kev!
Whoo!
Hey, I haven't gotten one yet.
Yes, I have not
gotten one either.
So, keep going.
More Dundies!
Dundie, Dundie.
All right, all right,
all right, okay.
All right,
we'll keep it rolling.
Okay, this is
the Fine Work Award.
This goes to Stanley.
For all the fine work
he did this year.
You know you did.
Hear, hear.
Speech, speech, speech,
speech, speech, speech...
Well, the last year,
I got Great Work.
So I don't know what
to think about this award.
But, at least I didn't get
Smelliest Bowel
Movement like Kevin.
And this next award is going out
to our own little Pam Beesley.
I think we all know what award
Pam is gonna be
getting this year.
It is the Whitest
Sneakers Award.
Because she always has
the whitest tennis shoes on!
Get on down here!
Pam Beesley,
ladies and gentlemen.
Ooh, here we go.
I have so many people to thank
for this award.
Okay, first off, my Keds,
because I couldn't have
done it without them.
Thank you.
Let's give Michael
a round of applause
for emceeing tonight,
because this is a lot harder
than it looks.
And also because of Dwight too.
Um, so, finally,
I wanna thank God
because God gave me this Dundie.
And I feel God
in this Chili's tonight.
Whoo!
Pammy B.,
ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah!
Chair?
Oh!
What a great year
for the Dundies.
We got to see Ping.
And we learned Michael's
true feelings for Ryan.
Which was touching.
And we heard Michael
change the lyrics
to a number of classic songs.
Which for me,
has ruined them for life.
What?
Nothing.
Okay.
What?
I don't know, what?
Oh, my God.
- You are so drunk.
- Did you get that?
Please tell me that you got...
Vince, Vince!
Woman has had a seizure!
Grab her tongue!
It's okay,
I'm a sheriff's deputy.
Well, he's a volunteer.
Don't get into that now.
We need something
to cushion her head.
A throw pillow?
A cushion?
Okay, I'm gonna use my shirt.
Get off of me.
I'm sorry, sir, you're gonna
have to put your clothes on.
People are trying to eat!
Was this year's
Dundies a success?
Well, let me see.
I made Pam laugh so hard, that
she fell out of her chair.
That she almost broke her neck.
So I killed.
Almost.
Oh, my God!
I just wanna say,
that this was the best
Dundies ever!
Whoo!
Whoa, whoa.
Careful, careful.
We have a strict policy here
not to over serve.
Apparently this young woman
was sneaking drinks
off other people's tables.
I Xeroxed her driver's license,
and she is not welcome
at this restaurant
chain ever again.
Great work tonight.
Watch your step.
Excellent.
Thanks.
I had to, uh, check her pupils
to make sure
that wasn't a concussion.
Yes, that too,
but I mean with the audio.
Great, great work.
I feel bad about what I wrote
on the bathroom wall.
No, you don't.
Oh, here she is.
Careful, careful, whoa.
All right.
Easy.
Almost there.
Hey, um, can I ask
you a question?
Shoot.
Um... I just wanted
to say thanks.
That's not really a question.
Okay, let's get
you home, pronto.
All right. Good night. Bye.
Have a good night.
Thank you, Angela.