Hey, what's up?
Hey.
Any emails today?
Um, I don't think so.
No?
Um, check your spam folder.
Oh, there it is.
What?
Um... 50 signs your priest
might be Michael Jackson.
Well done.
Topical.
I am king of forwards.
It's how I like to do business.
Everybody joking around.
We're like Friends.
I am Chandler.
And Joey.
And, uh, Pam is Rachel.
And Dwight is Kramer.
So the monkey
does the sex thing right...
here!
That's funny!
That's funny.
Not offensive.
Because it's nature,
educational.
Do want the link?
'Cause then you could
forward it around.
Um, I...
Consider it.
Maybe, maybe.
Well, we'll see.
Because I don't know
if it's a...
Wha... come on!
What has two thumbs
and likes to bone your mom?
This guy!
Oh, you are so bad.
Yeah.
Oh, phew, ro, rah!
Aaah!
Oh, this guy is out of control.
He is a madman.
Better get the bleep button
ready for him.
Bleep bleep!
What's up, Halpert?
Still queer?
Uh-oh!
Oh ho ho!
Todd Packer and I are total BFF.
Best friends forever.
He and I came up together
as salesmen.
One time we were out
and we met this set of twins.
And Packer told them
that we were brothers.
And so, you know,
one thing led to another.
And we brought 'em back
to the motel.
And then Packer
did both of them.
It was awesome.
It was...
Ow ow ow!
Oh.
Okay, grade A gossip
for you right now.
Randall, CFO, resigned.
Nobody knows why.
Are you kidding?
Everyone knows why!
You don't know?
Oh, okay, check this out.
All right, so here's the story.
So Randall is nailing
his secretary, right?
And she's totally incompetent.
Really?
Here we go.
Buckle up, it's gonna be
a bumpy one.
We're talking "blonde
incompetent," right?
Oh, yeah.
Like, uh, ten words a minute.
Talking.
Well, to be fair,
blondes, brunettes.
You know, there are a lot
of dumb people out there.
They are women, right?
Oh, wow!
I didn't say it!
I said it.
And then, suddenly,
for no reason,
this bimbo blows the whistle
on the whole thing
just to be a bitch.
Oh, wow, what'd I tell you
about the bleep button?
Hey, what has two thumbs
and hates Todd Packer?
This guy!
I meant to ask you,
you think you can get someone
to drive me around because of
the DUI situation?
Oh, bad boy.
Um, Ryan.
Come on, kid, let's go.
Oh, man.
That Todd Packer
can do anything.
Except pass that breathalyzer.
You a big William Hung fan?
Why does everybody ask me that?
Who the hell is that?
I'm really excited
to meet your mom.
You are?
My mom is coming in to visit.
And she lives, like,
two hours away.
And she doesn't
have a cellphone.
Which is cool,
'cause it's kind of adding
some suspense to my day.
And I keep looking
over at the door,
hoping she'll walk in.
I'm excited to show her around.
She really wants
to meet everybody.
Oh, yeah?
Good.
'Cause I have
a lot of questions.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
As a child did Pam
show any traits
that would hint towards
her future career
as a receptionist?
Hey, send me that link
to the monkey sex video.
I'm going to forward it
like it's hot.
Yes!
Old school.
Michael?
Yes, Toby.
Um, I need to talk to you
in your office.
It'll just take two seconds.
Um, literally two seconds?
Toby is in HR,
which technically means
he works for corporate.
So he's really not
a part of our family.
Also, he's divorced,
so he's really not
a part of his family.
The full story
is that Randall resigned
because of sexual harassment.
So corporate asked me
to do a five minute review
of the company's
sexual harassment policy.
No, no, Toby.
No.
It's really not
a big deal, Michael.
It is a big deal.
It's a big deal!
What are we supposed to do,
scrutinize every little thing
we say and do all day?
I mean, come on.
And then corporate
is gonna send in a lawyer.
What?
No!
Just to refresh you
on our policy.
What?
N-he... no.
Okay, what is a lawyer
gonna come in and tell us?
To not send out
hilarious emails
or not tell jokes?
Maybe not some of them.
Maybe not inappropriate ones.
There is no such thing
as an appropriate joke.
That's why it's a joke.
Everyone?
Hello?
Everyone.
Hi.
Uh, sorry to interrupt.
I know you're all busy
and the last thing you want
is for a major interruption.
But Toby has an announcement
that he insists on making
right now
in the middle of the day.
So take it away.
Yeah, okay.
Corporate would like us
to do a five minute review
of the company's
sexual harassment policy,
so I'll go over that later.
I wish you luck, Toby,
I really do.
But you are going to have
a mutiny on your hands.
And I just can't wait to see
how you handle it.
A guy goes to a five dollar...
lady of the night.
And he gets crabs.
So the next day,
he goes back to complain.
And the woman says,
"Hey, it was only five dollars.
What did you expect,
lobster?"
This is what's at stake.
Time to bring out the big guns.
I am heading down
to the warehouse,
where jokes are born.
Find a killer joke
that'll just blow
everybody away
at the seminar later.
And remind them what is great
about this place.
So... ah!
Here they are.
Guys, wondering if I could, uh,
get your help for something?
I am looking
for a new joke to tell.
And it needs to be just killer.
And it does not
need to be clean.
So what you got?
Like, a joke?
A knock knock joke?
Um, yeah... no.
I mean, better.
Better than that.
The type of stuff you guys
tell all day.
Well, those are some
awful tight pants you have on.
Where did you get 'em,
like, Queers 'R' Us?
Boys 'R' Us.
Oh!
All right, all right.
Well, yeah, but you know.
A joke but not necessarily
at my expense.
Man, we can see
all your business
coming around the corner, okay?
You need to, you know,
hide that.
Good thing you don't have
a lot of business
to start with.
Ohhhh, okay.
That was still about me.
Hey, hey, hey.
So you don't have
the biggest package.
Don't feel bad.
I don't feel bad.
I think he feels bad.
No, I don't.
You look like you feel bad.
Okay, well...
You know, not exactly
what I was looking for.
But thanks, guys.
Thank you!
You look good in those pants.
He get it from his mama!
So, remember,
intent is irrelevant.
And that's it.
Pam.
Um, I just wanted to say
that... just,
my mom's coming in today.
Mmmmilf.
Thanks, Kevin.
Usually the day we talk about
sexual harassment
is the day that everyone
harasses me as a joke.
She's coming in today,
and maybe just don't joke
around about that stuff
in front of her?
Great point.
Uh, in fact, uh,
basic rule of thumb.
Let's just act every day
like Pam's mom is coming in.
All right, that's it.
If anybody has any questions
about anything,
you know where I sit
in the back.
Oh, is it over?
Uh, yes.
No.
I know, I know.
It's good.
It is not over.
It is not over 'til it's over.
Did he tell you everything?
Obviously he didn't,
because you all still look
relatively happy,
albeit bored.
Do you realize
what we're losing?
Seriously.
Email forwards.
Exactly.
Can we afford to lose
email forwards?
Do we want that?
I hate them.
You send me these filthy emails.
And you say,
"Forward them to 10 people,
or you'll have bad luck."
Give me a break.
Um, Stanley how about
that hot picture
you have by your desk?
The centerfold in the
Catholic schoolgirl's outfit?
I mean, it is hot, it is sexy,
and it turns him on.
I will admit,
best part of my morning
is staring at it.
But what, are we just
gonna take it away?
That is my daughter.
She goes to Catholic
girl's school.
I'm taking it down right now.
Um, what about office romance?
Office relationships
are never a good idea,
so let's just try to avoid 'em.
But if you already have one,
you should disclose it to HR.
Um, all relationships?
Even a one night stand?
I think the old honor system
was fine.
For example, I have never
slept with an employee.
And believe me, I could have.
Yeah, Meredith.
No, no, Catherine.
Remember her?
Remember how hot she was?
She would have definitely
slept with me.
She wasn't that hot.
Yes, she was.
Dammit, Kevin!
I'm in an office relationship.
It's special.
Mmm, she's nice, she's shy.
She's actually here
if you wanna meet her.
Hold on a second.
Oh, my God.
Put on a shirt!
Put... I told you
that you'd be on camera.
I'm sorry, she's European.
No, I told you
that you'd be on camera.
Stop.
What if Pam was a lesbian?
What if she brought
her "partner" into work?
Would that be crossing the line?
No.
What if they made out
in front of everybody?
Well, that would be...
At home?
And I told everybody
everything about it?
Okay, I'm lost.
Okay.
Well, then, let's act it out.
Pam, you will be girl A.
And girl B will be...
Okay, we'll use the doll.
Pam?
I wish Todd Packer was here,
'cause he would love this.
I wonder if anybody else
would like to join us.
Oop.
Coming out of my mouth.
Hey, um,
we have to watch Toby's video
that he's showing us
in order to brainwash us.
And I was wondering
if anybody'd like to join in?
Gonna be fun.
Got microwave pizza.
What do you say?
Jim?
No, thanks, I'm good.
That's what she said.
Pam?
Um, my mother's coming.
That's what she said...
No, but... okay.
Well, suit yourself.
Hey, Toby.
Hey, Dwight.
You said that we could
come to you
if we had any questions.
Sure.
Where is the clitoris?
On a website it said
on the crest of the labia.
What does that mean?
What does the female vagina
look like?
Technically, I am
in human resources.
And Dwight was asking
about human anatomy.
Um, I'm just sad
the public school system
failed him so badly.
You know, maybe when you get
really comfortable
with each other,
you can ask for that.
Good.
And...
I should get back to work.
Okay.
In today's fast paced
business climate,
it can sometimes to hard to know
when a comment or an action
crosses the line.
Let's take a look
at a couple of scenarios
and ask ourselves,
where is the line?
The natural redhead.
Hey, Marie.
Hey, Joe, Mike.
Hey, settle a bet.
Are you a natural redhead?
Oh my... ay, stop the video!
Wait, go... stop it right there.
Stop it right there.
That's that girl
from that thing.
I banged this girl right here.
That's her?
Yes, this is the one.
You remember...
No, the party?
You banged her?
Right here.
You are a naughty girl.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, hypocrite.
Okay, she is a hypocrite.
That is such a scam.
Okay.
Yes?
Yes, I did.
Okay.
Well, we can talk
about that later then.
Okay, you are never
gonna believe this.
The girl in the video
we're watching
that corporate gave us.
Darryl banged her!
And...
He's about 90% sure.
Don't ever let this little bitch
drive you around town.
We got lost for half an hour.
I don't have any DUls,
so I can drive myself.
But thanks.
Where is Michael Snot?
Sniffing some dude's thong?
Probably.
So you are the lawyer,
Mr. O'Malley.
I know a lot of lawyer jokes.
I love lawyer jokes.
Well, it's probably because
you don't get 'em.
When I said before
that I was king of forwards,
you gotta understand
that I don't
come up with this stuff.
I just forward it along.
You wouldn't arrest a guy
who's just delivering drugs
from one guy to another.
You seem a little bit
agitated, Michael.
What's the problem?
The problem is that...
I am the boss.
And apparently
I can't say anything.
Well, that's... that's true
in a way.
You can't say "anything."
Where's the line?
Where's the line, Jan?
Do you need to see
the video again, Michael?
No, I've seen the video.
He talked the whole time.
No, I didn't.
What?
Attention, everyone.
Hello?
Uh, yes, I just want you
to know that, uh,
this is not my decision.
But from here on out,
we can no longer be friends.
And when we talk about
things here,
we must only discuss
work associated things.
And you can consider this
my retirement from comedy.
And in the future, if I want
to say something funny,
or witty, or do an impression,
I will no longer ever
do any of those things.
Does that include,
"That's what she said"?
Mm-hmm, yes.
Wow, that is really hard.
Do you really think
you can go all day long?
Well, you always left me
satisfied and smiling, so...
That's what she said!
Michael...
Michael!
Michael, please.
Come on!
You would have done the same.
You just didn't
think of it first.
Mi-Michael, please.
I-I... really.
That's not my sense of humor.
Okay.
Hello.
Jan, Mr. O'Malley,
this is my lawyer
James P. Albini.
I believe you may
recognize his face
from the billboards.
He specializes
in free speech issues.
And motorcycle head injuries,
worker's comp,
and diet pill lawsuits.
This guy does it all.
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
Michael, Mr. O'Malley
is your lawyer.
What?
Mr. O'Malley
is our corporate lawyer.
We have him on retainer
to protect the company,
as well as upper level
management
such as yourself.
So I'm not in trouble?
I am so used to being
the bad boy.
I am so used
to fighting corporate
that I forget
that I am corporate.
Upper management.
They hooked me up
with an attorney.
To protect me.
You can't be too careful
about what you say.
Mo' money, mo' problems.
Okay, well, let's get you
out of here, James.
Um, I think
we're under an hour still.
Yeah, but I did a lot
of paperwork at home.
We'll talk about it later.
Thanks for coming in.
Um, hello.
Oh, my God!
I finally made it.
Hello!
I love my mom.
Okay, that's probably the
most obvious statement ever.
This is all yours?
Yeah, I am in charge
of this whole area.
Oh, my goodness.
That's great.
So a guy goes home,
tells his wife,
"Honey, pack your bags,
I just won the lottery."
She goes, "Oh, my God.
That's incredible.
Where are we going?"
He goes, "I don't know
where you're going,
just be out of here by five."
Boom!
This is where
I used to keep my computer.
Oh, right, I remember.
With the picture, yeah.
But I switched stuff around
because I actually needed,
like, more room
for organization.
This is, like, um...
Oh, there he is.
How are you?
Hey, handsome.
You look great.
Oh, thank you.
So, we ready for dinner?
Well, you know,
actually I kind of need to
stall a bit.
But it's okay,
because I am very used
to killing time.
Oh, I don't believe that.
Okay, I'm gonna go wait
in the parking lot.
And what kind of tunes
do you want for the ride?
A little classical,
a little oldies?
Oh, anything is fine.
All right, we'll see ya.
So which one is Jim?
Mom!
I just wanted to know.
No, it's...
All right, okay.
10 minutes,
then we can go to dinner.
I'll make myself busy.
There's this guy,
he's at a nymphomaniac
convention.
And he is psyched,
'cause all these woman
are smoking hot perfect 10s,
except for this one chick
who looks a lot like...
Phyllis?
Yeah.
No, no, no.
That crosses the line.
Ex-squeeze me?
Not you.
Kevin.
Just unwarranted.
Hostile work environment, Kevin.
Packer said it.
No, you said it.
He pointed.
A point is not a say.
Look, Kevin,
we are a family here.
And Phyllis is a valued
member of that family.
Like a grandmother.
I'm the same age
as you, Michael.
I don't know about that.
We're the same
high school class.
Well, I have a late birthday
and usually September
is a cut off point...
You know what?
You just crossed the line, okay?
There is a line
and you went over it.
And you must be punished.
So go to your corner.
You mean where my desk is?
Yes, your corner.
Go.
Okay.
I have a lot of work
to do, anyway.
Oh, my.
They really got to you,
didn't they?
They didn't get to me.
I got to them.
I am still
the same old Michael Scott.
New and improved.
You know what?
I love Phyllis.
You know what else?
I think she is gorgeous.
I think she is an incredibly,
incredibly attractive person.
Come here.
Give me a kiss.
Come on.
Michael, come on,
you don't have to worry.
I'm not gonna...
I'm not worried.
Report you to HR.
You know what?
The only thing
I am worried about
is getting a boner.
Good work today, everybody.
Times have changed a little.
And even though
we're still a family here
at Dunder Mifflin,
families grow.
And at some point,
the daddy can't take a bath
with the kids anymore.
I am upper management.
And it would be inappropriate
for me
to take a bath with Pam.
As much as I might want to.
He said what?