Let's think this through.
If we ask corporate
for that, then...
They are either gonna say...
yes or no.
Could go either way.
We don't know
what they are going to say.
Think it through!
Have to think it through.
Because if they say no...
Can we not?
No... yes, we have to.
You know why?
'Cause I don't like to be
cooped up in that office.
In that box all day long.
Heisman!
Because I need to think.
Okay, Jim?
Oh, Kevin!
Oooh!
Ugh!
Nice catch.
Mm mm mm mm.
Oscar!
Intercepted.
Right here.
Give it to me.
Phyllis, give me the ball.
Okay, give me the ball.
You guys...
Creed, give me the ball
right now.
Give it to me.
Ryan.
Aaaah!
Aaaaah!
Fumble!
Yeah!
All right, hey, Dwight!
Whoo!
Hut hut hut hike!
You all right, Ryan?
Yeah.
Pam!
Oh, they're having
a sale on TiVo.
Maybe I should get a TiVo.
Ooh, DVD burner.
Maybe I should get one of those.
You are so lucky, Jim.
You are so lucky
you don't have this problem.
What was the ninth place
prize again?
A loaf of bread?
Cojino's pizza.
Oh, great.
Tasty terrific pizza.
Question, do their pizzas
play DVDs?
Dwight was the top salesman
of the year at our company.
He wins a little prize money
and gets honored
at some convention.
It is literally
the highest possible honor
that a Northeastern
Pennsylvania based
mid-size paper company
regional salesman
can attain, so...
What did I do to deserve this?
Are you sad
that Dwight beat you?
No.
Are you gonna cry, Jim?
Do you need a tissue?
Hey, I heard you got
a wedding dress.
Do you have pictures?
Oh, yeah.
I'll show 'em to you later.
Oh, I should get back.
Talk to you guys later.
Okay, cool.
I have a ton of stuff
to do for the wedding.
And I have to do it
in the office.
And that can be kind of awkward.
Uh, just because
people can get all weird
about wedding stuff.
I just... I don't
want to offend...
Angela.
Or someone.
That's what she said.
Ha!
I don't get it.
Grapes, seductive.
So, you ready for the
big speech this afternoon?
Well, it's not really
a big speech.
You're still coming, right?
Oh, absofruitly.
Fruit, grapes.
Nailed the joke.
Matter of time.
Uh, and yes, it is a big speech.
Biggest of your life.
Speaker at the sales convention.
Been there, done that.
Went there again, did it again.
Two years in a row.
Consecutive.
I just... I miss the feeling
of knowing
that you did a good job
because somebody
gives you proof of it.
Sir, you're awesome.
Here's a plaque.
What, a whole year has gone by
and you need more proof?
Here's a certificate.
They stopped
making plaques that year.
What if I give a really long
extended thank you?
For instance,
thank you Mr. blank.
Thank you very, very...
That would look terrible.
These are mostly salesmen.
And salesmen expect
to be entertained.
And you are the main act.
When I was in the sixth grade,
I was a finalist
in our school spelling bee.
It was me against Raj Patel.
And I misspelled, in front
of the entire school,
the word "failure".
I can't do this.
That's because
you're incapable of doing it.
Because you don't know how.
Because you have no skills.
Dwight, there's no way
I can possible teach you
what you need to know
about public speaking
by speech time.
Okay.
But I can teach you enough
so that you don't
embarrass me or the company.
Okay, deal.
I'll do whatever you say.
No questions asked.
Well, if you have a question,
you should ask me.
I'll try and think of one.
Don't try to think
of a question to humor me.
Just try not
to be such an idiot.
Is that an insult or is that
part of the public speaking
advice?
Insult.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I know you and Dad are
chipping in for the wedding,
but I do not want
orange invitations.
Yes.
Well, if you really want...
Hi, yeah, can I talk to
one of your travel agents.
I'm gonna take a trip.
I'm gonna get out
of town for a while.
And go someplace...
not here.
Where do I wanna go?
Um, that is
an excellent question.
And one I probably
should have thought about
before I called you.
I get here early every morning
so I can set the thermostat.
I like it a little cooler,
around 66 degrees.
I'm more productive.
Maybe some people don't like it
as cold as I do.
But I don't care.
But seriously,
what's the difference
between a salesman
and a saleswoman?
A saleswoman has a vagina.
It's a joke, Dwight.
It's not a sex ed class.
But I'm right.
Yeah, you're right about
the difference
between a man and a woman
but not about the punchline
to the joke, all right?
The difference between
a salesman and a saleswoman
is boobs.
Hey, do you remember
the speeches that you gave?
I do, both of them.
Could I have a copy
of one of them?
No no, they would remember.
Look, it doesn't matter
what you say,
it just matters that you're
saying something
that people care about.
Yeah?
All right, here we go.
Watch this.
Attention everybody!
Attention please.
I have some very great news
from corporate.
We had a wonderful quarter,
and as a result,
all of you are
getting bonuses for $1,000.
Yeah!
Congratulations.
You see that?
You see how
they responded to me?
In that moment, I had them.
That is so great
about the bonus!
No no, it's not true.
I was just talking.
So just go out there
and say anything.
They'll eat it up,
they're a great audience.
Go ahead, get the wallpaper.
Wallpaper the ceiling
if you want.
Excuse me?
May I have
your attention please?
There had been an accident
on 84 West.
Cars have skidded off the road
into the safety railing.
Several cars have flipped.
There is broken glass
everywhere.
Several people are injured.
Do we know anyone
who was in the accident?
Brad Pitt.
Also, there will be no bonuses.
Why would this
affect our bonuses?
They're unrelated.
Is Brad okay?
He will never act again.
Also, this branch is closing.
What the hell is going on here?
Are we out of jobs?
Yes.
This is karma because
of what he did
to Jennifer Anniston.
He was kidding.
Dwight was kidding.
And I don't know why
because it wasn't funny.
And it was just horrible.
Michael?
Yeah?
You said we were
getting bonuses.
All right, everybody
in the conference room now.
Let's go.
Let's do it.
Cancel the wallpaper.
As your leader and your friend,
I sort of demand
that you can all
speak in public as I can.
And did.
Twice.
You saw the plaque, right?
All right, we're all
gonna go around the room
and we're going to make toasts.
And that way we will
overcome our fear
of public speaking.
You mean toastmasters?
Pam, I'm public speaking.
Stop public interrupting me.
Actually, this would be
good practice
for your wedding toast.
Yeah, the bride doesn't
really do...
Have you ever been to a wedding?
Can I go?
Yes, good.
Jim taking the initiative.
So, uh, I am going on a trip.
But I'm not really sure
where I'm going yet.
It's kinda open ended.
So I was hoping maybe you guys
would have some suggestions.
You should go to Hedonism.
What is that?
It's like Club Med,
but everything is naked.
I was thinking more like Europe.
Or something like that.
But good second choice.
Been to Amsterdam.
Oh, okay, you know what?
That's not a toast.
You're not standing up.
To Amsterdam.
When did you go there?
Um, after my divorce.
Really?
For like how long?
About a week or...
Maybe a month.
Jimmy, listen to me.
You do not want to go
to Amsterdam, trust me.
Where do I wanna go?
I'd send you to Hong Kong.
I'd like to say hi
to my friends in China.
Okay.
Dwight.
Show us what you have
learned today.
Good morning, Vietnam!
Okay, you know what?
This isn't working.
Because, um, I'm not nervous
in front of them.
They're my subordinates.
No, we're not.
Uh, yes, you are.
I am the
assistant regional manager.
Which means absolutely nothing.
Michael, can you explain?
Well, it's mostly made up.
Dwight is not going
to do a good job, it's sad.
And they're expecting excellence
because I did do
such a great job.
Two years in a row I killed.
It was amazing.
Confidence, Dwight!
Dwight, if you could travel
anywhere in the world,
where would you go?
I can travel anywhere,
except Cuba.
And I will travel
to New Zealand.
And walk the
Lord of the Rings trail
to Mordor.
And then I will
hike Mt. Doom.
Now just leave me alone.
Okay, just trying to
get some advice on my trip.
Please, you're not
taking any trip.
You know, I majored
in public speaking in college?
You did?
Mm-hmm.
And the first thing
that they teach you
is that you've gotta
be true to yourself.
And you are all about authority.
Yes, I am.
The great speakers
throughout history
were not joke tellers,
they were people of passion.
So, if you wanna do well today,
you gotta do what they did.
Which is?
You've gotta wave your arms,
and you've gotta
pound your fists.
Many times.
So as to emphasize your point.
Okay, I didn't actually
major in public speaking.
But I did download speeches
from some of history's
famous dictators.
Like this one.
Originally given
by Benito Mussolini.
Okay, look, I know
you're giving this speech
on your own.
But I wrote up
a few talking points
for you to take a look at.
Hope you don't mind.
I'll glance at it.
It's time, Dwight.
The grim reaper is here.
The very best of luck
to you, Dwight.
Thank you, Angela.
Why'd you pick the VA
for the reception?
Roy has a connection.
It's nicer than you think.
You're inviting Jim?
Of course, he's one
of my closest friends.
All right, ready?
Here we go!
Wow, it's a little bit bigger
than I remembered.
Come on, we're down here
in the front.
I am just feeling
under the weather.
And I think that I will
go home and rest.
I've never ever seen you
take a sick day.
Well, I've seen you take enough
for the both of us.
Next, I'd like to introduce
the Dunder-Miflin
salesman of the year
Dwight Schroot!
Dwight, they called your name.
Dwight, how we doing?
Okay, you know what?
You know what?
Okay.
No, no problem.
You are lucky you have me here.
I am going to cover for you.
All right!
Good morning, Vietnam!
I am not Dwight Schrute.
Not at all.
I am Michael Scott,
his mentor and boss.
And until Dwight comes up,
if he ever does,
I wanted to say a few words
about excellence.
What makes
a work environment excellent?
Well, there are many things,
I believe,
that do such
a thing of that... nature.
And one would be humor.
What is the difference
between a salesman
and a saleswoman?
I always set it at 69.
Maybe we'll use a DJ.
That's the one thing
Roy's in charge of
for this wedding,
but all he's managed to do
is set a date.
Well, he did a great job.
June 10th is perfect.
I want a June wedding.
I've always wanted one.
Ryan, do you know when
you would want to get married?
Actually, I don't see
ever getting married.
Oh.
Ryan, you should be
more sensitive.
It's obvious she likes you,
and comments like that...
I know what I said.
I'm very sorry, I did not know
that you were wearing
a hearing aid.
And I just thought
you were speaking abnormally.
And now, the black guy from
the Police Academy movies.
A robot.
Michael Winslow.
Anyone?
A car starting.
All right,
Dwight Schroot, everyone.
Good luck.
That is a tough crowd.
Blood alone moves the wheels
of history!
Have you ever asked yourselves
in an hour of meditation,
which everyone finds
during the day,
how long we have been
striving for greatness?
Not only the years
we've been at war,
the war of work.
But from the moment, as a child,
when we realized that the world
could be conquered.
It has been a lifetime struggle.
A never-ending fight.
I say to you,
and you will understand,
that it is a privilege to fight!
We are warriors!
Salesmen of Northeastern
Pennsylvania,
I ask you, once more,
rise and be worthy
of this historical hour!
I got a time share on Key West
that might be available.
Maybe.
Thanks.
You really think
you're gonna go?
Yeah, I'm definitely going.
Nice.
Send me a postcard.
Jim has worked at the
same place for five years.
Jim eats the same
ham and cheese sandwich
every day for lunch.
I don't know,
if I were a betting man,
I'd say he will have
a fun weekend
in Philadelphia.
No revolution is worth anything,
unless it can defend itself!
Some people will tell you
salesman is a bad word.
They'll conjure up images
of used card dealers
and door to door charlatans.
This is our duty
to change their perception.
I say, salesmen...
and women...
of the world, unite.
We must never acquiesce.
For it is together!
Together that we prevail!
We must never cede control
of the motherland,
for it is...
Together that we prevail!
Australia?
I have always wanted
to go there.
I'm going.
I'm a little nervous
to run into Dwight
on his connecting flight
to Mordor,
but other than that...
Yeah, I bought the ticket.
Non-refundable.
That's awesome.
Where are you staying?
I don't know.
I feel like I have
plenty of time
to figure out the details,
but...
When are you leaving?
I'm leaving on June 8th.
Oh.
Yeah, and I'm really sorry
about that.
Oh, yeah, that's too bad.
Yeah.
Do want me to take these
on my way out?
It's okay, I got it.
All right.
Thanks.
Okay.
There you are.
What happened?
I got thirsty.
How'd it go?
It was amazing.
I wish you
would have been there.
You would not believe
what happened here.
What, did something happen?
Oh, this woman came in.
Sat down.
Ordered a drink.
The bartender asked for her ID,
which I thought was odd.
Because I pegged her as,
like, 35.
Weird.
Yeah, really weird.
So, she's like,
I don't have my ID.
Please give me one.
And he's like, I can't do that.
I can't serve you.
Con artist.
She might have been.
So she says fine,
I will go to my room.
I will get my purse.
I will come back.
I'll show you my ID.
She hasn't come back yet.
She's probably in the room
drinking from the minibar.
Dwight gave a great speech.
That's the word
on the street, anyway.
And I entertained Dwight
to no end
with my bar story.
So I captivated the guy
who captivated 1,000 guys.
Can you believe that?
1,000 guys.