Tonight the Scranton Business
Park is having Casino Night.
And we are converting
our warehouse
into a full-blown
gambling hall.
And I know it's illegal
in Pennsylvania.
But it's for charity.
And I consider myself
a great philanderer.
It's just nice to know
at the end of the day
I can look in the mirror
and say,
"Michael, because of you,
"some little kid in the Congo
has a bellyful of rice
this evening."
Just... makes you feel good.
Ahem.
Excuse me.
How long is the wait
for a table for two?
I would never, ever serve you.
Not in a million, billion years.
It's a nice tux.
I know. It belonged
to my grandfather.
He was buried in it,
so... family heirloom.
So what's the deal?
We've gotta pay
for our own drinks?
That's lame.
Come on, it'll be fun.
And besides,
I'm a roulette expert.
Impossible.
Roulette is not a game of skill.
It is a game of chance.
I can always kind
of win at roulette.
Oh, really?
Mm-hmm?
How would you do that?
Mind control.
You can't be serious.
Are you serious?
Ever since I was little kid,
like eight or nine,
I could sort of control
things with my mind.
I don't believe you.
Continue.
It was just
little things, you know.
Like I could make
something shake.
Or I could make a marble
fall off the counter.
You know, just little things.
Heh!
That's ridiculous.
You know what? Uh...
Why don't you move
that coat rack?
Excuse me, everyone!
Attention in the office, please.
Jim is about to prove
his telekinetic powers.
And he needs absolute silence.
Go ahead.
Okay. I'll try.
Oh, my God.
I try not to think of it
as lagging behind.
It's more of a David
and Goliath thing.
Well, the fact of the matter is,
that your branch is
currently number four
of the five branches
that I oversee.
Top 80%.
Michael...
Yep?
You know that
I'm very serious here.
Jan, listen. I promise I will
kick it up a notch.
Bam!
What?
Emeril. Oh, actually,
while I have you...
Not that I have you
or have ever had you.
But we're having
our Casino Night tonight,
and I think everyone
would love to see
their fearless leader here.
I thought that you were
their fearless leader.
I am, but you are my Eva Perón
to my César Chávez.
I, um, think you can
handle it probably, Michael.
Oh, come on, come on!
It'd be fun.
I can hear it in your voice.
You need a break.
Goodbye, Michael.
Jan and I understand each other.
The romance thing is sort of
on hold for the time being.
But we've remained good friends.
Good friends with privileges.
Not now.
Someday.
Okay, everybody.
Tonight's event
is to benefit
the Boy Scouts of America.
Again.
We do that every year.
Well, they need our money.
They don't have cookies
like the Girl Scouts.
It'd be nice to do
something for people
who are actually suffering.
Well, Oscar,
if you don't like it,
then you should
concentrate on winning.
Because the person
at the end of the evening
with the highest chip count
will receive $500
to donate to the charity
of their choice.
And they will get a mini fridge
compliments of
Vance Refrigeration.
So, get your charities into Pam.
I, for example, am playing
for Comic Relief.
That doesn't exist anymore.
Comedy's very much alive,
as are homeless people.
No, they stopped
making that show.
Well, then they need
our money more than ever.
You have to pick an approved
nonprofit organization.
There's a great soup kitchen
in downtown Scranton.
Delicious pea soup on Thursdays.
I'll probably give
the money to them.
Something with animals.
Or people.
Kobe Bryant has a foundation,
and he is so hot.
And he gave his wife
the biggest diamond ring.
I know he didn't do it.
Maybe he did it.
We are giving money
that has been gambled.
Why don't we just deal drugs
or prostitute ourselves
and donate that money
to charity?
Oh, and another fun thing.
We, at the end of the night,
are going to give the check
to an actual group
of Boy Scouts.
Right, Toby?
We're gonna...
Actually, I didn't think
it was appropriate
to invite children since it's...
You know, there's gambling
and alcohol.
And it's
in our dangerous warehouse.
And it's a school night.
And, you know,
Hooters is catering.
Is that enough?
Should I keep going?
Why are you the way
that you are?
Honestly, every time I try
to do something fun
or exciting,
you make it not that way.
I hate so much
about the things
that you choose to be.
Okay, you know what?
I will not donate my winnings
to Comic Relief since
apparently it doesn't exist.
I am going to donate to
Afghanistanis with AIDS.
I think you mean
the Aid to Afghanistan.
No, I mean Afghanistanis
with AIDS.
Afghani.
What?
That's a dog.
No, that's Afghan.
That's a shawl.
Wait. Canine AIDS?
No, humans with AIDS.
Who has AIDS?
Guys, the Afghanistananis.
You know what?
No. No.
AIDS is not funny.
Believe me.
I have tried.
There are certain topics that
are off-limits to comedians.
JFK. AIDS.
The Holocaust.
The Lincoln assassination
just recently became funny.
"I need to see this play like
I need a hole in the head."
And I hope to someday
live in a world
where a person could tell
a hilarious AIDS joke.
It's one of my dreams.
What are you doing?
Oh, nothing.
"Till Death Do Us Rock."
They're wedding bands.
Oh.
Roy was supposed to
pick the band,
but he's concentrating more
on the bachelor party now.
Wait, wait, where are you going?
I mean, even if you don't
hire a band,
you still have to
watch the bands.
Pam, these are people who have
never given up on their dreams.
I have great respect for that.
And yes, they're all
probably very bad.
And that'll make me feel better
about not having dreams.
There's a KISS
cover band in here.
Let's do it.
I'm pretty happy these days.
I'm getting married soon,
and I'm getting along
with everybody at work.
Why did I talk to Jan
about transferring?
Well, you know...
I have no future here.
I have already put down
the deposit.
Do you understand
how a deposit works?
Mike, I am not having fire
eaters in a paper warehouse.
It's Casino Night.
Like Las Vegas. There are
fire eaters all over the place.
Except my warehouse.
Actually, it's my warehouse.
Actually, it's owned
by Beekman Properties,
and Dunder Mifflin is four
years into a seven-year lease.
Why are you here?
When Darryl was coming,
you said you wanted me
here for protection.
N-N... I said not that.
We just have a lot
of stuff down there
that could be stolen.
That's ironic.
What?
That you are afraid.
Why? 'Cause
I'm from the hood?
Dinkin flicka.
I taught Mike some phrases
to help with his
interracial conversations.
You know, stuff like
"fleece it out,"
"gormac five,
"dinkin flicka."
You know, things us Negroes say.
Give me some.
Oot!
Oh, yeah. I taught him
a handshake, too.
Wow. I don't know
how you're gonna decide.
They are all extremely good.
I think I should hire them all.
Do like Lollapalooza.
Have three stages, yeah.
Your mom would love that.
She would.
Now this band is
called Scrantonicity.
Let's take a look.
Nice.
Oh, wait.
That's Kevin.
On the drums.
What?
On the drums! Oh, my God!
That's Kevin.
Great song, Kev.
Oh, my God. He's the drummer
and the singer.
We really don't do
a lot of weddings.
We actually don't play
in public very often.
We're all really hoping
that Pam's wedding works out.
This could be a turning point
for the band.
Wow. Oh!
Yeah, you haven't seen
that since 1983.
That is amazing.
Okay, we have to sign him.
I'm gonna call the label...
No, no, no!
Come back!
Hey, you're gonna lose him
to another wedding. Kev!
Jim is great.
Being with him just takes away
all the stress
of planning my wedding.
Yes?
Michael, Carol Stills for you.
Who?
Carol Stills.
Do I know a Carol Stills?
Your realtor.
Oh, yeah, put her through.
Hey, Carol, how goes
the real estate biz?
Is it real good?
Still me.
Sometimes I don't put
Michael through
until he's already
said something.
I look at it as
a practice run for him.
He usually does better
on the second attempt.
Carol, you're on with Michael.
Hello, Michael.
Hi, Carol.
how you doing?
I'm great. I just needed
one last signature
for your mortgage insurance.
Oh, hey, no problemo.
Incidentally, I love the place.
Oh, great.
Has a little bit
of a weird smell.
It's okay. At Christmas,
the tree helped.
Oh, good.
I'm glad.
Um, can I drop it over later?
Actually, I'm sort of
hosting this charity thing
in our warehouse.
Casino Night.
Oh, great.
Yeah, it'll be good.
You know what?
Why don't you come by?
Bring the papers.
I'll sign 'em.
And then you can stay
and have a drink.
To the casino thing?
Yeah, it'll be fun.
What do you...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Can you hold on?
Michael, Jan's on line two.
Okay.
Put her through.
Jan Levinson, I presume?
It's still me.
Jan, here's Michael.
Michael?
Hey, Jan.
How you doing?
You know, I... I thought
about it,
and you are right.
I am?
I could use a little fun.
So I am going to drive up
for your Casino Night.
Uh... okay.
Incidentally,
what is the charity?
AIDS.
Okay then. I will...
I'll see you tonight.
Okay.
Sounds great.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Uh, hello, Carol?
Sorry about that.
No problemo.
Right. Um...
To answer your question, yes.
What?
I'd love to go.
Okay.
I have to get a sitter,
but that shouldn't be a problem.
Problem. Good.
And I'll bring the papers too.
Good. All right.
Sounds great.
Well, I'll see you tonight.
Bye.
Two queens on Casino Night.
I am going to drop a deuce
on everybody.
Oh, my God!
Mwah!
That's great!
Hey, Carol.
You look great.
Thanks.
Thank you for inviting me.
It looks so great in here.
Well.
That's how we do it
in the paper biz.
It's European.
Michael.
Yes? Ah, Dwight!
Codename Re/Max is here.
No sign of Ian Jevinson.
I'm Michael's wingman.
I've got his back.
Two dates.
He's got two dates tonight.
My job is keep Jan
away from Carol.
And vice versa.
Michael said, "We must deceive
them so as not to hurt them,
and in that way,
we honor them."
Can I get you a drink?
The food is from Hooters.
A drink would be good.
Okay.
Oh, I steal things all the time.
It's just something I do.
I stopped caring
a long time ago.
You should see how many supplies
I've taken from this place.
Honestly, I love
stealing things.
I'm gonna get a drink.
Do you need anything?
No, I'm fine.
Thanks, sweetheart.
Billy, your nurse is hot.
That's my girlfriend.
Your nurse became
your girlfriend. Sweet.
She was never my nurse.
I met her at Chili's.
She was my waitress.
Chili's is great.
Willkommen. Bienvenue.
And welcome to Monte Carlo.
Dwight.
I am no longer your boss.
Lady Fortune is your boss.
Will Lady Fortune
give me a raise?
Shut it, shut it.
Will Lady Fortune
be your mistress?
Only time will tell, my friends.
Leave all your preconceived
notions about casinos
at the door.
Old friends.
New lovers.
And the disabled.
Welcome all!
Great. Okay.
Shuffle up and deal.
Let's get it started.
Black-eyed crows.
Okay, the game is no-limit
Texas Hold 'Em.
Good luck, everybody.
That's at least
four red chips to you, sir.
All in.
Oh!
Bluffing is a key part of poker,
which is too bad,
because I am not
very good at bluffing.
Did you believe me?
I'll call.
What are...
That's insane.
I have good cards.
Well, Toby, I went
all in on the first hand,
so doesn't that tell you that
I might have good cards too?
So don't be stupid.
Just take it back.
I'm sorry. He can't, sir.
He's gone all in.
Okay, all right, whatever.
Flip 'em.
You really screwed that up.
Way to go, Toby.
I don't really play cards,
but I'm not gonna lie to you.
It felt really good to take
money from Michael.
Gonna chase that feeling.
That's the normal question.
I expect to do
very well tonight.
I have an acute ability
to read people.
Jim for instance
has a huge tell.
When he gets a good hand,
he coughs.
Uh, I will raise.
Thanks.
It's the weirdest thing.
Every time I cough, he folds.
Wow. Bad luck.
Ah, yeah, whatever.
Hey, you know what?
If luck weren't involved,
I would always be winning.
Oh, my God.
Michael.
Jan.
Hi.
Look, okay.
I think we're all adults here.
And it has always been
my understanding
that we have
an open relationship.
What are... Wait.
What are you talking about?
What does that mean?
After you said
you weren't coming,
I invited Carol to come.
And I don't think that
I did anything wrong.
No.
No, you didn't.
Hi, I'm Jan.
I'm Michael's boss.
Hi.
Does anyone want a drink?
No, I'm good.
Okay.
Heh. Um...
Hey, hey.
Hey... what?
Jan's here.
Give me the dice.
Come on, Dwight.
It's on you, baby.
Good evening, Dwight.
What is this?
Evening, Angela.
This is craps.
I need to roll an eight.
If I do, everyone wins.
Then roll an eight.
Thank you, Angela.
Good luck, Dwight.
Yeah! Yeah! Mwah!
That's good stuff.
Dwight, let's keep it going.
Let's keep it going.
Let it ride.
Let it all ride.
Give me the dice!
Yeah, right.
"Yeah, right," what?
What was this?
I have good cards.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
And I'm gonna take you all in.
Wow.
I think you're bluffing.
Yeah, I think she's full of it.
Straight.
Oh.
Three nines.
Jim Halpert,
ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
Cosmopolitan, please.
Can I get a red wine?
So, uh, so two hours.
That's a long drive.
Well, it's part of the job.
You know, keep an eye on things.
So... why not?
So how long have
you and Michael been, um...
Oh, uh, well, actually,
I guess this would be
our first date, I guess.
Casino Night in the warehouse.
Good sport.
Well, I'm having a nice time.
Oh, me too.
Me too.
One beer, and one 7 and 7
with eight Maraschino cherries,
sugar on the rim,
blended if you can.
So that's still going on, huh?
You and Kelly?
All right!
Point is four.
Shooter roll a four.
Come on, shooter!
Blow!
Blow for luck.
Yeah!
Also you.
Not playing favorites.
All right, here we go.
Yeah!
Five.
Aw, so close, so close.
Come on.
So, where are you
staying, Radisson?
What? Super 8? Motel 6?
Best Western.
I didn't...
Holiday Inn?
The Hyatt
in Wilkes-Barre?
Are you staying with Michael?
All right!
I won the 2002 $2,500
No-Limit Deuce to Seven
Draw Tournament
at the World Series
of Poker in Vegas.
So, yeah, I'm pretty good
at poker.
All in.
Okay, let's do it.
Good luck, honey.
Oh, thank you, Bobby,
but it doesn't matter.
It's just fun to play.
Three queens.
Nice, very nice.
I have an Ace.
No, that's a flush.
Oh, man!
I have a flush!
Yes!
Look, I won. Look,
I have all the clovers.
You want to play again?
I suck.
She took you down, huh?
I do not want to talk about it.
Hey, I saw your tape.
Your band, Scrantonicity.
You guys rock.
Yeah?
Yeah, you guys want
to play our wedding?
Awesome.
Did Pam say it was okay?
Whatever.
I'm in charge of the music.
Dude, you will not be sorry.
Sweet.
All right.
Smoke?
No, thanks.
You having fun?
Fabulous time.
I drove two and a half hours
to get here.
Yeah, we all really... Left
work early, drove down here.
And I am completely
underdressed.
I think you look great.
Why did I hook up with Michael?
Yeah, why did you?
It was very late, Jim.
Very late and, uh...
Have you given any more thought
to the transfer?
Oh, yeah.
Good.
Mm-hmm.
Have you told anyone?
No.
Well, you should.
Uh, excuse me.
Uh, big moment.
The evening's chip leader
and winner of this beautiful
mini refrigerator
courtesy of Vance Refrigeration,
Creed Bradden,
Dunder-Mifflin.
Thanks. I never owned
a refrigerator.
Sorry, babe.
I'm just beat.
It's okay. I'll see you at home.
Okay.
Hey, don't try to lose
too much money, all right?
Okay. In case you still
want a honeymoon.
Hey, Halpert.
Keep an eye on her, all right?
Okay.
Will do.
Bye.
Hey.
Hey, how's it going?
Good.
Especially after I took all your
money in poker. Ha-ha, yeah.
Hey, can I talk to you
about something?
About when you wanna give me
more of your money?
No. Did you wanna do that now?
We can go inside.
I'm feeling kinda good tonight.
I was just, um...
I'm in love with you.
What?
I'm really sorry if that's
weird for you to hear,
but I needed you
to... hear it.
Probably not good timing.
I know that, I just...
What are you doing?
What do you expect me
to say to that?
I just needed you to know.
Once.
Well, I, um...
I...
I can't.
Yeah.
You have no idea...
Don't do that.
...what your friendship
means to me.
Come on.
I don't wanna do that.
I wanna be more than that.
I can't.
I'm really sorry
if you misinterpreted things.
It's probably my fault.
Not your fault.
I'm sorry I misinterpreted
our friendship.
Hey!
I'm leaving. Hey! Okay.
So I just wanted
to congratulate you
on a fantastic evening.
Did the company proud.
Thank you.
And, uh, thanks for inviting me.
You were right.
I needed it, so thanks.
Okay. Thanks for coming.
Nice to meet you.
And you guys have a good
time together. Okay.
Talk to you Monday.
Yep.
Bye-bye.
Good night.
She's a good boss.
She seems really nice.
Oh, she's great.
Love triangle drama.
All worked out
in the end though.
The hero got the girl.
Who saw that coming?
I did.
And Jan is really happy for me.
So actually,
the hero got two girls.
He got the girl
that he works with,
and he got the girl
that he buys real estate from.
So I've got my New York girl
and my local flavor.
Life is good.
About ten minutes ago.
No, I didn't know what to say.
Yes, I know.
Um, I don't know, Mom.
He's my best friend.
Yeah, he's great.
Yeah, I think I am.
Um, I have to go.
I will.
Listen, Jim.