What?
Oh, nothing.
Pam's on vacation,
and she gets back tomorrow.
So, it'll be nice to see her.
It'll be nice.
And, uh, she set a date
for the wedding with Roy.
Uh, June. Summer.
So, that'll be nice.
And that's that.
What?
Oh, nothing.
Jim's been looking at me
kind of a lot all week.
I would be creeped out by it,
but it's nothing compared
to the way Michael looks at me.
Spamster.
Um... Pam, plus Spam,
plus...
Hamster.
Right.
Welcome back.
How was your vacation?
It was great.
Yeah?
Did you get lucky?
Oop! Boink.
Roy and I just got back
from the Poconos.
I get ten vacation days a year.
And I try to hold off taking
them for as along as possible.
And this year I got to
the third week in January.
I am Pam.
Spicoli guy.
Oh, God.
He needs numbers.
Okay.
Whoa! God! Yuck!
Yuck, yuck, yuck.
What?
Yuck! Wow!
What happened in there?
I don't know.
There is stink in there.
My God.
What is that?
Oh, I don't know.
Is that a bird?
I don't think it's a bird.
Oh, God, how could that happen?
How could...
Right in the middle
of the carpet.
What's going on?
Uh, somebody vomited
right in the middle
of the carpet in my office.
I don't think that's vomit.
Check it out.
Me?
Don't be a wuss.
Just get...
No, I'm not holding your coffee.
Tell me what it is.
Oh, that's a real bitch.
What is it?
Michael.
No, just tell me what it is.
Michael, I gotta get outta here.
I can't hold my breath
that long.
Open the door up.
It smelled terrible.
Oh! Phew!
Oh, no.
Mmm-mmm.
I cannot believe a pipe burst
and left that there.
That's no burst pipe.
Well, how do you know that?
What is it then?
Hey, guys.
Somebody making soup?
Here she comes.
All cleaned? Great.
Too stinky.
That is worse.
She probably scrubbed it
into the fibers of the carpet.
Total permeation.
I am a big Fear Factor fan.
Um, I'm a big fan of anything
Joe Rogan does, actually.
So, this is sort of like
my audition tape.
Um...
I can't stand it.
I can't stay in here
another second.
- Hey, welcome back.
- Thanks.
So, how was the resort?
Did you ski a lot?
A little.
Good.
What's going on in here?
What? I did not do that.
That sounds disgusting.
It wasn't me.
Um... it wasn't me.
It was not me.
Oh.
Wow.
Hey, Jim, I thought
that we would be desk buddies
while they change my carpet.
That might be a little difficult
with the one computer.
Oh.
But there's definitely a desk
open in the back.
Yeah...
Which I guess I'll be taking.
No, no, no, seriously.
I don't mind sharing.
No, no, no.
Seriously, I'll be in the back.
Hey, Kelly.
Are you moving back here?
Um, just for the day
while Michael's at my desk.
Because Toby used to sit there.
But then he had to move over
there because of an allergy.
Allergy to... the desk?
Weird.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ol' bullpen.
Ha, ha, ha.
The ol' bullpen.
Don't hate me.
Okay.
This is great.
Yeah.
The pressures of my
office are insane. Mmm.
I just... you
couldn't understand.
But, man, you guys have it
easy out here.
You know, I used to sit
right here?
No way.
Yeah.
And who had your office?
Ed Truck.
Yuck.
Ed Truck was the manager
before me.
Horrible.
He hated fun.
It was like, oh, Ed Truck
is walking toward us.
Stop having fun.
Start pretending to do work.
What a jerk.
He's...
You know what?
I swore to myself,
that if I ever got
to walk around the room
as manager,
people would laugh
when they saw me coming.
And would applaud
as I walked away.
I'm serious, my closet doors
will not shut.
I mean, it only takes so long
to measure to make sure
that clothes will hang up.
'Cause aren't all hangers,
like, that big?
So I don't understand why
the closet engineer
didn't think of that.
So now I'm doing this new thing
where I just leave piles
of clothes on the floor.
And I walk around the piles
to get an outfit...
You know who used
to sit at that desk?
That guy Miles who quit
to form his own company?
Mmm-mmm. Todd Packer.
No. I thought he was
out on the road.
He was, but, uh...
that desk was empty.
He'd come in and sit
there sometimes. Ah.
When I was in training,
many years ago, not so long ago,
I worked side by side
with a fellow named Todd Packer.
And together we
rocked the office.
Packer and I once spent
a whole day with our pants off.
And when people noticed,
we convinced them
that they were crazy.
I would gladly pay you Tuesday
for a Hamburger today.
Excuse me one second please.
What is it that you need
right now that can't wait
until I'm off the phone
with a customer?
Ooh, a customer.
Well, sound the alarm.
Okay.
Another time, Packer held this
guy's head in the toilet
for like a minute.
Guy had no sense
of humor about it.
Probably why he wasn't hired.
Unnh!
Oh.
What did you hit me for?
Oh, Charlie horse. Charlie horse!
What?
You shouldn't have
hit me, Michael.
Okay.
Gah.
Once as a joke, Packer banged
every chick in the office.
It was hysterical.
Beyoncé, pink, the color,
Pink, the person,
hot dogs, basically anything
that is awesome.
Sno-cones.
Hey, Jim,
Michael wanted me to ask you how
to raise your desk chair.
It's the lever on the side.
That's what I told him.
Thanks.
Oh, my God, he is so cute.
Would you talk to him for me
and see if he likes me?
Oh, no, I don't think I can...
Oh, please, Jim.
Please, please, Jim.
Please, please, please?
He's so cute.
I like him so much.
And I would do it,
but I'm too shy.
Please, Jim?
Please, please, please?
Please, Jim, please?
Please, please?
Dwight.
Michael.
Let's set up accounting.
What?
Old-fashioned raid.
Sales on accounting.
Follow my lead.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Michael. Hey, Dwight.
What's up?
Whoo hoo!
Come on, come on, come on!
Sales rules!
Yeah, yeah!
Should we help them
pick up their stuff?
No, no, no, no.
We don't do that.
Watch out, Pam.
You're next.
You're gonna throw
my things on the ground?
Maybe.
What happened in Michael's
office was wrong.
I understand it.
It makes sense.
But it's... but it was
still wrong.
Why would somebody ruin
a perfectly good carpet?
I don't know.
Could be done out of hate.
Could be done out of love.
It could be completely neutral.
Maybe somebody hates
the cleaning lady.
Well, she doesn't
do a very good job, obviously.
Because my office still reeks
like you would not believe.
I hate her.
You know what?
I am beginning to think
that what happened to my carpet
was an act of terrorism
against the office.
The only thing
that makes any sense.
Hello, am I the 107th caller?
Hello, Rock 107,
am I the 107th caller?
I'm totally going to win us
that box set.
Stop.
Stop it.
Don't.
I need to make a sales call.
Please.
All right.
Am I the 107th caller?
Yeah, right.
Every day I go to bed,
and I have, like,
a weird pinch in my back.
And when I wake up, I feel fine.
But it's so hard to fall asleep.
cause I try to go to bed
at, like, 9:30 every night.
Hi, guys.
We haven't finished
getting things in order
from your last visit.
- I'm just walking around.
- Were you?
Well, yeah. It's just
that we're really swamped
- over here, Michael.
- Oh, and I'm not?
Why would you say that?
Because I'm having fun?
You guys just are working
for the weekend, are you?
I'm working for the week.
Sales team.
Listen to me.
This is what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna up the ante
a little bit literally.
Right here, I'm going
to put a crisp $100 bill.
The person with the most sales
at the end of the day
gets to keep the cash.
- Sound good?
- Yeah!
70, 80, 1, 2, 3.
$83. Still a lot of money.
And I'm going to...
I'm going to leave it
right over here
where everybody can see it.
I will be taking
Jim's clients today
because he is not here.
And out of sight,
out of the contest.
Let's see who winds up
with the cash, shall we?
You're going to compete
against us?
Oh, it is on, Phyllis!
It is so on!
God, this is gonna be fun.
Michael is gonna wipe
the floor with us.
So you have 40 boxes going out.
And I will deliver those
personally in a Sebring.
Very good.
Nice doing business with you.
Thank you.
Yeeeeeees!
Ho ho ho ho. Yeah.
Ooh, look at that.
Look at me, Phyllis.
Oh, what is that?
That's my sale.
What... what's that?
What you doing?
Nothing.
- I think he's dancing.
- No, just...
That was definitely not dancing.
You know what, guys?
It's none of your concern.
It was official business.
- Paper business.
- Yeah, paper business.
- Is this done?
- No.
Extreme Home Makeover
puts together a house
in an hour.
If you were on that crew,
you'd be fired like that.
Somebody did something bad
to Michael's carpet.
Maybe that's all
we need to know.
Who do you think did it?
Are you kidding?
I thought it was you.
Really. I thought you.
This was no act of God.
A person did this.
A person who works
in this office.
Maybe all of them.
You know what?
Today is not a good day
for a sales contest.
We're... we're... we're not
doing this today.
That doesn't seem fair.
You want to talk about fair?
Does anyone need to smell
my old carpet?
You explain to me
how that was fair,
and I'll explain to you
how this is fair.
Plus I just... I think
that picking today
was sort of taking advantage.
But you're the one
who picked today.
I am a victim of a hate crime.
Stanley knows
what I'm talking about.
That's not what a hate crime is.
Well, I hated it a lot, okay?
I... You know what?
If the guilty person
would just come forward
and take their punishment,
we'd be done.
Very well.
Then you're all punished.
What's our punishment?
You're all on a time out.
Just sit there quietly.
No, no.
- Hey.
- What's up?
Nothing much.
Let me ask you something.
It's actually a little awkward.
What do you think of Kelly?
I don't know.
Depends if you like
a little junk in...
Um, she's really cool.
Are you interested in her?
Yeah, totally.
- Really.
- Did she say something?
She said lots of things.
Do you know if she's looking
for a long-term thing
or if she'd be cool
just hanging out?
I have no idea.
Can you find out?
Yeah.
Sure.
Oh, long-term,
definitely.
Fall in love, have babies,
spend every second together.
But don't tell him that, okay?
Just tell him I'm, like,
up for anything.
I mean, I'm not a slut,
but who knows.
Do you remember Ed Truck?
Sure, he hired me.
How's he doing?
How would I know?
I thought you might.
My biggest fear
is turning into him.
Michael, you should have
much bigger fears than that.
I wasn't talking
literally, Creed.
Yeah, being buried alive
would be worse.
Happy?
Why am I talking to you?
Ed? Hi, thanks
for meeting me.
Must be kind of neat
coming back.
Yeah. Shall we go upstairs?
Uh, well, honestly, Ed,
I really don't want
to be up there right now.
So what's the problem
with my pension?
Oh, no, no, no.
You're good.
It was clerical.
Um, well,
somebody did something
in my office,
and I now think that they
did it on purpose
and it was directed at me.
But what was done?
I didn't get a good look at it.
But it smells horrible.
Yeah, somebody once
did that in my office.
- Really.
- Yeah.
Well, that figures.
So how did you deal
with people not liking you?
You can't expect
to be friends with everybody.
Well, sure I can.
No. They'll always
think of you as a boss first.
Not necessarily.
You can love a boss
like you do a father.
I'm not sure that ever happens.
Well, okay,
different management styles.
Why can't your workers
be your workers,
family be your family,
your friends be your friends?
Last week, I would've
given a kidney
to anyone in this office.
I would've reached
right into my stomach
and pulled it out for them.
But now, no.
I don't have the relationship
with these people
that I thought I did.
I hope they ask.
So they can hear me say, uh, no.
I only give my organs
to my real friends.
Get yourself a monkey kidney.
Hey, Brenda,
this is, uh, Jim Halpert
from the boat.
And I got your number
from the corporate directory.
And, well, I was assuming
that you probably
gave it to them
because you wanted me
to ask you out, right?
Um, so give me a call back.
You can get my number
from said directory,
um, or just check your email
cause I just sent you one.
Yikes. Uh, give me
a call back...
I hope. I'll talk
to you later.
Bye.
You just asked a girl out
on the phone.
Yup.
Yes.
Hello. Yes.
I'm looking for a gay nerd
named Michael Scott.
Who is this?
How did you get this number?
Your mom, you gay nerd.
Oh my God. Packer.
Packster.
Wacky Pack.
How you doing?
Hey, listen, did you get
that package I left for you?
Uh, no.
Did anybody see a package
here today?
No. How big was it?
It was pretty big.
Really?
Yeah.
Did you see a big package?
Where did you leave it?
Left it in the middle
of your office.
Really. Guys, did you see
a big package
in my office?
You mean the thing?
Are you kidding me?
Oh.
Special delivery.
That was Packer!
Oh, you're...
oh, you are dead.
You are dead, my friend.
That is hilar...
Oh God!
Of course it was you.
Sit on the throne, Michael.
Oh, yeah, yeah!
Oh my God.
It was Packer.
It takes an advanced sense
of humor.
I don't expect everybody
to understand.
It was done out of love
just like I thought.
It's, uh, God,
these people are so...
these are good people.
We have fun.
We just have fun.
Oh, I'm just so sorry
that I threw the thing out.
You have seven unheard messages.
Hey, Jim. It's Pam.
I keep looking up
to say something to you,
and then Michael's there.
And it's horrible.
Anyway, I'm bored.
Come back.
Hey, guess what.
I moved my computer
so I can't see Michael's head.
I think I can have a career
as a very specific
type of decorator.
Sudoku. Level: moderate.
Time: 18 minutes.
Suck on that, Halpert.
I'll transfer you.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Hold, please.
Dunder Mifflin, this is...
Okay, sorry.
Michael was standing at my desk
and I needed to be busy
or who knows
what would've happened.
So thank you.
Hey, what's that word we made up
for when you have a thing
stuck in your shoe?
Anyway, I have a thing
stuck in my shoe.
Hey, I have a chance
to sneak out of here early,
and I'm not messing this up
so I'll see you tomorrow.
Calling from my cell phone.
I don't know
if you guys figured out
who did that to Michael's
carpet yet,
but I have a theory
that it involves
an interdepartmental
conspiracy...
everybody in the office.
We need to talk.