Nothing much.
What's up with you?
I cannot believe
I feel for that.
Gosh.
Ha ha. What?
What?
Where's the funny?
Give it to me.
Um, is it me or does it
smell like updog in here?
What's updog?
Nothing much.
What's up with you?
Oh, wow.
I walked right into that.
Oh, that's brilliant.
Hey, Stanley.
Is that jacket made of updog?
I'm on the phone.
Mm!
What flavor coffee
is that, updog?
What's that?
I don't know. Nothing.
What's up with you?
Huh? No. Damn it.
What does that mean?
What does what mean?
That thing you just said.
Just forget it.
Dwight.
Hey, is it me,
or does this place
smell like updog?
What's updog?
Gotcha!
Oh, God!
Crap.
Nothing.
How are you doing?
Good.
Mm.
Today is spring cleaning day
here at Dunder-Mifflin.
And yes, I know it's January.
I am not an idiot.
But if you do your spring
cleaning in January,
guess what you don't have
to do in the spring?
Anything.
They say a cluttered desk
means a cluttered mind.
Well, I say an empty desk
means an...
Empty mind.
No, that's not...
No.
That's not what I was gonna say.
Meredith, men's room.
Make sure you replace
the urinal cakes.
They're worn down.
Kevin, file drawers.
Angela, kitchen.
Oscar, dusting.
Where is Oscar?
He's out sick.
That's unacceptable.
I agree.
It's unacceptable.
What are you guys doing?
Michael.
- Yes.
Oscar is out sick.
On a Friday?
- Can I do some of the talking?
- I will do the talking.
Okay, let him know
that I'm here though.
- What difference does it make whether you're here?
- Hello?
Hi, Oscar, it's Michael.
And Dwight.
Yeah, um, heard you were
under the weather.
Yeah, I think I came down
with the flu.
Really. Oh, that is a shame.
You know, it's cleaning day
here today.
Could've used some of that
famous Hispanic cleaning ethic.
Yeah, I feel terrible about it.
Ask for his symptoms...
I'm on WebMD.
What are your symptoms?
I have the chills,
I'm feeling nauseous,
and my head's killing.
Checks out.
Michael, is there anything
you need from me?
I would like to go back to bed.
I need you to go to bed.
I need you to get better.
See you Monday,
unless you're still sick.
So, have a great long weekend.
I'll just be sleep...
Okay, first impressions.
He sounded sick.
Which is exactly how you'd
want to sound
if you wanted someone
to think you were sick.
That's exactly what
I was thinking.
Question, may I investigate?
Yeah, drop what you're doing.
Make this a priority.
Because an office can't
function efficiently
unless people are at their desks
doing their jobs.
I bought my veil.
Oh, my God, that is so exciting.
Can I be a bridesmaid?
Um...
Listen, you don't
have to answer now,
but how are you gonna
do your hair?
Okay, I was thinking about
wearing it down.
Kinda like,
I don't know, like...
loose with big curls.
You look like an angel.
I'm seriously gonna cry.
Wowie.
Mikey likey.
Why don't you wear your hair
like that all the time?
It's much sexier.
Man, this must be
torture for you.
Yeah, on the booze cruise,
I told Michael about
some feelings
I used to have for Pam.
I had just broken up with Katie,
and had a couple of drinks,
and I confided in the world's
worst confidant.
Okay.
Hey, Mike.
Hey, Jim bag.
Remember that thing I told you
on the booze cruise about Pam?
That was personal.
So, if we could just keep
that between you and me,
that would be great.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Who else knows?
Nobody.
Wow.
Jim and I are great friends.
We hang out a ton.
Mostly at work.
But the fact that he told me
his secret and no one else,
says everything about
our friendship.
And it is why I intend
on keeping that secret
for as long as I possibly can.
Bangles.
All right, great, thank you.
Listen, temp, I am conducting
a little investigation.
So, I am no longer gonna be able
to head up spring cleaning.
Do you think you can handle it?
Yeah, I think I can handle it.
Do you think, or do you know?
I think.
Oh, God.
Here.
Hey, whatcha getting?
I'm going with grape.
Ah, good stuff.
Good stuff.
Yup.
See the game last night?
Which game?
Any of 'em.
So, uh, what's the 4-1-1?
Any updates
on the "P" situation?
I don't know what you mean...
P-A-M...
P-A?
Okay.
No, it's okay.
We're talking code.
Well...
What is?
Listen, Stan...
how long does it take you
for you to pick out a soda?
I'm gonna take off, actually.
All right, well.
Cool.
Still deciding?
Hmm?
Peach iced tea.
You're gonna hate it.
Hey, Oscar, how you doing?
Dwight Schrute calling.
Listen, little question
for you, buddy.
I called six minutes ago,
and no one answered.
So I was wondering
if you could expl...
Oh, I see.
So, sounds like you're too sick
to come into work,
but you're well enough
to go to the pharmacy.
There are several different ways
to tell if a perp is lying.
The liar will avoid
direct eye contact.
The liar will cover part of his
or her face with his hand.
Especially the mouth.
The liar will perspire.
Unfortunately, I spoke
to Oscar on the phone.
So none of this is useful.
It's grrrrape soda.
Tony the Tiger, you don't hear
that much anymore.
Not so much.
Okay, what is going on here?
Nothing.
Oh, really, nothing?
Fact, you are
drinking grape soda.
You never drink grape soda.
Fact, you are talking to Jim,
you never talk to Jim.
Fact, I love grape soda.
I always have.
Fact, Jim and I talk
all the time.
We tell each other secrets.
Okay, so what is the secret,
Michael?
Um, I had asked Michael
if I could head up the Oscar
investigation,
and he said that only Dwight
was capable of handling
such sensitive material.
Is that true?
Um...
I-I don't know.
Uh, yeah, yeah, it is.
Thank you, Michael.
I know you're telling the truth.
Okay.
I can tell.
I won't let you down.
Good.
Thanks.
Nice, that was... that was slick.
What're you doing for lunch?
I don't know, I'm probably just
gonna eat my ham and cheese
sandwich in the break room.
Oh, nonsense.
No way, no.
Why don't, uh...
Why don't I take you
out to lunch? My treat.
Uh, no, that's all right.
Thank you, though.
It's... I gotta do
some cleaning.
I should probably
stick around here.
Hey, you know what we could do?
Spread out a blanket
in the break room,
have a little picnic,
order some 'za.
Talk about you-know-who.
Oh, um, nope.
You know what, let's go out.
That was a good idea.
- Let's go out.
- I know just the place.
Oh, man.
You should order milk.
Get it?
Why do I like Hooters?
Well, I will give
you two reasons.
The boobs and the hot wings.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
Bogie at three o'clock.
Hi.
Hey, I'm Dana.
Welcome to Hooters.
We're not worthy.
Hello, Dana.
I am Michael, and this is Jim.
And we are brothers.
Nope. We're not brothers.
I'm his boss, actually.
And I treat him well.
I'm taking him out to lunch
because I can afford it.
And he can have
whatever he wants.
I'll just have the ham
and cheese sandwich, thanks.
And for you?
Tell me, Dana.
How is your chicken breast?
Oh, it's great.
It's served with our
world-famous wing sauce.
Mm, sounds yummy.
I will have a chicken breast.
Hold the chicken.
Is that what you really want?
No, I'm gonna have
the gourmet hotdog.
Great.
Who took all the black ones?
That's a communal bowl.
So, how did Oscar sound
when he called in?
Sick. Like, lots of sniffling.
I don't know.
Sniffling how?
Um, how many different ways
are there to gonna sniffle?
Three.
Okay, it was the second one.
Okay, good.
Thank you.
That wasn't so hard, now was it?
Mm-mm.
What do you like best about Pam?
Oh, I really don't wanna
talk about it.
Her legs or boobs, or...?
Um, she's easy
to talk to, I guess.
And, uh, she's got a really good
sense of humor.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
She never gets any of my jokes.
What about you?
Her boobs, definitely.
Wow, that's not what I meant.
- Here you go.
- Oh, thank you.
And I understand,
We have a birthday today.
- Oh, happy birthday, Jim.
- Ready, girls?
Thank you.
Whoo! Yeah!
Thanks.
Thanks, Dana.
Thank you very much.
Whew.
That was hilarious. Hey.
What did you guys talk about?
Just, you know, politics.
Literature.
I hate you.
Quick Oscar update.
I have conducted interviews
with everyone in the office...
Just go to his house
and see if he's sick.
I could've done this
investigation in,
like, 20 minutes.
Including prep time?
Just do it.
If I had to, I could clean
out my desk in five seconds
and nobody would ever know
I had ever been here.
And I'd forget too.
Expense this.
Michael, is that a wig?
No, it's...
I wear it like that sometimes.
Is that a wig?
This is from Hooters.
Yeah, it was a business lunch.
Did Toby approve this?
No, he did not.
I don't need his permission.
They just just got your
corporate credit card back.
Do you really want me
to take it away again?
It's ridiculous.
They took my card away
because I spent 80 bucks
at a magic shop.
What they don't understand
is that I bought the stuff
to impress potential clients.
So business-related, right?
I put a cigarette through
a freaking quarter.
And you know what, Toby?
They almost bought from us.
I'm not processing this.
Look, Jim needed
a relaxing lunch.
He has been depressed.
And it has been affecting
his productivity.
How is that not work-related?
He seems fine to me.
You're not his friend.
You don't know.
He is in love with a girl
he works with who's engaged.
So just cut me some slack,
please.
Pam?
Hey, Angela,
who would you choose?
Jim or Roy?
It's nobody's business, Phyllis.
Roy.
Jim has got it bad for Pam.
Oh-ho.
Which one is Pam?
Well, she di...
Hey, Michael?
Hmm?
So do you think Jim will try
to break up the wedding?
You know what, Kevin?
Jim is a friend of mine.
So the only people that
this crush really concerns
is Jim and Pam... and me.
As a volunteer sheriff's deputy,
I've been doing surveillance
for years.
One time,
I suspected an ex-girlfriend
of mine of cheating on me.
So I tailed her
for six nights straight.
Turns out she was.
With a couple of guys,
actually, so.
Mystery solved.
Jim, why didn't you tell me
that you had a crush on Pam?
Well, the cat's out of the bag.
I used to have a crush on Pam.
And now I don't.
Riveting.
Yeah.
No, it's not.
Nice.
She is so hot.
Hey.
Did you find anything good
in your desk?
Uh, coupon for a free sandwich.
- Score.
- Expired in August.
And my cell phone charger
from two years ago.
Big day.
Hey, uh, listen.
Um...
I told Michael
on the booze cruise...
So stupid.
Um...
I told Michael that I had
had a crush on you
when you first started here.
Oh.
Well, I just thought that...
I figured you should
hear it from me.
Rather than, I mean,
you know Michael.
Right.
And... seriously.
It's totally not a big deal.
Okay?
And when I found out
that you were engaged, I mean...
No, I... I know.
Like, I kind of...
Like, I...
I thought that maybe you did.
- When I first started.
- Oh, you did?
No, I mean, just 'cause we,
like, got along so well.
No, I know, yeah.
You saw through me.
Great.
So are you gonna be, like,
totally awkward around me now?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Hope that's okay.
Mm-hmm.
And Pam.
It was, like, three years ago.
So I am totally over it.
Cool.
Okay.
This is it. There he is.
He's been gone
for at least two...
Who is that?
Come to Papa.
I got it. Close that.
You got those.
Oh, yes. Oh, nice.
Let's roll.
I knew it!
Oh, man, you are so busted.
Ice-skates.
Shopping bags.
I think I know what's
going on here.
You weren't sick at all.
Who's this?
This is Dwight Schrute.
Who is this?
Gil.
Are you going to tell Michael?
How 'bout this?
I don't tell Michael,
and in exchange,
you owe me one great, big,
giant favor
redeemable by me at a time
and place of my choosing.
Guess what I found out
about Oscar tonight?
He was lying about being sick.
Should I have reported
Oscar's malfeasance?
Hmm, probably.
But know I know something
he doesn't want me to know.
So I can use his malfeasance
to establish leverage.
Otherwise, it's just malfeasance
For malfeasance's-s sake.
Hey.
I know.
I know, I know.
Um...
What happened?
I... oh.
Just, um, you know,
I was trying...
just the expense reports.
And then... God, Toby, you know?
He just...
I know.
I just...
I just hope that...
Oh, I just hope that this
doesn't affect our friendship!
It's stupid.
It's so stupid.
Hey, hey, whoa, whoa.
Listen, man, it's...
You know, it's not a big deal.
It's gonna be fine.
No, I know.
I'm good, I'm good.
It's just...
Look, it's one day.
Everything's gonna be all right.
- Yeah, okay.
- You good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Okay.
Creed, did you organize
the menu book?
Oh, I thought that was
more on a volunteer basis.
No. That was mandatory.
Oh, I thought it was
a volunteer thing.
Hey, here's your schedule
for next week.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Look.
About you and Jim...
Oh, no, that's...
You don't have to...
No, I just feel it's my
responsibility
as your boss-slash-friend...
No, it's really... it's okay.
Um, I know that Jim had, like,
a crush on me
when he first started.
But that was a long time ago,
so...
It wasn't that long ago.
It was on the booze cruise.
Jim had a crush on me
on the booze cruise,
or he told you about it
on the booze cruise.
Um... okay.
Shut it, Michael.
I'm done.
That's it, I'm out.
- Ready?
- Yup.
People are always coming to me.
"Michael, I have a secret.
You're the only one I trust."
No, thanks,
because keeping a secret
can only lead to trouble.
Like, I was watching Cinemax
last weekend, this movie.
Portrait of a Prostitute.
Something... Secrets of a...
More Secrets of a Call Girl.
And the lead character, Shila,
is framed for murder.
Goes on the run, and winds up
working at a bordello in Malibu.
I don't... I don't wanna
live like that.
I like it here.
I don't wanna be Shila.
I like being Michael Scott.