The Stanford branch is closing,
and everybody's just
packing up their stuff.
Andy Bernard
made these tasteful hats.
...that's the other thing
you gotta watch out... Yo!
Tuna, I wanna talk to you about
this new boss, Michael Scott.
Yeah?
So, what's he like?
Likes, dislikes,
favorite sports,
favorite movies,
favorite... men's magazines.
You know what, I think you
just need to meet him.
Playing your cards
close to the vest, I get it.
Good luck over there, Tuna.
Cross me,
and I will destroy you.
Sounds good, Andy.
This is gonna be an adventure.
Yes, this is going to be
very interesting.
All right.
I'm outta here.
See you later?
Right on.
Hey, is that Josh's comput...
What?
Hey.
- Hey.
How'd the run go?
Ah, pretty good.
I finished.
That's great.
- Thanks.
Why is that great?
Because he
accomplished something.
What was your mile time?
About seven.
I could beat that
on a skateboard.
Well, that has wheels.
Yeah, well, my feet don't,
and I could still
crush that time.
Really, Dwight?
How fast are you?
Let's just put it this way...
Last weekend, I outran
a black pepper snake.
Really?
I am fast.
To give you a reference point,
I'm somewhere between a snake
and a mongoose.
And a panther.
Man, what is
taking Toby so long?
Oh, I'll just time him later.
And you'll compare the times?
Yeah.
Are you ready?
Set, go!
- No. My groin's really tight.
I can't...
Am I being mean to Dwight?
I don't know.
I did just make him
run around the building,
and I have no intention
of timing him.
This isn't even a stopwatch.
It's a digital thermometer.
He does make my life
harder sometimes.
And on purpose.
Like he tried to put meters
on the bathroom stalls
as a way of bringing in
more money for the company.
Hey!
Three more laps to go!
You gotta pick it up
if you're gonna beat Toby!
Well, I should probably
get back to work.
He-e-ere...
Who's here?
Nametag?
- Yes, please.
Karen Filippelli.
Karen Filip...
Karen a-Filippelli.
Probably Italian.
Possibly Filipina.
Okay.
My branch is absorbing
the Stamford branch.
Or, as I like to put it,
my family is doubling in size.
And that's all
I'm gonna say about it
because I have a gigantic
performance ahead of me
and I have to get
into my head and focus.
And who's next?
- That is Andy Bernard.
Andy Bernard.
If I were you...
- St. Bernard.
I would fire Anthony Gardner...
- What?
- before noon...
- I'm not...
- to consolidate power.
I'm not firing somebody
on the first day.
No, no, no, not somebody.
Gardner.
The Japanese camp guards
of World War II
always chose one man to kill
whenever a batch
of new prisoners arrived.
I always wondered how they
chose the man who was to die.
I think I would have been good
at choosing the person.
Good morning.
You got the food.
Good!
Lookee, lookee, lookee.
What I want you to do...
Set it up
in the conference room, please.
Make it look nice,
as if you were trying to
impress a much older man
who's way out of your league.
- Okay.
Yes, I'm in a good mood today.
I'm excited to meet
all of the new people
and to see my old friend again,
definitely.
That's always a thing
that makes people happy,
to have an old friend back.
Hello?
Ah! Ding ding ding ding ding!
Our first arrival.
Welcome to Scranton.
This is
Hannah Smoteridge-Barr.
Welcome to our humble abode.
Follow me to your desk.
Your ball and chain
is right over here.
You know, a lot of these people,
this is the only family they
have.
So...
As far as I'm concerned,
this says,
"World's Best Dad."
Ah... there he is.
Tony...
- What's your last name?
- Gardner.
Gardner.
I knew that.
There you go.
Gift bag...
For you, okay?
- Thanks.
Michael, I didn't get
a gift bag.
Well, they're just for guests.
If there are any left over,
you can buy one later.
My bag's mostly pencils.
Wwoo-aa-and coupons...
...to various hot spots
around Scranton.
All right, let me show you
to your area, sir.
Come on, big guy.
Can I have your pencils?
- No.
Hi.
- Hi.
I'm Pam.
- Karen. I love your sweater.
Oh, thanks.
My mom made it for me.
Really?
That's so cool.
I've always wanted to
learn how to knit.
Welcome, welcome, welcome!
Take me to your leader.
Oh, wait.
I am your leader.
Uh, wait, are you a robot
or a Martian?
Hmm? Ah...
I'm actually your boss,
Michael Scott.
Hi. Karen.
- Welcome.
Wow, you are
very exotic-looking.
Was your dad a G.I.,
or...?
I'll be the number two guy
here in Scranton in six weeks.
How?
Name repetition,
personality mirroring,
and never
breaking off a handshake.
I'm always thinking
one step ahead,
like a...
carpenter...
that makes stairs.
Hello.
Ah!
You must be Andy Bernard.
Aloha and welcome.
And you must be Michael Scott.
Aloha and hello.
Very good.
Welcome to our little kingdom.
Uh, we have a bag
of nifty gifties for you.
Well, Michael, thank you
for welcoming me
to your little kingdom, Mike.
Oh.
Nifty!
They are nifty.
They're nifty gifties.
You know who I really like
is this guy Andy Bernard.
He has got this
very likable way about him.
Which is why they need a passing game.
- Right.
No way.
Get him outta here.
We don't want any
of this kind in here.
Good to see you, man.
- Wow. Okay.
How are you?
Martin Nash, I presume?
This is a little gift bag
for you, free of charge.
Follow me.
I will show you
where all the slaves work.
Not...
So your desk is...
Hi. I'm Jim.
I'm new here.
Oh, my God!
It's really you.
I was just doin'
a little joke there
about how we'd never met.
I know.
I don't care.
Awesome.
Good to be back.
The place looks really good.
It's really good to see you.
You, too.
Where do I stand with Pam?
Um... no idea.
I mean, we're friends.
Always have been friends, um...
That is where we stand.
Well, well, well.
Look what the cat
dragged in from Stamford.
Hey, Dwight.
Fact: I am older.
I am wiser.
Do not mess with me.
Okay.
Sounds good.
What are you doing?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
Do I have a spider
on my forehead?
No. Look good.
Why are you looking
at my forehead?
I'm not.
Meet my eye line, Jim.
I am.
Stop acting like an idiot!
Okay.
Hey, buddy.
Welcome back.
Hey, how are you, man?
Good to see you.
I'm good.
How are you?
So...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you sitting here now?
Yeah.
Oh.
Um...
unless you really, really
want it back.
You know, man,
it's really your call.
Cool. Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Let me get that for you.
You got it?
Mm-hmm.
This one taken?
No? Good.
Yeah, Jim is a nice guy.
That's why I got the desk.
Hey, this came
with the Stanford people.
Can you take care of it?
Oh, yes I can.
In general, they do not give me
much responsibility.
But, they do let me shred
the company documents,
and that is really all I need.
Michael Scott, thank you.
I appreciate it, Mike.
All right.
Hello.
I don't believe
we've been introduced.
Dwight Schrute...
assistant regional manager.
Andy Bernard, regional director
in charge of sales.
So you'll be
reporting to me then.
Mmm... on the contrary.
My title has "manager" in it.
And I'm a director,
which on a film set
is the highest title there is.
Do you know anything about film?
I know everything about film.
I've seen over 240 of them.
Congratulations.
He-ey, Toby.
- Hey, Jim.
- How are you, man?
- Really good, how're you?
- I just wanted to say hi.
Hey, welcome back.
Oh, is-is that like
your new thing, or...
No, I'm sorry, thats...
- No, it's cool.
- No, it's not.
Well, let's just...
- All right, good to be back.
- So... okay.
All right.
All right, sor-
sorry about that.
- It was...
- No problem.
What?
Nothing.
This thing is so awesome.
It will shred anything.
Ooh... it'll shred a CD.
It will shred...
...a credit card.
Oh...
Shoot.
"I present
the orientation video."
We need to talk.
Not now.
Which is higher,
assistant regional manager
or regional director
in charge of sales?
I told you,
the titles are irrelevant.
They just relate to pay scale.
Okay, so who gets
paid more, me or Andy?
It is not a matter
of more or less.
Your pay is just different,
okay?
All right.
Show time, part one.
Okay, who reports to who?
I don't care, Dwight.
You all report to me.
That's all that matters.
The rest of it just work out
amongst yourselves, okay?
- And then if I want...
- Work it out amongst yourselves!
- I...
- Please! I have a company to run.
Will you let me run the company?
- I...
- Will you?
- One...
- Please?
- Ji-i-im!
- Kelly!
Oh, my God,
I have so much to tell you!
- Really?
- Yes!
Tom Cruise and Katie Holmes, they
had a baby, and they named it Suri.
And then Brad Pitt
and Angelina Jolie,
they had a baby, too,
and they named it Shiloh.
- And both babies are...
- amaa-azing!
Great.
What's new with you?
I just told you.
Okay, everybody settled in?
Good.
Why don't we all proceed
into the conference room?
Or, should I say,
the banquet hall?
For...
drumroll, please...
The official Merger Day
All-Family Welcome Breakfast.
Come on in.
Don't be shy.
Hey, champagne.
No, no.
Guests only.
- Smoked salmon.
- No... um...
For the guests, it is.
For you, consider it cow meat.
Strictly taboo.
Well, then, consider it
poisoned beef.
- The beef is poisoned?
- No, it's not-be-just-
Sit down, please.
Welcome, help yourself.
You might want
these orientation materials.
Wrong, Toby, this is
an orientation,
not a "bore-ientation."
Okay, do not worry,
all of your questions
are about to be answered.
Cell phones and pagers
off, please.
Oh, this looks promising.
You won't be disappointed.
Let's face it,
moving to a new job
can be very stressful.
So, I have made
an orientation video
especially for you newcomers.
But it's not like
any orientation video
that any of you have ever seen.
It's funny.
It's got a little bit
of a zing to it.
And I hope that it gives you
a flavor of what we're all about
here at Dunder-Mifflin,
and what we're all about
here in Scranton.
So let's just all
laugh together and watch...
Lazy Scranton.
It reminds me
of the orientation video
Michael showed on my first day:
The Scranton Witch Project.
I am so scared
when people don't label
their personal food.
Well, so far,
I think it is killing.
I thought it would
either be an A or an A-plus.
But I completely forgot
that there is an A-plus-plus.
This is Karen Filippelli,
please leave a message.
Terrible.
Totally unconvincing.
This is Karen Filippelli,
please leave a message.
Not bad, but...
...you are Italian, so...
Try it more Italian.
This is Karen-a Filippelli,
please leave-a me
da message.
Abbondanza.
- You feel good?
- Mm-hmm.
All right.
Karen Filippelli
Hey buddy.
Anything new to report?
Do you mean to me, from you?
'Cause that's how it works.
Sure thing, buddy.
Am I trying
to get under his skin?
Y-y-yes, because the angrier he gets,
the more marginalized he becomes.
Meanwhile, Andy Bernard
is out there...
...layin' on the charm.
Hey, Angela, check this out.
It's my new screensaver.
Oh.
Do you like it?
I do like it, actually.
Thank you.
You have...
such a pretty smile, by the way.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hey.
What happened to grape soda?
Oh, yeah.
I'm trying to move away
from that.
I'm getting into more
of a bottled water phase.
Oh, you've changed so much.
Well, I'm evolving, Pam.
So when do I
get to hear everything?
Are you still getting unpacked?
Or you want to grab a coffee
or something after work?
Oh, um...
Tonight, actually?
No.
I'm just still getting settled.
Oh, yeah, no.
You know, whenever.
- Okay
- O-o-kay.
- Sorry to interrupt, I...
- Nope.
You're not
interrupting anything.
- No, I'm-Don't...
- All right.
- Okay.
I should probably
get back to work.
I have to work.
- Yeah, I know. Me too.
- All right.
The day's going fine.
It's been a little chaotic,
but it's fine.
It's great.
A lot of distractions,
but it's good.
Take a picture.
It'll last longer.
I'm sorry, it's just...
It's a little distracting.
Ditto that, my brother.
Look what's on his computer.
What is that,
a squid's eye, or...
It's my left breast.
- How did... you...
- Right place at the right time.
Oh.
What's that smell?
What smell?
It's...
Must be air freshener
plugged in somewhere.
It smells like a funeral home.
Oh, I'll help you find it.
Oh, you know what?
Never... never mind.
What is it?
I... I think
I'm just allergic
to your perfume.
My perfume?
It's just my crazy nose.
I'm, um...
used to different smells.
Bob Vance bought
this perfume for me
in metropolitan Orlando.
It's made from real pine.
Who's Bob Vance?
You have a lot to learn
about this town, sweetie.
I don't know who
these new people think they are.
I've sat downwind of Phyllis'
stinky perfumes for years.
Never said a word.
People hate people
that are different from them.
That's natural.
But you know what makes people
forget their differences?
That is why I created
the integration celebration.
This is the moment
when Scranton and Stamford
come together as one,
united in applause.
I know what a lot of you
must be thinking.
"Wow, what a day.
"It feels more like
a night at a party
than a day at work."
Well, in my opinion,
business should feel
like a night out,
a night...
at...
the Roxbury.
Okay, there's
supposed to be music.
And it's... I got it!
I got it!
Dwight, just...
Do you have batteries in that?
- Stupid.
Um...
That's it.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Here we go. Uhh!
Oh, my nose is so itchy.
Why is my nose so itchy?
Uh, probably because
of all the nose candy.
I told you these guys
have a sense of humor.
Very funny, Michael.
Okay, okay. All right.
- Really funny, Michael.
All right, all right,
I'm on a roll.
Why are the new people
on the table?
To show them
that we are not above them.
Shouldn't we be equals?
Not today.
No.
Tony, please join your cohorts
on the table, if you would.
Uh, this is difficult for me.
Hey, I understand.
We're all friends.
No, I mean, I can't physically.
I can't get on the table.
Oh, well...
just use the momentum
of your lower half
to hoist yourself up.
Okay?
You know what?
I'll help.
I will help.
- No. Please...
don't.
Don't be shy.
Dwight, let's do this.
Come on.
We're doin' this thing.
Ready? On three.
- Let's get up.
One, two...
- Bend at the knees.
- Go!
- Okay, here we go!
Here we go.
I'm under this...
I'm under this hock here.
I don't know what
I'm grabbin' here.
All right, all right, stop.
Put me down.
- Put me down.
- Push it! Push it!
I'm right in your crack.
Put me down now!
- You're almost there!
Put me down right now!
I've had enough!
- You've got it.
Put me down right now!
Whoa whoa whoa!
Okay.
Hey, hey. Easy.
- Easy.
I'm sorry.
Don't...
It's just not
going to work for me.
I have to go.
I don't understand.
I was on the fence about this,
and it's just not a good fit.
Well, we'll squeeze you in.
I can't work here.
I have to quit.
You can't quit on the first day.
That's...
heresy, my friend.
Okay, let's talk about this.
What happened?
I mean, what...
Was it Toby?
Did he say something?
'Cause he's...
No, Toby was helpful.
He was very kind.
It's just your management style.
My management style?
So...
Didn't you think
Lazy Scranton was funny?
No.
Was it supposed to be funny?
Okay, well...
Don't bother quitting
because you're fired.
Excuse me?
- You are fired!
I'm sorry, but we don't
have quitters on this team.
Just clean out your desk!
But there's nothing
in my desk except coupons.
Don't try to apologize
to me, man.
It's too late.
Just get out.
Take your bad vibes with you.
That was my advice, remember?
I'm the one who suggested
that you fire him.
Probably the best advice
you ever gave me, Dwight.
And what advice
has Andy given to you today
that you have acted on?
Would "none" be
an accurate estimate?
None advice?
Fire Andy.
Fire... Andy.
Dwight may have won the battle,
but I will win the next battle.
Tony was right.
This environment
is dysfunctional.
Well, maybe that's
because some people treat it
like their own private
Hooters strip club.
Whoa, Angela, hold on.
Hooters is a restaurant
with over 400 locations
worldwide.
Back to work.
We don't have to get along.
We just have to work together.
No, we do have to get along.
Can't we all just get along?
Or have we forgotten the words
of the Reverend King?
The word "merger"
comes from the word "marriage."
And that was what today
was supposed to be.
The loving union between people.
Instead, it has become like...
when my mom moved in with Jeff.
And, once again,
it becomes my job to fix it.
Hey!
Hey, everybody!
Something happened!
Those guys
from Vance Refrigeration,
they let the air
out of our tires.
- What?!
- Yeah! They punked us!
They punked us good.
Come on.
Does Bob Vance
work for Vance Refrigeration?
Does he ever.
Man, they got us so bad.
We cannot let 'em
get away with this.
We have got to
pull together as one
and steal their refrigerators.
Yeah!
- Yeah?
I don't think we can do that.
Go home, Toby.
Just...
Hey!
Why doesn't your car
have a flat tire?
Why?
I will tell you why.
Because they saved
the worst for me.
They put a hate note
under my windshield wiper.
Check this out.
It's so hateful.
"You guys suck!
"You can never
pull together as one
"and revenge us.
That is why
you suck."
For crying out loud.
No. No, no, no, no.
No.
You are falling for it.
You are playing
right into their hands.
This is just what
they want you to do.
Man, what is with this guy?
Got an hour?
I'll try to explain.
This is egregious!
Trust me, it only gets worse.
Is he always like this?
Sometimes he brings
more costumes.
Hmm.
When do people work?
Oh, we find little times
during the day.
How're we gonna get home?
Bob Vance has an air pump. He
said he'd fill all our tires up.
Bob Vance
of Vance Refrigeration.
See that?
Mission accomplished.
They're like a bunch
of fourth graders.
Sometimes what brings
the kids together
is hating the lunch lady.
Although that'll change
because by the end
of the fourth grade,
the lunch lady
was actually the person
I hung out with the most.
Jello.
- Michael.
- Hi, Jan.
Did you fire Tony Gardner
when he was trying to quit?
I did.
Major personnel crisis averted.
Do you realize, Michael, that we
now have to pay him severance?
Yes.
You do?
But do you realize that that
was actually Dwight's idea?
Bad advice from my number two.
What...?
No. No.
No, Jim is your number two.
He's the only one who has
worked with both groups.
I sent you a memo about this.
Yes, I know that,
for I do read the memos.
So, after a great deal
of thought
and introspective-shun,
I have decided to make Jim
my new number two.
If he even wants it.
It doesn't come
with a pay raise.
No, it does, actually.
So who will be
your new number three?
Uh, that I have not decided yet.
Michael, I would just
like to say
that you have handled
this entire situation
with great aplomb.
Thank you, Andy.
That's very kind.
And I have to say
that your leadership...
Shut it.
That's...
Suck-up.
Hey.
Where you at, Filippelli?
I'm at the grocery store
buying a corkscrew
to give myself a lobotomy.
What's wrong, you didn't
have a good first day?
Oh, my God.
Hey, you want to meet
at Cooper's in an hour?
I need a drink.
Yeah, sure.
Sounds good.
I...
Hey, you know what?
Can I give you a call
right back?
Yeah.
- Okay. Thanks.
Okay.
Hey.
I thought you had already left.
Uh... no.
I just had some
other stuff I had to do.
- Oh, good.
What's up?
Oh, nothing.
I just feel bad.
I feel like things
were a little weird today
or something.
What do you mean?
I just think I should tell you
that I've sort of
started seeing someone,
Oh.
and, uh...
That's totally cool.
You can do whatever you want.
Oh. Okay, uh...
Good.
We're friends.
We'll always be friends.
Right.
It's good to have you back.
Yeah.
Good to be back.
Where'd you get that salad?
Staples.
I saw your dork-mobile
in the parking lot.
What does it get,
like four miles to the gallon?
Uh, try double that.
Classic Trans Am,
vintage American muscle.
- Please. - 'Kay, my
Xterra's pretty sweet.
Luxurious, yet rugged.
Leave it to the Japanese.
"Xterra" is not even
a real word.
Actually, it is.
It's Latin for "Earth."
Oh, so you drive
an "X-Earth?"
- Yeah.
- That makes sense.
I'd rather drive
a classic Trans Am
than an "X-Earth."
Yeah, I bet you would.
Oh, uh, by the way, 1985 called.
It wants its car back.
Well, I hope 1985
has a time machine,
'cause I drive an '87.
Oh, speaking of time machines,
I just got back from the future,
and I went to your funeral,
and... guess what?
Nobody came.
Speaking of funerals...
Why don't you go ahead
and go die?
Oh, that was a really...
...well constructed sentence.
You should be
an English professor
at Cor-not University
Idiot.
If I were an idiot,
I'd be driving a Trans Am.
If you were driving a Trans Am,
you would be the smartest idiot
in the whole world.
Idiot.
You're the idiot.
Nice comeback.
I was making fun
of your comeback.
That's why it worked.
I totally got the best
of that interchange.