Oh, damn.
Lost another file.
Gonna have to reboot...
again.
Hey, Dwight,
do you want an Altoid?
What do you think?
In school, we learned
about this scientist
who trained dogs to salivate
at the sound of a bell
by feeding them
whenever a bell rang.
So for the past couple weeks
I've been conducting
a similar experiment.
Dwight, want an Altoid?
Okay.
Altoid?
Sure.
Yes.
What are you doing?
I...
What?
I don't know, I...
Oh, my mouth tastes so bad
all of a sudden.
Ugh.
Always the bridesmaids.
Right, ladies?
Okay, for this next one,
everybody hop out.
Just Phyllis and Dad.
Actually, let's bring Mom
back in.
And the sisters.
And you and you and you.
Great.
Phyllis is getting married.
And I am in the wedding party.
She has asked me
to push her father's
wheelchair down the aisle.
So basically,
I am co-giving away the bride.
Since I pay her salary,
it is like I am paying
for the wedding.
Which I'm happy to do.
It's a big day for Phyllis.
But it's an even bigger day
for me.
Employer of the bride.
Yes, I put Michael
in my wedding.
It was the only way
I could think
to get six weeks off
for my honeymoon.
No one else has ever gotten
six weeks before.
Phyllis ended up using
the exact same invitations
as Roy and me.
So it was kind of like
being invited
to my own wedding.
And I was like, wait...
I thought I called that off.
So, what's in the box?
A toaster. You?
Uh, toaster.
Unbelievable.
Hello, Angela.
You look as beautiful
as the Queen of England.
Thank you.
Don't linger.
Break left.
Left.
The Schrutes
have their own traditions.
We usually marry
standing in our own graves.
Makes the funerals
very romantic.
But the weddings
are a bleak affair.
Those flowers are nice.
Yeah. "P and R?"
"Phyllis and Robert."
Ah, of course.
Also "Pam and Roy."
There she is!
I swear, Phyllis,
you are as beautiful
as the first day
you started work
at Dunder-Mifflin.
Thanks, Michael.
That's sweet.
Same as when you said it
outside.
Mm, how you doing?
You excited?
Yes, very.
Me too.
If, um... if you need to vomit,
that is okay.
I did.
Do you want to talk
about tonight?
No.
Because I know
you're probably worried
about pleasing Bob.
A lot of pressure.
Phyllis, did you break wind?
It's okay if you did.
It's a very natural reaction.
It's your wedding
and you're nervous.
Um, that wasn't me.
Okay.
Um...
I'm sure that Bob...
wow, that is...
that is pungent.
Um, I lost my train of thought.
Uh...
are you set on that hairstyle?
I thought it was...
Here, let me...
Michael, no.
Just cover up that bald patch.
No, Michael.
Please, I just need
some time alone.
Okay, okay.
You might be surprised to learn
that I have only been
to one other wedding.
It's actually a very cute story.
My mom was marrying Jeff
and they asked me
to be ring bearer.
And I was understandably
emotional
and somehow my pants became wet.
I hate you!
Long story short...
Jeff's dog ended up
as ring bearer.
And the irony is that
after the ceremony,
that dog peed on everything.
And nobody said boo.
Why are all these people here?
There's too many people
on this earth.
We need a new plague.
Who are all these people?
You know what?
I bet a lot of them are
wedding crashers. No way.
Did you ever see that movie?
Of course I saw it.
I saw Wedding Crashers
accidentally.
I bought a ticket
for Grizzly Man
and went into the wrong theater.
After an hour, I figured
I was in the wrong theater.
But I kept waiting.
Because that's the thing
about bear attacks...
They come when
you least expect it.
You know, I just wish...
I wish I had
the investigative powers
to actually smoke
some of these guys out,
you know?
Once again, Jim...
I will take care of this.
I will locate
the wedding crashers
and report them to Phyllis.
That way
I won't have to get her a gift.
Hi, I'm Kevin.
Where'd you find her?
At the gym.
Right.
The gym!
Could you scoot over?
You're on my dress.
I thought you're not supposed
to wear white to a wedding.
I know, but there was
an emergency.
I look really good in white.
This strapping young lad
sitting here
is Phyllis' father, Elbert.
And he is quite the ladies' man,
aren't you, Elbert, huh?
Ah, ring bearer.
I could've done better.
I will do better.
I am going to be better.
Can't believe I'm actually
doing this.
Are you ready for this, Elbert?
I am.
Let's do it!
That's my dress.
No, no, it's okay.
It's...
It's a miracle.
This is bull.
Me walking Phyllis
down the aisle
was supposed to be
the highlight of the wedding.
And now...
the wedding has no highlight.
I can't believe I pushed that...
that guy's lazy ass around
all day
until he was ready to stand up
and steal the show.
That's...
well, I got news for you,
Elbert...
if that's your real name...
the show's not over.
Phyllis and Bob,
Bob and Phyllis...
And do you, Phyllis,
take Bob Vance
of Vance Refrigeration
to be your lawfully
wedded husband.
I do.
Ladies and gentlemen!
May I present to you,
for the first time as a couple,
Mr. and Mrs. Bob Vance!
And do you, Bob, take Phyllis
Oh, shh...
to be your lawfully wedded wife?
I do.
You may now kiss the bride.
Ladies and gentlemen!
For the first time as a couple,
Mr. and Mrs. Bob Vance!
Yeah!
That's what I'm talking about!
Congratulations, Phyllis.
Oh, thank you.
You look lovely.
Your dress is very white.
So white my eyes are burning.
Thanks, Angela.
Congratulations, Bob.
You're a good man.
But just know...
if you ever lay a finger
on Phyllis,
I will kill you.
If yo ever lay a finger
on Phyllis,
I'll kill you.
Agreed.
No fingers will be laid
on Phyllis!
Oh, decide
to sit down again, huh?
Great.
Bet you can hear me too.
Best of luck, Phyllis.
Also, I'm gonna need to see
a copy of the guest manifest,
as well as photographs
of the caterers.
I don't have that, Dwight.
Damn it, Phyllis!
Are you all right?
This must be so awful for you.
What do you mean?
Well, this was supposed
to be your wedding.
Oh, um, no, that's, um...
it's actually fine.
There's no way it's fine.
I'm sorry.
If I was you, I would just,
like, freak out
and get really drunk
and then tell someone
I was pregnant.
Okay, that's a lot
of good ideas.
Thanks.
Excuse me, sir.
How do you know
the happy couple?
Who?
The bride and groom.
What are their names?
Oh, I... I don't, uh...
I'm not sure.
Oh, I get it, I get it.
Come on, freeloader,
let's move it.
Oh.
Come on!
Okay, okay.
Where are we going?
Gotta find yourself
another wedding to crash,
my friend.
Oh!
Phyllis, are you happy
with everything?
What can I do
to make it more perfect-er?
Oh, it's beautiful.
Why don't you find your seat
and enjoy the buffet?
I'm already on it.
Chicken, totally undercooked.
I sent it back.
It's fish.
I will take care of that.
I do... I know a fair amount
about fine food and drink.
Um...
This is a white.
No, this is not
our first wedding.
This is the third wedding
that Scrantonicity has played.
We also played
our bassist's wedding
and our guitarist's wedding.
Attention, everyone.
Attention, please.
Uh, I'm supposed to ask
if anyone has seen Uncle Al.
He is old and has brown eyes
and dementia.
His family is very concerned.
It's a very serious
situation.
Hey.
I know I don't normally notice
these kind of things, but, uh...
this wedding's really nice.
I mean, the flowers and stuff.
Phyllis has got
some great taste.
You're kidding me, right?
I know you probably
aren't gonna remember this,
but, um, those color roses...
I got you those color roses
for our prom.
Roy, I picked those flowers.
Phyllis just stole all
of my ideas for our wedding.
I guess I wasn't really
too involved in the planning.
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
Well, you think
it sucks for you.
I'm the one who actually wanted
to get married.
Phyllis,
you're a wonderful woman.
And you're a hell of a bowler!
She is.
Cheers!
Thank you, Randy!
That was great.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Hi, I'm Michael Scott.
And for the next 40 minutes,
I am going to be your tour guide
through the lives
of Phyllis Lapin and Bob Vance.
One of the great,
seemingly impossible
love stories of our time.
My name is Michael Scott.
Webster's Dictionary
defines "wedding"
as the fusing of two metals
with a hot torch.
Well, you know something?
I think you guys
are two metals...
gold medals.
For those of you
who don't know me,
I'm Michael Scott,
Phyllis' boss.
To quote from
The Princess Bride,
"Marriage"
The most important part
of a speech
is the opening line.
When time is not a factor,
I like to try out
three or four different ones.
Phyllis and Bob...
their celebrity couple name
would be "Phlob."
You look at her,
and she's kind
of matronly today.
But back in high school,
I swear her nickname
was "Easy Rider."
Now, as for Bob...
Bob Vance...
Okay, that's enough.
Thanks.
Is a guy that...
Thanks, Michael.
Give me the microphone.
He works...
Okay, hold on.
Hold on, hold on.
Look, um...
I didn't say anything
when Phyllis' dad upstaged me
at the ceremony.
And I think
you owe me this, okay?
Give me the microphone.
No, I'm not going to.
It's okay.
Okay, good.
You're outta here!
Yeah, I'm...
you're outta here.
I hate you!
Hey!
Hey.
When are we gonna get to see
some of those famous
Beesly dance moves?
Oh.
I'm pacing myself.
Come on, get out there!
Give the people what they want.
No, I'm such a dorky dancer.
I know!
And it's very cute.
Hypothetically, if I thought
Pam was interested, then...
No, it's totally hypothetical.
Come... come on!
I can't let you in, Michael.
Dwight, just...
No, it's Bob and Phyllis'
orders.
Look, I just wanted to go in
and quietly sit
and have a piece of cake.
I'm not even gonna dance.
One song maybe.
You are a real-life
wedding crasher
and I must bounce you.
I'm sorry.
It gives me no pleasure.
Okay.
Hey.
They're playing our song, huh?
Yeah, that's weird.
I thought they only played
The Police.
I know.
I, uh...
I gave 'em 20 bucks.
You wanna dance?
Hey, you want
to get out of here?
Here's a non-hypothetical.
I'm really happy I'm with Karen.
[playing The Police's
One, two, three!
Totally! Yeah!
I just want Phyllis
to have a great day.
Phyllis and you
will be great together.
We are great together.
We are a great team.
The Celtics were a great team.
Yes, yes... they were.
Robert Parrish.
I should talk to her.
I don't want this
to ruin her honeymoon.
Well, nobody ever helped me.
I had to do it myself.
Even the doctor didn't know.
Dude, keep it together.
I listened to you
for a half an hour
even though most of that stuff
went right over my head.
Oh.
Phyllis...
Phyllis, wait, please?
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to make this
a day to remember.
You found Uncle Al!
Yeah, yeah,
he's kind of a weirdo.
Thank you, Michael.
You're...
You're welcome.
They say that your wedding day
goes by in such a flash
that you're lucky
if you even get
a piece of your own cake.
I say that's crazy.
I say, "Let them eat cake."
Margaret Thatcher said that
about marriage.
Smart broad.
Be careful with the...
Oh no!
Oh, wow!
Phyllis, Phyllis!
Come on!
You look like a clown.
Here.
Get me, get me!
Ah!
Oh!