There you go.
Oh.
Nice dress, Ryan.
It's not a dress.
It's a kurta.
Okay.
Tonight, one of our most
ethnic coworkers, Kelly,
has invited us all
to a Diwali celebration
put on by her community.
What is Diwali, you may ask?
Well, to have Kelly explain it,
"It's..."
"It's so super, fun.
And it's gonna be great."
A lot of gods
with unpronounceable names.
20 minutes later, you find out
that it's essentially
a Hindu Halloween.
You look so handsome.
You really do.
I love the material.
I know.
How come you didn't get me one?
I...
Okay, so between
Meredith's minivan,
and if I borrow Bob's Yukon,
that should fit about 12 people.
I actually might not go.
I'm feeling kind of tired.
Do you wanna make Appletinis
and watch Sex and the City
at my place?
Oh, I don't know.
I haven't decided yet.
I don't get why you won't go.
Did I do something wrong?
I mean, I thought we
were really close friends.
I just feel kind of tired,
you know.
Maybe you've got mono.
Maybe.
I just...
I don't really have
anyone to go with.
Well, go with Dwight.
He's single too right?
Yeah, totally single.
100% available.
Are you guys going to this
Indian thing tonight?
I don't know.
Who's, uh, who's going?
Ohh... you mean, like,
is Pam going?
Don't go.
They eat monkey brains.
Hey, hey, hey, stop that.
That is offensive.
Indians do not
eat monkey brains.
And if they do...
sign me up.
Because I am sure
that they are very tasty.
And nutritional.
It's important that this company
celebrates its diversity.
And you know what, Stanley?
Come Kwanzaa time,
I have got you covered, baby.
I don't celebrate Kwanzaa.
Wha... really?
You should.
It's fun.
I love the people here.
And if there was one thing
I don't really care for,
is that they can be
terribly, terribly ignorant
about other cultures.
And I don't want them
embarrassing me
in front of my girlfriend Carol.
Diwali is a very
important holiday
for the Hindus.
But, frankly,
I'm a little appalled
that none of you know very much
about Indian culture.
So with out further adieu,
Kelly!
You are on.
Um, Diwali is awesome.
And there's food,
and there's gonna be dancing.
And, oh,
I got the raddest outfit.
- It has sparkles...
- Kelly...
Um, why don't you tell us
a little bit about
the origins of the holiday?
Oh, um, I don't know.
It's really old, I think.
How many gods do you have?
Like hundreds, I think.
Maybe more than that.
And that blue, busty gal...
what's her story?
She looks like Pam
from the neck down.
Pam wishes.
Kelly, I'll take this one.
Diwali is a celebration
of the coronation god king Rama
after his epic battle
with Ravena,
the demon king of Lanka.
It symbolizes the battle
between good and evil.
All right, all right.
This isn't Lord of the Rings.
Hey, Polly.
Oops, sorry.
Sorry.
I started biking to work.
Josh does it.
And he lives a lot
farther away than I do.
And also, it saves gas money.
It keeps me in shape.
Helps the environment.
And now I know it makes me
really sweaty for work.
Nice basket.
Thank you.
Now, a lot of people say
that Kelly is one in a million.
And that's true,
but it's also not true.
Because, frankly,
there are literally
billions of people
just like Kelly in the world.
Here are some famous Indians.
Subrahmanyan Chandrasekhar.
He is a Nobel-Prize-winning
physicist.
Impressive.
Apu, from The Simpsons.
Hilarious Indian.
M. Night Shyamalan.
The Village, Unbreakable,
Sixth Sense.
I see dead people.
Okay!
Spoiler alert.
He was dead the whole time.
Just stop it!
What's...
Oh, wha...
Where did that come from?
Karen, my chips got stuck
in the vending machine again.
I need your...
skinny little arms.
Oh.
Did you shake it?
Yeah, I shook it, I shook it.
We have such
a roller coaster thing,
Karen and I.
Excuse me?
Roller-coastery friendship.
Hot and cold.
On again, off again.
Sexual-tension-filled
type of deal.
It's very Sam and Diane.
Wow.
From Cheers.
Yep.
Yeah.
And another thing about
the Indian people,
they love sex positions.
I present to you The Kama Sutra.
I mean, look at that.
Who has seen that before?
I have, that's
the union of the monkey.
Oh, that's what they call it.
This is the best meeting
we have ever had.
Thank you, Kevin.
I find this
incredibly offensive.
Well, I find it beautiful.
Well, whatever Kelly wants to do
in her own house is fine.
But we shouldn't
all be subjected to it.
Actually, she's right.
This isn't appropriate.
Why don't I take these?
You're not gonna collect them.
No, this is delightful,
charming culture.
My Indian cultural seminar
was going great
until Toby decided
that he was too immature
to deal with
culturally explicit images.
It's just sex, people.
Everybody does it.
I'm doing it with Carol.
Probably tonight.
All right.
I think you guys
should be all set.
Oh, here's the corporate card
for dinner.
Thanks.
Now, Karen...
Let's keep it
to $20 a person this time.
Got it.
Once a quarter,
the sales staff at this branch
has to stay late to do
order form consolidation.
Which... amazingly,
is even less interesting
than it sounds.
You guys ready to party?
What's that?
I said, are you ready
to part-ay!
Isn't this fun,
not wearing shoes?
I wish some of us still
had our shoes on.
Stop it.
It's a disease.
I've... told you.
I thought you said
this was a costume party.
What does that look like to you?
An Indian woman in a sari.
No one's even gonna notice it.
Nice outfit.
Hey, Kevin, it's a costume.
You just cool it, okay?
Carol? Carol.
I'll have one of those as well.
Thank you very much.
Now, these are limes,
lemons, onions.
I'm a vegetarian.
What can I eat?
It's all vegetarian.
I'll just have some bread.
You used your hands.
Oh, yuck.
Oh.
What, is it too spicy?
Yeah.
These s'mores are disgusting.
They're not s'mores.
They're samosas.
Do you think
they have any s'mores?
All they are is chocolate,
graham cracker, and marshmallow.
How difficult would
that have been?
So... you're Kelly's
sisters, huh?
What?
Rupa, Neefa, Tiffany,
stop acting like such
little losers,
and just be cool.
Come on, Ryan.
Come on.
Leave him alone.
I hate you guys.
They said something
about Zach Braff.
Don't even listen to them.
No, you know...
That's very official.
I decided to come.
Uh, I feel a little
underdressed.
But at least I'm not dressed
like a slutty cheerleader,
right?
Is that mean?
Temp! Temp!
I don't even
wanna hear it, okay?
Stop it right now.
Ryan is a temporary worker,
makes no money.
Wali is a whole doctor,
so handsome, makes good money.
- You think I wanna date a doctor?
- He's a perfect match.
Hey, big tuna, you ready?
Yep.
One, two, three.
Shot!
Ohh! Holy mother of God.
Ooh, that burns.
Golly!
Good.
Whew.
Wow, 30 years!
And you two only met
once before the wedding night.
Yes.
Wow.
How long have you been
married to the cheerleader?
Oh...
She's not a cheerleader.
She thought this
was a costume party.
Um, no, we're not married.
Yet!
She's very fair.
She is very fair.
Very fair and very kind.
So, um,
tell me, is your marriage
the kind of thing
where when you die,
she has to throw herself
on fire?
No?
Okay.
It's still very cool.
Okay, thanks.
One, two, three.
Chug!
Ooh!
Are you okay?
I'm gonna be.
Hi.
I'm just gonna...
Just a sec, just a sec.
Um, everyone.
I'm sorry, could I have
your attention, please?
Thank you.
Ha ha! Hi!
Sorry, I just have
an announcement to make.
Um...
Okay.
I have learned a lot
about Indian culture tonight.
But I have learned
even more about love.
And I know you're all thinking,
"Who is this crazy gringo,
and what is he talkin' about?"
Well, I'm not crazy.
Maybe I'm crazy in love.
So, without
further adieu,
Carol...
Carol Stills...
I would like you...
to do me the honor
of making me your husband.
Oh, Michael.
What do you say?
Can we talk
about this in private?
I didn't hear you.
Can we talk about this
in private?
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Okay.
No, I get it.
I get it.
You're not ready.
We'll wait.
This is our ninth date, Michael.
Well, yeah, but I...
I feel like I've known you
many lifetimes.
Maybe I'm Hindu after all.
Okay, I'm not Hindu.
But... Carol...
Carol, I just feel like...
I just like you so much.
I'd better go.
Okay? You can find
a way home, all right?
Yes.
Okay.
Good night.
Hey, you know what?
Why don't I come with you?
'Cause I've got this book
called The Kama Sutra.
Okay, good night, Michael.
All right.
Good night.
Well, I was a temp,
but I got promoted.
So, um... the compensation
is a lot more competitive.
So you're saving money now
to start a family and home?
Oh, um, or travel.
And, um, and buy an Xbox.
Is there anything you wanted
to ask us tonight?
Can you believe my boss
proposed to his girlfriend
in public?
That is so Michael.
Is it?
He's really outgoing, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, would you excuse me
for a second?
Okay.
It's hot in there.
How's the naan?
Dry.
You looked like you
were having fun.
I am.
You should come dance with us.
I have to watch our shoes,
so they don't get stolen.
- Who are you texting?
- No one.
Andy, no a cappella.
Wait, wait.
It's not good.
Tuna! Are you kidding me?!
Ohh!
Oh, my God.
Oh! Wow!
- Here.
- That's so spicy.
Yeah.
Ohh.
You waiting for a call?
Uh, no.
Wow.
Pam...
When Carol said no tonight,
I think I finally realized
how you must be feeling.
We are both the victims
of broken engagements.
Well, you were
never really engaged.
I was in that marriage arena,
though.
- Yeah.
Ohh... well.
I kind of thought something
would happen tonight too.
We're so alike.
So alike.
What are you doing?
- I'm rejecting your kiss.
- What?
I didn't...
I wa...
Can I have a ride home?
If you sit in the back.
Okay, guys.
Hey, can I have a ride, man?
I, uh, I have my bike.
No way, dude.
I am not driving home.
I brought an inflatable bed
for just such occasions.
You're welcome to share it,
though.
It's a roomy twin.
Okay.
Hey, dummy, get in the car.
I'm a drunk driver.
Yes, you are.
Here, let me take that.
Just, uh, get in the car.
You can really hold
your liquor, though, really.
Yeah, you can't.
Okay.
And I am just going to lie down
in the back,
if that's all right.
Sure.
Here's your... bag.
Just don't puke on anything.
You okay?
- So good.
- Good.
These are not my shoes.
This is just like
that show Taxi Cab Confessions.
If you say one more word,
I'm stopping the car.
Sorry.
This is going out
to Indians everywhere.
It's a tribute
to one of the greats.
Mr. Adam Sandler.
Let me tell you something.
Tonight has been...
Happy Diwali!