Hello, son.
If you're watching this,
that means I'm already dead.
Life is a road...
How do you know it's gonna be a boy?
How...
Would you stop interrupting,
please?
Yesterday,
I was scraping some gunk
off my wall sockets
with a metal fork,
and I gave myself
the nastiest shock.
And when I came to,
I had an epiphery.
Life is precious.
And if I die,
I want my... son...
to know the dealio.
The dealio of life.
Here are some things
that I want to teach you
that your mother
won't be able to.
To jump-start a car,
first pop the hood.
Then you take these bad boys
and clip them
anywhere on the engine.
Then, you take these,
and clip them wherever.
Number eight.
Learn how to take off
a woman's bra.
What? We will
demonstrate on Pam.
No.
And...
Come on.
You just twist your hand,
until...
something breaks.
Ow.
Well, you get the picture.
Thanks, Pam.
And remember, no matter what,
I will always love you.
What if he's a murderer?
He's not gonna be a murderer.
Maybe that's how you die.
You know what?
Dwight,
do you want to do this or no?
I want to do this.
Okay.
From the top.
Ready?
3...
Action.
Hello, everyone.
As you know,
we are six days away
from Phyllis's wedding.
So get your suits
to the dry cleaners,
and get your hair did.
And Karen, um...
you might want to invest
in a... a dress
or a skirt of some kind
if you don't already have one.
This may be Phyllis's
only wedding ever.
It's my job to ensure
that none of you
look like ragamuffins.
So... I am instituting
primae noctis.
Primae noctis,
I believe
from the movie Braveheart,
and confirmed on Wikipedia,
is when the king
got to deflower every new bride
on her wedding night.
So...
I'm sorry.
I...
had a very different
understanding
as to what primae noctis meant.
I'm trying to get everyone
excited about Phyllis's wedding,
because I want her
to get people excited
about my wedding,
when the time comes.
Which won't be hard.
Because it's gonna be awesome.
A lot better than hers,
that's for sure.
It'll probably be on a boat.
What's up,
spinstas?
Nothing.
You know, this
is a luncheon shower.
Girls only.
No problem.
The guys are having
a little shindig of their own
in the warehouse.
From 2:30 to 3:15.
It is the only time
that Bob was available.
Sort of a guys' night out.
A G-N-O, if you will.
A g-no.
Actually, it's more
of a guys' afternoon in.
A G-A-I.
A gai.
Not...
Not... it's, uh...
not gay.
It's a, just a...
It's a bridal shower for guys.
A guy shower.
An hour-long shower
with guys.
I guess Jim and I
have had a little bit
of a rough patch
for the past couple weeks,
but we had
some really good talks.
And actually,
now I think
that we're better than ever.
Karen and I
had a long... talk last night.
And the night before that.
And, uh...
Every night...
for the last five nights.
Something's up
with Jim and Karen.
Not that I've been
eavesdropping.
It's not really
any of my business.
But...
I've gotten pretty good
at reading
the back of Jim's neck.
Halpert!
Tall, queer, handsome as ever.
"Hey, everybody, it's me.
Jim."
Hello, hello.
Todd Packer.
Karen Filipelli.
Jim's girlfriend.
Shut up!
Yep.
Shut it!
That's rude.
Either this chick is a dude,
or Halpert got scared straight!
Yes, yes.
Oh ho!
Yes.
Oh ho ho ho ho.
There... uh!
What happened?
Quick, somebody help!
Help the man!
Ow, no, no!
I can't believe
you're not going to be there.
It's gonna be good.
It's gonna be
a great bachelor party, man.
I have a full day
of sales calls.
You should get out of them.
I can't.
It's... it's the only time
he can do it.
2:30 to 3:15.
It's gonna be great.
We're going to be doing
some darts,
we're gonna be, uh,
grilling up some steaks.
I got some pie...
Going to be very delicious...
And what kind of stripper
did you get?
I did not order a stripper.
Whaddaya mean,
you didn't order a stripper?
Have you ever even been
to a bachelor party?
Yeah.
Um...
Not personally, no.
All right, Mike.
Okay?
A stripper
is Bachelor Party 101.
I know, I... If you
don't get a stripper,
your party is gonna suck.
I can't get a stripper here.
Sexual harassment.
I just...
Get one for the girls, too.
That evens it out.
You know, separate but equal.
So that's what that means.
Okay, everybody.
Slight change of plans.
We are still going to be
having two parties,
but each is going to get
a little extra dose
of naugh-tay.
Unh!
All right!
Gay...
What?
Okay, co-ed naked strippers
in this office.
For realsies.
Under no circumstance
should a man
strip off his clothes
in this office.
Shut up, Angela!
Hey.
Uh...
Everything okay?
Oh, yeah.
Why?
Well, you seem a little tired.
Oh.
Yeah, well...
I guess there's been
a couple of late nights.
Karen and I
have been up talking.
You should get more sleep.
Yeah.
I know I should.
Never underestimate the power
of a good night's sleep.
No, I'm sure you're right.
When I get eight hours,
compared to, like, six hours...
it's like, big difference!
Really?
Oh, yeah.
Gotta get your REM cycle.
Going with the whole...
sleeping...
better than not.
Good advice, Beesly.
Thanks.
See you out there?
Yeah.
Don't fall asleep at your desk.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
We are off.
Ryan and I are going to go
get some supplies.
And I need you to handle...
hiring the strippers.
Absolutely not.
I'm on it.
Well, get on it,
and make it happen.
Ruddy cheeks, thick calves,
no tats, no moles.
No tats.
No, tats.
Of course I want...
Stop.
That's disgusting.
Leave me alone
and get the male stripper.
Fine.
I knew you would, Nancy.
Sally.
Uh... no preference.
Uh, what do you think,
a redhead or brunette?
Blonde.
Nice.
Do you have any blonde women?
Hmm.
He hasn't even said a word yet.
Just giggling.
Gotcha.
- Yes?
- You okay?
I'm in the...
I'm in the sex shop.
Ah, gotcha.
Okay, so they have
Albert Einstein,
Ben Franklin,
or SpongeBob SquarePants.
SquarePants?
Yep, SpongeBob SquarePants.
And you think that'd be sexy?
Michael referred me
to a male strip club
called Banana Slings.
Instead, I called
the Scholastic Speakers
of Pennsylvania.
Ooh, ha ha!
Hold the door, please!
Oh.
Thank you.
Ho ho. Hello.
Hello.
You wearing a thong?
What?
Sparkling cider is very good.
I think that's champagne.
Hello, ladies.
Who here is a history buff?
Um...
Who's a fan of buff naked?
Without further ado, the one,
the only...
the sexy
Mr. Benjamin Franklin.
Thank you for that introduction,
Mr. Scott.
And good afternoon,
fine gentlewomen
of Dunder-Mifflin.
Huh?
Half pants, right,
Mr. Franklin?
Knickers, in fact, yes.
He's in his knickers.
Mr. Franklin.
Hmm?
I would say
you were probably one of
the sexiest presidents ever.
Well, actually,
I never was president.
Yes, but Ben Franklin was.
Ah.
I am here to teach you
a little bit
about my life.
And the era
of the Founding Fathers.
And when they came over
on the Mayflower.
Bow-chicka-bow.
Wait.
This is the entertainment?
Yeah.
All right.
So I want you to give him
your undivided attention,
and Mr. Franklin...
Hmm?
If any of these ladies
misbehave,
I give you permission
to spank them.
Especially that one.
Have you ever
seen a stripper before?
Yes.
Jennifer Garner
portrayed one on Alias.
It was one of her many aliases.
Yeah.
Me neither.
Hey.
Hi.
I'm Elizabeth.
I'm the dancer
that was requested.
Okay. Ha.
I specifically ordered
a stripper.
I'm the stripper.
Oh.
Okay, good.
Well, in future, please
identify yourself as such.
Oh, God.
Okay...
"Is she hot?"
Text back,
"Kind of."
It was a warm June evening
in 1752,
the night of my fateful
kite flight.
Mr. Franklin.
Yes?
Do you have a girlfriend?
I have a lovely wife.
Deborah.
But don't you also
have girlfriends in Paris?
Mm.
Like, a lot of them?
Ah, well, that
is a gray area of my life.
Okay? So.
It was a warm June evening...
Look at that.
Nothing like grilling
in the great outdoors.
Is this the same grill
you grilled your foot on?
No.
Yes.
Oh, gross. But I got all
the foot off of it.
Mm...
Okay, Ben Franklin.
Ah... aha!
Oh, Ben Franklin
tied a cherry stem in his mouth!
Well, that is because
I am a Renaissance man.
Ben Franklin?
Hmm?
Do you wear boxers,
briefs, or pantaloons?
Well.
You're very saucy.
Guys! Beef!
It's what's for dinner.
Who wants some man meat?
I do.
I want some man meat.
Michael,
Dwight would like your man meat.
Well, then,
my man meat he shall have.
There you go.
Deliciousity.
Of course.
There we go.
So I guess you have
the Ben Franklin wig,
and the costume, and you figure,
"How could I put this
to practical use?"
Well, I like to think
that his dad
was a Ben Franklin impersonator.
And he really
pressured him into it.
Hey, um,
I wanted to talk to you.
I-I know this is weird
or whatever,
but, um...
Jim told me about you guys.
What do you mean?
Well, that you kissed.
And we've talked it through,
and it's totally fine.
It's not a big deal.
It was just a kiss.
Wait, you're not still...
interested in him?
Oh, yeah.
Really.
Oh, no.
I'm... I was confused
by your phrasing.
You should definitely
go out with Jim.
I mean,
you're going out with Jim.
I'm not going out with Jim.
You're dating him.
Which is awesome,
because you guys
are great together.
'Kay.
I'm not into Jim.
Yeah.
So, um... we're good.
Sorry.
What are you sorry about?
Um...
What?
What are you sorry about?
Nothing.
I was just thinking
of something else.
Okay, the game is no-limit,
deuce to 7 lowball.
Blinds 25-50.
Nickels are worth 10, dimes 25,
and quarters 50.
Nothing wild.
Michael shuffle!
Here we go.
Michael...
Ah.
Gentlemen...
The entertainment is here.
Everybody,
I'd like to introduce you
to Elizabeth.
Hi, guys.
Nice outfit.
I hear there's
an important meeting here.
I'm not really into strippers.
And... you know
what I find sexy?
Pam's art.
She's an artist.
And I appreciate that.
It's very moving.
And... sexy.
The art.
Hit it.
So where's the groom?
Oh.
He is right there.
There he is.
Absolutely not.
That's all you.
It's all you.
Okay.
All right, I'll do it.
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's do this thing.
Yeah?
What do I...
Just sit on down.
All right.
Okay.
And here we go.
Oh, here we go.
All right.
Yes.
Whoo!
Not bad, not bad.
You smell nice.
Like Tide.
Mm, what's that?
You smell like Tide detergent.
Do you use
Tide detergent?
Ha ha!
Whoo!
I have a girlfriend, so...
I bet she'd be jealous.
Yeah, she'd probably...
Yes, she would be.
You know what?
Okay. Excuse me.
This... please.
Stop it, stop it.
Turn off the music.
This is wrong.
This is wrong!
I have a girlfriend.
Uh-uh.
And you are engaged,
and I'm sure you have
a boyfriend
in prison or something,
so...
Let's just clear out, okay?
Shame on you.
Go back to work!
Elizabeth, I want you
to sit here.
When the phone rings, answer it.
You want me to answer phones
with my clothes on?
We hired you
for three hours' work.
And we're gonna get it.
Ooh, I love your poster.
Thank you.
You know,
I invented electricity.
I know.
Well, I'm sensing
a little electricity right here.
Didn't Ben Franklin
have syphilis?
Yes, but I don't.
My name is Gordon.
Oh.
On one hand,
I want to be honest with Jan
and tell her the truth.
But on the other hand,
I'm afraid she's gonna dump me.
You know, Michael,
I fathered an illegitimate son.
Really.
But I kept all this
from my wife, Deborah.
These things only serve
to upset the women.
They are the gentler sex.
Wow.
Ben Franklin,
you're really
kind of a sleazebag.
Stripper?
Could I ask you a question?
About women?
Um...
Should I tell my girlfriend
that you danced up on me?
Secret secrets are no fun.
Secret secrets hurt someone.
Wow.
Thank you.
Care for a piece of chocolate?
Chocolate!
Where did you acquire it?
That is a delicacy
in the Amazon,
but it has not yet been imported
to the United States.
Who was the king of Austria?
Joseph II.
Who was the king of Prussia?
Friedrich Wilhelm III.
Who was the king of England?
Why, the tyrant King George,
of course.
I don't care what Jim says.
That is not
the real Ben Franklin.
I am 99% sure.
Michael, I left a meeting.
What is so urgent?
Are you... are you okay?
Not really.
Look, I don't know
how to say this,
so I just will.
Okay.
I, um...
went to a bachelor party.
And things got
a little out of hand.
Uh, when... when did...
When, last night?
No, today at work.
You went to a bachelor party
at work?
Yes, I kind of arranged it.
Well, I don't even think
the stripper was that hot.
Do... do you guys
think she was hot?
Kelly, don't do this.
Do what?
I just asked you a question.
You know what you're doing.
Anyway, you know who was
totally flirting
with Ben Franklin?
Pam.
Really?
Looks like I hired
the right guy.
I'm glad.
Any real potential there,
Beesly?
Yeah. Right.
God, I need a boyfriend.
Um...
You know, Ryan,
I'm... I'm totally ready
to be set up with one of
your business school friends.
Whenever.
'Kay.
Oh, my God.
I would get so fat if I worked here.
Yeah?
I lose my appetite all the time.
You could strip, you know.
Thanks.
So you don't want
to end our relationship?
I'm closer to firing you.
That is so sweet.
You are the best
cheated girlfriend in the world.
Do you know that?
You are.
I'll talk to you later.
So you know who turned out
to be kind of a creep?
Ben Franklin.
And...
Elizabeth, the stripper?
Gave me great advice.
Which rhymed.
Really makes you wonder
how Ben Franklin
can become president,
but someone
like Elizabeth can't.
Are you nearsighted
or farsighted?
That's why I invented the bifocals.
Gaah!