Good morning, Pam.
Oh, welcome back, Andy.
Drew.
I'm Drew now.
Oh... Drew.
Sorry.
Apology not accepted.
Because it wasn't even necessary
in the first place.
Several weeks ago,
Andy Bernard had an incident.
Gaaah!
Ohh!
But after five weeks
in anger management,
I'm back.
And I've got a new attitude.
And a new name.
And... a bunch
of new techniques
for dealing with the grumpies.
Morning, Jim.
Hey, Andy.
How are you, man?
Good. Drew.
What's that?
You can call me Drew.
No, I'm not gonna call you that.
Cool.
I can't control what you do.
I can only control what I do.
Andy.
Drew.
Dwight.
How's it going, man?
Yes, I have decided
to shun Andy Bernard
for the next three years.
Which I'm looking forward to.
It's an Amish technique.
It's like slapping someone
with silence.
I was shunned
from the age of four
until my sixth birthday
for not saving the excess oil
from a can of tuna.
Jim, could you please
inform Andy Bernard
that he is being shunned.
Andy, Dwight says welcome back,
and he could use a hug.
Okay, tell him
that that's not true.
Dwight says that he actually
doesn't know
one single fact
about bear attacks.
- Okay, no, Jim...
- You guys.
Tell him bears can climb
faster than they can run.
Jim!
Tell him!
Andy...
Nah, that's too far.
Damn you.
Today is safety training day.
Toby is leading ours upstairs.
Yuck.
But I am giving everyone
a little bit of a treat.
We are going to listen in
on Darryl's presentation
to the warehouse.
And if I know Darryl,
it gonna be zoppity.
Now...
this is the forklift.
You need... you need
a license to operate
this machine.
That means the upstairs
office workers can't drive it.
Quiz. Mike.
Hmm?
Should you drive the forklift?
I can, and I have.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
I said should you?
You should not drive it.
You should not
drive the forklift.
- You understand?
- You're now allowed to drive the forklift.
It's not safe.
You don't have a license.
Guys, I'm not the only one
who's driven the forklift.
Pudge has driven the forklift.
Madge.
I thought your name was Pudge.
No, it's always been Madge.
Okay.
Um, her.
Her, yes, "her" is qualified
to work a dangerous machine.
You are not.
Okay?
Ah... fine.
Do you understand that?
Yesh.
We do safety training
every year.
Or after an accident.
We've never made it a full year.
This particular time,
I was reaching for a supply box
on the top shelf,
when one office worker
who shall remain nameless
kicked the ladder out
from under me and yelled...
"Hey, Darryl,
how's it hangin'?"
And I fell
and busted my ankle and...
I'm legitimately scared
for my workers.
The bailer can flatten
a car engine.
It can cut off your arm
and crush your entire body
without skipping a beat.
Yeah!
It's on.
How many people a year
do you think
get their arms cut off
in a bailer?
Bail 'er?
I hardly know her.
Damn it, Michael,
pay attention, man.
Anybody wanna take a guess?
Five bucks says it's over 50.
You really wanna bet?
Anybody?
Ever since March Madness ended,
I am so bored.
- How many?
- Okay, you're on.
Ten people, Michael.
Ten people.
Would you like
to be one of them?
No, don't worry about it.
We'll just go double or nothing.
On what?
I don't know.
We'll figure something out.
What are you guys talking about?
These are very dangerous
machines down here.
And the upstairs workers,
Michael...
should not go
anywhere near them.
Yes, yes.
But it wouldn't be
the worst thing in the world...
It would be the worst thing
in the world, it would!
What the hell
is wrong with this man?
It's a big, red trash compactor.
It's not a trash compactor!
It's a bailer.
Okay, I got it!
I got it!
Only on the rarest
of occasions...
No, do not touch it!
There is no occasion for you
to go near this stuff, okay?
Toby now has the floor.
And he is going to try
not to screw this up.
Like everything else
in his life.
Let me rephrase that.
I believe that you can do
safety training
and make it sound
just as good as Darryl.
Here we go!
Okay, um... one thing
you're gonna wanna look out for
is carpal tunnel syndrome.
It's recommended that you take
a ten-minute break
from typing every hour.
For your circulation, um,
you're gonna wanna get up
out of your chairs,
and, uh, and move around
about ten minutes every hour.
Yes, good, fine.
Like stretching and...
Um... yeah.
Your computer screen
can be a big strain
on your eyes.
So it's also recommended
that you step away
for about... about
ten minutes every hour.
Wow, that is...
that time really adds up.
That's like a half an hour
every hour.
Take them at the same time.
Okay, you know what?
You're making it
sound kind of lame.
So skip ahead to the really
dangerous stuff.
Like sometimes,
computers can explode.
Can they not?
No, no.
Um, you always want
to keep a sweater or cardigan
of some sort
in case it gets drafty.
What about
a long-sleeved tee?
Well, that'll work.
Long johns? A shawl?
You know, anything
that warms you.
Okay, you know what?
I think that everybody
is going to vomit
due to boredom.
Sorry, he is very lame.
Um... let's see.
Seasonal affective disorder.
"A depression
that includes weight gain,
"fatigue, irritability,
brought on by the low light
of winter."
Thank God we only had
the bailer to deal with.
Yeah, that dim light
is a bitch, ain't it?
Okay, guys, you know what?
I didn't interrupt
when you were having
your presentation.
Actually, you did.
Yes.
Okay, let's do another one.
This is a good one.
"A particular concern
for office workers
"is a sedimentary lifestyle,
which can contribute..."
Sedentary.
Yes, "which can contribute
to heart disease."
Heart disease kills
more people than bailers.
That's called having
a fat butt, Michael.
Mmm, no, no, it's...
Yeah, yeah.
That's fat butt disease.
That's what you're
suffering from?
No. Fat butt disease, Michael?
No, I...
Excuse me, Sea Monster,
you weigh, like, 1,000 pounds.
Yeah, I bet you'd like to swim
with this sea monster,
wouldn't you?
Ryan!
Dude, please,
tell your girl to shut up.
What? Kelly, you
insulted the gentleman.
Please, apologize.
Are you kidding me?
All right, we out of here.
Darryl, I did not walk out
in the middle of yours.
So I...
Yeah, but ours
was real, Michael.
- Yes.
- That's what we been trying to tell you, Mike.
It's serious down there.
We do dangerous stuff, man.
This is shenanigans,
foolishness.
NERF ball.
You live a sweet little
NERF-y life.
Sittin' on your biscuit.
Never havin' to risk it.
Okay...
What, NERF isn't cool anymore?
Darryl thinks he's such a man
because he works in a warehouse.
Well, big deal.
I worked in a warehouse...
Men's Wearhouse.
I was a greeter.
I'd like to see Darryl
greet people.
Probably make 'em
feel like wimps.
Not me.
I...
Hello, I'm Michael.
Welcome to Men's Wearhouse.
We have a special
on khaki pants today.
This is one example.
Ten.
Really, ten?
That's your guess?
You're a professional
accountant.
There's, like, ten green ones.
42.
I'm gonna say 50.
51.
- Oh, don't be that person.
- Come on, that is lame.
It's a strategy.
It's called being smart.
- Thank you.
- Oh, jeez.
I don't know how the whole
betting thing started,
but it's fun.
- Ten.
- Kev's out.
Damn it!
47, 48, 49!
Jim wins!
Oh!
That is not fair.
He has spent hours up here
at reception with you.
Hours and hours.
Okay... okay.
No, constantly...
like, for years.
Okay.
Pam, depression is as scary
as a bailer, right?
I...don't understand
the question.
"Working in a office
can lead to depression
"which can lead
to suicide."
I mean this
is really serious stuff.
Yeah.
I... I...
Nobody commits suicide
because they work with a bailer.
And yet those guys
are making fun of me.
Calling me a NERF.
That...
It's really hard
to demonstrate depression.
Their safety training
had visuals.
Yeah... you are...
Ah, so right.
They have visual aids.
And all we had were the facts.
You don't go
to the science museum
and get handed a pamphlet
on electricity.
You go to the science museum
and you put your hand
on a metal ball.
Your hair sticks up straight.
And you know science.
So you're okay?
Indubitably.
They use props.
They use visual aids.
And they just made us
look like dopes.
Idiots!
God, what are we gonna do!
I don't know.
Because you know what
our killer is?
Depression.
Wolves.
Visual aids.
Yes.
A quilt...
depression quilt?
No time to sew a quilt.
I got it.
Give me the number
for the Giant Big Box toy store.
You may be asking yourself,
"What am I doing
on a trampoline?"
Well, I thought I'd bounce here
for a while,
relieve some stress,
and then move on with my day.
Not!
Here's the plan.
Dwight is going to gather
all of the office workers
and all of the warehouse guys
and we're going to have
another safety seminar.
Only this time, where's Michael?
Oh, my God!
He is on the roof!
Now I've got their attention.
I tell them about
the cold hard facts
of depression.
And then I say,
"Hey, you ever seen
a suicide?"
And I jump.
And they freak out.
And they get to see
the dangers of depression
with their own eyes.
Nice side note...
they might think,
hey, I should've been nicer
to Michael.
But that's not why
I'm doing this.
Then I land on the trampoline,
take a couple extra bounces
for fun.
I climb off,
walk around the corner.
Ta-freakin'-da!
So then the next movie
moves to the top of the queue.
So number five becomes
number four.
Number six becomes number five.
Number three becomes number two.
Etcetera, etcetera.
And let's just say
that I just sent back
Love Actually,
which was awesome.
And they sent me Uptown Girls,
which is also awesome.
But guess what?
Now I want to see
Love Actually again.
But it's at the bottom
of the queue.
Oh no!
What do I do?
What I do is this:
I go online,
I go "click, click, click,"
and I change the order
of the queue
so that I can see Love Actually
as soon as I want to.
It's so easy, Ryan.
Do you really not know
how Netflix works?
I guess I forgot.
You're such a ditz.
Ryan, well done.
2 minutes, 42 seconds.
Additionally, Pam, you win ten
because she said "awesome"
12 times.
And Jim, you win five
because she mentioned
six romantic comedies.
Okay, let's do this thing!
I'll go summon the troops.
Maybe we should test this first,
Letterman-style.
Throw a TV over.
We measured it once.
Go buy some watermelons.
Seedless?
Just...
Creed is eating an apple.
I found a potato.
Hey, Creed.
Hey!
- Hi.
- Hello.
Yes!
Here you go.
Nice.
I don't know this place
as well as I thought I did.
I'm getting cleaned out.
- Ready?
- Let's do it.
Drop that sucker.
Yeah, bingo!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, crap!
Deactivate the car alarm,
clean up the mess.
Okay.
Find out whose car that is.
If it's Stanley's,
call the offices
of James P. Albini.
See if he handles hate crimes.
Got it.
Also, take apart the trampoline,
stick it in the bailer.
We're not allowed
to use the bailer.
Have Patch do it...
or the sea monster.
I'm on it!
Eh...
I'm temporarily lifting
the shun.
Thank you.
It means nothing.
I need you to do something
for me.
Anything.
Okay, calm down.
I need you to acquire
an inflatable house
and/or castle.
You mean a moon bounce?
What do you think?
You've got an hour.
I'm gonna need petty cash.
Shunning resumed.
Do you... do you want
a drawbridge?
Un-shun.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Re-shun.
Oh, yeah, this is much better.
Safer.
An excellent decision.
Yes.
Thank you for seeing that.
When you land,
try and land
like an eight-year-old.
These bouncy castles
are not designed for adults.
I don't know
if I want to do this.
Do you want to do another test?
I got plenty of watermelons
in my trunk.
No.
No more;
the tests are going terrible.
If we keep doing them,
I'm not gonna want to jump.
This is about doing,
not thinking.
Right, doing!
Totally doing!
It's rock and roll!
Rock and roll!
Yeah!
You're right;
I'm not thinking.
Yes, yeah!
I am ready to do this!
I'm ready to make a point!
Hey, guys, listen up.
Michael is up on the roof
and acting strange.
Whoa, what's the situation?
Un-shun.
I think he's suffering
from depression.
Re-shun.
Okay, when's the shunning thing
gonna end?
Un-shun... never!
Re-shun.
I think he wants you all
to come out to the parking lot
and watch him die.
Is it nice outside?
It's gorgeous.
Let's go!
Do I need my jacket?
No, really, it's very nice.
Come on!
Will I be too warm
in a long sleeve T?
Everyone's gonna be fine
in exactly what they're wearing!
Let's go!
Come on, hurry up, you guys!
My life!
Oh, my life...
Michael, what's wrong?
Everything's wrong.
The stress of my modern office
has caused me to go
into a depression.
Depression?
Isn't that just a fancy word
for feeling bummed out?
Dwight, you ignorant slut.
Depression is
a very serious illness.
Over 32,000 people
commit suicide every year,
according to a 2004 study.
Is that the last year to date
it was available?
Yes.
My head is in such pain
and turmoil!
Don't do anything rash.
Dwight, where are
the warehouse guys?
I didn't...
I didn't think you need them
for this part.
Okay... that's...
- You said to just...
- That's the whole point, dummy.
Okay, I'm on it.
Okay.
Attention blue collar workers!
What are the odds that this
is in any way real?
I'd say, like, 10,000 to 1.
Okay, I'd like ten bucks
on those odds.
If someone gives you
10,000 to 1 on anything,
you take it.
If John Mellencamp
ever wins an Oscar,
I am going to be
a very rich dude.
Michael's up on the roof
and he's acting strange!
Oh, my life!
Michael, what's wrong?
Everything's wrong, Dwight!
The stress of my modern office
has made me depressed.
Depressed?
Isn't that just a fancy word
for feeling bummed out?
Dwight, you ignorant slut.
Well, you know,
the first performance
was a little off.
But I really think
they hit their stride
in the second show.
Um...
Might even bring my parents
tomorrow to the matinee.
And that is why...
Oh, excuse me.
It's my favorite part.
I am going to jump off
this roof.
This is just offensive.
At least we're outside.
Hey, check it out.
There's a castle over there.
Oh, my God.
There is a castle.
No, there's nothing to see
over there, people.
There's nothing to see.
They found the castle, Michael.
Damn it.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God!
He's gonna jump.
Oh.
He's going to kill himself
pretending to kill himself.
Yeah.
Hey, uh, Michael.
Don't jump on the bouncy castle.
You can't do that
'cause you are going to get
horribly, horribly injured.
Hey, Michael.
I have a present for you
but you have to come down
and get it.
What is it?
Come down and open it
and you'll see.
Dwight, find out
what the present is.
Okay, uh...
I don't see anything.
She might be bluffing.
Dwight.
What are you...
Oh.
It's, uh...
A Repliee Q1 Expo female robot.
They're only available in Japan.
Dwight, you are such a liar.
Pam, really, what is it?
Mike, this is the opposite
of safety.
You jump, you're gonna
seriously hurt yourself.
You told me that I lead a...
a cushy, wimpy, NERF life.
Yeah, but I never said
you had nothing to live for.
What do I have to live for?
A lot... of things.
Uh, you, uh...
What about Jan?
Lovely, lovely, lovely Jan, man.
It's going good, right?
It's complicated with Jan.
And I don't know where I stand
or what I want.
The sex isn't nearly as good
as it used to be.
Mike...
you're a very brave man.
I mean, it takes courage
just to be you.
To get out of bed
every single day
knowing full well
you gotta be you.
Do you really mean that?
I couldn't do it.
I ain't that strong
and I ain't that brave.
I'm braver than you?
Way braver!
You Braveheart, man.
I Braveheart.
I am.
Come on down, okay?
Okay.
Pam, I'm coming down
to get my present.
An office is as safe
as the people in it.
And sometimes those people
can drive you to do crazy things
to show the dangers
of the office.
That's the danger
I found myself in today.
I saved a life... my own.
Am I a hero?
I really can't say.
But, yes.