- Pam?
- Yeah?
Did you see Oprah yesterday?
No, I didn't.
I, uh...
I am going to be a father.
What was Oprah about?
Angelina Jolie was on.
And she adopted a baby from Asia
and she said that
it changed her life.
And that really inspired me.
So I want you to look in
to see how much
a little Chinese baby
would cost.
That's a really big decision.
I know.
Maybe you should wait
before you adopt.
Or not adopt.
Just do it, okay?
Roy's sister looked into it.
And the application alone
costs $1,000.
Um...
Find out if there's a cheaper...
Less expensive baby
out there, okay?
You know... she also said
the waiting list
is like eight months.
- Eight months?
- Yeah.
I don't even know if I want
a baby in eight months.
Probably won't.
You know, Pam,
if in ten years...
I haven't had a baby,
and you haven't had a baby...
No, Michael.
- 20 years.
- No, Michael.
30.
Sure.
It's a deal.
All right, three pairs of pants.
Mm-hmm.
- Three pairs of socks.
- Mm-hmm.
Three packs of condoms.
Yeeeash.
Uh, fun jeans.
Ah.
Sign.
Per diem.
Guess where I am going?
I will give you a hint.
It is a booze-fueled
sex romp
where anything goes.
You are correct sir!
I am headed to Philadelphia
for the annual
Northeastern Mid-market
Office Supply Convention.
And Jim Halpert
is going to be coming,
which will be fun.
Poor little guy has been stuck
working under Josh.
The poor man's Michael Scott,
as he is known around my condo.
Don't be mad.
It is a business trip.
But I don't understand.
It's for managers.
Monkey, I am an ARM.
Assistant Regional Manager.
I know.
I was just really hoping
we could
spend some time together.
Are you still there?
Yes, Monkey.
Don't monkey me.
You can't wait
to get out of here, ARM.
In the Martin family,
we like to say...
looks like someone
took the slow train
from Philly.
That's code for
"Check out the slut."
What is...
Why are there flies in here?
Oh, my God!
Are you so excited for tonight?
I'm so excited... you guys
are gonna click.
I can feel it.
So what are you wearing?
This.
You look so pretty.
Thank you.
Yes, I have a date.
He's a cartoonist
for the local paper.
Which is really neat,
because I like to draw too.
I'm kind of nervous.
I haven't been on a first date
in nine years.
Probably shouldn't
broadcast that.
Well, remember, no matter
how much you may want to,
do not sleep with him
on the first date.
It gives him all the power.
Sleep with who?
Whom.
Whom?
My neighbor Allen.
They're going on a date tonight.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
I have a great idea.
You know what you should do?
Be hilarious?
Wear your wedding dress.
That would be
a great icebreaker.
And your veil.
Yeah.
Do it.
I'll probably just wear this.
Really?
Okay.
Well, a word of advice,
unbutton that top button.
Let those things breathe.
Any message you want me
to relate to Jim?
Um...
Um.
Okay, um.
- Um.
- You got that?
I got it.
Write it down.
Um.
Um...
There's my girl.
I noticed you
handing out some shekels.
How would one get on that train?
That was per diem
for Philadelphia.
Ugh, that town
smells like cheese steaks.
That town is full of history.
Andrea's the office bitch.
You'll get used to her.
Mmm.
Creed.
Can I have my neck pillow back?
Michael!
Hey, Michael.
Hey, Josh, how you doing?
Pretty good.
How you doing?
Great to see you.
There he is.
There's the traitor.
Traitor!
Come here, you.
Come here!
Aaagh!
The product... the progidal...
My son returns.
I was shocked when he told me
he was transferring to Stamford.
It's like with firemen.
You don't leave
your brothers behind.
Even if you find out
that there is
a better fire in Connecticut.
Really good to see you, man.
Yeah.
Wow.
I didn't expect that.
It's good to see you too.
Oh, hey.
How's it going up there?
Have you made any sales yet?
Yeah, sold about 40,000.
Shut up.
That's impossible.
No, it's not.
And I did.
Yeah.
Well, I did it too.
You know, when I saw Dwight,
I realized how stupid and petty
all those pranks
I pulled on him were.
And then he spoke.
I wonder how hard it would be
to get a copy
of his room key.
So did you hear?
What?
Pam's back on the market again.
Really?
She's dating?
Oh, if I weren't engaged,
I would so hit that.
So what kind of commissions
you get up there?
Oh, Dwight,
I missed you so much.
You're so immature.
Listen, Michael, I heard you
were a great salesman.
And I just wanna let you know
that if our branch
absorbs your branch,
I'm gonna look for a place
for you in Stamford.
Oh, hey!
Hey, Jan.
We all checked in?
Yes.
Great.
Let's dump our stuff
and meet back
down here in a half an hour.
Okay.
Jan?
Look, I think we need
to set some ground rules.
What are you talking about?
The 800-pound gorilla
in the room.
Carol.
I'm still dating her.
So nothing can happen between us
at the convention.
Step away from me, Michael.
Thank you for being
so brave with all of this.
Thank you.
Allen's cartoon
is so funny, right?
Mm-hmm.
And they're, like, so smart.
I don't even know
what they mean half the time.
That is specifically why I chose
a room close to the elevator.
More foot traffic.
Check it out.
That is crooked on that side.
Wow.
Hey hey!
That is a lot of liquor.
Yeah.
And a dart board.
Well, that's how
we do it in Scranton.
Or did you forget?
We should probably
head on down, you know,
hook up with Jan.
Well, we have time.
One for the road, gentlemen?
A shot of Midori, perhaps.
Oh, no, sorry,
it's an inside joke.
There was this bartender
in Stamford who...
You know what?
You just have to be there.
Wish I was.
I love inside jokes.
Love to be a part of one
someday.
Um, we should...
Yeah, all right.
All right, see you guys
down there.
See you guys.
Change your mind, come back up.
I'll do a shot
with you, Michael.
Yechh, don't be gross.
It's not even lunch yet.
SWAG!
Stuff We All Get.
I basically decorated
my condo for free
with all of my SWAG!
Check it out.
Hi, I'm Michael Scott.
Dunder Mifflin.
Dwight Schrute.
Assistant Regional Manager,
Dunder Mifflin.
I am a huge fan.
Thanks.
I appreciate it, guys.
You know what?
I am having
a big blowout tonight, room 308.
Hope you can come.
I...maybe.
If I can.
Well, cool!
Okay, so can I tell people
you're gonna be there?
No, you cannot.
So maybe.
See ya.
Why do they call him The Bus?
Because he's afraid to fly.
Smile.
Do you remember me
from last year?
There's a party in my room, 308.
Can't miss it.
Right off the elevator.
Tonight.
Be there.
All right, Jan just emailed me.
She wants us
to meet her up front.
Yep.
Yeah, she's up front.
You don't have email
on your phone.
I don't have to, I just know.
Yes, hello?
No one just called you.
All right, nice meeting you.
Take care.
See you soon.
Bye-bye.
May I have a moment
of your time, please?
I need you to do something
for me.
Yes, anything.
I want you to
dig up some dirt on Josh.
Find out if there are
any skeletons in his attic.
I'll talk to my buddy
down at the station stat.
Hey, Pam.
Hey, what's up?
What's up?
I wanted to ask if you wanted...
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
He's not in the office.
Can I take a message?
I will.
You too.
Sorry.
What's up?
Um, if, uh...
Um...
I just completely forgot
what I was going to say.
That's so weird.
Okay.
Well, if you think of it,
I'll be here.
Okay.
So I called my buddy
down at the station today.
Mm-hmm.
I had him run a background check
on Josh Porter.
See if there's
any known aliases, etc.
And?
He wasn't volunteering today.
Yeah.
Things have been pretty crazy
around the office.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
We moved Ryan over to your desk.
Oh.
Tell him I say hi.
I will call him later
with that message.
Hey, how's...
Toby?
Toby Flenderson is everything
that is wrong
with the paper industry.
Is he why you left?
Oh, no.
It was just...
you know,
a good opportunity for me,
a promotion.
Opportunity, promotion.
Blah blah.
You know, Jim,
those are just words.
Have you taken into account
other factors?
Vis-à-vis bosses?
Is Josh funnier than I am?
Does he even have a girlfriend?
Because I have two, basically.
Michael, it's really not
a competition.
Jim got a us a great lead
with a new rep
from National Envelope.
We can grab lunch
with him tomorrow.
Hey, Jan.
Jan?
Don't worry.
I have got the tip.
Whoa, Michael.
Wow.
Oh, my God, thank you.
Is that your per diem?
No, that was a different
hundred dollar bill.
What have you generated,
Michael?
I have generated
a lot of interest
in my party this evening.
What party?
Party I'm having tonight in 308.
Obviously, you are invited.
Michael, um...
Jim and Josh are in meetings
all day and I am
in and out of meetings.
I can't stay on top of you 24/7.
You should order
the most expensive thing
on the menu.
So he knows you're worth it.
If you do that,
you're gonna have to put out.
Oh, yeah.
You'll have to put out.
Is there a key for Jane Doe?
Thank you.
Any messages for 308?
All right.
Hey hey, fellers.
- Michael.
- Hey, Michael.
Hey, what's up?
Uh, well, Jim and I
have a meeting with Uniball
in about 45 minutes,
so we should probably go.
Hey, check this out.
How about that?
A little friendly competition.
Stamford versus Scranton.
I don't think so.
Oh.
Jim?
Looks like you picked a bad time
to defect, my friend.
Fine.
All right.
Okay.
Excellent.
Oh, just shut it.
Hey, Pam, what's up?
Yeah... uh, no.
Tell him I will give him
general specifics tomorrow,
okay?
Yes.
Say hi to Pam!
Hi, Pam.
Yes, that is Josh
and Dwight and Jim.
Pam says hi.
Have fun on your date.
Very good.
Talk to you later.
Bye.
You first.
Oh, nice try, Josh!
Not.
Hit the rim.
Okay, and...
Okay, double or nothing.
What, we didn't
bet anything, Michael.
Well, let's...
You know, we should go.
Come on, come on.
Come on!
We'll do it later.
Say, while I have you here,
can I talk to you about
some new and exciting advances
to our product line?
Fine.
Jim and I have different
definitions of friendship.
I think it's talking
and being friends
and Jim thinks
it's moving to Connecticut
and being best friends
with Josh.
Well...
phooey on that.
I, uh...
I'm done.
I am not going to be
speaking with him anymore.
Whatevs.
Long distance relationships
never work.
That is so true.
Ready?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, let me tell you
what we're looking for.
Sorry, my meeting ran late.
- Really?
- Yes, Jan.
Really.
With a rep from Hammermill.
They're exclusive with Staples.
Used to be.
Evan'll call you in the morning
to work out the details.
We can now
sell Hammermill products.
Yes!
Ha!
Well, Michael...
I underestimated you.
Yeah, well, maybe next time
you will estimate me.
Dwight's room key.
And Dwight's room.
What can I say?
Old habits die hard.
D?
Oh, my God.
Dwight got a hooker.
Oh, my God, I gotta call...
I gotta call somebody.
I don't even know who to call.
Dwight got a hooker!
So, Allen, Pam is obsessed
with your cartoons.
She reads them every day.
Oh, great.
I don't like ketchup.
You love ketchup.
He loves ketchup.
So how do you come up
with your cartoons?
I just... I kinda think about
stuff that I see.
Or dream them.
You dream in cartoons?
How fun.
Hey!
First guest!
You are going to have
some tequila, my friend.
Um, I thought there was
a party in here.
This is the party.
This is room 308?
Party central.
So what can I do you for?
All right.
See this one is great.
Because it could work
on a couple different levels.
Huh.
Your freedom fries
for the table.
Freedom fries.
Yeah.
People always say, like,
don't be edgy.
But, I don't know.
I don't know any other way.
Oh.
Yeah, you get it.
Well, it was really nice
meeting you, Allen.
Yeah, next time bring some of
your illustrations.
I'll let you pick my brain.
More freedom fries.
Yeah.
That's great.
Okay.
I went on a date.
It wasn't a love connection.
Um, I think when
I like someone again,
I'll just kind of know.
Michael.
Am I the first the arrive?
People have been filtering
in and out.
Can I get a drink?
What?
Sure.
You like cosmos?
Yeah, sure.
Sounds good.
So why are you here?
Is Josh busy?
Michael...
I get it, you know?
- Did I do something?
- No, I totally get it.
He made a better paper airplane.
Stamford does better in sales.
I get it.
We had some fun.
We had some laughs.
Wait wait wait, I didn't
transfer because of you.
You're a good boss.
You're a great boss.
Pfff.
Not better than Josh.
Michael, it's not about...
I transferred because of Pam.
Oh, my God.
You don't even know.
She's single now.
No, I heard
something about that.
It's just, I kind of
put it all on the line.
Twice, actually.
And she said no.
Twice.
I'm sorry, man.
I'm sorry.
Hey, you know what?
I will talk to her.
No, that's okay.
Yeah.
That's all right.
I will.
I'll talk to her.
You should at least
talk to... Roy.
I mean, he knows
exactly how you're feeling.
Yeah.
Okay, maybe.
Are we early?
Hey, no.
You know, people have been
filtering in and out.
Hey.
Evan, this is Jim.
How are ya?
Hey, Arnie Risman.
Michael, Jim.
Hey, Arnie, how you doing?
You guys work together?
No, we used to.
- Yeah.
- Now, we're friends.
Best friends.
Some people
need dozens of friends
to say, hey, look at me,
I'm popular.
But not me.
I'm very picky.
I need three.
Maybe two?
When you meet
that someone special,
you'll just know.
Because a real relationship...
can't be forced.
It should just come about
effortledlessly.
Now, would you do me
the pleasure of
hitting the lights, sir?
Ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Whoa.
What are all those stains?
Blood, urine, or semen.
Oh, God, I hope it's urine.