Can you confirm
that the straps are tight?
Yes.
But this one's a little...
And now the chains!
A lot of people think
that magic camp
is just for kids.
And that's why so many
other people
in my class were kids.
Self-fulfilling prophecy.
It's, um, really for anybody
with a dream,
and a belief in magic,
and a little extra time
after school.
Magic, magic, magic, magic...
And now, Michael the Magic
will attempt to escape
from extreme bondage.
Can he do it?
I don't see how he can.
I know how.
He'd dislocate his shoulder
and slip his arm out.
No! No.
Everyone now count down with me.
Three!
Sorry.
Sorry, quickly.
So is it true
that if you can't get out,
you don't want anyone
to help you?
I will get out.
Oh, yes, I will.
So we shouldn't help you,
no matter how much
you might beg and plead.
No, all right, just...
this is getting hot.
So let's just do this,
okay, ready?
Three!
Two.
One!
Go!
Mm-hmm.
Aah!
Is everything okay, Michael?
Yes.
I cannot tell you
how I plan to escape.
Other than by using magic.
That is the magician's code.
Help.
Separately,
on an unrelated note,
if you happen to find
a small brass key...
All right, ready?
Come on, guys,
early worm gets the worm.
Another worm?
Like, are they friends?
It's early bird gets the worm.
Okay.
Pam, would you smell my breath?
No. No.
Let me smell.
Good, not great.
Michael, you go to parties
all the time.
Why is tonight so special?
Well, tonight is so special
because my boss's boss's boss,
the CFO, not his initials,
common mistake,
is having a little shindig
for all the managers
in the company, and Jan and I
are going as a couple.
For the first time.
So it's kind of
our coming out party.
Really.
And that is why tonight
is so special.
Jimbo, last chance carpool.
Oh, no thanks, I think
Karen and I'll take my car.
Sure? Might be a good idea.
If we all went together
we could save some gas.
Have fun. Long trip!
Thanks.
Play some games?
Oh.
Um... no, we're good.
I Spy.
Yeah.
Why don't I wanna go?
Didn't expect to need a reason,
so let me think here.
Um...
I don't know
any of these people.
It's an obligation.
I don't like talking paper
in my free time.
Or in my work time.
And... did I use
the word "pointless?"
Thanks for inviting me along.
Oh, sure.
Really didn't give it
any thought.
Wait, should you be going?
Hey-wo, you!
Michael?
Hey, buttercup.
I am on my way,
should be there in about 15...
Let's just blow this party off.
That's what she said.
Yeah.
Am I on speaker phone?
Ah, yes you are.
Is anybody else...
Hello, Jan!
Hi, Dwight.
Okay, Michael,
take me off speakerphone.
No le problem.
Okay, let's just go
to a motel...
Okay!
And, like, rip into each other
like we did
on that black sand beach
in Jamaica.
Hey, Jan?
Jan, this party is actually
a very big step for us.
So I...
Still on speaker?
Um... I don't know.
Are cameras there?
Maybe.
All right, see you soon.
Okay.
Talk to you later, Jan!
All right, bye.
Hey, Michael left early,
so a bunch of us
are gonna go to Poor Richard's
for happy hour, you should come.
I can't.
My brother just unloaded
the Jet Skis
and he kinda took a bath, so...
We're gonna go get hammered.
Okay, well, we're going
to a bar.
Hey.
You have to come
to stuff with me.
I'm serious.
If you're gonna be my boyfriend,
you have to do boyfriend things.
Okay.
I have decided that
I'm going to be more honest.
I'm gonna start telling people
what I want directly.
So look out world,
'cause ol' Pamie
is getting what she wants.
And don't call me Pamie.
Beauty.
Thank you, sir.
Ensalada.
Thank you.
You're dressed
exactly like the servants.
Shut up.
Okay, change shirts with me.
What?
Give me your shirt.
No, but yours won't fit me.
I don't care.
This is stupid.
Ah... wow.
Here.
Don't let my jacket...
Don't give me that.
That would have been
really embarrassing.
Yes.
Crisis averted.
Okay.
Oh.
That duck is so cute.
Hey, Pam.
Oscar.
Angela.
Uh, hi!
Actually, it's polite
to arrive early.
And smart.
Only really good friends
show up early.
Ergo de facto,
go to a party early,
become a really good friend.
Oh! Uh, potato salad.
Oh.
That's from both of us.
No, it's not.
It's my bowl.
Wonderful.
Let's, uh, see
where we can put this.
Okay.
Oh, you know what,
you probably wanna leave
the cover on
until the guests get here.
It's been sitting
in my car all day.
Sun beating down
on the mayonnaise...
Just... you never know.
Kevin, you and Stacey
set a date yet?
Yeah.
Oh, my God, when is it?
It's complicated.
I would appreciate
some space on this.
Hey!
You made it.
Yeah, you said
it was important, so...
It is.
How's it going?
What's up, Pam?
Hey, Kenny.
Sorry about the Jet Skis.
You guys all want
a round? On me?
Yeah!
Let's get you a drink.
Thanks, man.
I'm thirsty.
No, thank you, Roy, I...
You should get a round, Ryan.
Oh, you know that line
on the top of the shrimp?
That's feces.
Whatcha looking for?
Did you bring dip?
I'm sure that it's catered.
I need you
to sign these, Michael.
That's a waiver
of some of your rights.
You should read it carefully.
It releases the company
in the event
that our relationship
in your opinion,
or in reality,
interferes with work.
You get a copy, I get a copy,
and a third copy goes to HR.
Awesome.
I'm gonna frame mine.
I could frame yours too.
You realize this is...
this is a legal document
that says you can't sue
the company?
Over our love.
I've... never told you
that I love you.
You don't have to, Jan.
This contract says it all.
I am taking a calculated risk.
What's the upside?
I overcome my nausea,
fall deeply in love,
babies, normalcy,
no more self-loathing.
Downside, I, uh,
date Michael Scott publicly
and collapse into myself
like a dying star.
What's this over the I?
It's a heart.
Why is this so hard?
That's what she said.
Oh, my God.
What am I saying?
I love this woman!
Oh, no, Michael,
please, Michael, please.
Do you ever watch
Battlestar Galactica?
No.
No?
Then you're an idiot.
Hello, Michael.
Rachel, boy,
do you clean up good.
Place looks great
with all the lights on.
And everything
actually looks bigger
with people in it, weird.
Jan, glad you could make it.
Oh, of course, of course, David.
Do you remember, uh,
Michael Scott?
Of course I do.
From Scranton branch.
How are you, Michael?
Jan and I are lovers.
That feels so good
to finally say that out loud.
David, can I, um,
speak to you privately
for just a moment, please?
Excuse me.
Okay.
Oh.
No. Actually, one of these
is supposed to be a light.
Oh, sorry.
So the merger goes smoothly,
or...
It did.
"Like butter."
Mike Myers, SNL.
You should ask Karen,
she was one of them.
Yeah, I'm the only one left.
Everybody else
was either fired or quit.
And there's one
in anger management.
Yeah, but you're great now,
right?
We're all great.
Aren't we great?
We're good.
Michael, st...
please stop that, okay?
Uh, can I get anyone anything?
I could go
for an appe-tease-er, yep.
Martini, please.
Bagel bites or something.
Rachel, your house is beautiful.
Oh, thank you.
What's the square footage?
Wow.
Uh, about 5,000.
Does that include the garage?
Dwight, that's not appropriate.
I don't know.
It's a common question.
David, how much
did this house cost?
These old colonials
are great... when they're sound.
I'd love to, uh,
take a look around.
I'll show you around, sure.
Cool, let's start
with the banisters.
Hey.
Do you see that guy behind you
in the blue blazer
against the wall?
Mm, yup.
That's Drake.
And just so you know,
I don't wanna be weird
or anything, but, um,
we used to date.
Oh.
Okay, cool.
Thanks for telling me that.
And it didn't end well.
Gotcha.
All right.
This was a gift...
from Lee lacocca.
20-year-old,
single malt Scotch.
Here is to Mr. Iacocca
and his failed experiment,
the DeLorean.
Are you okay?
Yeah!
Do you have any ice?
Sure.
How about some Splenda?
1, 2, 3, up chickens!
Down chickens!
Uh, I think I heard
the quarter over here.
Where?
On this side.
No, it is definitely
under one of these hands.
I kind of heard it
on Roy's side too.
No, it is here.
Not here.
Not here. Not here.
Good thing you didn't listen
to me.
Yeah, close one.
Not here. Not here.
Okay, it's either here or here.
Not here.
Yes!
Nice job.
I can read you like a book.
Oh, yeah?
You can't keep anything from me.
Bottom's up.
Hey, Creed.
Hey.
What's up, Creed?
What are you guys up to?
Ah, hello.
You're the man, buddy.
I run a small fake ID company
from my car
with a laminating machine
that I swiped
from the sheriff's station.
Huh, yeah.
These studs
are way too far apart.
What's in here?
Ah, it's a guest room.
Just the one window?
Oh, I must get that.
You'll have to excuse me.
Are those real pearls?
Uh, yes.
They're...
Yes.
Good.
Well, it was nice
meeting you guys.
Take care.
Well, if you're wondering why
his wife was staring daggers
at me, it's because
I kinda saw him
for a little bit
when they were separated.
Oh.
Didn't notice.
Really? I thought
it was so obvious.
I'm glad it didn't make you
uncomfortable.
No, it was before I knew you,
so... it's fine.
Wow, this one really smells
like vanilla.
Mm.
Check that out.
That's nice.
You and the Mrs.
should join us
at Sandals Jamaica
next Christmas.
I...Michael, I think
David probably wants
to spend Christmas here
with his family.
Oh, yeah.
They don't allow kids
at Sandals.
They are... are
persona non grata.
Please stop.
They're... uh,
but it's fun.
It is an awesome place.
You would not believe
how low this girl can limbo.
David, I'm sorry.
You're just gonna
have to excuse us
for just a couple minutes,
sorry.
Okay, okay.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
What is it?
Sorry.
What... what's the matter?
What's...
Come here.
Just... just... just... just...
What are you doing?
Don't you know what I'm doing?
Yes, but you could tell me.
What are... what is that?
Why are you... why are we going
in the bathroom?
I thought this is where
you liked your privacy.
Shut up.
What has gotten into you?
No, no, no, no!
What?
Come on, let's go back
to the party.
Come on, wait,
let me just do my dress.
Don't take that... no!
Stop it! Stop it.
Jan, no, no, no!
Michael!
No means please don't.
Slam me up against the wall,
right here.
I'm not gonna slam you
up against anything.
Oh, please, I want you so...
You're acting inappropriate.
I'm acting inappropriate?
Jan... yeah.
Forget it, get away from me.
Here.
Hey.
Where have you been all night?
I was looking forward
to hanging out with you.
I was...
Hey, don't you have a daughter?
Yes.
Oh, good, you're up.
Hey, who makes' this chair?
I don't know,
it was here when I was born.
Hmm.
I want one.
Really good, solid construction.
It's comfortable.
What is this? Oak?
I don't know.
What do you know?
God, I hate these parties.
You wanna sneak out back
and shoot some hoops?
Meet me outside in two minutes.
You stay here and have fun,
'cause I'm gonna go out back
and shoot hoops
with David Wallace.
Okay.
Oh, um, don't mention
that you and I are dating,
'cause I think he might
still have feelings for me.
Wallace?
What the hell?
Have you dated, like,
every guy here?
Wow.
Okay.
You got me.
I so got you.
So, none of them.
Of course not.
I mean, you're kind of,
like, my first.
Really?
Oh, my God, it's so easy,
it's not even fun.
Okay.
Hey, Jan.
Not too good.
Did you get a chance to try
Michael's homemade potato salad?
Rachel thinks that I brought
homemade potato salad.
And I just picked it up
at the supermarket.
It's funny, I wish I could make
potato salad that good.
It's just potatoes
and mayonnaise.
There's something wrong
with Jan.
What's, uh, what's
with Jan and Michael?
I don't know.
Where to begin?
My ball.
The chimney's in decent shape.
Not great, I found
some termite damage
in a crawlspace
and some structural flaws
in the foundation,
so all in all...
it was a pretty fun
cocktail party.
What?
I want us to make it.
I want a fresh start.
That's awesome.
That's what I want.
Okay, but in order
for us to make it,
there can't be any secrets
between us.
The... I didn't do anything.
Ask anybody, I totally could've,
and I didn't at all.
Just listen.
Remember that casino night
about a month
before we were supposed
to get married?
I kissed Jim.
What?
He told me how he felt,
and I guess I had feelings too,
and we kissed.
Jim came on to you?
Just listen.
No, I am listening!
That's the problem,
I'm listening!
Don't yell.
Don't yell?
This is over.
Yeah, you're right,
this is so over.
You kidding me, Pam?
Come on!
God!
Damn Jet Skis!
Our first fight.
If this is about what happened
in the bathroom,
there was no place to cuddle.
I feel sick.
You didn't have any
of the potato salad, did you?
You know, we were good when we
were just running around.
You know, in secret.
It was wrong,
and it was exciting.
And maybe it was a mistake
to take it public.
Well, if that's the way
you feel,
my lady, then you
have hurt me greatly.
Michael.
Greatly.
Please don't cry.
I'm not going to cry.
I feel like it,
but I am not going to.
Why don't you just take
your stupid love contract
and tear it up
into a million pieces?
It was never
a love contract, Michael.
And besides, I've already given
a copy to David
and it would be
just as embarrassing
to get it back from him
as it was handing it to him.
I want the house, Jan!
I want the picket fence.
I want the ketchup fights,
and the tickling,
and the giggling.
I didn't mean it, okay?
I was... I was tired.
Whatever.
I'm tired,
and I didn't eat enough.
You didn't mean it.
And that's all.
That's was it.
That's it, you didn't mean it.
No, I didn't.
So...
That's all, I'm just saying
I didn't mean it.
I love you, Jan.
Okay.
Don't break up, you guys.
You're great together.
Are they gonna call the cops?
No, I paid them off.
Jet Ski money?
All of it.
I'm gonna kill Jim Halpert.