This is ridiculous.
Do you have any idea what
time we'll get out of here?
Nobody likes to work late,
least of all me.
Do you have
plans tonight?
No, I don't.
Remember when you told us not to
make plans, 'cause we were working?
Yes, I remember.
Hmm.
This is BS. This is BS.
Why are we here?
I am gonna call corporate.
Enough is enough. I'm...
God, I'm so mad! This is
Michael Scott, Scranton.
Well, we don't want to work.
No, we don't!
It's not fair
to these people!
These people are my friends,
and I care about them!
We're not gonna do it!
Everybody, I just got off
the horn with corporate,
and basically I told them where they could
stick their little overtime assignment.
Go enjoy your F'riday.
Thank you, Michael.
All right.
Happy F'riday.
Well, I think we dodged a bullet, there.
I think you did.
I think we should
celebrate.
How about you, Pam, mi casa. A
little dinner, dancing, drinks?
Oh, I... You said you
didn't have plans.
That's what you said.
Michael has asked Pam and me
to dinner at least nine times.
And every time, we've been
able to get out of it.
But I've got to give him credit.
He got me.
Because I'm starting
to suspect
that there was no
assignment from corporate.
Michael, what time
should I be arriving?
Dwight, it's couples only.
And besides, I only have six wine glasses.
So it will be me and Jan, and Pam and Jim.
And Angela
and Andy.
Hey, oh!
Does it bother me that I wasn't
invited to Michael's dinner party?
- Hi.
- Hello.
How are you?
Come on in.
Good to see you.
Chilly, huh?
I'm so glad
we finally...
F'inally got to do this
with you guys.
This is great.
You want to take
their coats, babe?
Yes, I would.
Okay.
All right. So, what
have you been doing?
Let's see, since I saw
you an hour ago? Yeah!
I have been getting ready,
and then driving over here.
Well, we've been doing
pretty much the same thing.
Really?
Except driving.
We got you this.
Pam!
Thank you. That's so nice.
Thanks.
This will be great
to cook with. Really.
Well, have a seat,
or come on in, or...
I don't know, make yourself
to home. This is our casa.
- It's really nice.
- It's great.
So, what do you guys think?
Should we do the tour first,
should we have
appetizers first?
Tour. Let's do the tour first.
Okay.
You have a preference,
babe? Upstairs first?
Totally your call, babe. All
right, well, let's go, then.
All right.
I say upstairs.
You guys doing
a little construction?
Oh, just redoing
the sliding glass door.
Yeah, so sorry about this God-awful carpet.
We are still a work in progress, here.
This is my office.
Yup. Never been used.
Not super-exciting.
No.
And this is my work space.
This is it.
Check that out.
You smell that?
Uh-huh.
As you can smell, there's a lot of
different odors going on in here.
So you have an office
and a work space.
I do, you know. I just... I
cannot create in the same space
that I conduct business. I'm sure that
you're the same with your doodles.
Smell.
It's fire.
Bonfire.
Bond!
Men love this one.
James Bond-fire! "I am
Bond-fire... James Bond-fire."
Michael Scott!
When I get frustrated,
or irritated or...
Angry, I come up here and I
just smell all my candles!
And it just... Poof!
Goes away.
Just like that.
So this is the
master bedroom.
And these walls, they used to be,
like, white, like an asylum.
So I wanted it to be softer, so I
had it painted an eggshell white.
Guess what? White and eggshell
white are exactly the same color.
Babe...
Exactly.
I thought you said that you
were gonna tidy things up.
Well, I...
Shame on you.
What a cute bench.
Thanks.
That's my bed.
Jan has some space issues,
so I curl up on that puppy.
Really? 'Cause... It seems
pretty narrow and short.
It's actually a lot bigger than it seems.
Look at this!
See?
He fits perfectly.
I finally
broke down
and bought myself
a plasma TV.
Check it out. I actually hung
this on the wall myself.
That's good. I want to
show you something.
A lot of people in the room,
you need more space...
Voilà.
Right into the wall.
Wow!
Sometimes, I will just
stand here and watch television
for hours. I love it.
I love this TV. And I
also built this table.
What is that,
chestnut?
No, I think that is either
pine or Nordic cherry.
It's pine. Yeah.
Michael, I'm just terrible at all
this stuff, so that's really cool.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah, he tried to set up my TiVo for me,
but then I didn't have audio for a week.
If you ever need any help,
I'm just a phone call away.
I bet you are.
Well, I saw...
Oh, your Dundies.
I'm surprised they're not out on the
coffee table for everybody to see.
Well, it was between the neon
beer sign and the Dundies.
So I said, "Honey,
keep the trophies."
Oh, honey, I have the best trophy
right here. Aside from my Dundies.
Oh, excuse us for just a second.
I'll get it.
So glad we were finally
able to do this.
So glad we...
No. No.
Okay.
Tuna!
What's up, Tuna? We gonna
have some tuna for dinner?
I bet you're sick of tuna, right?
You probably have tuna every night.
All right.
Tuna.
These are for you.
Oh, how thoughtful.
Very nice.
Except for one flower,
which is for my flower.
Aw.
What am I supposed
to do with this?
Well, how about we do the short
tour, and then I'll start dinner?
Oh, I can help starting
dinner, if you need it.
Oh no, no, no, it's just the Osso Buco,
needs to braise for about three hours.
Everything else
is done.
Three hours from now, or three
hours from earlier, like 4:00?
You know, Pam, in Spain, they often
don't even start eating until midnight.
When in Rome.
You have a preference?
Upstairs first?
Whatever
you say, babe.
F'ollow me.
All right.
How about a toast? Shall I?
Here's to good friends.
Cheers.
Mmm.
A sort of an
oaky afterbirth.
What was that?
Music? Should we turn
some music on?
That sounds good.
Do you guys remember
my old assistant, Hunter?
He is an excellent songwriter. Wait
until you hear this. Okay, here we go.
You know what? Hunter was
a terrible assistant.
That is why
Ryan fired him.
Well, I think he's probably
just about as reliable as Pam,
being that it usually takes you
an afternoon to get back to me.
Sometimes I think
she holds on to faxes.
I don't care what they say about me.
I just want to eat.
Which I realize
is a lot to ask for
at a dinner party.
Cow. No, it's a hump,
there's a hump.
Joe Camel! Joe Camel! Yes!
Okay, yes. F'irst
name of that animal,
and the second name is the state
where Helena is the capital.
Montana.
Joe Montana?
Yes! Yes!
Time's up! All
right, two pieces!
Why didn't you just say
49ers quarterback?
All right, my... my... my... my turn!
My... my... my... my turn!
Babe, can you just, like, really...
What?
You're just, like, really...
What? What?
Could you just simmer down?
Seriously.
I'm just making people laugh.
No.
Yes, I was watching Jim's face.
I was watching Jim.
And he was laughing.
No smile.
Look at him.
He's laughing.
Michael and Jan seem to be
playing their own separate game.
And it's called, "Let's see how
uncomfortable we can make our guests."
And they're both winning. So I
am going to make a run for it.
You'll never guess. I just got
a message from my landlord.
Apparently,
my apartment flooded.
Something with the sprinkler.
Oh, no!
Pam, we should probably get
going and see the damage.
Oh! Okay.
Well, you don't need
two of you to do that.
That's true...
Dinner sounded
delicious.
Pam, I'll see you at home.
Thank you so much.
Oh, Jim, I don't think you're going to
abandon this party here, all by itself.
I don't know, because
everything I own is there.
You can buy new stuff, but
you can't buy a new party.
That's true. That is a great point.
Come on down here.
Sit down on that couch
and be amongst friends,
and we're not gonna think about all
your stuff being destroyed. All right?
Michael, you're up.
Here we go.
This is gonna be fun.
- Ready...
- Go!
All right.
F'irst name is Tom.
No, no, no. No names. No names,
no rhyming, no sound-alikes.
All right, okay. Okay.
You're getting into my head!
F'irst name is blank,
and he goes on a cruise.
He goes on
a Caribbean cruise.
I don't know.
Katie Holmes.
No, but he's married to her!
Oh, Dawson's Creek.
No, it has to be a real person, Jim.
Come on!
No, no, I'm gonna pass.
I'm gonna pass.
Okay!
Rhymes with Parnold Sportsanegger.
No rhyming!
Not really a rhyme.
Another clue!
Okay, he's the governor
of California.
He is the Terminator.
Those aren't helpful.
Tom Cruise!
No!
Time!
God! Does anybody
read the paper?
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm so, so sorry for the
temperature in here.
The sliding glass
door shattered.
So...
It's okay.
It's actually
a really cute story.
Do you want to tell it,
babe, or should I tell it?
I don't like
that story, babe.
Come on!
It's a cute story... Michael ran
through the sliding glass door
because he thought he heard
the ice cream truck.
Stop. Stop it!
I mean, I like ice cream,
okay? Sue me.
Oh, no, don't.
I shouldn't say that jokingly,
because she will sue me.
She loves to sue.
She loves lawsuits.
You know, honey, that door was extremely
clean, and it looked invisible.
You are so right.
You are so right!
Because before I lived here, the
glass was always covered in smudges.
And I moved in and I cleaned it, so
I guess that makes me the devil.
You are! She is! She is the devil!
I'm in hell!
I'm burning.
Help me!
You shouldn't
joke about that.
Is there more wine
in the kitchen?
No, I will get it.
I will get it.
What kind of hostess would I
be if I didn't get my wine?
It's okay, I don't mind. No, no, no.
In fact, you know what?
Girls' trip. Angela,
come on. Girls' trip.
Oh, not even close.
So, you keep
a very tidy house.
You should see our bathroom
after Michael takes a bath.
But I don't have
to tell you, Pam.
Oh, yeah...
What?
Oh, don't tell me that he's really
changed since you guys dated.
Oh, are you joking?
No, Michael told me a little bit about
it, but I see the way you look at him.
I have never, ever dated
or wanted to do anything
resembling dating Michael, ever.
Not ever, not now, not then,
not now, not ever, ever.
I've noticed how you look
at him at the office.
Mmm-hmm.
So, I spend most of my time right here.
Have a hand.
So, Jim, I noticed you
checking out Jan's candles.
Oh, no, she just put it
in front of my face.
Yeah, did you know
that candles
are the number-one fastest-growing
product in the scent-aroma market?
$2 billion a year industry.
And for only $10,000,
you could become a co-owner
of "Serenity by Jan."
What do you think about that?
Thought about it. I'm in.
I'm sorry, are you really trying to
get us to invest in Jan's company?
I'm sorry.
What now?
Coming.
Hello.
What are you
doing here?
We came here to eat dinner and to party.
This is a dinner party, right?
Awesome!
What is he doing here?
Yes, what are
you doing here?
Dwight is my friend.
We weren't invited?
You said that I could not invite Dwight
because he was not part of a couple,
and because we didn't have
enough wine glasses.
Dwight brought glasses
and a person.
F'ine.
Whatever you want.
Just like always.
Whatever I want?
It's never whatever I want.
It's fine, Michael. When
I wanted to see Stomp
and you wanted
to see Wicked,
what did we see?
We saw Wicked...
When I said that
I wanted to have kids,
and you said that you wanted me to
have a vasectomy, what did I do?
And then, when you said that
you might want to have kids,
and I wasn't so sure, who
had the vasectomy reversed?
And then when you said you
definitely didn't want to have kids?
Who had it reversed back?
Snip, snap! Snip, snap!
Snip, snap!
I did!
Okay...
You have no idea the physical toll that
three vasectomies have on a person!
And I bought this condo
to fill with children.
I am so sorry
that I don't want to bring kids
into this screwed-up world.
Okay? But look...
I'm sorry, too.
- If you want to have kids, then fine, you win.
- Let's have a kid!
Do you mean it?
You want to have a kid?
I hate my life.
So, can we come in?
Mmm.
Great turkey leg.
Okay, I'm just gonna
check on dinner.
Angela, would you like
some of my beet salad?
I hate beet salad.
It's actually
really good.
Hey, hey, hey.
I know you love beet salad. I've
seen you eat it many times.
The thought of popping one of your beets
into my mouth makes me want to vomit.
Pam...
I hope she didn't
do anything to the food.
Like what?
I can't prove it,
but I think she might
be trying to poison me.
Hey,
looks great, babe.
Yeah,
it really does.
I know Jan didn't poison the food.
I know that.
But if she was going to poison the
food of someone at that table,
wouldn't it be me?
Michael's former lover.
Can you not do that?
It's disgusting.
You know I have soft teeth.
How could you say that?
Oops.
Excuse me
for a second.
So, how do you guys
know each other?
I was his babysitter.
And now you guys
are dating?
Purely carnal, that's
all you need to know.
Would you write down your e-mail?
Because I have, just,
so many questions.
E-mail?
Never mind.
Okay.
All right.
There we go.
There.
Okay.
That's nice. Everybody
enjoying their meal?
- Hey, babe.
- Yeah.
How about we take the beer sign
down until our guests leave,
and then we can
discuss it?
No, no. I'm gonna leave it up. I think
it ties the whole room together.
Okay.
Jan thinks Hunter's
very talented.
You know what? I don't
think he's that good.
At least he's an artist.
BF'D, I'm a screenwriter.
And I'm a candle maker, but you
don't hear me bragging about it!
No, all you do is you get me to
try to work on my rich friends.
F'or an investment
opportunity!
Man, I would love
to burn your candles!
You burn it,
you buy it!
Oh, good, I'll be
your first customer!
You're hardly my first.
That's what she said!
That is a $200 plasma screen
TV that you just killed!
Good luck
paying me back
on your zero-dollars-a-year
salary plus benefits, babe!
I'm gonna get going.
F'ine, get out of here.
It's getting late.
We should...
You know what, you guys? She'll
be out of the bathroom soon.
Of course.
Get out of my way.
I'll take care of this.
Okay, what seems to be
the problem, Officers?
Not now, Dwight. We got a
call about a disturbance.
No. Nope.
Nothing disturbing here.
Just a couple of friends having
an awesome dinner party.
Your neighbors say
they heard some shouting.
Yes, there was
screaming, but...
My girlfriend threw a Dundie
at my TV, plasma.
You want to
press charges?
Would she get
into trouble?
Yeah, she'd
be charged.
I will take the fall.
I did it.
You know, you don't have to press charges.
You could just try to be more quiet.
Michael!
Yes.
Wait, what are
you doing to him?
Sir, do you have any other
place you could stay?
Maybe with one
of your friends, here?
Michael can come
home with me.
Jim, Pam?
Oh, my apartment's
on fire.
F'looded.
You people!
Come on, you're sleeping with me.
No.
I'm gonna take you home, Michael.
All right.
Bye, babe!
This is the best burger
I've ever had, babe.
Babe, I should have told you, but...
I did something bad.
I stole this.
F'or you, babe.
One night
I love that.