Yeah, that's no problem.
Pam.
Sure.
Pam, knock knock.
I'm on the phone.
I know you are. Knock knock.
You can fax it over.
Yeah, 5-7-0-5-5-5...
4-9-1...
...0-1...
...7-4...
...7-5.
Five-ling.
0-1 -7-5.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
That really makes us
look unprofessional.
They would never know
it was me doing it.
Here we go. Knock knock.
Who's there?
Buddha.
Buddha who? Buddha this
bread for me, won't you?
Great. I need something
to wipe my hand.
Now, there's butter on my desk.
That was melting.
It was a classic.
I got a knock knock joke.
No. God.
Michael, please,
please, please.
Please let me.
All right.
Knock knock.
Who's there?
KGB.
KG...
We will ask the questions.
What the hell was that?
- What are you doing?
Hey, hey! Stop it! Stop it! Hey! Come on!
You like that? You like that?
What are you doing? Mine was
part of a hilarious joke!
Mine was retribution.
What are you doing?
No more knock knock jokes.
That's it.
Ding dong.
Who's there?
KGB.
Dwight, get the door.
I'm not answering it.
Answer the door.
Ding dong.
- No way. It's the KGB.
- Ding dong.
I'm not answering that.
Yes, you're going to.
You answer it!
I'm not going to answer it.
Ding dong. I'm not going to answer it.
It's the KGB.
The KGB will wait for no one!
It's true.
Good morning, Michael.
No, no, no.
I am not Michael.
I am Willy Wonka!
Good morning, Mr. Wonka.
Here are your messages.
Why, thank you very much.
What are those? What are those?
Tell me, please.
Jellybeans.
No, no, no.
They are not just ordinary
jellybeans, little girl.
These are extraordinary
jellybeans.
The Willy Wonka
golden-ticket promotional idea
is probably the best idea
I have ever had.
It's probably the best idea
anybody's ever had.
Three days ago,
I slipped five pieces of gold paper
into random paper shipments.
This entitles the customer
to 10% off of their total order.
It will be a day for them that is full
of whimsy and full of excitement.
And full of fantasy.
I've written these things
because it is my responsibility
as manager of this branch
to profiligate great ideas.
And I think I have done my part
with the golden-ticket promotion.
Now it is your turn.
I want to hear some great ideas from
you that are just as good as mine.
We own our own
delivery trucks.
We could lease them out on the weekends...
Too many words.
Good ideas are simple,
golden ticket.
Free paper.
No, Jim.
We're a business. Post-its,
that is a golden-ticket idea.
NASA took five or six golden-ticket
ideas to get men on the moon.
Golden Girls. That's
a golden-ticket idea. Right?
I mean, how great
was that show?
Golden Grahams.
Another. It's a...
I don't get this.
No, you don't. No. It...
What will be
the state of this company
if I am the only one coming up
with the great ideas, right?
I think I should call her.
No. No. No.
Why is it so bad for me to call
and ask her to lunch today?
You're making
it too easy for her.
You're just conveying, "I like
you just the way you are."
But I do like her
just the way she is.
Well, that's not
what we agreed on.
What are you doing?
Why don't you just
go on a date with her?
Try to spark up an ongoing joke
and then, in a month or two,
if it feels right, you'll know.
No.
You don't have
to wait that long.
I mean, you don't have to wait a month
to ask her out. Just ask her out.
You're asking him
to give up all of his power.
What power?
Andy, Pam and Jim
are all telling me
how to deal with this
girl that I like, Lynn.
I don't like getting advice from
more than one person at a time.
I'm a textbook over-thinker.
You can't let a girl feel good about
herself. It will backfire on you.
Every compliment
has to be backhanded.
"I like your dress, but I'd like
it more if you had prettier hair."
That's psychotic.
Do guys
actually do that?
Guys with girlfriends don't.
That's low, Tuna.
Hey, Tom. What's that?
Oh, you found
a golden ticket.
One of my clients
found a golden ticket.
Yeah.
No, congratulations
about that.
Yeah, I'll take that down right now.
Tell me,
was it a spoiled
little girl
with big lips?
I'm on the phone.
Or an odd little boy
with a cowboy obsession?
Hold on one sec.
Invite them on the tour.
It's actually Blue Cross
from Pennsylvania. Really?
Yeah. That's kind
of a big client.
Hey, Oscar.
How much of a hit is 10%
of our Blue Cross account?
10%?
Yeah.
They're our largest client.
- That's going to hurt.
- Hold on one sec.
Hold on one sec, Tom.
What's that?
You found
five golden tickets?
And does it say
limit one per customer?
Nope. It doesn't.
How do you not spread out the
tickets into different shipments?
I thought I did,
so no harm, no foul. Okay, well
I'm going to go call corporate
to make sure that they know
I didn't lose half my sales.
You didn't. It'll be fine.
It'll be good.
Hey, hey, hey. You idiot.
Start over.
Sir, I placed a bunch of golden
tickets into five separate boxes
and somehow they all
ended up at Blue Cross.
How does this happen?
Were the boxes
near each other?
Irrelevant.
I put three pallets on the truck
to Blue Cross once a week.
They use a lot of paper.
Okay, I'm going to ask you something,
and I want you to be honest.
What is a pallet?
My golden-ticket idea, okay.
Why would anyone think that
this is my golden-ticket idea?
There's a one in 13 chance that this
could be anybody's golden-ticket idea.
That...
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Hi, David.
No, I'm sorry. He's not back
from the civil rights rally.
I'll have him call you the minute he
gets back from the Lincoln Memorial.
When Michael's skirting a phone call, he
gave me a list of places to say he is.
"Stopping a fight
in the parking lot.
"An Obama fashion show."
Whatever that is.
Or "Trapped in an oil painting."
I'm going to save that one.
Nobody panic.
The good news is
they can't fire all of us, right?
They can.
No, they can't.
Yes, they can.
Well, Oscar, you don't know what
the hell you're talking about.
Michael, what do you think
shutting down a branch is?
All right,
then we're screwed.
I am just a net that traps all of
your crappy subconscious ideas
and adds a little bit of my own
childhood memories and whimsy so...
Okay, well, I lost
a ton of money today.
And I have a mortgage,
so I'm a little pissed, too.
Thank you.
Jim is with me.
Absolutely not.
I'm mad at you.
Well, you know what, Jim, it is not my fault
that you bought a house to impress Pam.
- That is why carnations exist.
- That's not why.
Okay, we need a gold-ticket idea
to get us out of this mess. Yes?
Does that mean an idea that
blows up in our faces later?
Good one.
Okay, don't get that. Please.
I've got
a golden-ticket idea.
Why don't you skip on up
to the roof and jump off?
That is not constructive.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Oh, hi, David.
He's having a colonoscopy.
All right. I'll find out
if he's out yet.
Hello, David. I just got back
from my procedure, so...
Michael, what the hell
is going on here?
How are you doing?
Fine. What is going on?
My colonoscopy
was an examination
of my large colon
and the distal part of my
small bowel with a camera.
Why did you okay
this golden-ticket idea?
We're going to lose a fortune, Michael.
How could you let this happen?
Well, there is an explanation that
involves me not letting it happen,
and I just don't...
I don't know.
How could you
not know, Michael?
I think we might have hired an
outside marketing consultant.
You might have...
Okay, what firm?
You're breaking up.
Michael.
Okay. I think it might have
been an inside consultant.
Was it the sales department?
Yes.
Was it Jim?
No.
Okay. Was it Dwight?
Yes.
Come on in. Good to see you.
Have a seat.
I just wanted to congratulate you
on that great golden-ticket idea.
That was your idea.
Whoa, wow, who told you that?
You did.
No.
Several times.
I don't think I ever did.
Over and over again.
That was your idea, Dwight. You
were dressed as Willy Wonka.
I'm not taking credit for that.
So... Wasn't my idea.
Would love to, but I can't.
Wait a second, wait a second.
Wait a second. I wrote
it down in my diary.
You don't keep a diary. Yes, I do.
You've just never seen it.
March 4th, "Dwight came up with the
best idea today about golden tickets."
Hold on.
March 4th,
"Michael Scott came up with golden-ticket
idea to give five customers
"10% off for one year."
Why do you have a diary?
To keep secrets
from my computer.
Okay, you know what,
you came up with this idea.
I remember you told me that you
loved the Willy Wonka movie
when you were growing up.
Impossible.
Yes, you did. I wasn't
given candy as a child,
so a movie that fetishized it that
much would've made no sense to me.
Plus, we weren't allowed
to see movies, so do the math.
What are you writing?
"Had conversation with Michael about taking
credit for an idea that wasn't mine.
"Discussed movies."
Would you like to go to lunch with me?
Just the two of us?
With all my heart.
You guys are throwing
a lot at me.
Well, all I'm saying is it's the first
date, so just keep a respectful distance.
Right.
I don't think Jim means to say
that you shouldn't touch her.
No, that is what I mean.
Kevin, a playful touch on
the arm or on the back,
it can show your interest,
and it's really romantic.
Like that?
No. Stop it.
Don't touch her, don't talk
to her, don't look at her.
He wants to be more than just friends.
Put your heart out there,
it's liable to just turn into
this blackened, carbon brick,
where it has barbeque sauce
of shame and rage.
And two hot people
with a perfect relationship
would not understand that.
We think a lot alike.
Sometimes you will think something,
and I will say what you're thinking.
Okay, what am I thinking
right now?
Nacho chips.
No.
I was thinking about how the skin
is the largest organ of the body.
Okay. Let me just cut
to the chase, Dwight.
I want you to fall
on your sword for me.
Oh, not gonna happen.
I did fall
on my sword once.
I was running with it in my belt.
Won't happen again.
Why do you even want to stay at Dunder
Mifflin? I mean, what's the point?
You're cooped up in there all day.
You don't get to do your farming.
You're not dating
Angela anymore.
It doesn't matter if you get fired for
taking credit for the gold-ticket idea.
It doesn't matter.
Me, on the other hand, I would
be lost without this place.
You, way too manly.
What about Shoe La La?
It's not
ready yet.
I have an idea for a fancy men's
shoe store called Shoe La La.
And it's just men's shoes for the
special occasions in a man's life.
Like the day that you get married,
or the day your wife has a baby,
or for just lounging
around the house.
May I have your attention, please?
I have an announcement.
Mr. Dwight Schrute and I just returned
from a wonderful stroll together.
And although I probably will
never do it again, I had fun.
I really had fun with my best friend,
Dwight. These aren't announcements.
Yes, they are. You just don't
care about the information.
I love working here,
and I do not want to leave.
He doesn't love
it that much.
Wouldn't be such a bad
thing for him to be fired.
Well... I mean, like
we were talking about,
that is why he has come
to the conclusion...
We discussed the fact
that I'm cooped up here
instead of experiencing
the whole wide world.
Right. You know,
plowing my own acres.
Going around shirtless all day.
You know, experiencing freedom.
That's it. That's it. You
can't put a price on freedom.
Try me.
That's why you've made the decision.
That's why you made...
I haven't made a decision yet.
You kind of have.
No.
Yes, you have.
You cannot take
the fall for him.
He said he would
do the same for me.
He can do the same for you right now
by getting fired instead of you.
So what are you
going to do?
I'm going to go back to work, after
I write you up for insubordination.
There he is.
Oh, my God. Dwight!
Dwight, get in.
What's it going to be?
What are you going to do?
What's it going to be? Are you
going to do this thing for me?
Dwight?
Hey, David, how are you?
Michael.
Good to see you. Nice surprise.
Hey.
Yeah.
Dwight and I were just having a
very unfortunate conversation.
That's too bad.
Yes, it is. But it had
to be done, didn't it?
Hopefully, nothing that can't be undone
because, Dwight, I owe you an apology.
The head of Blue Cross
just called.
They were so excited
by the golden-ticket discount
that they have decided to make Dunder
Mifflin their exclusive provider
of all office supplies.
Congratulations, Dwight.
David,
you're welcome.
Yeah.
I just want to say
that this golden-ticket idea
is one of the most brilliant signs of
initiative I've ever seen at this company.
And how about a big round of
applause for Mr. Dwight Schrute?
All right, Dwight!
This is huge.
That's what she said.
Hey, Dwight, great idea.
Dwight, Dwight, great idea.
How'd you come up
with that idea?
Inspiration.
Really?
How were you inspired? Never
know when it's going to strike.
How did it pop into your head, Dwight?
Just boom.
Just give me the details
of how that happened.
You're talking to Dwight Schrute,
the biggest Wonka fan I know.
I mean, you've been talking
about that movie for years.
What?
You know what,
I even made fun of you
when you dressed up as Willy
Wonka to pitch this idea,
and, for that,
I apologize.
Apology rejected.
Thanks so much for helping
the company, Dwight.
Oh, Pam.
Good work, kid.
Thanks, old man.
This is...
This is great.
Okay, look, I want to get you on the horn
with the marketing people in New York.
- They should meet you.
- Great idea. Yeah.
Pam, could you set up a call in
there in about 15 minutes, please?
Sure.
David. David.
David. David. 'Cause I've
got this idea for a...
Yeah? Could I be part
of the meeting also?
You probably have
too much to do around here.
I don't want to take up your
time with another meeting.
Yeah, let's face it, this meeting
sounds like it's Wonka fans only.
He's never seen the movie.
All right.
Hey, guys, I have with me Dwight Schrute.
Dwight, take it away.
Okay, guys, listen up. Here's the deal.
I love candy, sweet, sugary candy,
from the second
it touches my tongue
to the moment it's metabolized
by my stomach acid,
so naturally
I liked Willy Wonka.
Wait, do you
guys hear that?
There's not a dog listening in, is there?
I hear panting.
No. No dogs.
So I love Willy Wonka.
The golden-ticket scene
is so inspiring to me
that that's where
I came up with that idea.
There is no movie
called Willy Wonka!
It's called Willy Wonka
& the Chocolate Factory.
It's actually based on a book called
Charlie and the Chocolate Factory.
I can't vouch for that.
Pam.
But I do know this. He is a liar.
He has taken my idea.
That is my idea. We are going
to call you back, guys.
What is going on here? Okay,
here's what happened, David.
It was all my idea.
You called me, and you
were really angry at me,
and I got scared, so I had
Dwight take the fall.
But now it turns out
that it's a great idea,
and Dwight will not confess.
Can you believe that?
No. No.
It is my idea.
How dare you, Dwight?
I'm filled with good ideas.
Are you?
Thousands of good ideas.
You are?
Yeah.
Good ideas?
Hey, did you come up
with Toilet Buddy?
It's a net, a circular net
you put inside the toilet
to catch all of your change and your
wallet from falling into the toilet,
formerly known as Toilet Guard.
Horse Boat.
Oh, please. A canoe
built around your horse
so you can go from riding to water
travel without slowing down.
Horse Boat.
Toilet Sponge.
It's a hollowed out sponge...
Give me a break.
...that is more absorbent
and softer than toilet paper.
I have a lot of toilet ideas.
That's 'cause they're easy.
They're not easy.
Guys. Guys.
Everybody...
Women's urinal.
Everybody has to go to the bathroom!
Enough. Please, enough.
Well, is this true, Dwight?
I mean, is this true?
Yes, it's Michael's idea that he
forced on me on threat of death.
Thank you.
I don't know what... What do you
want me to do now, Michael?
What am I
supposed to do now?
Well, David,
I will be honest with you.
I do want the credit
without any of the blame.
Okay. I am going
back to New York.
Pam, do me a favor,
don't send me those notes.
Okay.
I am gone.
When they look back on this
day in the history books,
all that will be remembered
is that I had a good idea.
And that's what I'm going
to write down in my diary.
And that is what I want
you to write down in yours.
Oh, I am.
In my own words.
I want to see it.
No.
I want to see that.
No, Michael.
Give me the diary.
No. No!
Hi.
Lynn,
I'm just going to say to you
everything that I'm thinking.
Okay. I think you
have the best smile.
I'd like to take you out
to dinner and a movie.
Okay.
Nice...
...boobs.
Well, it's his funeral, so...
Ding dong.
Who is it?
KGB.
All right.
I just got out of the shower.
I'll be one second.
When you are done,
open the door.
Hello in there?
Yeah, I'm late for work
so I have to brush my teeth.
It's a whole routine.
We have other
houses to visit.
If you want to come back,
then that would be fine.
We'll come back at...
How's 4:45?
I get home
from work around 6:00.
How about 5:15?
You can try.
That might work.
Very well, we will
come back at 5:15.
All right.