Wow, you guys
look amazing.
Stanley, I thought
you hated Halloween.
He wears it so he can
sleep at his desk.
Who are you?
I'm Carrie Bradshaw
from Sex and the City.
I like your shoes.
Thank you.
Will you help walk me
to the fax machine?
Sure.
I got her. I got her.
I can help you.
You look amazing.
Inappropriate.
Thank you.
Who are you,
Larry King?
Gordon Gekko.
From the insurance
commercials.
Yeah.
Whoa! Awesome.
Let's put
a smile on that face.
Damn it, Creed.
I've been up since 4:00.
Sweet 'stume, dude.
Who are you
supposed to be?
Dave.
Cool.
And you are?
A cat?
We were looking
for kitten.
Give me one second.
- Jim Halpert.
- Hey.
Hey, New York.
Happy Halloween.
Thanks.
My costume's getting
a lot of attention.
So apparently no one dresses
up for Halloween here.
I wish I had known that
before I used greasepaint
for my mustache,
and I can't even take off my
hat because then I'm Hitler.
Want to see
a magic trick?
I'm going to
make a pencil...
...disappear.
Okay,
I think we are set.
We have puzzles,
string for cat's cradles.
Burned this last night.
Little road-trip CD.
Puppets.
Look at all this stuff.
It's only seven hours.
When corporate found out that
we were dating, they decided
they were going to
transfer Holly back
to her old branch in
Nashua, New Hampshire.
Michael's taking a personal
day to move me out.
Road trip!
Right?
Breaker 1-9, copy?
Copy that, breaker!
Those Duke boys
are at it again.
Hey, do not
touch my radio.
We're not.
Kidding.
We're not doing anything.
It's been a weird week since
we found out I had a transfer.
Michael wanted me to quit and
get some job here in Scranton,
and I said, "Well, why don't you
quit and get some job in Nashua?"
And he said,
"I asked you first,"
and I said first
at the same time he did,
and then I said, "Jinx."
And then we never
talked about it again
and haven't been back
to the conversation, so...
All right, everybody,
I am out of here.
Jim, you are in charge.
I'll walk you out.
You are
quite the gentleman.
You can let people go a couple
minutes early if you want.
All right, we'll see.
I am off to New York.
My brother Pete from Boston and
my brother Tom from New Jersey
are taking Pam and I out for lunch
to celebrate the engagement.
Or maybe to beat me up.
I can never tell
with those two.
Morning, temp.
Morning.
Wow. Good morning, Dwight.
I thought I'd go
casual today.
Morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Hello.
How you doing?
How are you, Phyllis?
That's funny.
Take that sweatshirt off.
Hey, buddy.
Andy.
Do you remember
when I jokingly
yelled at you to take
your sweatshirt off?
Totally joking, but you should
know those colors are sacred.
Not that I care, but if
you're not a Cornell man,
you probably
shouldn't wear them.
No, I get it.
I totally understand, and I
just want to assure you that
I mean no disrespect.
You see, I'm applying.
Come on. You think you
could get into Cornell?
Well, if someone who
barely outsells Phyllis
can get in,
then I should be fine.
I'm sitting
right here, Dwight.
I meant that
as a compliment
to you, Phyllis, as well
as a slight to Andy.
Cornell is a good school,
and I want to better myself
through higher education.
If it makes Andy angry,
so be it.
I have to unpack this weekend,
but maybe next weekend
we go to the outlets.
Cool.
Mike, you driving
this every weekend?
We're going to switch back
and forth with the driving.
Sometimes we'll just meet
in the middle. Be fun.
Wait a sec.
I love this song.
Life is a highway I wanna
ride it all night long
If you're going my way I wanna
drive it all night long
If you're going my way
Hey, there.
So, how do you think we're going
to do against Penn this year?
Nathan Ford's arm
looks pretty strong.
Well, he's had a pretty good season so far.
Stop saying "we."
You did not go
to Cornell, okay?
You're just doing this
to screw with me.
Not so.
Cornell is
an excellent school.
Without
its agricultural program,
we probably
wouldn't have cabbage,
at least
not modern cabbage.
I know it's an
excellent school, Dwight.
I went there.
My blood runs Big Red.
Someday we'll both get
together in Comstock Hall
and just laugh
about all of this.
Hey.
Hey, future baby sis.
How are you, Tom?
Nice to see you.
Good.
I asked Tom and Pete to
come early so we could play
a prank on Jim at lunch.
Pretty awesome, right?
I think
they're into the idea.
They're probably thinking,
"That Pam Beesly,
"she's the coolest
sister-in-law on the planet.
"She's the best,
the absolute best."
Okay, so here's
what I'm thinking.
I'm going to say that before
ceramics class I took off my ring,
and then when I changed
back out of my smock,
it wasn't in my pocket
anymore and I lost it.
That's perfect. You know what
would be even more hilarious?
Remember that
thing we did when
Jim was in high school
with his girlfriend?
Right.
That would be hilarious.
Yeah, we should totally dog
her about being an artist,
never making any money.
That is awesome.
Like, she basically
has a hobby for a job.
Oh, yeah.
So, not the ring, then?
The... Not doing
the ring, though?
This is better. The other
thing will get Jim...
This is nice and it's fun.
It's fun.
Okay, okay.
He hates it when we pick
on his girlfriends.
Okay.
They came up with that
idea really fast.
This trip is longer
than I thought.
Yeah, it did look
shorter on the map.
Hey.
Wow, I was
having a nightmare.
You were sleeping?
Yes.
You were talking before.
Was I?
Really? Was I saying
anything interesting?
Not really.
All right, what's the scoop?
How far?
Four hours.
Almost halfway there.
We're only halfway?
Halfway, okay.
You know what I want to do?
I want to pull over
and find a little
bed and breakfast
for when we
meet in the middle.
Emphasis on the
bed and the breakfast.
Next exit
isn't for 5 miles.
Let's check there.
Hey, guys.
How are you?
Hi.
Good to see you.
Nice to see you
again, Pam.
Pam, I haven't seen
you in so, so long.
All right,
so now we can sit
and get comfortable.
There's nothing
out here, man.
Yeah.
I don't know. I just
imagined a hotel right here,
pool over here,
little breakfast place
with really good bacon.
Just...
Here we go.
Fourth time's the charm.
Life's like a road where...
It's one day here
and the next day there
Sometimes you deal
with the things you don't
Sometimes you... Walk
There's a world
out there...
Hey, are you crying?
No.
Allergies?
Did Darryl touch you?
What?
No. Darryl did not
touch me.
Can we just
keep going, please?
What's the matter?
No. It's not
going to work.
There's too much distance.
Sure it is.
No, no, no. It's going to work.
It'll be fine.
Michael, we've only been dating
each other for a few weeks.
Listen to me,
I like you so much.
I like you, too.
And I've dated almost
four women in the last...
I dated four guys
last year, too.
Not last... No, in,
like, the last 10 years
I've dated almost four women, and you
are so far above them, it is stupid.
Michael, no, don't.
It is...
Don't make it harder
than it has to be.
I'm...
That's what she said.
Holly thinks that
this relationship is over.
Well, you know what?
I am not going to
give up that easy.
I'm going to make this way
harder than it needs to be.
Take that down.
Excuse me?
You know, I once dated a
couple guys from Cornell.
They were really nice.
They gave me a ride home.
I seriously doubt that anyone
from Cornell dated you.
It's pronounced "Colonel." It's
the highest rank in the military.
It's pronounced "Cornell." It's the
highest rank in the Ivy League.
Andy, let's just talk about
this man to man after work.
Fine.
What do you say, okay?
Yeah. Good. Can we...
That's Big Red Bear.
That's a bobble
Big Red Bear. God!
And if you leave
on Friday by 5:00,
you'll be rolling in
at midnight at best...
Yeah.
...and then
sleep in Saturday.
That only leaves us
less than 24 hours
before you have
to go back again.
Okay. Okay.
I will talk to you on the
Bluetooth the entire trip
so we're talking
constantly all the way.
I'll tell you everything that I
see, everything that I pass by,
things that I witness
on the road.
Well...
Maybe I'll see an
accident one weekend.
How long can
we keep that up?
Years.
Years?
Yeah.
Years of just a few
hours every weekend?
Here's my wish,
I want you to meet a great guy
and I want you to be happy.
Thank you.
My wish has come true,
incidentally,
because you've met me
and you are happy.
Clever, Mike.
So, Pam, how much money
does an artist make
after they leave
art school?
Yeah, not a lot of money
in the arts, right?
That's not really true.
There's a lot of things you can
do with an art degree, actually.
Maybe Pam should
pay the check
by drawing a picture
on this napkin.
Wow, that's
a little rude.
What's your deal?
Hey, just having
fun, Jimmy.
Yeah. Right, Pam?
Yep.
You know what? I think
we're a great couple.
I think we are
a classic couple.
I think we are like
Romeo and Juliet.
I think we go together so well.
We're like peanut
butter and jelly.
Don't you think?
I do. I think so, Mike.
Well, then don't do it.
Please don't do this!
Hey, what's up? Just
thought I'd try you.
Thinking about
that story where
you ran into the girl
you used to baby-sit.
I don't know
what I am gonna do.
Please call me back.
Please...
I promise you.
I'm not going to be okay.
Please...
No, I won't.
I'm not strong. I'll go back
to Jan, and I hate Jan.
Oh, God.
You might be...
What?
Dwight...
Andy, I've been
meaning to ask you.
Which a cappella group
should I join?
The Harmoniacs?
Or the Do-Re-Migos?
Assuming you had the voice to be
in any of them, it's irrelevant,
because I called admissions
and it looks like
I will be conducting
your university interview.
That's a conflict
of interest.
Yeah. Big one.
So should I not
let you in now?
Or do you want to
do the interview
and then
I won't let you in?
Interview.
Excellent.
When the hour glass strikes
3:00, then in the room
whence employees confer.
What?
The conference room.
Okay.
Who are your role models?
If I had to put Dwight's
chances into a percentage,
I would say he has
none percent chance.
So, Dane Cook,
Jack Bauer and Eli Whitney.
You're doing great.
Life is a highway
I wanna ride it
all night long
Oh, wow. This is
my niece Vanessa.
She's a trumpeter,
and look at her.
Cute.
That must be really fun
for you and Marci, huh?
Yep.
She only knows how to play When
the Saints Go Marching In.
I love that one.
Yeah, but
she doesn't think
she's going to be, like,
a career musician, right?
Here we go again.
What is your deal today?
I'm just saying how
many famous trumpeters
can you name
besides Louis Armstrong?
Miles Davis.
One.
Chet something.
Half.
The point is, Pam,
that there are jobs...
Dizzy Gillespie.
Also good.
...and there are hobbies. I love
baseball more than anything,
but you don't see me
trying to get on the Mets.
You don't. Pete, you
couldn't make the Mets.
She's at Pratt.
You played JV baseball.
Will you lighten up
a little bit?
I'm just calling it
like I see it.
I don't know if I'm
going to make any money
with art.
Pam, don't worry about it.
I mean, it's a very competitive
field, but I have a professor
who says that I have
a lot of promise,
and if I don't try now,
I never will, so...
Guys, what is going on?
We pranked you.
It was Pam's idea.
Pam was the mastermind.
Got you.
That was killer.
I was so close to blowing it.
Let's see how well you
know your Big Red history.
Bring it.
Who was Cornell's
eighth president?
Dale Raymond Corson.
I'm sorry, that's incorrect. Cornell's
seventh president was, in fact,
James A. Perkins.
"Comprehension
skills subpar."
"Interviewing skills,
subpar."
What are you writing?
You can't even give Cornell
your full attention.
On the contrary,
I'm helping Cornell
by evaluating
their interviewers.
Nobody wants that
to happen.
Well, when they get
my evaluation,
we'll see
if they're interested.
"Applicant is attempting
to blackmail interviewer,
"showing
low moral character."
"Interviewer is
threatening applicant
"with an arbitrary
review process."
"Applicant is
wasting everyone's time
"with stupid and
inane accusations."
"Interviewer has
suspect motives."
"Applicant has a head shaped
like a trapezoid."
"Interviewer has turned off
applicant's interest in Cornell
"and they are going to go to the
vastly superior Dartmouth."
Ever heard of it?
I think I have
everything I need.
You'll be hearing from the
Cornell Application Department.
And you will be hearing from the
And you will not be
pleased with the result!
And your affiliation with
Cornell will end completely.
That is all, sir.
You may go.
There's another dolly
in the truck, Mike.
You can take
more than that lamp.
For the record, I wanted
to go another direction,
which was way better.
Well, I'll be the judge of that.
What do you got?
Okay, I lost
my engagement ring
in ceramics class,
left it in my smock.
I had this whole thing
where I go back to class,
wrongly accuse another girl.
Look, I even used makeup
to put a ring
around my finger.
You can hardly see it.
It's very subtle.
That is good.
Thank you.
Truthfully,
anything would have been
better than
that prank.
Text message from my brother. "Pam cool.
Welcome to the family."
Hey, how about
at Thanksgiving
we "prank" Tom
about being bald?
This is the last of it.
That's mine, actually.
Maybe put it
back in the truck.
You're not staying?
You know,
I have some things
I need to do this weekend.
I just remembered, so...
I'll just ride back
with you.
But you want me to put
it back in the truck?
I'll be down in just a sec.
Holly?
So...
I think I'm going to
go back with Darryl.
Okay.
Bye.
Okay, bye.
I know it's hard, Mike.
Breakups hurt.
We didn't break up.
Looked like it.
Sometimes when I'm down like this,
it helps to sing the blues.
Okay.
That's a really
pretty song.
No, no,
check it out, look.
When I do that...
Okay.
...that's when you hit me
with what's getting you down.
All right.
No, wait,
you're supposed to...
Never mind.
Yeah.
Well, I thought I'd
come in casual today.
Man, hungry. Anyone
else feel like a beet?
Where did you get those?
What, these?
Bernard Farms. Best
beets in the state.
I see what you are doing,
but I do not know where
you are going with this.
Well, you will as soon as
you visit my new beet farm.
You're supposed to
cook these, aren't you?
Cornell.