It's 4:30 in the morning. Do
you know where your kids are?
If you are Ryan's parents or Pam's
parents or my parents, you do.
They're going to be
in this van, with me.
Who am I?
Nothing to fear.
I am just a 44-year-old guy
with a paper route.
Time to make
the doughnuts!
Come on!
No, I promise
I won't do it again.
Come on.
I lied!
We've been making 5:00 a.m.
deliveries for a couple weeks now.
Ever since I've gotten clean, there's
something about fresh morning air
that just really
makes me sick.
Hello! Time
to make the doughnuts!
Oh, Halpert, wow!
Boner patrol!
Arrest that man!
Your doughnuts
make me go nuts!
Hey, Pam.
We got the van
at a used car lot.
We think it says "Hallelujah
Church of Scranton" in Korean.
It was either this or an old school
bus with an owl living in it.
You didn't happen to bring any
coffee, did you, Michael?
Milk and sugar.
Oh, awesome.
You're a lifesaver.
Wait, is this
just milk and sugar?
That's what I said.
Do you drink
this every day?
Every morning.
We're...
We're doing okay.
A couple weeks in,
and we're having fun.
Yep, we have 20 of those...
Oh, excuse me! Sorry!
Sorry, no, it's...
It's a paper company now.
It's not for the church.
Okay, who covers
Van's Pet Grooming?
Oh, they're my client.
No, they were your client.
They just called and said
they were switching over
to Michael Scott
Paper Company.
Shame, Jim.
I expected more.
In the last month, we have lost 10
major clients to Michael Scott.
What are we supposed to do? They
keep undercutting us on price.
I don't want to hear excuses.
I want to see improvements.
This is unacceptable.
Hey, boss, I'd just
like to point out
that I have been here
less time than these guys.
Why are you telling me this?
I just think the bar should
be lower for a newbie.
Is that something you
really want to have said?
I don't want
to have said that.
But I think it's important
that you know it.
I don't know what to do
to inspire these people, okay?
Maybe it's my fault.
It's not your fault.
Some people just don't
want to be inspired.
I wrote a memo to all departments
asking them to find ways to save money.
But...
Charles.
I got your memo. Thank you.
I want you to know, I'm putting my foot
down when it comes to expense reports.
Waste not, want not.
Well said, Angela.
Been there, done that.
You know what we need?
We need some couches in here.
Michael, we should really
consider getting a delivery guy.
Oh, know what you would love?
Is if we built a loft.
Why would I love that?
Can we afford
a delivery guy?
Like in a dorm room,
you put your desk underneath,
you have your loft up top,
you can sleep up top.
Yeah, I know
what a loft is.
Most dorm rooms
don't even have that.
Most do in the magazines.
Let's see what
a delivery guy costs.
We should look into that.
Or we just go for the loft.
Hi.
Could you let Charles know
that David is here, please?
Jim, hey.
Hey, David.
David Wallace! Hello, we've been
expecting you, David Wallace.
Charles and I
were waiting for you.
There he is! There he is!
How was the trip up?
A lot better than a month at the
Scranton Radisson, I'm sure.
Oh, you know what?
It hasn't been that bad.
Hasn't been that bad. These people
are the salt of the Earth down here.
You couldn't ask for a better
way to learn a company.
I feel like I should
be thanking you.
The conference room is ready,
if we want to get started.
You know, I just want
to address everyone first.
Oh, yeah, take your time.
Stanley, pay attention.
Hi, everyone.
Hi.
Hi. Look, it's no secret...
Hello. It is no secret
that Michael Scott Paper
has siphoned off a large
chunk of our core business,
and I'm here, I just want
to reassure everyone
that we think this is
just a temporary setback.
Right.
Okay?
Maybe, and I don't know, if you'd
just returned Michael's call,
none of us would
have lost clients.
I've been wondering
that myself lately.
We're just going to get started,
we're going to figure this out.
Rest assured. Jim, can you
come in with us, please?
Oh, Jim, hold on.
You know, David, Dwight's
been my guy, okay?
Yeah, Jim...
Really? I find that
extraordinarily surprising.
He shows promise.
And Jim, I don't...
He's been a disappointment.
We'll bring them both in.
Okay, great.
Dwight,
come on in. Also, Jim.
Come along, afterthought.
How much can we afford
to pay a delivery guy?
Well, if these numbers
you gave me are correct...
They
are correct, sir.
Then you can't afford
to pay him anything.
Okay.
A lame attempt at humor.
Swing and a miss.
Your prices are too low.
Lowest in town.
Why do you think Staples and Dunder
Mifflin can't match your prices?
Corporate greed?
Look, our pricing model is fine.
I reviewed the numbers myself.
Over time, with enough volume,
we become profitable.
Yeah, with a fixed-cost pricing
model, that's correct...
Yeah.
But you need to use a
variable-cost pricing model.
Okay, sure...
Right. So...
Why don't you explain what
that is, so they can...
Just explain what that is.
Explain what you think that is.
Okay.
Just explain it.
As you sell more paper and your
company grows, so will your costs.
For example, delivery man, health
care, business expansion...
Whatever. Yeah, so...
At these prices, the more paper you
sell, the less money you'll make.
Our prices are the only thing
keeping us in business.
They're actually putting
you out of business.
Okay, okay.
Hold on, hold on.
Ty, I would like you to
crunch those numbers again.
It's a program.
There's no such thing as...
Just crunch them.
Just crunch them, please.
Crunch.
Did it help?
Hi, Jerry. Michael Scott.
Well, this is
slightly embarrassing.
I'm going to have to ask you to
pay me a little bit more money
for that delivery
we dropped off yesterday.
Yeah, we did.
We got the check.
But we're just going to need
a much, much bigger check.
When a child gets behind the wheel
of a car and runs into a tree,
you don't blame the child.
He didn't know any better.
You blame the 30-year-old woman
who got in the passenger seat
and said,
"Drive, kid. I trust you."
Now, would corporate approve a temporary
price reduction for returning customers?
God, no.
That's stupid.
Yeah, it makes us
look weak.
I agree. It just...
I say we fill Michael's office with bees.
My apiarist owes me a favor.
Really?
Does he do good work or...
No, Jim,
I use a bad apiarist.
Fellows, why don't
we take a five-minute break?
And then we will come back,
start fresh, sort this out.
Five minutes
exactly. Okay.
Hey, Dwight, can I talk to you?
Sure thing.
Hey, I saw you called.
You're just
out of business?
We have maybe a month.
I don't know
what I'm going to do.
Oh, yeah, well, don't worry about it.
We'll figure it out. We'll be okay.
That's what Michael said.
Oh, yeah, well, only this
time we will be okay.
Idiot.
Idiot. Idiot.
That's my new Dwight ring.
I like it.
Good, right? Hello?
Idiot, we're starting back up.
This is Dwight, by the way.
Oh, okay.
Don't worry about it.
Did I ever tell you about the
day that Steve Martin died?
Steve Martin's not dead, Michael.
I know.
But I always thought that the day that he
died would be the worst day of my life.
And I was wrong.
It's this.
You want to hear
something sad?
I would love that.
So Jim and I are getting married,
and the wedding's really expensive,
so I tried to get a job on the
weekends to earn extra money.
I applied to Old Navy,
Target and Walmart.
None of them
called me back.
Not even
for an interview.
I never went to Thailand.
Really?
I went to Fort Lauderdale.
Was it nice?
Yeah, it was amazing.
There is a great
pad thai place, though.
I love pad thai.
You never had pad thai.
No.
There's a lot
I haven't done.
Now, this is a projection
of over three months.
We still have the retail...
Well, that's assuming that...
Hey, let me float
something out there, okay?
Can I just say...
Can I say something?
There is a hive of bees
outside the front door.
We kidnap the queen,
extract her alarm pheromones,
place them on a flushable wipe
and put that in his bathroom.
I can't believe I'm about to say
this, but the cheapest option
is to make Michael an offer.
Yes. Yes, I was going to say the
same thing. We can buy him out.
- Oh, but you didn't.
- Oh, man!
If only Michael had children. That's
how you really apply the pressure.
What
is wrong with you?
Jim, you're pretty close with them. You
think they'd be up for hearing an offer?
Oh, I don't know. You know, they've
taken a good deal of clients, so...
I mean, I guess I could go down there and
try to nudge them in the right direction.
You know what?
Why don't I do it, okay?
Michael adores me. I'm the man for this
job. Charles, you got my back on this?
No. Jim, I think
you should go.
Okay. So I'll be back in...
Back in a bit.
Hey. Can I talk to you
guys for a second?
We're not hiring, Jim. Actually
here for something else.
Listen, I can't make
you laugh right now.
You know I love
a good guessing game,
but why don't I just tell
you what I'm here for?
Turns out you guys have made a pretty
big dent in the Dunder Mifflin sales.
Oh, that's nice.
David Wallace has asked me
to come down here,
and see if you would be interested
in Dunder Mifflin buying you out.
Seriously?
Are you being serious?
He's bluffing, Pam.
Jim, what you don't understand
is that this company's worth...
No.
We don't have...
See, I'm here to learn as
little information as possible.
All I really need to hear is if
your incredibly successful company
would be receptive
to a buyout.
Yes.
Maybe.
Three yeses.
I will see you
titans of industry upstairs.
Yes, well, we are not only tight
ends, we are also quarterbacks.
I missed
the last part.
That's a pun.
Got it.
Yep.
Oh, wow.
Okay, so you're not going to reveal
in any way that we're broke?
Of course not.
That we're having any
problems at all. Nope.
Right, just to reiterate, none
of us is going to say anything
that might indicate
we are going broke.
Right, right, there is no way in hell
that I am going to say that we're broke.
Oh, I'm really worried
I'm going to say it.
No, Michael.
No, man.
You're...
You're fine.
We have to come from a
position of strength.
Yeah, just put it out of your mind.
It is.
I'm good.
Hello.
Hi.
Michael Scott Paper Company
to see Mr. David Wallace.
I believe
we're expected.
Well, well, well,
how the turntables...
Michael, in order to
expedite these negotiations,
we are prepared to make you
a very generous offer.
And we are prepared
to reject that offer.
Michael, you haven't
even heard...
Never accept
their first offer.
What is your second offer?
$12,000.
Are you kidding me?
That is insultingly low.
I don't even want to hear
what your first offer was.
What do you hear?
Here's the situation. Your
company is four weeks old.
I know this business. I know
what suppliers are charging.
I know you can't be
making very much money.
I don't know how your prices are so low.
But I know it can't keep up that way.
I'm sure you're scared,
probably in debt.
That's the best offer
you're going to get.
I'll see your situation, and
I'll raise you a situation.
Your company is losing
clients left and right.
You have a stockholder meeting coming up and
you're going to have to explain to them
why your most profitable
branch is bleeding.
So they may be looking for a
little change in the CFO.
So I don't think I need
to wait out Dunder Mifflin.
I think I just
have to wait out you.
Okay, now, I don't know that I can get this.
I do have to go to the board for approval.
How's about $60,000?
$60,000.
Michael?
We're going to have to talk about this.
Just amongst ourselves.
Okay, done.
Please, take the room.
We're outside.
Take your time.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
$60,000?
We are so rich.
Are you
kidding me?
Well, Jerry, the one
who got away.
May I ask why you're leaving the
Michael Scott Paper Company?
Really?
Please hold.
Charles...
Dwight.
May I have your attention?
The Michael Scott
Paper Company is broke.
What? How'd
you hear that?
They've been calling all their clients
and begging them to pay more money.
That can only mean one thing.
They're desperate.
Which can only mean one thing.
They are total failures.
Great work, Dwight.
Quiet, you.
No, I mean,
great detective work,
'cause this must be the first
case you've ever cracked, right?
You don't "crack a case." That
has a pejorative connotation.
It's like calling
a policeman a cop.
You solve a case, and,
yes, I've solved plenty.
So, how long
can they stay viable?
What are your top
five cases?
I'm going to answer
Charles first.
Because he's solved
zero cases.
Okay, one,
Case of the Beet Bandit.
Missing beets from all over
the farm, no footprints.
Inside job, Mose in socks.
Boom, case closed.
Okay, do not go anywhere
near the conference room.
Done.
Because you have embarrassed
me for the last time today.
Got it?
I'm not following you.
You two are morons.
Got it.
Get out.
So, you've thought it over, yes?
And you accept our offer?
We can finally put
this whole thing behind us?
No.
Can you give us another
minute, please?
Yeah.
Okay.
Michael... How could you
do this to me, Michael?
You just cost me
$60,000.
Why are you assuming
you'd get the whole thing?
It's a lot of money, okay? But we
need money coming in every week.
We need jobs.
Wouldn't you rather have
a fishing pole than a fish?
I would rather have
$60,000, honestly.
No, Michael's right.
Jobs are safer.
Agreed?
Agreed.
Yeah.
But that's all, okay?
Yeah, discuss
these things...
Hello?
I want my old job back, I want
my old parking space back,
I want a Sebring...
They don't make them anymore.
I can...
And I want Charles gone.
I'm not firing Charles.
He's very valuable.
That's very kind
of you to say, David.
I need him gone.
No.
Okay, then
I want Pam back.
You already have
a new receptionist.
Sales.
Thank you.
Pam's not a salesperson.
Yes, she is, at the Michael Scott
Paper Company in its heyday.
That's right.
Okay.
Please continue.
And Ryan.
Ryan cost Dunder Mifflin hundreds
of thousands of dollars, Michael.
You know...
Ryan...
David, I don't care if Ryan
murdered his entire family.
He is like a son to me.
Do you realize
what you're asking for here?
You're talking about salary,
plus health benefits...
And dental this time.
Insurance, taxes, social
security for three people?
This is a heck of a lot
more than 60 grand.
You're talking about
a multi-million dollar buyout.
These are our demands.
Your company cannot
be worth that much.
Our company is
worth nothing.
That's the difference
between you and I.
Business isn't about
money to me, David.
If tomorrow my company goes under, I
will just start another paper company,
and then another
and another and another.
I have no shortage
of company names.
Michael...
That's one of them.
Yes. These are our demands.
This is what we want.
Our balls are in your court.
Okay, deal.
Okay?
Can we have
the room, please?
Yeah.
Can you
believe it?
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
- Oh, my God!
That's what
I'm talking about!
There are certain defining
moments in a person's life.
The day he's born, the day he grows
hair, the day he starts a business,
and the day he sells that
business back to Dunder Mifflin.
What have
I learned from all of this?
It is far too early to tell.
I just know that I am flying high, and
I don't even want to think about it.
I just want to enjoy it.
Hey, guys...
No. No, you're done.