Hi.
Good morning.
Can I help you?
Yes. I'm from Tech Star, about
a new phone system for you.
I was wondering if I could
talk to Michael Scott?
I'm sorry.
He's not in right now.
Really? He's never
around when I come by.
Shoot.
They have new
phone systems now
that can ring
directly to a salesman,
or someone presses star
and they go to accounting.
Basically, 95% of my job.
But I'd like to see a machine
that puts out candy for everyone.
Vending machine.
How about I make an
appointment to come back?
That way I know
he'll be here.
That is a great idea.
Great.
Oh, boy! Let's see.
He's really...
Michael Scott, manager.
Hi, how are you?
Hi.
There he is.
Nice to meet you.
Great. Look at that.
I can assure you we don't
need a new system, though.
We're happy with ours.
Hello. May I help you?
Jim-bo.
Jim.
Aye!
Okay. I'm going
to get going then.
Aye!
What was that?
That was funny.
Let's go do it
to somebody else.
Aye!
Look at that.
Cupids and hearts. Really shoving
our faces in it this year.
You doing okay, bud?
I miss Stacy.
Yeah. I hear you. It's been four
months since I was with Holly
and she was way
hotter than Stacy.
So if you think
you're hurting...
I can't even imagine.
This is our first and only
Valentine's Day as fiancés.
You're only engaged once.
Well, present company
excluded, but...
Really, Jim?
On Cupid's birthday?
Yeah.
She's fine.
So I received my first Valentine
from a secret admirer.
"Roses are red,
violets are blue.
"It's time for your dental
cleaning and maybe a checkup too."
Wow. Look at those.
How nice for you.
Up there, front and
center, beautiful.
I think they would
look better right here.
They're very pretty and
I wouldn't want them to fall.
Just about everybody in this
office is single right now.
Including me.
And everyone is experiencing an
incredible amount of emotional pain.
Especially me, because of my
great capacity for emotion.
And it is my first
Valentine's Day since Holly,
so I think that I am well
qualified to understand
that these people need to be
protected from having love
shoved into their faces.
Pam, really? They're back?
I can't see them when
they're on the floor.
They're for her
to look at, Michael.
Can I have a word with you?
Yes, let's have a word.
Yes. Jim.
Today is a very difficult day for
a lot of people in this office.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
And the sexy looks
between you and Pam,
the general sexiness,
the flowers,
it's creating a bit of a
hostile work environment.
I understand. It's so
sexy it becomes hostile.
I actually thought we were
keeping it pretty low-key.
Well, if you guys insist
on having your own
private little love fest...
We do.
...that none of us
can be a part of...
You can't be a part
of our relationship, Michael.
Then we are going to have
our own private
Valentine's Day party.
That sounds fun.
So suck it.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Hey, everybody, I just
invited Jim to suck it,
and I am cordially inviting all
of you to a special convention,
a lonely hearts convention
this afternoon.
Singles only.
Yeah. Deal with it, Pam!
So, we may not have someone
in our lives that we love,
but we do have each other.
Having trouble
finding a vein?
Yeah. A little.
How about now?
I trained my major blood vessels to
retract into my body on command.
Also I can retract my
penis up into itself.
I am about to give blood.
The gift of everlasting life,
the transfer of
my bodily fluids...
Wow, that's a big needle.
You're going to need to
lie down right over here.
Okay. Hello.
Hi. I can't talk right now.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I'm really nervous.
Yeah. Me too.
Yeah?
When I get nervous,
I sort of clam up and...
Well, that's fine.
It's better for me
just to be quiet. Yeah.
Yeah. Can I point
something out to you?
Sure.
You're actually talking a lot.
Yeah. Sorry.
That's the other thing I do
when I get really nervous.
Okay. Here we go.
All right,
here we go.
Oh, God.
Just relax.
Yeah. I'm good.
I feel like
a human juice box.
Oh, God.
Hawaiian blood punch.
That's gross.
Type O-cean Spray.
God, stop. Stop it.
Yeah.
Wouldn't it be cool?
Hey. Why don't you guys come
have lunch with Bob and me?
We'll take all afternoon.
Michael is
terrified of Bob.
What do you think?
I have a lot of work
to do this afternoon.
Those mines aren't going
to sweep themselves.
We're in.
What?
I looked at the bag.
I looked straight
at the bag.
That's not good.
Could you distract me
for a second?
Just talk about things that
don't have blood in them.
Well, okay. Bags.
That...
All right.
That was bad.
That was mean.
A hat.
A hat with no blood in it.
That is full of soup.
You're cute.
What?
You're done.
Already?
We did it.
Wow, I was
so nervous about this.
I don't think
I ate for three days.
Is he okay?
Oh, my God.
How long was I out?
What?
Excuse me, waitress,
where did the lady go?
She left.
Okay.
Wait a second. Wait a second.
That's hers. This is hers.
She left her glove.
I need her name if I'm
going to return her glove.
I'm sorry, sir. We can't
give out that information.
What are you doing?
Decorating.
I'll help.
Now it's just
a stupid baby.
Yeah. Thanks.
It is so nice to go out
with another couple.
Anything to get
out of that office.
I know.
I honestly don't know how you
can work with that jackass
and that other jackass
and that new jackass.
He's talking about
Michael, Dwight and Andy.
Yeah. I understood.
Well, here we all are,
alone but together.
No flowers for us.
Relationships. We don't need
no stinking relationships.
I think we should all go around and
tell our worst relationship story
and then get past it.
Just blow through it. Yeah?
Kelly, what about Ryan? He
treated you pretty terribly.
Well, his heart was
in the right place.
Yeah, but now his
heart is in Thailand,
along with the rest of his
body, having random sex.
Okay. Sorry.
Let's... Who else?
Oscar?
I don't think so.
Come on, I'm sure there's something
you need to get off your chest.
Thank you.
You want to...
Just anything? You sure?
I'm sure whatever you
did wasn't your fault.
Okay, well, who else?
Everyone here who's bowled a
280, please raise your hand.
No way.
Wow.
A 280?
That's impressive.
Okay, now everyone here who's
bowled under 70 raise their hand.
Yikes.
Come on, Bob, raise your hand.
No, Bob.
No.
What?
One time. You love
bringing up that one time.
Yes, I do.
Jim uses a six-pound ball.
That is a lie.
Yes. He bowled five frames
with this pink sparkly thing until a
little girl had to ask for her ball back.
But that girl must have had monstrous
hands because the holes fit.
No, you just have
little dainty fingers.
You could always
model lady's jewelry.
Nobody asked, Bob.
Do you risk telling
them how you feel?
Do you say something that you
can barely admit to yourself?
God, what did you do?
Not that I approve
of any of it, but...
I was stupid.
I told him.
Was he into you in,
like, a gay way?
Moron, if he was
there wouldn't be a story.
He told me he wasn't gay.
- Really sad.
- I'm not done yet.
Oh, my God.
A week later, a friend
of mine calls me up
and he says, "I just saw him
in a gay bar in Kansas City."
Well, then it's a happy
ending, because he was gay.
You should call him.
My worst breakup was actually two breakups.
Two different men.
I was in love with both of
them and when things went bad
they had a duel over me.
Yeah, Dwight and Andy.
We were here.
No.
This was years ago when I was living
in Ohio. John Mark and John David.
Angela, you had two sets of different
men actually duel over you?
I guess I have.
All right, who's next?
Where's Andy?
He's on one of
his honeymoons.
What?
He made nonrefundable deposits
on his honeymoons,
so he's just knocking
them off one at a time.
I think today he's
hot-air ballooning,
and later he's got
a couples' massage.
My worst breakup
was with Stacy.
It was a Sunday morning.
We were reading the paper
and I said, "Oh, my God, I think the
Eagles could clinch the NFC East."
And she said that we're done.
You know what, guys, I don't
think we need to do this.
You're right. Okay,
everyone, back to work.
No, no, no, no. I mean
have this kind of party.
I look around and I see all
these beautiful people
who are alone on Valentine's
and I think that there are other
single people out there, too.
We just need to find them.
There's a girl out
there for all of us.
Maybe even in
this office park.
There has to be a way to get all
these lonely people together.
A net? A giant net?
No, not a giant net.
What do you have in mind?
I was thinking
maybe like a mixer.
Oh, God, that's
a terrible idea.
Old-fashioned
meat market.
No.
I don't think it is.
Lonely people mixing with
one another, breeding,
creating an even
lonelier generation?
You're not allowing natural
selection to do its work.
You're like the guy
who invented the seatbelt.
These people need love.
And I am going
to get it for them.
Who cares if we sell a
little bit less paper today?
A great boss cares more
about the happiness of his
employees than anything else.
I am going to be Cupid.
And I'm going to shoot my
sparrow at unsuspecting victims
and they are going to get hit
and say, "I'm in love.
"I was hit by
Cupid's sparrow."
Funny little bird,
but he gets the job done.
Hey.
Hey. No movement.
Still early.
Yeah, it's not that early.
So how are you holding up?
I'm okay.
I feel a little lopsided
because of all the blood they
took out of my right side.
No, no. I meant
about being single today.
Meh.
Meh!
Exactly.
Here we go.
Hello.
Dwight K. Schrute.
Why don't you introduce me to
your little friend? Hi. Dwight.
Babe alert. Hello. I'm Michael Scott.
Welcome to our little shindig.
Hi. I'm Lynn.
Lynn, follow me.
Come on in.
Here we go.
For you we have one
of our top people,
Kevin Malone. Kevin, come out here.
Show your beautiful self.
Hello.
Hi.
So run with the ball.
Run with it, Kev.
Where are you from?
I'm from here.
Yeah, okay. Well, he
only gets better.
Thank you, Michael.
Okay.
I can untie any knot.
I'm serious.
Name a knot, any knot.
Go ahead.
I believe you.
You shouldn't believe
everything you hear.
In fact, there are many knots
that I cannot untie.
So what's a woman as charming as
yourself find herself employed
on a day such as today?
I work at a place
that does catalogs for
community colleges
and small businesses.
You must use a lot of paper.
Oh, God, tons of it.
What's the rule
about eating
when people are
in the bathroom?
I think if you ordered hot
food you're allowed to eat.
Damn.
They've been in there
for like ten minutes.
Look at that.
Bob ordered hot food.
Yes.
And I think they
gave him too many fries.
We should help him out.
At the Circle Drive-in,
they show old movies.
It's really cool.
That does sound cool.
I used to go there
with my fiancée.
Before she left me.
I mean, before I left her.
She left me.
Shoot.
I think I blew it.
It all happened so fast.
So fast.
So, Erik, you
mentioned before
that you are in
tool and die repair.
I am.
Meredith recently had
a total hysterectomy.
So that's sort of a repair.
All right,
I'll let you guys talk.
It's going very well. People are mixing.
A lot of hope,
'cause that's what you hate to
see, when hope gets crushed.
Sorry. Thought I heard
somebody coming in.
So, it's not too late.
And the kind of discounts we're
talking about are not...
Hold on. Michael, why do you
keep looking at the front door?
No reason.
Is somebody after you?
Why do you always
go to that?
Has anyone ever been after
anyone in this office?
Hey, it just takes one.
Nobody's after me. I just...
I met a woman when
I was giving blood
and I thought
she might come by.
You met a woman when you were giving blood?
That is so romantic.
It's not a big deal, really.
I just, you know,
met somebody.
We hardly talked.
I picked up her glove so I was
hoping I could give it back to her.
Oh, my God, that makes it
even more romantic.
This is like a modern-day Enchanted.
It's like a fairytale.
She could be
your soul mate.
Not likely.
With three billion
women on the planet,
most of them live in Asia, so
the numbers just don't add up.
It's possible.
Could be.
Believe me, it's nothing.
I hardly even talked to her.
We just... We were lying
there next to each other.
I think our
blood bags touched.
Aww!
Here they come.
What?
No. Just kidding.
Seriously though,
that's enough.
Why don't you cover it
with the broccoli?
Great, I have to cover it?
Do you think they
dined and dashed?
They didn't dine so, yeah,
maybe they just dashed.
I thought we were
having a nice time.
We were.
Yeah.
Empty.
Mine too.
Oh, boy.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Hi. Is this the party?
Nah.
Okay then.
So...
Where were we?
Bowling.
Yep, yeah, yep.
You didn't eat
much there, Jim-bo.
Initially I did.
Want some meat?
Sure, a little piece.
No mushroom, though.
I forgot.
Yeah. Thank you.
Hey, I'm sorry we did not
have a chance to talk more.
I get very nervous
talking to pretty girls.
Seriously,
feel how sweaty my hand is.
That's really sweaty.
Are you on e-mail?
Yeah.
Cool. Okay, bye.
Bye, Kevin.
Good Valentine's.
So basically the greater
volume you decide to buy in,
the greater discount
we can give you. Okay.
Okay? What's up?
Look, I'm going to go.
Before you go, I'd just love to
get a firm commitment on this.
You know, maybe sign...
Look, we already
have a paper supplier.
Okay.
Well, thanks for wasting
my time tonight, idiot. God!
Hey. You don't
deserve her.
Thanks, Michael.
Hey, if anybody wants to go...
We can stay a little longer.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Sure, Michael.
No, this is great.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Michael, it's time.
You know what?
You guys can get out.
I'm going to soldier
on for a little bit.
Come on. We'll all go.
Yeah.
Yeah. Let's go.
Okay.
Four months ago,
I dated a woman named Holly,
and this is actually the first
time that I've even considered
getting back into
that arena again.
You know what?
Sometimes it's not about
whether Cinderella
gets her slipper back,
but it's about the fact that the prince
even picked up the slipper at all.
There's a lot of
princesses out there.
You know, they have
all different sizes
and shapes of
feet and hands,
so I think...
I think my odds
are pretty good.
Pardon me, may I have
a chocolate chip cookie?
I gave blood earlier
and I'm still feeling woozy.
Of course.
That's weird.
You got a cotton ball
and tape and we've
been using Band-Aids.
I feel so woozy, I just...
Using Band-Aids.
Damn.