Oh, my God.
I can't believe it.
I just won
an art contest.
Thanks.
I still don't
understand why you
- wanted me to say that.
- Shut up.
I got her.
Not cool, Dwight.
Not cool, man.
Oh, no.
I still have the lease on the
Michael Scott Paper Company,
so occasionally, I will sneak down
here for a little coffee and dancing.
I actually dance
all the time.
Tip-toeing around
corporate, it is a ballet.
When I am breaking all the
rules, I'm break dancing.
And espresso.
Guys, I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
I think I'm growing
into a giant,
because look at this
normal-sized coffee cup.
Looks so tiny in
my giant hand now.
Anybody want to go to
lunch with me later on?
I do. Okay, how about a woman?
Pam?
I can't do lunch. I was
just sending you an e-mail.
Jim and I need to leave early today
to meet with our contractor.
Really? Okay.
Just sent it.
What about
the rest of you?
At Dunder Mifflin,
there is a very strict
no-lunch-with-the-boss policy,
and I don't know
who instituted it.
I think it started right after
my predecessor stepped down.
But at the Michael
Scott Paper Company,
I really enjoyed having lunch
with Pam and Ryan every day.
So, rules be damned, I want to
have lunch with these people.
Who else?
Who else? Ryan?
I don't do lunch. I'm doing
five small meals a day now.
Now that I'm back to doing
the job of a temp again,
I find that food is one
thing I can control.
Okay, anyone?
Anyone at all?
Accounting, I am a-counting on
you to go to lunch with me.
No, I don't want to stay late
to have a two-hour lunch.
Michael, we have
a lot of work to do.
What?
Work.
God. What happened
to you people?
"We are
just office drones.
"We are office drones.
All we do is work. Is work."
If you don't take out his battery,
he just keeps going all day.
Oh, no, your
battery fell out.
"I was just
learning to love."
Hi, guys.
How are you doing?
Erin, how many times
do I have to tell you?
It is not necessary for you
to ask us how we are doing
every time you
interact with us.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Now, how can I help you?
Did somebody here leave a map in
the printer to Youngstown, Ohio?
Attention, office. Who here is
planning a trip to Youngstown, Ohio?
I will take your silence to mean
that you are all hiding something.
This location is
the superior court...
So someone's going
to a court. Big deal.
It is a big deal, 'cause there's
only a handful of reasons
why someone would ever go
to a courthouse in Ohio
and not be charged with a crime.
Claim an inheritance
from a deceased relative,
to obtain a learner's permit
at age 14 1/2 instead of 15.
Erin, let me see
your birth certificate.
Sure.
There are other
reasons to go to Ohio.
We're getting
married today.
So, it turns out it's the closest
place to get a marriage license
without a three-day
waiting period.
Tell them how it happened.
Okay, so we're going through
all the wedding plans,
and, boy,
it is complicated.
And very expensive.
Very expensive.
'Cause you say you
want a small wedding
and that's great,
but then you have to...
You can't leave anyone out.
No one.
Okay, just get
to the good part.
Right, so, this morning, we are
having breakfast together...
Mmm-hmm.
...and I just looked up
from my cereal and I said,
"You know what I want to do today?
I want to marry you."
I had just woken up.
I didn't look cute.
That's how I
knew he meant it.
Michael?
Michael, sorry to bother you. Are
you going to be working down here?
Do you want
these down here...
No work! No work! No work!
I come here to
release frustration.
Well, I like to swim.
That's good.
You've got a
cool place to come.
If you ever want to come down
here, door's always open.
Lock's broken, so...
Thank you.
Give me your hand. Hey, here
we go, here we go. Yeah.
There we go. Now you got it.
Now I do got it.
Now you got it. Hey, you
want some espresso?
Yeah.
Gotta keep
yourself dehydrated.
That's rule number one. Okay.
I love it.
Guys, I believe that I have figured
out what is up your butts.
There's no reason
to be scared.
The bad man is gone.
Charles is gone.
Charles really did
a number on these guys.
They are way too
focused on work.
When I was in charge, this place
was like Dave & Buster's,
people just hanging out,
having fun, eating apps.
I don't know, it's like
Dave died or something.
Daddy's here, and Daddy is
going to take care of you.
Please don't refer to
yourself as our daddy.
I am your big daddy, and I am
going to kiss the boo-boo.
Little
Andy is afraid.
Andy's afraid?
Yes.
Are you all afraid?
No.
Daddy's here for you,
my little angels.
Okay,
I think that I have figured a way
to get you guys out of your funk.
What?
Funk is the problem,
and the solution.
That makes sense.
I have taken my
downstairs office
and I have turned it
into a place to hang out,
a place where unattractive and
attractive people can get together,
to meet, to greet, to see
the ones that you love,
to love the ones
that you see.
Is this our punishment for not
wanting to have lunch with you?
Why don't you get
over lunch, Oscar?
Everybody else is past it.
All work and no play
makes Michael a dull boy.
This is like a haunted
coffee house thing?
No, Dwight is confusing you.
It's more of a disco.
It's like a haunted disco.
With coffee, but
without the haunting.
It's a combo dance
house-coffee bar.
It is a daytime disco
on the ground floor
of an industrial
office building.
It's a Cafe Disco.
Exactly.
Like a disco-cafe.
What? No. No.
Not even close.
I can't force you to go
down, but I can entice you.
I'm going to
be down there.
Erin will be down there
from time to time,
and all-you-can-eat espresso.
Well, Kevin, I guess
it is just me and you.
Yeah.
Holding down the fort.
Yeah. This place is great.
Thank you.
Oh, my God, Kevin,
I am still on hold.
You were supposed
to get the answer
from Michael
and come back up.
This is a no-work zone.
Please respect the lei.
Yeah, respect the lei.
Come.
Kevin, stay.
Kevin, come.
Stay, stay.
Come on, right now.
Cookie, Kevin. Cookie.
There is
no cookie, Kevin.
Is there a cookie?
Mmm-hmm.
Come on.
For goodness sakes,
Kevin, there's no cookie.
There's no cookie.
Come on. Come.
I wanted a cookie.
Completely unacceptable.
Now I know what the founders
of Philip Morris felt like.
You just want to give people
a smooth, fun way to relax,
and suddenly, you're just
some terrible monster.
Here we go.
What the hell!
Hi, Jessica,
is Bob in?
He's on a call.
Well, I'll just
duck my head in.
It's pretty important. He
wouldn't want to be disturbed.
Can I give him a message
before he gets off?
Tell him I'm going
dancing downstairs
in the storage closet
between the bathrooms
that used to be a utility shower,
and he should join me there.
I'll let him know.
Mmm-hmm.
Phyllis?
Hi.
Hey.
Hey,
I like.
All right. Back... There you go.
There you go. You got it.
Show me some attitude.
Mother.
God. No, no, no.
Back.
Wow, what did you do?
You didn't do that.
You're okay.
Let's lie down.
Give me... You want
to go down? All right.
Sorry.
Okay, that's okay.
Backs are a problem.
Okay, sweetie...
Right here.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. I got your text.
Who's Phillip?
No, no, no.
Who tipped you over?
Was it Phillip?
It's my back.
It's her back.
We just... We need...
God, call a doctor.
You know what? We're going
to take care of you.
We're going to get you help.
Come on, come on.
Call Bob.
No, no, no,
this is no good.
Yeah, back
injuries are common.
Not as common
as knee injuries,
but more common
than wrist injuries.
I don't need a
history lesson, okay?
What do you
think history is?
Just... We need to
get her out of there
because no one is going
to want to go in there
with a woman writhing
around on the floor.
Wait, wait, wait,
but most importantly,
we need to get her some
medical attention ASAP, stat.
Here we go.
Ramming speed.
Okay, out of the way.
Move it or lose it.
Oh, my God, what happened? You
having fun taking a little ride?
Just having
too much fun.
Phyllis, we're gonna put you in here.
Dwight's gonna take care of you.
What? No, I thought we were
going to the hospital.
If you want to get sick,
you go to a hospital.
Okay, Dwight.
Okay, good.
I do not want
anybody to worry.
What happened
to Phyllis?
You know,
nothing. She's...
We were hanging
out at Cafe Disco
and she had a flare-up
of an existing injury,
but she's a
tough old bird, so...
Can you please
go back to work
instead of masterminding
these situations
wherein we
hurt ourselves?
Okay, fine. Phyllis
did injure herself,
but she injured
herself having fun,
and I don't think she would
trade that memory for anything.
I would like the
memory of a day
uninterrupted
by this nonsense.
You all took a life here today.
You did.
The life of the party.
Erin, I want you
to go downstairs,
and I want you
to shut it down.
You mean unplug the coffee
machine and bring it up here?
I don't care. Bury it.
I hope you're happy.
Okay. I'm going to need
two able-bodied men.
Cafe Disco? More
like crappy disco.
You're bad.
There's girls in there. Where?
The other room.
What other room?
Down the hall.
There's girls there?
What did I just say?
You bring my sandwich?
Forget the sandwich.
Girls. Girls.
I guess they got what they want.
I am eating alone.
Might as well be dinner.
Comfy? All right, all right.
Just relax, relax, okay?
Dwight. Dwight.
Come on, relax. This shirt
wasn't doing you any favors.
If my assessment is correct,
you grind your teeth?
I do.
No kidding. She sits three feet from me.
It's the most annoying thing.
It's like children
singing Christmas carols.
Yeah. I'm loving
the vibe down here.
Ashley. You made it.
You invited someone?
Oh. Yeah. Was I not
allowed to do that?
I don't know. I've been here
eight years, and I've never...
Rude.
I'm not sure, but I'm pretty
sure I'm in a dance-off.
Cafe Disco is dead, but I can
still hear the music in my head.
I hear it, too, boss.
It's better
than I imagined it.
It feels good, Dwight.
Tell me where it hurts.
Right... Right there.
Yeah, you've got
a knot in your crest.
This remedy has been passed down
in my family for generations,
and it always works.
My grandfather was told that Diamond
Dancer would never race again.
They were wrong. He came in
ninth in the Apple Creek Derby.
And his jerky came in
third the following year.
A majestic beast.
So fast, so tender.
Welcome, welcome. Cafe Disco.
I am Michael Scott.
Hey, Angela,
welcome to Cafe...
Stop!
Angela, Angela, Angela, may I
interest you in a triple espresso,
or perhaps a dance?
No, I didn't come down
here to get wet and wild.
I just need you
to sign these.
All right.
Here you go.
And, no, you need
to sign them all.
No, no, no.
Here is the deal.
One signature
for every song.
Look, I hate to
be "that" person,
but I just don't like the
general spirit of music.
I know, I know. Angela, a lot of
people doubted Cafe Disco at first,
but it is a magical place. You
have to give it a chance.
If these walls could
talk, they would say,
"This is a magical place.
You're safe here.
"We are talking walls.
We're not going to eat you."
No.
This is oil from
the gland of an otter.
It keeps their fur water
resistant, as well as traps heat.
Now, I need you to
lie still for an hour.
An hour? I can't
stay here an hour.
Whoa, whoa, girl.
Whoa. Whoa.
Boss, this used to hang from my
windshield, but it belongs in here.
Hey, thank you, Creed.
You really get this place.
No problem. I'll just have no
idea who's driving behind me now.
Look out.
Yeah!
Yeah.
Finish it off.
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Here we go. Okay,
something's gonna happen.
Here we go. Yeah.
I'm going to go
with the python.
But the rattler's so scary.
No, please, I find the rattle soothing.
Puts me to sleep.
I think Bob's going to cheat
on me with his new secretary.
What's so funny?
When I say it out
loud, it's so silly.
Hey, hey, Angela, no.
No cleaning up.
You are forcing me
to be down here.
Am I not allowed
to have some fun?
No cleaning up.
These are for you.
They're beautiful.
You ready?
Yeah.
We should probably stop by.
It would mean a lot to him.
Hey. Hey. Man,
Jim and Pam.
Can you believe this?
It's really happening.
Want to dance, Dwight?
Ordinarily,
I would say no,
but you need to move to
reduce lactic acid buildup.
Also, this song
is fantastic.
Mind if I steal my wife?
You can't steal what is
legally your property.
Are those staples?
This dance competition
is not over.
What dance competition? I was just
dancing casually with my friend, y'all.
Yeah, right.
You guys are the
best for coming.
You don't have to stay if you
don't want to. I understand.
We're going to stay.
Really?
At least for
one more dance.
No, not me. Not me. Get out of here.
Cafe Disco.
Hey, come on, man.
We're not even to "Y."
This is so cheesy.
Yes.
I like cheesy.
Me, too.
You know, I think maybe I
want a wedding wedding.
Me, too.
Really?
Yeah.
Would you like
to dance?
No.
Yeah. No, well, okay...
Stop squirming.
Well, stop trying to poke
me with a sharp thing.
You wanted to do this, okay?
Just be brave.
I know, but you're
not a professional,
and I'm thinking maybe we
should have gone that route.
I'm doing... No, I'm
doing it for free.
Just... You have
to stop squirming,
otherwise, I'm
going to mess up.
Are you sure that's
not the gay ear?
Gay ear?
Are you 12 years old?
Well, I...
Look, I'm going to
count to three.
Count to 20.
No, I'm going to count to three.
One, two, three.
Son of a bitch!
Andy, that was
just the ice.
It was?
Yeah, it was.