Dunder Mifflin,
this is Erin.
He's not available
right now.
Uh-huh.
Yes. Sure, I'll give him the message
when he gets up. Gets back.
Michael had chicken
pot pie for lunch.
Actually,
let me rephrase that.
Michael had an entire
chicken pot pie for lunch.
Let me be more specific.
Michael ate an entire, family-sized
chicken pot pie for lunch,
and then he promptly
fell asleep.
So, we're all trying
to be very quiet,
so as to not wake him up
before 5:00 p.m.,
which actually
should be in about
10 minutes.
Okay, I'm gonna go in there
and change the computer.
Are you sure you can
change his watch?
I can do it.
What do you
need from me?
Normally, I don't
condone leaving early,
but I have an appointment
with the horse doctor.
How that horse became a
doctor, I don't know.
No, I'm kidding.
He's just a regular doctor who
shoots your horse in the head
when its leg is broken.
Like clockwork.
Oh, no.
What's so funny?
You had to be there.
Oh, yay, geography joke.
Oh. Wow, okay. All right, let's all
go home. Come on. See you all tamale.
Bye.
See you later,
Michael.
All right,
you ready for this?
Yeah, we walk around, everyone sees
our faces, then we leave, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Wait, should I have
left the car running?
Oh.
Oh, don't get us wrong,
we like picnics.
Come on, who doesn't
like a picnic?
Tell them what
happened last year.
I had this huge spider
in my baseball mitt.
No, no, that guy
who hit on me.
Oh, right. Some drunk guy
hit on Pam last year.
Said he was grabbing
her for balance.
Yeah, you don't
grab these for balance.
Well...
I'm gonna say 30.
Ah, 40.
Insect repellent, which we clearly need,
reduces the effectiveness of SPF.
Good point, but thought of that
already, combination SPF/repellent.
Whoa. Homemade?
Of course.
You think the EPA would
ever allow that much deet?
Rolf is my best friend.
We met in a shoe store.
I heard him asking for a shoe
that could increase his speed
and not leave
any tracks.
Michael, isn't
that Holly?
We're just friends.
Hey, hey.
Wait a second.
Who let you in here,
is what I wanna know.
Oh, no.
I see they're letting
just anybody in here.
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, that's right.
All right.
All right. Mmm-hmm.
Hey.
Hi.
You remember A.J.,
my boyfriend?
A little bit. I meet
a lot of people.
Hey, Michael.
Hey.
Oh.
So, would you guys
like some lemonade?
Or one of you?
Or both of you?
Either-or. Combinations
are endless.
Lemonade sounds great.
Okay.
I'd love an
iced tea, actually.
You can go to hell.
I'm kidding.
Um, sure, I will get you the
best iced tea in the world.
I lied to Kevin.
Holly and I can never
be just friends.
I wrote down a list
of bullet points
why Holly and I
should be together,
and I'm going to find the perfect
moment today and I'm going to tell her.
Number one, "Holly, you
and I are soup snakes."
And the reason is
because in terms of
the soup, we like to...
That doesn't make any sense.
We're soul mates.
Holly and I are soul mates.
Jim, Pam.
- Hey, how are you?
- Hey, Charles.
Nice day, huh?
Yeah.
Must be nice to get a
rest from all your rest.
I don't get it. He's not
even my boss anymore.
Do you want me to
beat him up for you?
No, I shouldn't have to ask you to do
stuff like that. You should just do it.
Listen up, everyone. I've gone
over this lineup very carefully.
We cannot forget
the humiliation
we suffered last year
at the softball game
with Jim's whole spider-in-the-mitt
incident. Right?
Well, I could've
died, so...
I looked it up
online afterwards.
Erin, back row.
Ryan, you move up a row.
Bro-migo, do you think you
could put Erin on my row?
Why? I don't understand.
If... No, wait... Wait
a minute, I get it.
You want her to set you
up so you can spike it.
Uh...
I'll tell you what, I'm
gonna do you one better.
I'm gonna put you
next to Phyllis.
She's the best
setter on the team.
That's...
Sly dog.
...not what I meant.
Come on, folks!
What is up with
you two, Holly?
Um, not much.
We're designing a house.
Cool, for who?
For us.
Wow.
I'm designing a chair.
It's part of your pants.
You sit down,
you're supported.
I remember your chair-pants idea.
Yeah.
I like that. Put me down for a pair.
I'm a size-34 waist.
All right, fatty,
I will do it.
You know what, we should
actually rehearse.
Okay, yeah.
You guys are
really gonna do this?
You bet your
fat ass we are.
Well, in his
infinite wisdom,
David Wallace has authorized us
to put on a little presentation
about the history
of Dunder Mifflin.
Yep, old comedy team
is back together again.
That's right.
"Have you heard
the news?
"Extra! Extra!
Read all about it!"
"Newspapers for sale!"
Are you blind?
Sir? With the glasses,
are you literally blind?
I'm concerned you
might be in danger.
These are expensive
Ray-Bans, jackass.
Okay, I was just
looking out for you.
You're doing great,
by the way.
Thanks.
I got it.
Kevin, come on!
Are you blind?
I could've gotten that, idiot! Can
you see things with your eyeballs?
It's not a sledgehammer!
Come on, people. We need to
get our heads in the game.
Let's focus. Come on,
you're better than this.
I am better than this.
Phyllis, why are you
sitting on the ground?
We've been out here for a
while, I don't need this.
Oh, come... Ryan, come on, man!
One second.
Wait, wait, wait! Net, net.
Her hand's on the net.
So what?
Rule violation.
Ball is ours.
Give it to me.
What?
Our point.
Okay, hey, Pam,
how you doing?
Hey, do you know if you're right-handed
or left-handed, or do you even know?
What hand do you use
to answer the phone?
Back off, Dwight.
Nice hit, Pam!
What?
Maybe I played a little in
junior high and in high school.
Maybe a little in college.
And went to volleyball
camp most summers.
All right, come on!
Yeah, look at that. We win.
Nice shot, Beesly.
Yes, we advance
to the next round!
Oh, Lord in heaven.
Had to be
part of the group.
Brought some snacky-snacks
in case we get hungry.
Ooh, yes, please.
Mmm.
So, what do you have
planned for us today?
What? Do you have a script
for the sketch or...
Um, no, I just thought
we'd wing it. That cool?
Crystal cool.
Hit it, Andy.
Bump, I bumped it!
Set. Don't set it to yourself.
Yeah.
Ow! My ankle.
What happened?
I twisted it.
You weren't even moving.
Okay, sub.
I can play.
Is there a Meredith here?
Yeah! Man in!
Rolf, did you
not hear me?
I don't hear cheaters, tramps or
women who break my friend's heart.
Let's go!
We could do a movie
sort of thing.
We could do
Back to the Future.
Oh. We have to convince
Dunder and Mifflin
to go back in time,
fix their parents.
Could we get a DeLorean?
Jaws. They swim in the ocean and
they terrorize the whole community.
Oh.
Dunder, Dunder,
Dunder, Dunder...
We haven't found
our great idea yet.
No. No.
We're circling it.
Hmm.
Yes!
Oh, yeah!
Nicely done. We're still
gonna crush you, though.
Yes, we are. You suckers
are going down!
They're gonna wipe their
asses with your serves!
Piss all over
your faces!
That's true!
This reminds me of the
HR convention last fall.
Oh, yeah, with Bernie and Efrem.
That was hilarious.
Really, really funny.
Really funny.
Listen, guys. One more point
and we play corporate.
Settle down, gentlemen.
Good game!
Welcome to the 43rd Annual
Company Picnic, everybody.
Thanks for being here.
Now, a couple of employees have
volunteered to entertain us with a song.
Uh, it's
a sketch now.
Okay.
Introducing Scranton's Michael Scott
performing with Nashua's Holly Flax.
I have not seen this.
And now, presenting
SlumDunder Mifflinaire!
Are you ready to play
SlumDunder Mifflinaire?
Yes, I am.
For $100, where did
Dunder meet Mifflin?
A, on easy street,
B, a tour of
Dartmouth College,
C, they never met,
D, brushing their teeth.
Oh. I'm thinking.
I'm going to say
B, tour of
Dartmouth College.
That is correct!
How did you know that?
I was there!
I was a tour guide at
Dartmouth College! No!
Nice campus.
Think you'll get in?
Yeah. I'm definitely
getting in. I'm a shoo-in.
I'm Robert Dunder.
I'm Robert Mifflin.
Robert Mifflin
had a great life,
but unfortunately had
undiagnosed depression,
which over 9 million Americans
suffer from and is very treatable.
For $250, how did
he kill himself?
A, a rope,
B, a knife,
C, a gun,
D, brushing his teeth.
$250 is more money than
I've ever seen in my life.
I will say C, a gun. He
shot himself in the head.
That is correct!
Yes!
I usually don't
enjoy the theater,
but this is delightful.
The economic downturn has
been difficult recently,
forcing the closures of
both Camden and Yonkers
to be followed soon
by what other branch?
For $500,000, is it
A, Scranton,
B, Buffalo,
C, Utica,
or D, Toothbrush?
I will say B,
Buffalo, final answer.
That is correct!
- What is he talking about?
- What?
No way.
It's gotta be a joke.
How did you know that?
David Wallace told me!
David, is this true?
Uh, okay, everyone,
we're at a picnic today...
Are we losing our jobs
or not, David?
They didn't know?
I guess not.
I'm sorry. This certainly
wasn't the time or the place
to announce
this sort of thing,
but there have been talks about
closing the Buffalo branch.
And?
We're closing
the Buffalo branch.
Are you serious? You've
gotta be kidding me!
We're the best branch in the company.
I don't believe it.
How could you
possibly think
that the right way to
announce a branch closing
was in a comedy sketch
at the company picnic?
Well, I didn't know
they didn't know.
What about the fact
that they're here today?
What about that? That
didn't throw up any alarms?
No, Michael needed a little
bit for his comedy sketch
and he thought, "Oh, this would
be real funny." Thank you.
Damn it, Michael. I told
you that in confidence.
Now I have to go over and deal with
these employees and their families.
A little boy just
walked up to me and said,
"Is my daddy gonna have
a job by Christmas?"
Well, he's just thinking
about his own gifts.
Maybe we shouldn't play
due to the circumstances.
Hey, people need volleyball
now more than ever.
How do you figure?
Because if we don't play,
then the other team wins.
Dwight's right. Corporate
deserves to get its ass kicked.
Let's do this.
Jim, come on!
Look who just woke up!
I've been up for a while!
It's 6 to 6.
It's a nail biter.
Kevin! Now it's 7-6. Or is that
too much accounting for you?
Here's an accounting
question for you.
What does one fiancé
plus one lover equal?
Answer, one whore.
Okay, knock it off, Rolf.
What? She's sitting there casting
aspersions... Rolf, please.
No, wait a minute.
I am asking nicely.
Wait, you don't mean that.
Rolf, leave it alone.
You got it.
All right.
Got it. Damn!
- I got it.
- Pam!
You all right?
Yeah. No, no, no, I'm fine.
You sure?
Yeah.
Hey, easy, easy, easy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You want to get
that looked at.
No, no, it's fine.
Just give me a second.
I don't know. You know,
this is a company picnic.
So, technically, that is a
company injury, you know.
The safest thing to do is get
that examined. Right, David?
Yeah. All right, you know what?
You're just trying to get
rid of our best player.
Oh, Jim, you're
putting a volleyball game
in front of your
fiancée's health.
No... Look, seriously,
I can move it fine.
Come on, let's go. It's our ball.
Let's go. I don't know.
Yeah, I don't think we can
let you play with that foot.
Tell you what.
I spotted a small hospital
a few kilometers
south of here.
Get her back as soon as possible.
I'll stall them.
I guess that's
it for you, Jim.
All right, you know what?
Let's do this.
We'll be back.
Oh, man, I am so mad
that Pam got hurt!
I'll get it.
Probably shouldn't
have mentioned Buffalo.
Hindsight.
Should've had hindsight.
How do you think it went
before the Buffalo thing?
I think it went well.
I think it was good.
There weren't any laughs.
Well, that was
a tough audience.
Yeah, but we wrote it
specifically for this audience.
Believe me, I have seen a lot
of tough audiences in my time,
and that was one of them.
Well, I'm glad we did it.
Me, too.
We have a lot of good material
for next year's sketch.
I can't wait.
Yeah, she's with the nurse right now, so
you'll have to stall a little longer.
No. Don't send in the subs yet.
Dwight, I don't know.
Think of something.
Well, to be safe, we should do an x-ray.
How long will that take?
Well, it shouldn't be too bad.
It's a slow day.
So, no other
radiation this year,
no metal plates, no
chance you're pregnant...
I'm sorry. Could we
just hurry this up?
I've got a game
to get back to.
Oh, good, because
my next question was,
"Do you have a game
to get back to?"
What did you think?
I loved it.
You know, there was
a part near the end
that seemed like that went
on a little long, but...
Well, you guys
should hit the road
before I close down
another branch.
Okay. So good
to see you.
Good to see you.
A.J.
Michael.
I didn't find
the perfect moment,
because I think that today
was about just having today.
And I think that we are one of
those couples with a long story
when people ask how
we found each other.
I will see her
every now and then,
and maybe one year,
she'll be with somebody,
and the next year,
I'll be with somebody,
and it's gonna
take a long time.
And then it's perfect.
I'm in no rush.
Ha! Dwight, come on, now.
It's time to put in the subs.
Yeah, it looks like Pam
won't make it back.
Okay?
Okay, fine.
All right! Come on. Okay.
Except you know what?
It's not fine.
How many people need to get hurt
before we learn a valuable lesson?
One? Two?
Three? Four?
Dwight...
No, no. Hear me out.
Five? Six?
Dwight.
Seven?
Can I finish, please?
Okay.
Eight?
Oh, Dwight, we're so close.
Just buy us
a few more minutes.
Well, they just called me in for an
update, so I'll call you right back.
Okay. Okay, great.
Hey, Dwight. Uh...
Send in the subs.