Hey, Michael?
Yeah?
Contractions are coming
every 10 minutes.
Okay, just remember
to keep breathing.
My cervix is ripening.
Okay, good.
Jan is about to have a baby
with a sperm donor,
and Michael is preparing for the
birth of a watermelon with Dwight.
Now this baby will be related
to Michael through...
Delusion.
Michael!
Yeah?
My water's breaking!
Okay. Okay.
What do you do?
I get a call from Jan, and I
meet her at the hospital.
Right. Highways
or surface roads?
I take Quincy Ave to Gibson.
No. Gibson is covered
in potholes.
Your car breaks down.
Adapt.
I checked the route.
There are no potholes.
It's about adapting
to the circumstances.
Andy, would you like to have my baby?
Yes! Yeah.
No. Okay, no.
I'm crowning. I'm crowning!
All right. Come on. Sorry.
Here we go.
Here we go. Here we go.
- The pressure!
- Do it!
The pressure! Scream. Scream it out!
Scream it out!
Babies are one of my
many areas of expertise.
Growing up, I performed
my own circumcision.
Just keep pushing.
Hold me.
I'm right here. I'm right here.
Cradle my head!
I'm right here. I'm screaming.
I'm screaming!
All right. Dwight.
Just push and breathe. Numb me up.
I want anesthesia.
No, you can't have it.
It's too late.
No, I don't want natural.
No, you have to just push it out.
Okay.
Keep simulating. Okay.
Do you have the Sharpie?
Keep simulating.
Yes, I do.
Okay! When the baby emerges, mark
it secretly in a kind of a mark
that only you could recognize and
no baby snatcher could ever copy.
Okay. Yes.
Ready?
Okay. Coming!
Here we go!
God. Wow,
what was on that?
Butter. Newborns
are slippery.
Nice touch. Good.
Let's try that again.
This is going to be
the happiest day of my life.
Hello, ladies.
How is my shower going?
Phyllis, did you get
the live storks? No.
Damn it, Phyllis.
I'm sorry.
Damn it, Phyllis, it was hard
enough to convince Jan to come.
So are we set
for refreshments?
Per your instructions
we have the personalized M&M's
with the baby names. This is your
boy bowl with the name Chevy.
That was me.
And this is the girl bowl with
M&M's with the name Astird.
That can't be right.
Michael wrote down "Astird."
She said it is the name
of a Viking princess, so...
Astird.
I know. I know.
It is beautiful. No, thank you.
Is this it?
I mean, is this... Two bowls
of M&M's and some balloons?
You know what, Phyllis? I
think you need to step it up.
I think you need
to get the lead out,
because if I'm not mistaken, we
gave you your wedding shower here.
We all came into this room
and gave you a golden shower.
Well, you know what, where's
my golden shower, Phyllis?
It does not matter to me at all whether
this baby is biologically mine.
I'm going to love it. It's like
when the dog nurses the tiger cub.
Have you seen that video?
It is... It's so bizarre
and unnatural,
but it happens.
Okay, I'm collecting
for the baby shower.
But, Phyllis,
it's not his baby.
I know, Kevin. Why do
we have to pay money
to get a gift for his ex-girlfriend's
unborn sperm-bank baby?
Look at it as if you're paying for
the cake, not the baby. Sheet cake.
I do enjoy being the head of
the Party Planning Committee.
I'm no longer under Angela's heel, and
her little grape head is under mine.
Hey. Hey. What are you doing?
Don't talk to them.
I'm sorry.
Make the party.
Don't... Make the party,
please, Phyllis.
Pump it!
So you know Stacy, right?
Right.
The one from England.
There's no one from England, Jim.
Katie studied in Ireland.
This is Stacy. The one who does
the Murakami-style collages.
Right. That style.
So Stacy and Eric get to Foner's
G-tech half an hour early
so they don't have to
sit on the slab. Okay.
Anyway, Foner's TA
Sarikaya comes in.
Wait,
who's Sarikaya Komzin?
No, Sarikaya comes in. Don't interrupt.
I have, like, 30 seconds to finish this
and get to Digi Crit.
Okay. Okay.
So Sarikaya says to Eric, "No
way, you can't reserve seats."
And then Stacy
gets all up in her face,
and Sarikaya picks up
Stacy's Mi-Teintes pad
and throws it
at the light box.
No way.
Yes!
That's hilarious.
No, it was horrible.
Jim, she might get arrested.
Who? Stacy?
No, Stacy is a boy.
This is so frustrating. Why can't
you just be in art class with me?
Wait, I gotta go.
Class is starting.
Okay, I'll...
I'll talk to you later.
That was a good story.
Who's Sarikaya Komzin?
Yo, got the "Nard" puppy for you.
What's going on here?
It's a baby game where you
guess whose picture is whose.
Check it out.
Who would have thought that this little
baby would be marrying that little baby?
That's Phyllis.
Well...
Yeah, it is.
So I hope you two are very
happy together. Pervert.
Wait, why does that
make me a pervert? I...
Well, it does.
That's me.
That's not you.
Yes, it is.
That's mean,
come on. That's...
Ahoy, matey!
Ahoy!
Ahoy. So, how are you doing?
Good.
Listen, Jan Levinson
is coming in today,
and she is in the terminal
stages of her pregnancy.
A child of which
I have a vested interest.
It's all kind of weird.
Anyway, she is incredibly fat
and enormous right now,
extremely unattractive, and
you are, on the other hand,
one of the more attractive
people in the office,
so while she's here I am going to
be acting kind of cold to you,
and I am doing this
to pay respect to her
bloated feelings.
And I'm treating Ryan the same way.
Of course. Yeah.
I do not like pregnant
women in my workspace.
They're always complaining.
I have varicose veins, too. I have
swollen ankles. I'm constantly hungry.
Do you think my nipples
don't get sore, too?
Do you think I don't need to know
the fastest way to the hospital?
- Jan.
- Hi, Jim.
What do we have here?
This is my baby.
Really?
Oh, no.
Jan had the baby, and Michael
wasn't there to mark it.
So the baby could be
anybody's, except Michael's.
So this is Astird?
Astrid.
Oh! Oh.
Okay.
Why didn't you call me?
Well, you know, labor just kind
of started very suddenly...
I could have helped... and
the birth instructor thought
it wasn't a good idea
for you to be there...
You listened to that guy?
...so I just...
He had no sense of humor, and I
proved him wrong in so many ways.
Michael, you don't have any
idea what I've been through.
No, I don't.
So, I just... I'm sorry.
I thought today at the baby shower would
be a good time for the two of you to meet.
Can I hold her?
Yes. Yes, you can.
You know, I think just
leave her in the car seat.
Just... Yeah.
Okay. All right.
Okay.
I love babies. I think they are beautiful
in all sorts of different ways.
I try to pick up and hold a baby every
day, if possible, because it nourishes me.
It feeds my soul.
Babies are drawn to me,
and I think it's because
they see me as one of them.
But cooler, and with my life
put together a little bit.
If a baby were president, there would
be no taxes. There would be no war.
There would be
no government,
and things
could get terrible.
It actually, probably...
It would be a better screenplay
idea than a serious suggestion.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is my privilege
and honor to present for the first time
in her life and in the office, As...
Trid.
...trid Levinson. Hi! Astrid,
this is everybody, look.
This is your family. You're going to
know them for the rest of your life.
Well... Well, he may not be here.
Say hello.
Okay. Here we go. Lion King.
Michael, Michael, Michael!
That's... That's too high.
I'll take that.
Okay! Come on.
Let's get our shower on.
Conference room.
Choppity, chip, chop.
Are you okay?
You seem kind of...
I'm fine, weirdo.
Such an HR weirdo. Try not to suck all
the air out of there when you walk in.
Ready to play some games?
Let's do it!
Michael, the baby's
already been born.
Yeah, duh.
So we had games planned, but
the baby ruins all of them.
No, the baby doesn't
ruin anything, Kevin, okay?
The baby multiplies the fun. Let's
just do what you were going to do.
Okay. Who wants to guess
when the baby will be born?
All right, how about some presents?
I want to see some presents.
I got this so I can write
down for thank you notes.
Thank you. That's very sweet, thank you.
What do we got?
We all chipped in
and got you this stroller.
Oh!
Thank you.
She already has a stroller.
And this is way worse than
the stroller she came with.
She's got an Orbit.
That's a $1,200 stroller.
$1,200 for a stroller?
Okay, what else?
$1,200 is what I spent
on my whole bomb shelter.
For that kind of money, this
stroller should be indestructible.
Being good isn't always easy
No matter how hard I try
When he started
sweet-talking to me
He'd come and tell me
everything is all right
He'd kiss and tell me
And can I get away
again tonight
The only one...
- Hey, you.
- Hey, you busy?
Not even. I'm doing laundry for
the first time in, like, a month.
Okay, okay. You got to hear this. So,
Jan's shower's going on right now,
and she's singing
Son of a Preacher Man.
I can't hear anything.
There's like...
Everyone's just
staring at her like...
There's, like,
machines going.
...the song is about losing your
virginity next to a church,
and guess what? She's been
singing for the last 20 minutes.
I can't hear anything.
Okay, well, you know what,
just call me later.
Okay.
I'm not frustrated.
Even if I were in Scranton,
Jim and I would
have days like this.
We're just a little out of sync.
You know, that's all.
Oh!
Great, I...
I washed my lipstick.
How well I remember
The look that was in his eyes
Stealing kisses from me
on the sly
Taking time to make time
Telling me
that he's all mine
Learning from
each other's knowing
Looking to see how much
we've grown And the only...
Don't hit the fence!
Oh, no, my child!
Don't get stuck
on the barbed wire!
Playtime is over!
So, Jan, tell my intended about
the miracle of childbirth.
Well, actually I... I had a tub birth,
and it was really, really quite amazing.
You gave birth in a tub?
Yeah, it's a really nice
transition from womb to world.
You know, kind of
like a big womb.
So you're in the tub
with everything?
Yeah, the afterbirth floats.
Yeah.
Must be like the tide
at Omaha Beach.
No, it's actually
really hygienic, Creed.
After the birth, you get out...
I'm done.
Me, too... and you
deliver the afterbirth.
Hey, hey, no, no, no, no, no. No.
No. This is the birth story.
It was beautiful.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime
experience,
and I should have been there. I should
have been there to witness this.
I could have helped. You're
upset about this. I know that,
and I wish that I... But would it help if
you held Astrid for just a little bit?
Yeah.
Okay. All right.
I'm just going to lie down for a
couple of minutes. I'm exhausted.
So, remind me to talk to you about
Astrid's 529. Wake me in 20.
I usually love babies,
but when I held Astrid
I just felt...
Shortchanged.
Phyllis?
Could you take...
Sure.
Just for a second.
Okay.
Sweetheart.
Hey, guys.
What's up, Mike?
I need some advice from one
baby-daddy to another.
You a baby-daddy?
Yeah, I a baby-daddy.
When you first
became a baby-daddy,
did you have an immediate
connection with that baby?
Like, the first time that you held it,
did you find that with your baby baby?
Hell, yeah.
You know why?
'Cause that was my baby.
I just thought
as a baby-daddy...
You should stop calling
yourself "baby-daddy."
Why, Darryl? Because I'm quote
"white" quote, unquote?
Because you're not a daddy,
and it's not your baby.
Well... You feel connected
to his baby over there?
It's... That's different.
You feel connected to this?
That's not a baby. You want
to hold me, see how you feel?
Could I?
No.
Oh.
I was just catching up
on my sleep.
I can imagine.
Where's Astrid? I think
she's on a sales call.
On a what?
"Wah, more paper. Wah."
No, she's just on her coffee break.
That's funny.
She's with Angela.
That's good.
Now I need you to...
I need it to look up here.
Get the baby to look...
Okay.
...up here. Ready?
Yeah. Look at my finger.
Look. Look.
No. Come on, up here.
Look up here.
Your hand's in it.
What? Sorry.
What are you doing? Yeah,
that was a good one.
What's going on?
Excuse me.
We're taking a picture.
Honey, there you are.
She's nature's bounty. You don't
flash around a newborn baby.
Don't you know that?
What?
Michael, I need your help.
I was just going to...
I was going to talk to
Holly about her hygiene.
She smells like
old tomatoes and dirt.
Come on.
I like to call this
the bumper test.
Sure you can't stay
a little longer?
No, Michael,
you know what,
I really have to go.
Okay.
All right, everybody, they're leaving.
Jan and Astrid are leaving.
You know what, where is the
stroller that I came in with?
I took the liberty of putting it
in your trunk. Thanks, Dwight.
Okay. You know what, there is... There is
one more thing that you can do for me.
Okay.
Don't date Holly.
That's... I hate her.
Why? God, why would
you even ask me to...
I mean, not that it matters, 'cause I
don't, but... Okay. All right. Fine.
Thanks for the baby shower. It was great.
And I'll... I'll see you soon.
All right.
Okay.
You still going
to be mean to me?
Want to go out?
Yes.
I didn't feel much when I held Astrid,
but I got a good feeling from Holly.
Hey, it's Jim. Leave a message.
Hi.
Hey, this is Pam. Leave a message.
Hey. It's me. It is 5:03.
I figured I'd catch you
walking to your car, but...
Guess you must be out or something.
I'll leave a message.
Is it me or are we
just a little off today?
I guess this is just
one of those days.
It'll get better.
Hope you didn't have
any major laundry issues.
I finished my laundry.
Got all my socks.
Nothing like that time
that crazy guy pushed you.
Hey, do you remember that time
that I helped you do your laundry
and that crazy guy came in
and started yelling at you?
And then remember we went shopping the
next day to buy me a washer-dryer?
And yet, here you are,
back in a Laundromat.
You know, I'm just trying to
help you, Beesly. Be safe.
You're probably upset that I'm
even at a Laundromat right now,
but don't worry, I'm being
safe, and I'm headed home.
I'm headed to my dorm.
Not home.
Wish you were home.
Anyway...
Anyway,
I miss you.