Here are our final actual
costs for this year.
Okay.
As you can see,
we did pretty well, so...
Yes. Yes, I can see
that we did indeed.
Why don't you explain this to
me like I am an eight-year-old?
All right, well, this is the overall
budget for this fiscal year
along the X axis.
Yes. There's the X axix.
Right there.
You can see clearly on this
page that we have a surplus
of $4,300.
Okay.
But we have to spend that
by the end of the day
or it will be deducted
from next year's budget.
Why don't you explain
this to me like I'm five?
Your mommy and daddy
gave you $10
to open up a lemonade stand.
So you go out
and you buy cups
and you buy lemons
and you buy sugar.
And now you find out
that it only cost you $9.
So you have an extra dollar.
Yeah.
So you can give that dollar
back to Mommy and Daddy.
But guess what?
Next summer...
I'll be six.
And you ask them for money,
they're going to give you $9,
'cause that's what they think
it costs to run the stand.
So what you want to do is spend
that dollar on something now
so that your parents
think that it costs $10
to run the lemonade stand.
So the dollar's a surplus?
This is a surplus?
We have to spend that $4,300
by the end of the day
or it'll be deducted
from next year's budget.
We should spend this money on a new
copier, which we desperately need.
Okay. Break it down
in terms of...
Okay, I think
I'm getting you.
Guess what, everybody.
Christmas has
come early this year.
Oscar, very smartly,
has discovered
an extra $4,300
in the budget.
Thank you, Oscar.
And I have decided
with that money
I am going to buy a new...
Drum roll, please.
Can anybody guess?
New chairs?
No! A new copier!
All right.
Unless everybody can agree
on something better?
No, no, please.
Please do not do this.
Yes. Michael, new chairs.
These chairs are terrible. We were
supposed to get new ones last year.
So, we all agree to
get new chairs, then. Good?
Good. Yeah,
he said good. I'm good.
No, listen,
we are a paper company.
How can we take
pride in our jobs
if we have to put our fine paper
in this wretched machine?
Oscar, no.
This is not the time for one
of your principled stands.
Pam, you make more
copies than anyone.
Exactly. That should tell you
how terrible the chairs are.
Okay. Okay.
Good suggestions.
All good suggestions. Let's
just decide and agree upon one.
I'm with Pam. Chairs.
All right. So teams forming.
We should really have the
office's air quality tested.
I mean, we have radon
coming from below.
We have asbestos
in the ceilings.
These are silent killers.
You are the silent killer.
Go back to the annex.
You'll see.
Michael. I've talked to Meredith...
Yes.
...Stanley and Jim
about the chairs.
I know they're
with me on this.
Actually I'm going
to go with copier.
What? Jim.
Ever since Pam and
I started dating,
I just feel a little weird asking
her to make copies for me.
So I make my own copies.
And that copier sucks.
Let me tell you.
But you know what?
Pam and I don't have
to agree on everything.
Jim, good for you standing
up to Pam like that.
The balls on you, man.
So Michael,
what do you think?
Why me?
You have to
make the decision.
Wow! Okay. Well,
I swallowed all your ideas.
I'm going to digest them and see
what comes out the other end.
Dwight, I'm a little concerned
about some of these
directions to Schrute Farms.
Do tell.
I mean, like, "156 paces from the
light red mailbox, make a left.
"Walk until you
hear the bee hive."
How could it be
more clear?
They may not...
I think Andy makes
an excellent point.
Okay.
But my biggest concern is
that there's
only one bathroom.
We'll dig a trench.
As long as it's downhill from
the well, we should be fine.
Nana Mimi cannot
squat over some trench.
We're going to put out stumps.
Come on.
Let's three-way
this little issue
and come to a solution
by the time we get to Schrute Farms.
How's that for a plan?
We're getting married at
Schrute Farms, no matter what.
I have looked at 12 venues,
I have lost eight deposits
and I've seen Angela naked
zero times.
I am not losing
another deposit.
Hey.
So, I've been
thinking about this whole
chair/copier thing and...
Mmm-hmm.
I really think you
should reconsider.
Pam, I really
hate that copier.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah.
But I really think
you should reconsider.
Beesly, are you
threatening me?
Jim!
Jim, Jim, Jim,
I'm not threatening you.
I love you.
But you should know you're
on very dangerous ground.
All right.
Okay.
This is where you'll
have your receiving line.
Of course, we'll clear out all
the livestock and hay and such.
What's that smell?
You're going to need
to be more specific.
Manure. Get rid of it.
Manure covers up the smell
of the slaughterhouse.
Do you have to slaughter
on our wedding day?
You want to eat, don't you?
Honey, say something!
Dwight, if we pay extra,
can you slaughter the entrées
the day before?
I'll consider it.
See? That's how you do it.
We're making progress here.
Darn!
There's a hose out back.
Okay.
Remember you were going to get a
new chair and you were going to
give your old chair to me?
Remember that? Yes.
Well, that never happened.
Michael?
I don't know.
I haven't decided yet.
I'm just going
to grab some lunch.
Want to come with?
Really? Absolutely.
Yeah, that would be amazing.
Thank you. Are you
guys going to lunch?
Yes.
Mind if I join?
Oh, God!
All right. Let's go.
Yeah. Best lunch ever.
Let's do it.
All right.
- Cool.
- Where are we going?
I have no idea.
So I guess that's how
they're going to play this.
It is on.
It is so on.
Look, I really need
this new chair.
I mean seriously.
How is it possible
that in five years,
I've had two
engagement rings
and only one chair?
Stop...
Michael.
Michael,
that is hilarious.
There was so much
egg on my face!
The best.
Great food. Great friends.
Thank you, Michael.
Thank you, guys.
I got you some tiramisu,
so no hard feelings.
Yeah.
That's cool.
Good stuff.
You look really pretty.
Thank you.
Yeah?
Michael?
Yeah.
Hey, you got a second?
- I do.
- Good.
That must have been so fun.
It was fun.
We had a good time.
Have I told you,
you look really nice today?
Thank you.
Yeah. Is that a new tie?
No. No. No, I got it
at T.J. Maxx, $4.
That is amazing.
You think that's good,
check out these pants.
$9.
What?
$9. Boys' department.
No.
Look at the ass.
Check out the ass.
Look at that.
No way.
Yeah!
So I guess Oscar and Jim were
talking your ear off
about the new copier, huh?
Yes, they were.
Yeah.
They were.
Here's what I was thinking.
Everyone sits on
a chair every day.
But not everyone...
Sits on a copier.
Or even uses
the copier every day.
Yeah.
Yeah, right?
Very valid.
That's it.
Okay.
All right, see you later.
See you.
Hot-tie guy.
Well.
Have you made a decision
on the butter sculpture?
No. I haven't thought of it.
Okay, cow, goat or sheep.
It's not that hard.
I would like a cat.
Cats don't make butter.
I would like a cow-butter
sculpture of a cat.
It doesn't make any sense. I
am telling you! Yes, it does!
I want a butter
sculpture of a cat!
Cow, goat or sheep.
What is this?
Right. We're all on
the same team. Is it...
Why is that in the kitchen?
Close the DF cover.
I did, though.
You might want to consider
changing teams because we would...
We would love to have you.
No, copier's great.
Is it?
Yeah. I have my copies.
There they are.
And I have my original.
You got it.
So suck it.
Okay.
Michael, I got you
a hot chocolate.
I hope that's okay.
Thank you, my dear.
Wait, Michael, let me
open the door for you.
Well, chivalry is
not dead after all.
There he is.
Hello, hello. Hello.
Good to see you.
Yeah.
There's that ass.
Hey! Hey! Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't take it away.
I almost choked.
Here's another place.
It's beautiful.
So, why don't we try this out
to see what would happen?
Give it a little test drive.
What do you say?
You pretend to be
Angela's father,
you will play Angela
and I will pretend to be you.
That way you can see what it
looks like when you're up here.
Hello.
I'm Angela Martin and...
I'm Andy.
I work with Dwight.
He doesn't understand
a word you're saying.
What?
Although born just minutes from
here, he speaks only German.
Closed society.
So, now, after the readings
by all of your sisters,
we will arrive at the vows.
So, Conrad...
This is a little taste of
the ceremony, if you will.
He's explaining
why we're here,
what we're doing here,
making introductions...
Then he's going to have Andy
repeat a bunch of stuff.
He's going to ask Andy
to produce a ring.
I have now just a...
Just some twine
for our purposes.
And you will put
the ring on her finger.
Then he's going to ask Andy if
he would like to marry Angela,
and you will reply, "I do."
And he's going to ask Angela if
she would like to marry Andy,
to which you will reply...
I do.
And there we go.
That's just about it.
Man and wife.
Got a call about
a problem up here.
Did somebody call Hank?
Hank, thank God you're here.
The office is
at a crossroads.
So, there's no
security problem?
You know,
I hustled up the stairs.
Yes, I need
your sage advice.
And everyone, whatever Hank
decides, that is the decision.
That will resolve this issue.
Yeah, take as
many as you want.
Thank you. Thank you.
You know,
it's nice and warm up here.
Yes.
Well, what are we
talking about?
Okay, well,
we have a surplus.
Imagine that your parents give you
money for a lemonade stand...
I know what a surplus is.
Okay. Good. Good.
Well, here's the thing.
Some people want to use the
surplus to buy a new copier,
other people are complaining
about the chairs.
Is that the copier?
It is. Yes.
Hmm...
What? No, I was just thinking.
Let me see a chair.
Okay. Here we go.
You can try mine.
Hmm. Not much lumbar support.
Now, everyone bear in mind once
again that whatever Hank says goes.
He is an impartial
third party.
On the one hand,
this copier is very old.
You should see some of the
new copiers they have.
You would not
believe what they do.
So the copier?
- Well, let me finish.
- All right. Yes.
Now the chairs.
The chairs are very weak.
Very weak chairs. I could not
sit all day in this chair.
Well, what should I do?
Let me see the copier again.
All right, get out.
Get out. It's...
Dwight...
I thought I knew
what I wanted.
And then being here with you
and the German
Mennonite minister,
it just all felt right.
I made a mistake
picking Andy.
I know you did.
And that's why I have
taken care of everything.
What do you mean?
Well, monkey,
he's a real minister
and you said "I do"
and I said "I do" and Andy
wasn't signing a receipt.
He was signing our marriage
certificate as a witness.
Dwight, that doesn't count!
Yes, of course it does.
No! It doesn't.
It does in
the state of Pennsylvania.
Mrs. Schrute.
I didn't...
We are not married!
What?
Take this thing.
It's not my fault
you don't understand German!
I've been telling you
to take it for years!
Are we leaving or what?
Michael.
Hey, David.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm eating tiramisu.
Some of the chocolate powder
just went down my throat.
I'm stopping now.
Is this why
you're calling me?
No, no, no, no, no. No.
I'm calling...
Sorry.
Okay.
I'm calling because
we have a stupid budget
surplus and people...
Everybody wants
something different.
You want me to weigh in
on a minor budget issue?
No, no, no. I want you to make the
decision so I'm not the bad guy.
Well, if I were you I would
just return the surplus
and take the bonus.
The what now?
Branch managers who come in under
budget get 15% of the savings.
Like a tip?
$645?
I hate disappointing
just one person.
And I really hate
disappointing everyone.
But I love
Burlington Coat Factory.
You go in there with $645,
you are literally a king.
Yeah, we have that
going on Tuesday.
Okay?
Sure. No, I can... I'll
double-check that for you.
All right,
attention, everyone.
Let me call you
right back. Okay.
I have made my decision.
We do not need a new copier,
we do not need new chairs.
This copier is
working perfectly.
That's the original.
Pam, would you
stand up for a sec?
Hmmm.
See how relaxed I am?
I like this chair.
Offers good support.
It is erchonomically correct.
It's a good chair.
I think we're spoiled because we don't
appreciate the things that we have.
You think kids in
Africa have chairs? No.
They sit in big
piles of garbage.
Do you think
they have copiers?
They don't have copiers.
They don't even...
They don't even have paper. And we
are spoiled because we throw out
perfectly good tiramisu because
it has a little tiny hair on it.
My point is this, I have seen the
light in terms of what we need,
and it is nothing.
Do you know?
Do I know what?
I think you know.
No.
Know what?
Yeah, know what?
Does anyone happen to know
what 15% of 4,300 is?
$645.
Michael's a genius.
Right.
Why did you say "dollars"?
Because that is
how my mind works.
What's 15% of 200?
Thank you. Everyone, Michael
is returning the surplus
so he can keep
15% as a bonus.
Wait, what?
- You can do that?
- Hey, Michael.
What's 394 times 5912?
Let's see.
You're going to give yourself
a bonus of $645
instead of getting the entire
office something it really needs?
I don't need $645.
I already have $645,
more or less.
You're going to get us a copier then?
This is stupid.
Or chairs.
This is so, so stupid.
And, God, that's my phone.
I didn't hear
a phone ring.
To be continued!
No, I don't...
This doesn't change anything.
I have a very important
decision to make.
We need a new copier,
we need new chairs,
and I need to figure out
a way to keep this money
without having
everybody hate me.
Hey, Tuna, check it out.
Tuna sandwich.
Just like you.
What?
Now, I have to take
care of a legal issue.
Was that hot or what?
So what's it going to be?
Michael, you have
to make a decision.
The day is almost done.
Let me just say you've been
promising me this chair
since the day
you hired me.
You are a smart guy. I know
you'll do the right thing.
You think it's easy?
It's your job.
Okay, you know what, why
don't you guys deal with it?
I am going to get up and I'm going
to be out in the common area
but you need to decide, otherwise
I'm taking the bonus. All right?
It is a classic management tactic.
You have two sides,
a deadline, you know that neither
of them are going to concede,
what you do is you put them
in a room and you just...
Hey.
Hey!
Hey, we're going
with the chairs.
What?
I just figured I'd rather have
new chairs than nothing at all.
Thanks, Michael.
Good work.
I'm proud of you.
Mother...
What have we learned this week?
Well, one, thanks to me,
my team is much, much faster
at coming to decisions
than I thought they would be.
Number two, never buy a fur coat
with a credit card until you
absolutely have
the money to pay for it.
And three, you should know
that some people
think it's cool
to throw buckets
of fake blood on you
as you are walking out
of Burlington Coat Factory.
Truce?
Yeah, I guess, since I won.
You did win. You did win.
Anyway, I'm going to need three
copies of each of these,
stapled and collated.
I'm totally kidding.
I'm going to need four.