Last week,
I gave a fire safety talk,
and nobody paid
any attention.
It's my own fault
for using PowerPoint.
PowerPoint is boring.
People learn in
lots of different ways,
but experience is
the best teacher.
Today, smoking is
going to save lives.
Does anyone
smell anything smoky?
Did you bring
your jerky in again?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Fire!
Oh, fire! Oh, my goodness.
What's the procedure?
What do we do, people?
The phones are dead.
Oh. How did that happen?
It's out in the hall.
No. We don't know that.
The smoke could be coming
through an air duct.
Oh, my God!
Okay, it's happening.
Everybody stay calm.
Everybody stay calm!
What's the
procedure, everyone?
What's the procedure?
Stay... calm!
Everybody just... calm down!
No, no, Michael, no!
Touch the handle.
If it's hot there could
be a fire in the hallway!
What does warm mean? Oh, my gosh.
Try a different door.
Not a viable option.
What next?
- Don't run!
- Try the other door.
Here's a door. Check that one out.
How's the handle?
It's warm. Okay, go
to the back door.
Well, another option.
Another option.
Jeez! Okay,
settle down, everyone!
I forgot my purse!
Leave it, woman!
Get out of the way!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Things can be replaced,
Phyllis!
People, human lives,
however...
My hand! That's hot!
This one's hot, too.
Okay, we're trapped.
Everyone for himself!
Let's go! Let's go!
Get out of my way!
Okay. Okay. Okay!
Get out of the way!
Have you ever
seen a burn victim?
Move it!
Okay!
Procedure! Procedure!
Exit options!
Where do we go, folks?
Use a what to cover the mouth?
It's okay.
A what? A rag,
a damp rag perhaps.
Let's remember those procedures.
What are the options?
Okay! That's the wrong way.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
We've already tried that.
Remember your exit points.
Exit points, people.
Oscar?
What's next, huh?
Oscar!
Stay alive, I'm getting help!
Pull me up!
You're too heavy.
I only weigh 82 pounds.
Save Bandit!
How about 911? Anyone? 911?
What do we do?
Use the surge of
fear and adrenaline
to sharpen
your decision making.
Okay, I am not dying here.
Come on.
What is that?
The fire's shooting at us!
What in the name of God
is going on?
I'm trying to...
Help! Help!
Oh, my God!
Attention!
Employees of Dunder Mifflin!
This has been a test of our
emergency preparedness.
There's no fire.
It was only a simulation.
What?
Fire not real. This was
merely a training exercise.
So what have we learned?
Oh, come on.
It's not real, Stanley.
Oh, my God.
Don't have
a heart attack.
No, no, no, no,
you will not die!
Stanley! Stanley!
You will not die! Stanley!
Stanley! Barack is President!
You are black, Stanley! I'm
gonna give him mouth-to-mouth.
No, no, no. Don't give him
mouth-to-mouth for this.
He just swallowed
his tongue.
Michael! Michael! Open your mouth.
Don't swallow it!
I'm fine! Leave me...
I'm saving him!
How could you possibly
think this is a good idea?
A lot of ideas were not
appreciated in their time.
Electricity.
Shampoo.
You could have burned down
the whole building.
I just want to say, for the
record, I did not kill anyone.
Stanley was attacked
by his own heart.
And he should be
released from the hospital
and back in the office
in a couple days.
Did you shout "fire,"
causing a panic?
Yes, I shouted "fire."
I shouted many things.
I also shouted instructions on
how to get out of the building.
So you can imagine my
frustration, as safety officer,
when nobody would heed of...
Heeded... Heeded of...
"Head." "Head."
When no one headed...
"Take headed of."
No one would take headed
of my instructions.
So you...
"Heed." "Heed."
"Take heed of."
And I don't see my co-workers
heeding this right now.
Wait, what?
Okay.
The city.
Dwight.
We are not mad,
we are just disappointed.
No, we are mad.
Yes, we are.
We are livid.
But we are going to
let this one slide.
Thank you.
No, we're not.
I am not
a mind reader, David.
Look, this is
a very serious offense.
We have cause to fire you.
Can you shove down?
Instead...
Shove down, please.
Instead what I think
we should do is
strip you of your title
as safety officer. No.
And we should take
a part of his pay
and donate it to the
charity of your choice.
Something that
Dwight doesn't like.
PETA.
Michael, you have to
take responsibility here.
One of your employees
had a heart attack.
He could have died
because of the way
you're allowing
your office to run.
Do you want that
on your conscience?
Do you?
Michael?
Are you talking to me?
Yeah.
What?
Well, I guess we papered
over that pretty nicely.
Always amuses me when corporate
thinks they can make some big change
with a 20-minute meeting
in some fancy high rise.
What's the matter?
Are you hungry?
No, Dwight,
I am worried.
A man's life is
in my hands.
Now don't you
worry about that.
I got it covered. Okay?
I am planning a bomb scare that
should really get the blood pumping.
That's not going to happen.
I'm taking over
as safety man.
What? You?
Yes.
Come on.
I'm a smart guy.
That's preposterous. I'll figure it out.
No. I will.
Nobody should have to
go to work thinking,
"Oh, this is the place
that I might die today."
That's what a hospital's for.
An office is for not dying.
An office is a place to live life
to the fullest, to the max. To...
An office is a place
where dreams come true.
Don't excite him.
Don't make him excitable.
Welcome back, Stanley.
Thank you, Michael.
It's true, around this
office in the past
I have been a little
abrupt with people.
Not maybe, yes or no.
No way. Uh-uh.
Are you from another planet?
Boy, have you
lost your mind?
Because I'll
help you find it!
Did I stutter?
I'm done. Goodbye.
But the doctor said
if I can't find a new way
to relate more positively to my
surroundings, I'm going to die.
Andy.
A throne for your highness.
I'm not sitting
in a wheelchair.
No, no, no.
No debate.
You are going to
sit in that wheelchair
until you are
back on your feet.
I'm going to die.
ABC, okay?
And that stands for "Airway,
Breathing and Circulation."
Okay. You know what? That
could be a little confusing,
because in sales ABC
means "Always Be Closing."
This is a farce. I should
be teaching this course.
Shut it. Shut it.
We found ourselves on the
less prepared side of things
when Stanley had his...
When his heart went berserk.
And I knew
exactly what to do.
But in a much more real sense,
I had no idea what to do.
So I thought we should have
a CPR training class.
And of course you can't
get the practice dummy
unless the instructor
comes along with it.
Red Cross and their racket.
I can't keep
doing this forever.
It's been 20 seconds.
Call it.
Would you like to try next?
Absolutely I would not.
You know who I really
think should go?
Stanley.
Oh, I don't know.
It's not a good idea, Michael.
He needs to rest.
No rest for the sick.
We are not always
going to be there
to coddle your heart back when
it disappears to be working.
What are you going to do if you're
by yourself and your heart stops?
I would die.
And you're
okay with that?
I'm okay with
the logic of it.
Uh-uh. No, no, no. Come on.
Get up. Let's do this.
Yes,
I had a heart attack.
I would quit, but I'm too
old to find another job.
And I don't have
enough saved to retire.
I feel like I'm
working in my own casket.
Come on, Stanley!
You're losing you!
You're losing you! Do it!
Michael. This is you
we're talking about.
Michael.
Okay, okay, I'll show them.
Here we go.
- All right.
- So assessing the situation.
Are they breathing?
No, Rose.
They are not breathing.
And they have no arms or legs.
No, that's not part of it.
Where are they?
You know what?
If we come across somebody
with no arms or legs, do we
bother resuscitating them?
I mean, what kind of quality
of life do we have there?
I would want to
live with no legs.
How about no arms?
No arms or legs is basically how
you exist right now, Kevin.
You don't do anything.
All right. Well, let's get back
to it, because you're losing him.
Okay, too fast.
Everyone, we need to pump at a
pace of 100 beats per minute.
Okay. That's hard to keep track.
How many is that per hour?
How is that
going to help you?
I will divide and then count to it.
Right.
Okay, well, a good trick
is to pump to the tune of
Staying Alive by the Bee Gees.
Do you know that song?
Yes, yes. I do.
I love that song.
First I was afraid,
I was petrified
No, it's...
Stayin' alive,
stayin' alive
Okay. That's enough. You were
in the parking lot earlier.
That's how I know you.
Stayin' alive,
stayin' alive
Stayin' alive, stayin' alive
Well, you can tell by
the way I use my walk
I'm a woman's man,
no time to talk
Music loud, women warm Been
kicked around since I was born
Well, it's all right
It's okay
You can look the other way
Okay! Okay!
Stayin' alive,
stayin' alive
Yeah. Okay, you didn't maintain
a hundred beats per minute.
And the ambulance didn't arrive
because nobody called 911.
So you lost him.
Okay, he's dead.
Anyone know what we do next?
Anybody? Rose?
I have no idea.
Anyone else?
We bury him. Wrong! Check
for an organ donor card.
If he has one, we only
have minutes to harvest.
He has no wallet,
I checked.
He is an organ donor.
He is?
Get me some ice
and Styrofoam bucket.
Here we go.
- Oh, my God!
- Dwight!
Dwight!
Dwight, what are you...
What are you doing?
We search for the organs. Where's
the heart? The precious heart.
I'm not feeling well.
I need to sit down.
Stanley.
Hey, Stanley.
Are you okay?
Oh, my God!
Dwight!
Clarice.
Oh, my God.
Can you tell me why you had to
cut the face off the dummy?
I didn't think it was very
realistic in the movie,
and it turns out
it's pretty realistic.
We had to pay for it.
It cost us $3,500.
$5,300 for a dummy?
Wow.
Well, okay, look.
David, this is
why we have training.
We start with the dummy and
we learn from our mistakes.
And now Dwight knows not to cut
the face off of a real person.
Hope you brought your
apetitos, my lady, my Tuna.
A little movie popcorn.
Damn it.
This movie,
a lot of buzz.
Not coming out
for another six months.
Mrs. Albert Hanaday.
So the friendship with the
Nard-Dog has its privileges.
We don't normally
download films illegally
because we're honest,
hard-working people.
And we don't know how.
But Andy does, so we have
to watch it with him.
Punishment fits
the crime.
I want you to meet my nana.
Nana, this is Sam.
Hi. Nice to meet you,
Mrs. Hanaday.
Please, call me Lily.
Let's play bridge.
You can be my partner.
All right, Lily.
What's going on?
No one really knows, but Pam's
parents are going through
a little bit of a rough
patch in their marriage.
My dad spent the night
at our place last night.
My parents have been fighting
for weeks and it kind of sucks.
Jim's been great.
But I'm going to need
to buy my dad a robe.
He's not saying
what he needs to say.
Hmm?
Who? Jack Black?
Yeah.
I mean, they just need to
communicate, you know.
If they said to each other what they're
saying to everyone else, then...
Hmm.
Jim and Pam are
like movie geniuses.
They're catching things that are
totally going over my head.
Hi, everyone.
Corporate has given
Dwight two strikes.
They are very,
very upset with him.
So, as a
disciplinary measure,
he is going to have to
issue a formal apology.
Dwight, have you prepared
your statement of regret?
I have.
Let's hear it.
I state my regret.
You couldn't have
memorized that?
I could not
because I do not feel it.
Okay, everyone,
I'm going to need you
to sign
this statement of regret
as an acknowledgment
that you heard it.
Okay? Everyone come on up here.
It's not a big deal.
It is a big deal.
You almost killed Stanley.
Yeah, right. I filled him full
of butter and sugar for 50 years
and forced him
not to exercise.
Now take a lesson
from Stanley
and jog on up here
and sign this. Okay?
Make a line. Just form
a line right here.
Sign it! Sign it now!
Hi, Dad.
Yeah, Jim has shaving cream.
Check our bathroom.
Lily?
I'm in here.
I... I'm sorry.
I didn't
realize you were
in the bath.
Do you want me to go?
I want you to stay.
Oh, boy.
Oh, man.
You know, Lily was supposed
to be Nicole Kidman.
And it was going to be
Sophie's mom, not grandmother.
But then Nicole Kidman
dropped out,
so they went with
Cloris Leachman,
- with a small rewrite.
- Just give me your hand
and get that in there.
Help me pull it around.
Oh, yeah. You did
that one already.
I know,
but if I get it deeper...
What is...
He was pretty
talkative at breakfast.
What?
Breakfast?
You mean when they
were eating soup?
I don't think
that was breakfast.
Unless soup... Does soup
symbolize breakfast?
So he doesn't share
with his daughter,
but he shares with
his daughter's fiancé?
You guys, they're making out.
Hey.
Did my dad say
anything about my mom?
No. We mostly just
talked about cereal.
What?
I don't know.
I mean, maybe he'll talk to
you about some of the stuff
'cause he can't
really talk to me about it.
Mmm...
You're good to talk to.
I'm okay. I'm not great. And...
Everybody sit on the floor,
Indian-style like me.
My God,
if you're wearing a dress,
please keep your knees together,
nobody wants to see that.
My goal is to make
this office as peaceful
a place for Stanley Hudson
as I can.
And I think sounds have
a lot to do with that.
Here are some downloaded
peaceful sounds.
That one makes me think
of death.
It's kind of nice.
It is
a beautiful, sunny day
as we walk
through the meadow.
That is very
spiritual and relaxing.
And there are flowers and
it is sunny and beautiful.
Now, up ahead,
a castle in the distance.
Don't open your eyes.
What? Oh.
And you walk up
toward the castle.
And inside the castle
are four men,
and each of them...
None of them have shoes.
And they give you
a funny cigarette
and you feel
even more relaxed,
and then you want ice cream.
You want a big bowl
of ice cream.
So what kind of ice cream do you want?
Yell it out.
Chunky Monkey.
Too expensive.
Chocolate.
Racism is dead, Stanley.
You can have any kind
of ice cream you want.
What do you want?
What is that?
People, please,
I told you to get rid
of the cell phones.
It's my bio-feedback machine.
Oh, okay. What is that,
like a video game?
It alerts me when my stress level
goes up, so I can try to calm down.
You have stress?
Yes.
During our
relaxation exercise?
Let me
get you some water.
No, no, I'll help you up.
I'll help you up.
Here we go. Here we go.
Let me get you up.
No, Michael.
Would you step back?
Please, please.
Okay. All right.
- A little further.
- Okay.
That's better.
Okay.
I think that thing
is on the fritz.
Oscar, would you reach over
and touch his thing?
That's what he said. Right, guys?
Because of gay.
Let's give this a shot.
Hello!
Michael, I think you're what's
stressing everybody out.
So it wasn't
Dwight after all.
Looks like I'm the killer.
You never expect
that you're the killer.
It's a great twist.
Great twist.
Dunder Mifflin. This is Pam.
Oh. Hey, Mom. No.
What did Dad say?
What did you say to my dad?
What?
After you talked,
he called my mom
and said he was gonna look
for an apartment.
Oh, my God. Pam, I don't know.
I...
Nothing, truly nothing.
I mean, I just was
honest with him and I...
I'm so sorry. I don't know.
I'll call him again.
50 percent of marriages
end in divorce,
so it was her parents
or my parents.
What could Jim have said to make
my dad want to leave my mom?
And at what point in our marriage
is he gonna say it to me?
I don't get it.
Do I stress you out?
Nothing stresses me out.
Except having to seek
the approval of my inferiors.
Speaking of which...
Remember when
people used to say "boss"
when they were describing
something that was really cool?
Like, "Those shoulder pads
are really boss, man."
"Look at that perm.
That perm is so boss."
It's what made me
want to become a boss.
And I looked so good
in a perm and shoulder pads.
But now boss is just slang
for "jerk in charge."
Okay, everybody,
I figured it out.
The reason that you are
all so stressed around me
is that you are
too intimidated
to tell me
what you really think.
You are keeping these feelings
inside and that is causing stress.
So, what is the solution?
Solution is honesty,
laughter and comedy.
In short...
A vacation.
What? No. No. I'm talking about
a roast of Michael Scott.
Come on. Who here has the
Comedy Central Roast Channel?
You've seen it, right?
Everybody gets together and you start
hurling insults at the one guy,
and everybody's laughing and
everybody is hugging each other.
Michael, are you serious? Do you
really want us to roast you?
That's offensive.
It's not!
It's not offensive during a roast.
Anything goes.
And I want you guys to
really get cracking on this.
I want you to take me down.
Don't hold back.
I want you to really make fun
of anything about me.
It could be my race, could
be the fact that I'm so fit,
or I'm a womanizer,
fair game. Whatever.
I don't want to write
your stuff for you,
but I just want it
to be good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, man. Oh, my God.
I consider myself
a good person,
but I'm gonna try
to make him cry.
I can already feel people's
stress starting to melt.
I think they're very excited about
paying their respects this way.
I've got to make sure that
YouTube comes down to tape this.
May I have your attention,
please? Sign in.
Sign in on the sign-in sheet,
the clipboard.
This meeting is mandatory,
if you do not sign in,
your name will not be counted.
Thank you.
Hey, this is
your apology letter.
It was the last signature
I needed.
Welcome, welcome,
welcome, welcome, welcome!
You are all jerks.
Just kidding.
Not yet, anyway.
Welcome to the roast
of Mr. Michael Scott.
If you are here for
the Grabowski wedding,
it is the second door
on the left.
So, we all know
how these work.
It needs to get crazy.
Take your best shot.
I'm going to sit
right over chair.
And whoever wants to come up
and roast me, you may. Okay.
Lower the mike
for the midget.
If you ever wondered whether
you were Michael Scott,
here's a quiz to help.
If you ever put sun block on a
window, you might be Michael Scott.
I normally don't enjoy
making people laugh.
If you ever called
the fire department
because your head was stuck in
your chair, you might be...
Michael Scott.
Hey, hey.
I don't go make burgers
where you work
and then tell you
how to make burgers.
I have made a list of people
that I would make out with
before I would make out
with Michael Scott.
A turtle, a fridge,
anybody from the warehouse.
Yeah!
A wood chipper, Kevin,
a candle and Lord Voldemort.
Anyway,
happy birthday, Michael.
Yeah.
You'd be so lucky. Good one.
Michael, you ran over
me with your car.
You posted a picture of my bare
boobs on the bulletin board
with a caption
that said, "Gross."
Well...
Michael, you are
the reason I drink.
You are the reason
I live to forget.
No, no, friends only.
Friends only!
Several times a day,
Michael says words
that are way
beyond my vocabulary.
I know where
this is going.
Do you?
No.
Okay.
Remember spider face?
No.
Okay, because
the quote was,
"Cut off your nose
to spider face."
Spider... Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
How dare you all
attack him like this?
No, stop it.
Michael is your superior, okay?
Dwight. No, no, no, no.
You should be bowing
down in front of him.
Hey, hey. Right now. Okay?
They don't understand who they have.
That is the way
you're supposed to do it, idiot.
You're interrupting me.
I'm trying to get your back.
I'm trying to... Idiot, idiot.
Idiot. Are you
calling me an idiot?
Don't you ever
talk to me that way,
you pathetic
short little man.
You don't have any friends
or any family or any land!
- Yeah!
Well, I just want to take a
minute to talk to you all
about something
very serious.
Once every hour, someone is
involved in an Internet scam.
That man is
Michael Scott.
He's supporting about
20 Nigerian princesses.
Hey, you know what?
Forgive me for caring, right?
Well, you know, Michael
is a great delegator.
He never does
any work himself, ever.
And one time I walked in on him
naked and his thing is so small.
How small is it?
If it were an iPod,
it would be a shuffle.
All right, can I make
just a little announcement?
In a professional roast,
usually the roaster
will say something nice about
the roastee after they're done.
Something about how much they love
them, so just keep that in mind.
Mike claims
we're all a family.
You know what... We are.
We are a family.
Okay, so, what's his name?
All the way in
the back there.
Oh, very funny.
What's his name?
Uh...
I'm thinking Roy.
Roy left years ago.
What's his name?
I don't believe
I've had the pleasure.
Michael, I gave you
a ride home last week
and we spent
an hour in traffic.
What's his name?
Jefferson.
Nope. His name is Michael.
What I hate about you
You really suck as a boss
You're the laziest, jerkiest And
you're dumber than an apple sauce
We're stuck
listening to you all day
Stanley tried to die
just to get away
Well, it's true
That's what I hate about you
Yeah!
And now a man who deserves no
introduction, Michael Scott.
Thank you very much.
Thank you. That was great.
Great job, some great laughs.
Really, really went after
my intelligence there.
Dozens of online IQ tests
might prove you wrong, but...
And my thing isn't tiny, it's
average, so get your facts straight.
So when I heard that there was going to
be a roast in my honor, I thought...
Sorry. I think I have
a frog in my throat.
Um...
I decided to jot down some quick
thoughts about you people.
Um...
First up, Phyllis and Kevin.
Dunder Mifflin. This is Pam.
I'm sorry, Michael's
not here right now.
Can I take a message?
Great. I will. Thanks.
It's very unusual for Michael
not to show up to work.
My guess,
he's either deeply depressed
or an icicle has snapped off his
roof and impaled his brain.
He has this terrible habit of
standing directly underneath them
and staring up at them.
And I always say,
"Michael, take two steps back
"and stare at the icicle
from the side."
And he's like,
"No, I like the way they look
"from standing
directly underneath them."
It was only a matter of time.
Michael is so dumb
that he tries to put his
M&M's in alphabetical order.
All right, Kevin, enough
with the Michael jokes.
I think he got it
bad enough yesterday.
I'm almost done.
That reeks
and I'm trying to eat.
Attention, everyone, I've
just got a text from Michael.
He says "personnel day."
Are we hiring?
Yeah. You're being replaced.
I think he meant
personal day.
I don't know.
That's quite a leap, Pam.
I hope he's okay.
I feel bad.
Give it up. He's dead.
He just sent a text.
What's a text?
You know, sometimes
to get perspective,
I like to think about a spaceman
on a star incredibly far away,
and our problems don't
matter to him
because we're just
a distant point of light.
But he feels sorry for me
because he has an incredibly
powerful microscope
and he can see my face.
I'm okay.
No, I'm not.
Phyllis, there's
a package for you.
Oh.
Sign here.
Okay.
What?
Got it!
Sam, Sam, Sam.
It's not that you
dumped my granddaughter,
and it's not that you want children,
it's that you lied to me.
Can't you see that?
Can't you see?
I can never trust you.
Lily, no. Lily.
Lily, please.
Lily, stop!
I don't care how
much time we have left.
I don't care
what my friends say.
And I don't care
what your mom thinks.
Frankly, I'm pretty sure
she's not making any sense.
Please, move back
to my apartment.
Lily, I'm not giving up.
I'm not giving up.
Lily, Lily!
Push the reverse button!
Reverse the button!
Sam. Sam.
Hey, Dad. No, I know.
Mom told me.
Okay. Yeah,
I'll see you then.
So what did he say?
Was it my fault?
Yeah.
He said that you told him
how much you love me,
about how you feel
when I walk in a room
and about how you've never
doubted for a second
that I'm the woman you want to
spend the rest of your life with.
I guess he's never felt that
with my mom, even at their best.
You okay?
Yeah.
When you're a kid, you assume
your parents are soul mates.
My kids are gonna
be right about that.
I guess it also means
that sometimes love affairs look
different to the people inside them.
I'm not insightful enough
to be a movie critic.
Maybe I could be
a food critic.
These muffins taste bad.
Or an art critic.
That painting is bad.
Michael, it's
really good to see you.
Hey, why are you
wearing a turtleneck?
You all right?
Michael, I feel I was
a little harsh yesterday.
Yeah. Yeah, we're really sorry.
I spent the afternoon in the
park trying to feed the pigeons.
I guess they all flew
west for the winter.
And I just had some thoughts that I
wanted to share with you people.
What?
Well, I wrote them down
so I wouldn't forget.
Jim, you're 6'11"
and you weigh 90 pounds.
Gumby has
a better body than you.
Boom. Roasted.
Dwight, you're a kiss-ass.
Pam, you failed art school.
Boom. Roasted.
Meredith, you've slept
with so many guys
you're starting
to look like one.
Boom. Roasted.
Kevin, I can't decide
between a fat joke
and a dumb joke.
Boom. Roasted.
Creed, your teeth called, your
breath stinks. Boom. Roasted.
Angela, where's Angela?
Well, there you are.
I didn't see you behind that grain of rice.
Boom. Roasted.
Stanley, you crush
your wife during sex
and your heart sucks.
Boom. Roasted.
Oscar, you are...
Oscar, you're gay.
Wow.
Andy, Cornell called, they think you
suck and you're gayer than Oscar.
Boom. Roasted.
All right. All right, everybody.
You know I kid.
You guys are the reason that I
went into the paper business.
So, good night, God bless.
God bless America.
And get home safe.
Yeah.
They say that laughter
is the best medicine,
so, Stanley, you can
throw away those pills.
You are cured.
Actually, better hold on
to the pills, just in case.