Michael, since it is your fifteenth
anniversary at the company,
I thought it might be appropriate
to begin the festivities
with a 15-minute
round of applause.
I like it.
Followed by a 15-minute
moment of silence.
I don't know.
Is it classy enough?
Jim, enough with
the classy, okay?
I just feel like after 15
years at this company...
Bravo, by the way.
That we should celebrate with a very
classy event, a night to remember.
I think you're right.
This party has to have
all the excitement, drama
and intrigue of my time here.
And, of course, classy.
And classy, yeah.
Michael, you're just agreeing with
him 'cause he's wearing a tux.
Don't you see
what he's doing here?
Last week, Dwight sent out a
memo about the dress code.
So, this is me showing him that
I'm taking it very seriously.
Oh! Here's one. A string quartet
playing classical music.
You know, that's good, but it's not classy.
I need something
classy, like the opening
of a car dealership.
That's it.
Or Mr. Peanut.
Yes.
Mr. Peanut is not classy.
He is.
He is a regular peanut.
He just happens to have a cane,
a monocle and a top hat.
That's what
makes him classy.
Okay,
how about this?
An ice sculpture
shaped like you
covered in chocolate-covered
strawberries.
Dwight, you're trying too hard,
and that's just not classy.
See, the thing about classy
is, it's a state of mind.
Well, I'm sorry. I just don't
know what classy is, then.
Okay, let's just try
this one on for size,
and I apologize, 'cause it's
right off the top of my head.
An ice sculpture of you
completely surrounded
by a variety of
chocolate-covered fruits.
Strawberries?
That's inspired.
I said that!
Not classy.
Not classy at all.
Déclassé.
French!
Classy.
Hi, can I help you?
Yeah, I'm Charles Miner,
here to see Michael Scott.
Sure, just one second,
please. Have a seat.
Yes?
Michael,
there's a Charles Miner
here to see you.
Miner? I hardly know her!
Hello?
Yeah, are you
coming out now?
Uh-huh.
Well, well, well,
who have we here?
It is Prince
Charles Miner!
At your service. Everybody,
this is Sir Charles Miner,
and he is the new VP
for the Northeast region,
so just give it up
for this big guy, right?
Give it up!
Here he is.
There he is.
Hey. Hi.
Hi, everyone...
Wow! Hold that thought.
You know what? I want everybody
to go into the break room.
I have a little
surprise for you.
Go ahead. You, too.
Dwight, would you escort
our guest in there?
Come on. Here we go.
Don't be shy.
Don't be shy,
you're one of us.
Dwight, stall him a little bit.
I have to get the fish.
Hey.
Yes?
Really wish you would've told me
the new boss was coming today.
What? No! I didn't want to
make everybody nervous.
No, I mean I could've brought
a change of clothes, or...
You look dynamite.
What are you
talking about?
Very slick. Okay,
let me get the fish.
Originally founded in 1866,
Scranton quickly became
one of Pennsylvania's
largest anthracite
coalmining communities.
Surprise!
There's nothing in here.
The real surprise is
in the conference room.
Let's go!
God! Okay, come on!
Come on!
I'll finish it up later, but essentially
what we're talking about is...
Surprise!
As you can see,
I turned the bagels
from O's into C's,
for Charles.
Thank you.
Took me all night.
This is what you
did last night?
I met this guy at
corporate last week,
and we were just
digging each other's vibe.
I was totally grooving
on him, and vice versa.
And besides, the last two
people to have his job
were Jan and Ryan.
The former was my lover, and the
latter my best friend, so who knows?
I do.
It's gonna be mental!
It's going to be mental.
Oh, my God, he's like
a black George Clooney.
Really?
I don't see it.
I mean, he's okay. He's
not unattractive, he's...
Hey, how you doing?
I'm Jim Halpert,
from sales.
Hey.
Just wanted to say,
if you need anything,
let me know.
Why are you
wearing a tuxedo?
I didn't think you'd notice.
It's funny, actually. There's
another salesman out here,
Dwight Schrute, he sent out
this memo, as he always does,
and it was about professionalism
in the workplace,
and of course
he singled me out.
So I just had
to mess with him.
You'd understand if
you read the memo,
which I should
probably get you.
There's probably
one in the drawer.
It was pretty crazy.
But...
Not more crazy than
wearing a tux at work.
I'll grant you that,
so I'm gonna...
Your name's Jim?
Jim Halpert, yep,
so just gonna let you
get back to it, so...
He just had to
wear his tux today.
I thought I'd be funny.
Took him 40 minutes
to get ready.
All right, let me introduce
you to some of the troops.
Accounting,
front and center.
Come on up here. I'd like
you to meet somebody.
This is
the accounting department.
Hey. I come
from accounting, too.
Nerd alert!
This is Oscar Martinez.
He is Latino,
and he just got out of a long-term
relationship with a man, Gil,
who broke his heart, but he didn't
bring any of that into work,
it did not affect his job
performance whatsoever,
and I am very proud of him
for that.
Hey, Oscar,
it's good to meet you. Good.
This little hell-raiser
is Angela.
She has slept with a bunch of
different guys in the office.
The one over there,
in the orange.
Heyo!
Heyo.
Where's the other...
You know, Michael, I don't need to
know everyone's sexual history.
Well, perfect, because we
have now arrived at Kevin,
and he
has no sexual history.
Hey!
How about I just say hi
to everyone at one time?
Good! Good, good, good.
Everyone please give
it up for Charles Miner.
Thank you, Michael. Thank you
for the C-shaped bagels.
Well... Above and beyond.
Great. That's great.
Hey, you know,
we're in tough times,
and we're not immune
to this economy.
That's true.
But the goal is
to, you know, fight
our way through this.
Stanley Hudson. Are there
going to be layoffs?
No, absolutely not.
Hold on, Michael,
thank you.
Stanley, you know,
we can't make any promises,
but we'll try everything in
our power to avoid that.
Do you have specifics?
Well, Michael should have
filled you in last week.
Well, due to the economy, there's
a lot of worry going around.
I didn't want to worry people. Well...
You didn't tell them.
Why don't...
Yeah, what I told Michael...
Charles is going
to tell you.
...is that we are cutting
3% across the board,
which means we will
no longer be matching
401 contributions,
and all overtime
requests will need
to come through
the corporate office.
Fantastic.
Well, it's not official.
It is official. It is official...
Well...
And actually, guys,
I'm encouraging branches
to consider a freeze
on discretionary spending.
Such as salary benefits,
etcetera, etcetera...
No, no.
...insurance.
Not salaries.
Petty cash, supplies and parties.
Things like that.
Well... No.
What about your party?
Okay, okay.
You know what?
I think this has been great.
I think this gives us a lot
to think about, doesn't it?
Charles Miner, ladies and gentlemen.
He has a long trip home.
Thank you for coming in.
We have to get back to work!
Michael, I'm going
to stay for the day.
Oh, no, you don't
have to do that.
I've got this covered. This
was just a meet and greet.
No, this is a little
more involved than that.
I'm gonna set up
in here, okay?
I am thrilled
that the new boss
has taken such
an active interest
in all of the responsibilities
that I'm supposed to have.
Thrilled.
David,
it was my understanding
that I was not
going to be managed.
What gave you that idea?
It was my understanding.
I see.
Listen, why don't we just
leave that position vacant?
Truth be told,
I think I thrive
under a lack of
accountability.
Look, Michael,
Charles is very qualified.
Get to know him.
I really think the two of you
are going to make a great team.
But the branch is still mine?
You're still
the branch manager, yes.
And if you need anything else
at all, just let Charles know.
Ask him about the party.
Right. David, are you coming to
my fifteenth anniversary party?
I'll give it my
best shot, Michael.
No, no, no,
the other thing.
Okay. If we hire Cirque du
Soleil as salaried employees,
will that help us with
the year-end tax stuff?
Think he hung up?
No.
I just got off the horn with David
Wallace, and he said that you and I
should try to get to know each
other better, and I agree.
So, what I would like you
to do is tell me something
that you've never
told anybody before.
No.
Come on.
What's your wife's name?
Where did you work
before you came here?
Saticoy Steel.
Beautiful!
See, African-Americans have such
a rich history of unusual names.
No, I worked at a company
called Saticoy Steel.
You're not from paper?
No.
Does David know this?
Yeah, he knows.
He just wants
a good manager.
Well, that actually is
an excellent segue into,
really, what is my only point...
Yeah, what is that?
...and that is, I don't need
to be managed, Charles.
And if you want to pick up
some tips observing here
and take them to the other
branches, it's all good,
but Jan would mostly come by
when she was super horny
and Ryan would come by to visit
his parents and do laundry, so...
Are we clear?
That's not how I plan
on doing things.
Okay, okay.
Well, I'll just
bounce that off David.
See what comes back.
I'll tell David
what he needs to know.
Sorry.
David wants it this way.
Whatever David wants.
Okay.
Michael Scott
calling for David.
Well, just tell him to call
me ASAP as possible. Thanks.
Michael, come on, no.
You have to charm them.
David Wallace's office.
Hey there, gorgeous.
How you doing today?
I'm good, thank you.
How's it hanging?
All right.
Good, listen.
My name is Michael
Scotch,
and I just wanted to say
that I've got David Wallace's
son in the trunk of my car.
If he doesn't get on this
phone in five seconds,
I'm gonna start...
What are you doing? God!
Oh, my God.
David Wallace's office.
Hi, Stephanie,
it's Michael Scott again.
I just spoke
with Michael Scotch,
and the son's
going to be returned.
Everything's fine.
Michael...
And I really, really
need to talk to David.
Please hold.
Charles Miner.
Hello? Hello, who is this?
Who is this?
I was never given a name.
Hi, can I help you?
I don't think anyone here...
Pam. Hey, everyone,
lunch is on me today.
Whoa!
Wow! That is so unnecessary.
Are you kidding me
with this?
On the day that
I bring in breakfast?
Hey, man,
it's no big deal.
I wish you had told us sooner,
because I was going to go
to the vending machine
and get an egg salad.
You still have
that option.
Thanks again, Charles.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Nobody thanked me for
breakfast except Charles.
You say no more parties,
and then you spend all
of this money on lunch.
I think it's
a little hypercritical.
I do this for
every branch I go to.
If you do not like it, then I
think there are some bagels
left over
from this morning.
Damn it, Stephanie,
put me through to him.
Is that him in the background?
David?
David.
David, pick up the phone.
Should I seduce him?
No. No one
wants to see that.
Michael.
Okay. Yep?
I just realized that
I used the 2008 calendar
to do the spreadsheets
for January and February.
I may need to come in
this weekend to fix it.
Do some overtime.
Want to do some
overtime this weekend?
You know what, Kevin?
I applaud your initiative.
Yes, you may.
No, sorry, Michael.
No, Kevin, right?
Gonna need you to do that
during office hours.
Okay.
Okay. Thank you.
Kevin, this is my branch.
You don't ask Charles.
You ask me.
I say approved.
That's not the way
it's gonna work.
Yes, it is.
No, it is not.
Okay, so we're on
the same page, great.
the same page, great!
Okay, Michael.
No, seriously.
How old are you?
Oh, no.
I can tell Michael's mood by which
comedy routine he chooses to do.
The more infantile,
the more upset he is.
And he just skipped the Ace
Ventura talking-butt thing.
He never skips it.
This is bad.
Five years old.
Dude, stop.
Michael!
This is great.
- Michael, stop doing that!
- This is great.
- ...a whole mess of trouble.
- Stop it!
I'm going to walk away.
Stop doing that!
I'm kidding around.
Wow! Relax, everybody.
It's just a joke.
It's fine.
Boy, so touchy. PPC, let's
continue our morning meeting
in the conference room.
And then out of that cake pops another
stripper holding a smaller cake,
and then an even smaller
stripper pops out of that one.
What is that
smaller stripper holding?
A cupcake.
Nice.
It's cupcakes and strippers
all the way down.
Okay.
What exactly is the PPC?
That's the Party
Planning Committee.
They spend hours
planning parties.
Excuse me, guys.
What's going on in here?
Party Planning Committee.
Not your concern, Charles.
This doesn't seem like a good
way to spend company time.
Really? Well, then,
how would we come up
with great ideas
like Jim's? Go ahead.
No, I would like to get
back to work, actually.
- Please.
- What you got, Jim?
What is
a two-way petting zoo?
You pet the animals,
they pet you back.
It's a great idea.
And we have a cake
in the shape of
a bale of hay.
It's really just
a regular-shaped cake...
- But it's cool, and it's...
- No.
This isn't a good use
of company time, Michael.
Whoa. You're talking about
my anniversary party, so...
Okay, everyone except for
Michael, go back to your desks.
Thank you very much. Yeah,
why don't you do that?
Yeah, here we go. Okay.
Okay.
Okay, Michael, I'm
dissolving this committee.
What?
Yeah, I mean, come on!
This is a workplace. It isn't
designed for your vanity.
Newsflash. I've been
here for 15 years.
Headline. You have
been here one day.
End of story.
You have no right to cancel my
fifteenth anniversary party.
End of story. End of story!
End of story!
I don't care
if I've hurt your feelings
or you do not agree with my
methods, but it is over.
Okay, no, no, no, you know what?
I'm going to New York,
and I am going to talk
to David Wallace.
I'm going to
tell him everything,
and I'm sorry to say,
you're screwed.
And you know what?
You are gonna be through.
And I'm sorry. I'm sorry
to do that to you.
Right.
Do you even know
how paper is made?
It's not like steel.
You don't put it
into a furnace!
If you put paper into a furnace,
you know what would happen?
You'd ruin it!
Come in.
Hey!
Hey.
All right, Charles,
I gotta be honest.
I think we really got off
on the wrong foot here,
and, truth be told, I'm a pretty
smart guy and a hard worker
and I'm a great
number two for the office.
Number two?
Second-in-command
to Michael.
I didn't know that
position existed.
That's because at first it was
a made-up position for Dwight,
just to make him feel better.
Assistant to
the Regional Manager.
But then he lost that,
and Michael gave it to me.
So you're the Assistant
to the Regional Manager?
Assistant
Regional Manager, yeah.
Any responsibilities
come with it?
No, not exactly.
Do you want to keep
this made-up position?
It's important to you?
All right, I will...
I'm just going to let you get back to it.
Yeah, would you...
Yep.
Thanks.
Hello, Stephanie.
Okay, where is he?
Michael.
So is this the meeting
you've been in all day?
How did you get here,
Michael?
I drove.
Okay.
Cancelled my fifteenth
anniversary party.
Just pulled the rug
out from under me.
He said no figs.
I've already bought them,
and I don't have
a place to store them.
So I feel like
I've been sort of boned.
Michael... Did you talk
to him about this?
You've talked to him
all day, obviously.
Did you talk to him
about this?
Well, I didn't know about
the figs specifically...
No, okay,
then I don't get it.
It doesn't make
any sense to me,
because I thought
the new system was
that I was supposed
to talk to Charles,
and then Charles was
supposed to talk to you,
and that would dilute
any need for me
to ever talk to you again.
That's not
exactly the system...
Clearly that's
what you wanted.
No...
Fifteen years
I've been here,
and I have sacrificed a lot.
Yes.
I've put having
a family on hold.
We didn't ask you to do that.
And I have never
gone hang-gliding.
And I've never driven my car to
the top of Mount Washington.
Okay.
- Nice meeting everyone.
- All right.
I'll see you in a couple of weeks.
Cool.
Excellent.
It was very nice meeting
you, Charles Miner.
Okay.
See you.
See you!
Bye!
And for my next trick, I will
make my career disappear.
I could see our kids
facing obstacles,
being half black
and half Indian,
but it's so worth it,
you guys.
There's just me here.
I am going to get him to buy
me a prime rib tonight.
I think he left.
What?
Move!
Hello? Charles?
Charles?
Hey!
Is that his scarf?
No!
Charles and Kelly?
Absolutely not.
He is a sophisticated man.
He does not need to go dumpster-diving
for companionship, okay?
I don't understand that, after
15 years of service here,
I have to get in a car and drive to
New York in order to talk to you.
That doesn't
seem right to me.
That doesn't seem fair,
and I think
that I've earned
more than that.
Yep.
You're right, yes. I get it.
I get it, Michael.
Okay.
Here's what I'm gonna do.
We will move
some money around,
and I will personally see to
it that you have your party,
you have your figs.
I will be in attendance.
It's gonna be great.
How's that?
I quit.
What?
Michael. You have no
idea how high I can fly.