Parkour!
Michael.
Parkour! Parkour!
Extreme.
- Parkour!
This is parkour.
Internet sensation of 2004,
and it was in one of the Bond
films. It's pretty impressive.
The goal is to get from point A to
point B as creatively as possible.
So technically
they are doing parkour,
as long as point A is delusion
and point B is the hospital.
Parkour!
Yeah, parkour!
Andy, leap frog.
Go, go!
Do me! Do me!
Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
Parkour! Parkour!
Get off! Get off!
Okay.
Parkour!
Parkour! Jump over the camera.
Jump over
the camera.
Okay, we all go together,
or we go one at a time.
Here it is. Here it is. Truck
to refrigerators to dumpster,
360 spin onto the palettes, back
flip, gainer into the trashcan.
Yeah, gainer!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Parkour, parkour!
I'm right behind you,
Andy. Come on!
Let's do it!
Yeah!
Parkour.
Good.
Excellent.
Thank you.
Here you go. Is there
anything else I can do?
Yes.
See those files behind
Kevin's desk? Mmm-hmm.
Go put them all
in random order.
Okay.
Then come back here for your
next assignment concerning their order.
This is the last day of our
summer interns. It's been nice.
We haven't had
interns in a while.
Ever since Michael's
Monica Lewinsky incident.
He didn't do
anything sexual.
He just made far, far too
many Monica Lewinsky jokes.
It was just easier for corporate
to shut down the program.
Think she did him? I bet
there's something there.
I was with them in
the kitchen yesterday,
and they were all too happy
to be cleaning the freezer.
If they get married before I
do, I'm going to kill myself.
Who's getting married?
Nobody.
If somebody doesn't tell me,
I'm gonna start screaming.
It's Eric and Megan.
Oh!
Hey, I hired them.
Matchmaker.
This place is like
Spaniard fly.
They're not getting married.
It's just talk.
Did everybody know
about this but me?
There's nothing to know.
It's just gossip.
Okay. Okay.
We haven't told anyone
that I'm pregnant.
What with her being unmarried,
knocked up by some guy.
The yakety-yaks in this office
would have a field day.
Yeah, and we don't want
them at the wedding thinking
Jim's being marched down the
aisle by my dad with a shotgun.
Wait, there's not going
to be a shotgun?
Nope.
No shotgun? Because
that changes everything.
Can't back out
now, Halpert.
What are you going to do about
it? There's no shotgun, so,
free at last,
free at last.
No, keep it up.
You'll never guess
what I know.
Okay. Let me finish
this thought.
Eric likes Megan.
He most definitely does.
He's been asking her out
repeatedly for weeks.
She finally said yes. They went
out on a group date the other night.
Apparently
it went very well.
How do you know this?
People tell me things.
I guess I have
a face you can trust.
I think it's because
of my low cheek bones.
And boom. Okay, what is it?
What can't I guess?
I hate, hate, hate
being left out.
Whether it's not being picked for
a team or being picked for a team
and then showing up and realizing
that the team doesn't exist,
or that the sport
doesn't exist.
I should have known.
Poopball?
Oh, man, I know how
you feel. Third wheel.
I have been the third wheel
so many times in my life.
My mom told me something once
that made me feel a lot better.
She said, "The third wheel
is what makes it a tricycle."
What are you
talking about?
I am talking about your group
date with Megan and Eric.
At Tinks?
Yes.
How'd you know about that? Well...
Did Stanley tell you?
Stanley was on your
group date?
No. Stanley
was with his wife.
I waved at him
but he didn't wave back.
Does anybody else
know about this?
No.
There he goes.
So, what is the scuttlebutt?
Anybody hear anything?
Nothing? I got a little
something-something.
I don't know
if I should say.
So just keep it
to yourself, then.
Stanley is having
a midlife crisis.
Stanley is way past
the middle of his life,
especially considering
his height-to-weight ratio.
Well, apparently,
he and his wife
were out dancing at a
club for young people.
Teri's out of town,
Michael.
Who?
Stanley's wife, Teri.
She's at an interior
decorating expo in Philly.
And Stanley hates crowds, kids and music.
I think you should check your facts.
You stupid son of a bitch.
You set me up.
What are you
talking about?
Stanley's wife
is out of town.
He was with somebody.
He was definitely
with someone.
Oh! Was he? Well, who? His sister?
I don't get it!
If that was his sister, then what
they were doing was totally illegal.
Drugs?
Making out.
Okay.
No, it's okay.
Never mind.
Carry on.
Stanley
is having an affair.
What?
I know.
I am very happy right now,
thrilled perhaps, to be a part of the office,
to be a part of
the conversation.
When you have somebody's attention,
and their eyes are lighting up
because they are very interested
in what you have to say,
that is a great feeling.
And I experienced that
firsthand today.
It is wonderful to be
the center of attention.
That and that
are the same letter.
Q.
No. No.
Okay.
He's holding a pencil.
He could be doing a crossword
puzzle with that pencil.
What's that letter, right
there? Same letter here and here.
What haven't you guessed?
T.
T! Yes! Yes!
That is a T.
And there's another one right there.
Just sound that out. You're almost there.
Hey, Stanley, where are you
going, big guy? Up to no good?
I'm meeting a client. Do
you have a problem with that?
No, no, no, no, no. I just
had a quick question for you.
I'm casting a movie and I'm looking for
a woman who can dance, beautiful woman.
Do you know anybody?
Goodbye.
Pays 5 million dollars.
Nudity required.
You have to stop this.
Did you hear that
Stanley's having an affair?
I did. From you.
You got to stop telling people.
Okay. I get it. You feel out of the
loop and you feel sorry for yourself,
and it's really sad because
everybody thinks you're a loser.
Do you even know if it's
true? Do you have any idea?
Because you might be
ruining his life.
Hold up! Hold up! Hold up!
No, no, no, no!
It's time to stop being
polite and get real!
Stanley,
you having an affair?
That is ridiculous. Of course
not. Why would you think that?
So it's not true.
Okay. Well...
Oh!
Those interns, they told me
they saw you at the club,
and they all said
it was you.
It was clearly just racial
profiling gossip. The little...
Damn! I told her
it was a stupid idea...
It's so stupid.
...to go up in that club.
It's just that Teri's been
traveling a lot lately.
I know. I know.
It's been lonely.
Oh, I bet. I...
Cynthia's been
keeping me company.
She was my nurse when
I was in rehabilitation.
We used to go on these
long walks on the treadmill.
I didn't intend...
Wait, wait, wait.
So it is true?
Yeah, but Michael, I'm
going to go break it off.
That's where I'm headed
right now. I swear.
Oh, my God.
Wait a second.
Do people often say they're going on
sales calls and then go someplace else?
Because that's not cool.
I just need you to promise not to
say a word about this to anyone.
Michael, please.
I'm not saying
a damn thing.
I'm counting
on you, Michael.
Okay.
You can count on me.
Oh, that smells good.
Yeah, I might have extra. It
just depends on how many I eat.
Did you hear about Angela?
That's pretty weird.
Yeah. What do you
mean exactly?
Well, the fact that she apparently
is dating an 81-year-old billionaire.
Owns a Quiznos
on the turnpike.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Right?
How do you un-tell
something? You can't.
You can't put words
back in your mouth.
What you can do is
spread false gossip,
so that people think that everything
that's been said is untrue,
including "Stanley
is having an affair."
It's like the end of Spartacus. I've
seen that movie half a dozen times,
and I still don't know
who the real Spartacus is.
And that is what makes that
movie a classic whodunit.
Kelly has an eating
disorder? MICHAEL: Yes.
She always
eats my lunch.
Anorexia.
She's an anorexitic.
We should do something.
Nothing can be done.
Just have to tell everybody
and hope for the best, I guess.
I'm worried about Erin because
she's not a very good worker.
I don't know how long
she's going to last here.
Really?
Yeah. So...
And Andy is gay.
Andy Bernard?
Mmm-hmm.
Did you
hear Pam is pregnant?
Really?
Yeah.
She's going to hate
being a mom.
What?
Tea.
So?
You would.
I like tea.
Oh, I bet you like it.
Yeah. I like it a lot.
I love tea.
Do you like it as much
as you like men's butts?
What?
Because you're gay.
Who told you that? Was it
Broccoli Rob? Someone from Chi Psi?
Or did you run into
someone from my high school?
This is not the first time rumors
about me being gay have come up.
Twice before, actually.
Just a weird coincidence.
It's a little too weird.
Almost makes you wonder if it's
not a coincidence at all. Whoa!
Which it is, of course.
But it makes you wonder.
Did you hear the rumor
about me, that I'm gay?
I did, yes.
And?
What?
Do you think it's true?
Do you think that I'm gay?
Are you attracted
to other men?
No.
But let me kick
you a scenario.
I'm at, like, a beach cabana
and Brad Pitt approaches,
tries to lean in
and kiss me.
I would definitely resist, like,
at first, but if he was persistent,
I might give in a little bit to
just sort of see what it felt like.
Would I push him away? How hard? Like,
what if he's, like, really aggressive?
If you resisted Brad Pitt a little
bit, he would still need to get to you?
This is not real Brad Pitt, this is,
like, in my... This is my fantasy.
Or it's, like, not fantasy, it's,
like, what I'm... It's just a scenario.
Well, I wish I could help you. I don't...
You might be gay. You might be gay.
What exactly
is my responsibility here?
To comfort insecure
heterosexual men?
That can't possibly
fall to me.
How far along is Pam?
A few months. That's why
they're rushing the wedding.
Guys, guys, guys, you
can't believe everything you hear.
Like Stanley
having an affair.
That is crazy.
There's no stock in it.
It's a weird day for false
facts. Just let it go.
Okay, everybody, big day. Last day
for our interns. Lot of other stuff.
Who knows what to believe?
Dwight, the honors.
Present these to the Dean for credit.
And as a gift, I've attached my card.
Call me any time
of the day or night.
Why would we call
you at night?
Well, now you can't call me
at all, so problem solved.
You're going to regret that
when you find yourself
between a moose
and her cubs at night.
Look to the intern on your
left. Now to your right.
One of you will do exceedingly well
in business, just unlimited potential.
One of you will make a
living and nothing more.
And one of you will make a great mother.
It's up to you to choose
which you want to be.
I am so happy
you're eating again.
Me, too.
Tuna, how come you never
try to set me up?
I don't really do that. But Pam
might have some friends, though.
Women friends?
Yeah.
Not guy friends?
Are you interested
in her guy friends?
No. I mean, for the
record, I prefer women.
Okay. But off the record,
I'm kind of confused.
Really?
Yeah, the evidence is sort of
stacked against me, I feel like.
Well, you've got to figure
this out. Yeah, right?
Yeah.
How?
You've got to have
sex with a woman.
Righto.
And then a man.
And then compare.
Oh!
All right.
Well, hey.
Yep.
Congratulations to you.
On what?
Come on.
Little baby Tuna.
Little junior Toro.
You know, a baby conceived out
of wedlock is still a bastard.
What?
Want me to say it again?
Why did that come
into your brain?
Can I talk to you
for a second?
So, they know.
Who did you tell? I didn't
tell anyone. Who did you tell?
Nobody.
Hey, did one of you tell Stanley
that I have asthma? Because I don't.
If it gets out they
won't let me scuba.
If I can't scuba, then
what's this all been about?
What am I working toward?
What? You think I'm the
voice of the Taco Bell dog?
What are you guys talking about? I have
a daughter. How could I be a virgin?
Hey, has everyone heard a crazy
rumor about themselves today?
Yes.
Yeah, yeah! You know what,
let's discredit these rumors.
Yeah, sure, but who's been
saying all that stuff?
It's not important, Jim. I just think
we shouldn't listen to any of this crap.
Sure, but we should
get to the bottom of this.
Let's pick a rumor and trace
it back to the beginning.
I need to do
mine first.
Who's been saying that there's
another person inside of me
working me
with controls?
I heard that from Andy.
I heard it from Erin.
What?
I heard it from Michael.
Michael.
Michael?
He's over here.
Where are you going?
Nowhere.
Michael.
Hmm?
You told people that
I use store-bought manure,
when I showed you where
my manure comes from.
Hmm? Hmm?
Don't get on it.
Michael, don't.
- Don't get on. Do not.
- Michael, no.
Michael.
Stay, Michael.
Step away.
Stay.
- Come on, boss.
- No. No.
Okay, I made it all up. KELLY: What?
Even the fact
that I'm gay?
Yes.
Yes!
But, guys, I'm a victim here, too. Okay?
People have been saying
that I'm a J. Crew model.
No, we heard
that about Jim.
Jim? No, no, I spread the rumor that
somebody here was a J. Crew model
and I was referring
to myself.
How is that
a bad rumor?
Because a lot of people think that models,
even though they're very attractive,
are somewhat vapid. It's set
our industry back quite a bit.
Michael, why? Why say all these
things? Why make up an eating disorder,
Stanley's affair,
me being a spokesdog?
You told everyone
I was having an affair?
Okay, okay,
here's the thing.
There was one true rumor out there today.
I didn't want everybody to know what it was,
so all of you are off the hook
except for this one person.
Well, then what's
the one true rumor?
We have a right to know.
Michael, am I gay?
The one true rumor, and this is going
to ruin this person's life, is that...
That Pam's pregnant.
I knew it, I knew it.
I knew it!
Her breasts were a tiny bit
bigger. At first, I thought,
"Oh! She has a new
bra with padding."
But then I thought,
"Pam doesn't need padding."
It just didn't
add up, Jim.
Okay, thank you.
Congratulations!
That's really great, you
guys. RYAN: Don't vaccinate it.
Who's the father?
Jim.
- How far along?
- Four months.
Who's the OB-GYN?
Stop. Don't.
All right, you know, this is not the truth
and you can't fall on the sword this way.
The real thing is that
Stanley Hudson had an affair.
No.
Yes.
Thank you for trying
to defend us,
but actually Pam is pregnant
and we can prove it.
Yes. If everybody would
like to see the proof.
Wanna... Okay.
Okay.
We're just
going to wait here?
What's the proof,
I mean...
It's true!
Pam, look at that!
That is the inside
of your vagina.
That's not how
it works but...
It's clear why we were trying not to
tell people. That's clear now. Yeah.
How long have you known
about the pregnancy?
A week? A month? A year?
Michael, we only told
our parents last week.
Did you pee on a stick?
I did. But it
was inconclusive.
You should have told me.
You're right.
We should have realized that
you are an equal part of this.
Yes.
Michael, Teri Hudson
returning your call.
You called Stanley's wife?
Oh! Oh!
Yeah, a long time ago. Just to
make sure she was out of town.
Oh, God.
Don't take it.
No, I have to take it
or it'll seem suspicious.
If you talk to her, you're
going to tell her about Stanley
and that's going to
seem more suspicious.
No, no, no, I can do this.
You can't do this.
Yes, I can. I am going to tell her
that I need to redecorate my condo
and I need her help.
We will haggle about money,
and I will back down,
and then I won't talk to her until
this whole Cynthia thing has blown over.
Sounds terrible.
We think you should...
Michael, please don't.
Hey, what up, Cynthia?
Just hang on a second,
Cynthia.
Well, it turns out that
Teri was already suspicious
because she had caught Stanley
and Cynthia a few months ago.
So Stanley promised that he would
stop, and he did. End of story.
Well, not exactly.
Cynthia kept calling him.
She would not stop calling him,
and she was in love with him.
And get this.
Cynthia, also married.
So, you can't stop love,
I guess.
And quite frankly, I don't
think you should ever even try.
I learned that a company can describe their
internship as full of exciting experiences,
even if that's a lie.
There's no regulation.
I learned that half these people's
e-mail password is "Password."
I learned that a ream
of paper is 300 sheets.
I thought it was 500.
Oh!
I guess I didn't
learn anything.
I learned that if you look even
the tiniest bit like Jet Li,
Michael will call you
Jet Li all summer.
Julia Stiles.
Alan Thicke.