Dunder Mifflin
is about to be sold,
but first an investment banker has
to drop by and sign off on our branch.
And I'm pretty
nervous about it,
and I'm making
some cosmetic tweaks
to help create
a more appealing environment.
Is that dishonest?
Well, think of it this way.
When you look in
the mirror and you see
your push-up bra and
your fake eyelashes
and your makeup and
your press-on nails,
the principles that
I'm applying to the office
are the same ones that
have made Lady Gaga a star.
Or any number of drag queens.
Hi.
- Hello, Eric Ward.
Welcome to Dunder Mifflin.
I am Computron,
your answer to everything.
Hello.
I see you've met Computron,
our virtual helper.
I'm Michael Scott.
Welcome, welcome.
Computron is just one
of the many modern devices
that I have incorporated
into the office.
Watch this. Computron?
Yes.
What is the world's
largest ocean?
Calculating.
Pacific!
Pacific Ocean.
Pretty cool, huh?
Great news, Michael,
we're now the official
paper supplier of the NFL.
That is fantastic. It's good, but
it's not good enough. Keep working.
And here's Pam.
She's our international
sales consultant.
Hello.
The NFL celebrated
its 50th anniversary in 1972.
It might seem crazy, but since
there's no one left in New York,
Michael is Dunder Mifflin's
highest ranking employee.
So, that's where we are.
Hello, Stanley.
Hi.
For the record, not
onboard with fake Stanley.
Although, I get it.
I just need to check out your
warehouse and then talk to your HR guy.
That is pretty much the only
reason that I came here today.
Okay. Well, I thought I'd
show you around a little bit...
Right... Since you made the trip out.
And I got us reservations at
Coopers Seafood. You like lobster?
You've had
lobster before, right?
Yeah.
They make the best Maine lobster
in the world. You'll love it.
Mul Yam
in Tel Aviv is better.
No, Computron, actually,
I think Coopers is the best.
You're going to love it.
Are you calling me wrong?
Oh, my God.
It's called
due diligence.
Basically,
I confirm inventory,
take a head count, see if
there are any HR liabilities.
I'm a glorified fact checker.
Actually,
I am a fact checker.
All right.
Excuse me. If you will...
- Hey, Michael,
do you think I could get a space
here? Follow me this way.
I will introduce you to the
crack HR rep that you requested.
I give you Toby Flenderson.
Have fun, you two.
Oh, we will. Have a seat.
Mmm.
I left a copy of
Best American Mystery Stories 1999
in Toby's favorite stall. So,
yes, I think I bought us some time.
So, the manager,
Michael Scott
is a bit of a character.
He has more character in a
single flake of his dandruff
than you have in that entire
snow bank on your shoulder.
So, what was the question?
What are you
doing at my desk?
Ignore him.
He's the local lunatic.
Come on, Dwight,
get out of here.
Dwight? Who is this Dwight?
Oh!
You mean Dwight Schrute,
the company's top salesman
and the creator of Computron.
I wear many hats, but the
one I'm wearing currently
is that of gracious host.
Welcome.
Sorry. Hey, Toby Flenderson.
Nice to meet you. How can I help?
Are there any outstanding
liability issues to be aware of?
What do you mean?
Well, safety issues,
injuries that could leave
the company open to
any potential lawsuits.
Um...
Nothing comes to mind.
Mike, get off
of the lift. Please!
Come on, now.
I'm fine.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Look, would you...
Look...
We'll get somebody
to clean that up.
We're the ones
that gotta clean that up!
I feel very blessed.
Drop that sucker.
Yeah! Bingo!
Do it!
Yeah!
Today, smoking is
going to save lives.
- Run, run.
- Okay, okay.
Calm, please.
Oscar!
Stay alive, I'm getting help!
Pull me up!
You're too heavy.
I only weigh 82 pounds.
Save Bandit!
Seriously, are you
gonna sit in the back?
Yeah. It's the safest
part of a car.
In the event of a crash, the driver
always protects his side first.
My hair!
Get off! Get off me!
I got it! I got it!
Get it off!
You're welcome.
So, the staff,
are people generally happy?
Happy is a funny word.
In what way?
You know...
You know, what does
it mean to be happy?
Keep philosophers
busy for a while.
So, generally?
Yes.
Generally.
Generally happy.
I don't know what streets
we... Ow! What are you doing?
It would be better
if you were unconscious.
Ow!
Try my googy googy. Try
my googy googy. Try my...
Excuse me.
Don't touch me!
Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Can't we all just get along?
Or have we forgotten the words
of the Reverend King?
What about non-safety issues
in terms of liability?
Sexual harassment?
Anything like that?
Well, I don't know.
You don't know?
I don't know.
You're the head
of human resources.
I don't know.
No.
Okay.
Stanley? How about that hot
picture you have by your desk?
Centerfold in the
Catholic schoolgirl's outfit?
I mean, it is hot, it is sexy,
and it turns him on.
And I will admit, best part
of my morning is staring at it.
But what? Are we gonna
just take it away?
That is my daughter, she goes
to Catholic girls' school.
Michael.
Come in!
Hey!
Oh, my God!
What are you doing?
You said, come in! No, I didn't!
Just, please, get out. Oh, my God!
What's wrong
with my outfit?
You might consider
pulling it down a touch.
Bunch of prudes. You know,
Oscar's allowed to wear sandals,
But I'm not
allowed to wear open-toed shoes?
Is that how it goes?
Meredith, your boob is out.
Fine.
Too
far, Meredith! Too far!
Damn it, Meredith,
where are your panties?
It's casual day.
Come here, give me a kiss,
come on.
Michael, come on, you
don't have to worry. I'm not
gonna report you to HR.
I'm not... I'm not worried!
You know what? The only
thing I am worried about
is getting a boner.
I'm now going to read aloud your
submitted medical conditions.
When you hear yours read,
please raise your hand
to indicate
that it is real.
If you do not raise your
hand, it will not be covered.
Number one,
inverted penis.
Could you mean vagina? Because
if you do, I want that covered.
I thought your vagina was
removed during your hysterectomy.
A uterus is different from a
vagina. I still have a vagina.
Attention, everyone. Hello.
Yes, I just want you to know
that, this is not my decision.
You can consider this
my retirement from comedy.
Does that include
"that's what she said"?
Yes.
Wow, that is really hard.
You really think
you can go all day long?
Well, you always left me
satisfied and smiling, so...
That's what she said!
Michael!
Why did you
get it so big?
That's what she said.
Does the skin look
red and swollen?
That's what she said.
That's my joke.
Damn it, Dwight.
How about
the Phyllis-Angela dispute?
You already did me.
That's what she said.
Is there any mustard?
No mustard! No mustard!
Just eat it!
Eat it, Phyllis.
Dip it in the water
so it'll slide down
your gullet more easily.
That's what she said.
Oh,
no, no, no, no, not that...
Just come on,
you guys, let's do it.
I don't know how
I'm going to get through this.
I don't want to lie.
And I don't want
to tell the truth.
Hey, Tobes, what you doing?
What you guys talking about?
We're just going
over some stuff.
Stuff? I love stuff.
It's HR stuff.
HR stuff? H.R. Pufnstuf.
Right up my alley. What is
that? What kind of stuff is that?
It's a company
evaluation form.
Ah!
We're talking about...
Talking about what?
Waste is next.
Waste?
What does that even mean?
Like garbage?
No, waste of time,
resources.
Oh! Time and resources.
Look, you know,
in any company,
there's gonna be
a certain degree...
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Respectfully, Toby, no.
No. This company does not
waste time or resources ever.
Dig deep. Dig deep.
It's Phyllis,
Phyllis by a nose.
Gold medal in Flernenton.
Flonkerton.
Where is my desk?
That is weird.
Happy holidays, Dwight. But
do not open it till Christmas.
You're so pathetic. Well,
I hope it was worth it,
because I'm going to take it
apart in about five minutes.
I think it'll take you a
little bit longer than that.
If I can skin a mule deer
in less than 10 minutes,
I ought to be
able to cut my...
Damn it! Jim!
Okay. Hold on, hold on.
Judge is in session.
What is the problem here?
He put my stuff
in Jell-O again.
Bang, boom,
shake, klump!
Why, hello, everybody.
What are you doing?
Question, what kind
of bear is best?
That's a ridiculous question.
False. Black bear.
Well, that's debatable.
There are basically
two schools of thought.
Fact, bears eat beets.
Oh...
Bears, beets,
Battlestar Galactica.
Bears do not...
What is going on?
What are you doing?
Identity theft is
not a joke, Jim!
Millions of families
suffer every year!
Michael!
Oh, that's funny. Michael!
Is anyone near
retirement age?
This is Creed.
And he is in charge
of something.
Right?
That is correct.
Say hi to the kids.
Hi, kids.
Yay!
Have you ever seen a foot
with four toes? KIDS: Ew!
What are you doing? Stop it!
Stop it! Just... No, no, no, no, no!
Would you cut it out?
Okay. Ryan, you told Toby
that Creed has a distinct
old man smell?
I know exactly
what he's talking about.
I sprout mung beans on a damp
paper towel in my desk drawer.
Very nutritious,
but they smell like death.
Hey, where's Dwight?
You didn't hear?
Decapitated. Whole big thing.
We had a funeral for a bird.
I'm pretty sure
none of that's real.
You're not real, man.
Hey. Yeah, I finally got a
chance to sit down with HR.
So...
Well, I think I'm gonna
be here for a while.
This is a building where
friends become lovers,
and lovers become
sexually interactive, right?
Would you agree with that?
Michael, this is really
inappropriate to talk about.
That is true.
Mmm.
I like you.
But you need to access
your un-crazy side.
Darryl Philbin is the most
complicated man that I've ever met.
I mean, who says exactly
what they're thinking?
What kind of game is that?
I am so happy we don't
have to break up now, Ryan!
It is the best day
of my whole life!
When I said that
I wanted to have kids,
and you said that you wanted me
to have a vasectomy, what did I do?
And then, when you said that
you might want to have kids,
and I wasn't so sure, who
had the vasectomy reversed?
And then when you said you
definitely didn't want to have kids?
Who had it reversed back?
Snip, snap! Snip, snap! Snip, snap!
I did!
- Okay...
You have no idea the physical toll
that three vasectomies have on a person!
Kelly, I'm your
boss now, okay?
You can't keep talking to
me like I'm your boyfriend.
Oh, big strong man,
fancy new whatever.
I don't think you
ever cared about me.
I never cared about you?
Six months ago, Karen
Filippelli sent me an email,
asked me out,
I said no,
because I was committed
to our relationship.
Well, I hope you're still
committed, because I'm pregnant.
This is an image
that I want you people to
remember for a long time to come.
Whenever you come
into the office,
I want you to
think about this.
We don't need to.
Yes, we do.
What?
I did it!
Thank you.
Jim has got it bad for Pam.
Oh! Which one is Pam?
What?
Nothing.
Okay.
What?
I don't know. What?
Oh, my God!
Did you wanna
tell me something?
You look like you want
to tell me something.
You look like you have
something really important to say
and you just can't
for some reason.
Come on, you can tell me.
Jim, you can tell me anything.
You have new music?
Yeah.
Definitely.
Bring it in.
Here we go.
Look inside.
Oh, my God!
But I bet Jim got the job.
I mean, why wouldn't he? He's
totally qualified and smart.
Everyone loves him.
If he never comes back again,
that's okay.
We're friends.
We just... We never
got the timing right.
But you know what,
it's okay.
I'm totally fine.
Everything is
going to be totally...
Pam.
Sorry.
Are you free for
dinner tonight?
Yes.
All right.
Then it's a date.
I'm sorry.
What was the question?
Oh, my God.
Pam, will you marry me?
Oh, my God!
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
It's nice to meet you all.
Good to meet you.
Have a great day.
Thank you.
Hope to see
you soon. KEVIN: Yeah.
I feel very sorry
for that banker because
he has to evaluate
what we are worth.
He has to decide what we're
capable of. And how do you do that?
What is Jim capable of?
Or Pam? Or Kevin?
Out of paper, out of stock
Those friendly faces
around the block
Break loose
from the chains
That are causing
you pain
Call Michael
and Stanley, Jim, Dwight, Creed
Call Andy and Kelly
For your business paper needs
Dunder Mifflin
The people person's
paper people
Dunder Mifflin
The people person's
paper people
Dunder Mifflin
The people person's
paper people
I don't care if he
goes and files a report
that says that
we're nothing special
because I think our
future is very bright.
We have only just begun.
Computron
experiencing emotion.
Computron, I'm going to
pull your plug, okay, buddy?
Okay.
Just...
Please don't.
Computron wants to live.
Shut... Shut up. Shut up.
Sittin' in my office
With a plate of grilled bacon
Call my man Dwight
Just to see what was shakin'!
Yo, Mike,
our town is dope and pretty
So check out how we live
In the Electric City!
They call it Scranton!
What?
The Electric City! Scranton! What?
The Electric City!
Lazy Scranton,
the Electric City
They call it that
'cause of the electricity
The city's laid
out from east to west
And our public parks and
libraries are truly the best!
Call Poison Control
if you're bit by a spider!
But check that it's covered
By your healthcare provider!
Plenty of space
in the parkin' lot!
But the little cars
go in the compact spot!
Spot! Spot! Spot!
Snack attack time
Don't lose your head
We like Cuginos
for the tasty bread!
They call it Scranton!
What?
The Electric City! Scranton! What?