This here is
a radon test kit.
Okay, I'll be
putting them everywhere.
And please don't
throw these out.
This is a radon test kit.
Please don't
throw these out.
You'll see them
all over the office.
Toby has been leaving
radon kits everywhere
like he owns the place.
The first time I threw mine away,
I thought it was an ant trap.
But I figured I'd
rather live with ants
than with this
creepy little disk.
The second time, I thought
it was one of those,
you know, the things you turn
over and it moos like a cow thing,
but upon closer examination it was
another ant trap, so I threw it away.
And the third time,
I did it out of spite.
Come on, Michael,
you're interrupting.
You're kidding me! God!
You say radon is silent but
deadly and then you expect me
not to make farting noises
with my mouth?
What is this?
Please sit down.
You know what, we're
not gonna die of radon,
we're gonna die of boredom.
Yeah.
Right?
And if I had a gun
with two bullets,
and I was in a room with
Hitler, Bin Laden and Toby,
I would shoot Toby twice.
Okay, all right.
You were being really funny
and then you went too far.
I would kill Bin Laden
and then Toby.
No. That's still...
Okay, geniuses,
how would you do it?
Curve the bullet like in my
favorite James McAvoy film Wanted.
All that does is help you
shoot around things.
What does Bin Laden... Is
there a curtain rod in the room?
I don't know.
How about make-believe
land has anything you want?
Stanley, please,
this is serious.
Is this the thing where they use
an icicle so there's no evidence?
Yes, we should stab Toby
through the heart with an icicle.
Come on, the whole two
bullet thing is a red herring.
Here's how you do it.
You line them all up,
you take one bullet, shoot
them all through the throat
at the same time.
Watch this. Phyllis,
you're Hitler, come up here.
Toby, you're Toby. Andy,
you're Bin Laden. Line up.
- I don't want to do this.
- Throats together.
Toby, just do it!
Toby, come on.
God.
Ready, one bullet and...
Boom!
Yeah, that works.
It worked!
What flavors did you get?
It's so exciting, Pam.
The Eagles are doing a theme of
ice creams in honor of turning 60.
"Despera-Dough, Witchy-Womanilla."
Why do they do this?
Do you want me to
go back to the store?
No, no, no, it's fine.
I was just commenting.
We got to get these
out, open them up. Okay.
This is all for Michael. Turns
out his girlfriend was married.
Yeah, and when
Michael gets a broken heart,
this whole place
comes to a halt,
so, we're just trying to
get out in front of this.
After his last breakup, he ate
40,000 calories in three hours.
Right, Pam?
That's what Pam told me.
Yeah.
Or, no, well,
I don't know.
I'm sorry. I was up all night with Cece.
Otherwise I'd be
running this.
That's okay.
You probably shouldn't
keep a baby up that late.
We have Mr. Bean playing
in the conference room,
and the Pink Panther
movie in his office.
With half hour shifts
to watch with him.
And we need bodies in
both these rooms, people.
So, please sign up.
He's coming.
- Oh. Okay.
Everyone, remember
when he gets like this,
he will wallow
if you empathize.
Keep conversations light.
And if you get stuck and
you don't know what to do,
make a random
sound effect.
Okay, farting noise,
whatever. Okay.
Hey, everyone.
No, out.
Get out, right now.
Leave now.
Get out. Right now.
Please, please!
And if he makes a joke,
just laugh it up
no matter what, okay?
Morning, everyone.
- Hey!
Hey!
Hello.
Michael,
nice tie or something.
Thank you.
It's reversible, I think.
That's hilarious. PAM: That's awesome.
You want some ice cream?
Oh! Wow. Are those
Eagles flavors?
"Cake It To The Limit,"
that's my favorite.
I love that. Too much
for me to have by myself.
Anybody want to share?
Okay, well... That's random.
I will dig into those later.
I don't follow this
exactly.
"The descendents
of any replicants
"from this union
shall have..."
Joint custody.
Are we talking about
your grandchildren?
No.
Rather than spend
all day in court,
we have decided to settle
our dispute using a mediator.
It was an option spelled out
in our child-rearing contract.
Alleged contract.
Alleged?
I'm going to own your farm
by the time this is over.
Pfft. Yeah, just try. I
will do legal jujitsu on you.
Yeah.
See, don't even need to make
contact. The law will do it.
So much of this is
just impossible to verify.
Item five, point B,
the beet juice cleanse.
I'm doing it. You know
I am. It's disgusting.
How do we know this? I'd
like to see a stool sample.
Dwight, look at my teeth.
Ugh!
No secret crying.
Hasn't even opened
the tissue box in there.
Could he still be seeing her?
I don't think he'd do that.
So, we're gonna say
the most likely scenario
is that Michael
matured overnight?
It happened to
Tom Hanks in Big.
Exactly.
It happened in Big.
No, I gotta go.
Text me later.
I'm really too tired
to do this. Me, too.
Then let's just not do this.
Do you have any idea
of the risks involved?
Hey, Michael.
Hey.
We were wondering if you'd like
to have dinner with us tonight
in our home and
play with our baby?
We could order in
from Hooters.
Hooters to go, nice.
We can watch a movie
and play Rock Band.
Billy Joel Rock Band.
That exists?
Yes.
Okay, well, I'll have to take a
rain check, but thanks for the offer.
Michael Scott,
are you still seeing Donna?
Okay, Pam,
she's not invisible, so
stop asking silly questions.
Michael.
Since when is this an office
where we delve into
each other's personal lives?
I like Donna.
Is it wrong to
keep seeing her?
Depends on who you ask. I
mean, if you ask her husband
or you took a random poll,
yeah, it's wrong.
That is something
I would never do.
Well, I think we all know what
you're capable of, Meredith.
Hey, I have never cheated on, been
cheated on or been used to cheat with.
I ask everyone in the room,
"Are you in a relationship?"
People, this is Scranton
and many people
consider that to be
the Paris of
northeastern Pennsylvania.
And in Paris, it is rude for a
woman to have less than four lovers.
Ugh! Ryan, I do not want you
hanging out with Michael anymore.
Okay.
Okay, I will have you know
that I asked Donna about this
and she is fine with it.
And just to be sure, I asked
her again afterward, same answer.
How does he feel about it?
He is never gonna find out.
He is a high school
baseball coach,
he wakes up early,
he goes to bed early.
Look at how long it took
for him to find out.
It was right under his nose.
I had to tell him.
Okay, now you're
just being hurtful.
I'm sorry.
Why is it okay for Stanley to
cheat? Or for Phyllis to cheat?
Hey.
On her diet.
He's a sports guy.
He's scummy.
Dog fighting,
drugs, they spit.
Did Donna tell you that?
Real Sports with
Bryant Gumball.
So, you're just making a giant
assumption. You don't even know the guy.
You know what?
I am declaring a moment
of silence right now.
Ten minutes of silence
honoring Michael Jackson.
Just sit there and think
about Michael Jackson.
My name's Andy Bernard
and I am a cuckold.
For those of you unfamiliar
with William Shakespeare,
a cuckold is a man whose
woman is cheating on him.
I've lived the part.
And let me tell you, I would so
much rather play the part on stage.
So, here's the thing
about infidelity.
No, no.
When are you people going to
stop casting the first stone?
I am not in the wrong here.
I am the good guy.
How does that work?
Do you think this husband
is a super sweet, nice guy?
Do you think he's an angel?
I don't think so.
Why is his wife going off and having
a little something-something with me?
There has to be
a problem with him.
In any cheating movie, the person
getting cheated on is the hero.
You're Ali Larter,
I'm Beyoncé.
I am Beyoncé always.
Not this time.
Yes, I am.
This guy's a high school
baseball coach, right?
Let's go check him out, see
what a horrible person he is.
I would love that.
Yeah.
Those teams have games and practices
every day. Let's go check it out.
I have work to do.
Really?
I thought you were the boss.
Let's go.
I can't wait to see this jerk who
is making me cheat on his wife.
I should punch him
in the nose
for what he's
making me do to her.
All right, Andy, please.
Baseball!
Shh!
Try not to draw attention,
please.
That's him. That's him.
Where?
Right there.
The coach.
Stage right or stage left?
I played batboy
in Damn Yankees.
Right there. Look, look.
Follow my finger, okay? See?
The grownup by the base.
And now coaching third base
with two arms, two legs
and a heart capable
of feeling pain...
All right. Can you
just... Is number...
Can you just act normal
for a second, please?
Whatever.
I'm the one blending in.
Guys?
Pam?
Hey. Oh! Hi, Gabe.
Can you two please join
me in my office? Now.
You were supposed
to be the lookout.
Yeah, well, it's really warm in
here. It's like a sleeping bag.
I don't want to be the heavy
here, but honestly, guys,
this makes us all look bad.
Sorry about that.
So embarrassing.
Good, okay,
end of the dressing down.
I just hate that part of the
job, you know? The power dynamic.
Well, you were
surprisingly restrained.
We will be well
rested tomorrow.
Okay. That's great, actually,
because I wanted to talk
to you about something else.
Excellent. Go for it.
I'm sure you got my e-mail
about the printer fires,
the one with
the branching decision tree.
I actually
designed that chart.
Kind of hoping
it catches on.
Anyway, the question is,
what is the best way to
disseminate important information
in an efficient way?
Right. So let's...
Finally, there's a provision
here in the occurrence
that the child is
born an old man,
a la Benjamin Button.
Same page. Go to the next one.
Same page. We're fine there.
Just keep moving.
Despite
the provision covering
whether this is all
part of The Matrix...
Which we can't know...
...this is essentially...
...unless we're unplugged...
...equivalent to a donor
or surrogate contract...
...and wake up in the future.
...which is
actually pretty common.
So, I have to tell you that
this is a solid contract.
What?
Look, I can't enforce that anybody
have a child with anyone else.
What?
So essentially
this comes down to damages.
Now, there is some precedence
for the range of $30,000.
What?
I don't have
$30,000 lying around.
I have it buried very deeply,
and I don't want to dig past
a certain someone to get it.
Chase Dixon is up,
could be a big play.
You have no idea what
you're talking about.
I know it's like cricket.
No. No.
Well, home plate
is like a wicket.
You don't know,
you don't know anything.
Look at him.
Look at him over there.
High fiving?
He didn't even do anything.
The kid did all the work.
I bet he does that at home.
I bet it's like, "Hey, Donna,
why don't you wash the dishes?
"High five, Donna."
"Hey, why don't you bring me my slippers?
High five. I'm taking all the credit."
He seems pretty
well liked by the team.
Okay, well, that's because
he's paying their salary.
You do know that high school
coaches don't pay their players.
I know. I know. I know.
That was a euphemism.
$30,000?
There's got to be another way.
He has a 60-acre beet farm
that is worth a small fortune.
Look, I will not pay.
Well, I have an alternative.
"Intercourse to completion
five individual times
"rendered at my discretion."
Look, I don't think
that's actually legal.
Agreed.
Five times for $30,000?
Not a bad stud fee.
Better than most horses.
But not on your bed.
It's lumpy.
Those lumps are cats,
and those cats have names,
and those names are Amber,
Milky Way, Dianne and Lumpy.
Fine, five times.
Look, I can't legally
watch this unfold.
It's coming a little dangerously
close to prostitution.
I want eye contact.
No.
Yes.
Do you understand how rare
that is in nature?
I'm not some farm animal.
Great game, Coach.
Shh.
Okay, all right,
don't, don't, don't.
You guys are awesome. Best
game I've ever seen in my life.
Yeah, right. You must be
rooting for the other guys.
Ha! The other guys
can go die.
Okay.
Baseball!
Go talk to him.
No, God,
you go talk to him.
Shane, great game, man.
Do I know you?
No, just big fans.
Both of us.
Are you somebody's
parents?
Are you guys Kenny's dads?
No, no,
but we're gay for baseball.
Okay.
But I have a wife, actually,
who I really love a lot.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's go!
I am so into the
institution of marriage.
Isn't marriage the best,
you know?
Two good people
finding each other,
getting all committed to
each other.
You love baseball,
what else do you love?
Let's round you out
as a person.
Hey, I'm really sorry, I'm just
trying to focus here on the game.
I get it, man. I love it. That's
what makes you a good coach.
You know, but as a fan, it just
helps me enjoy the game better
if I know
the coach loves his wife.
Of course. Okay, I've
got to get back to this.
Of course.
All right.
But real quick, I want you
to meet my associate. Sheldon!
No, no, no. I'm good.
- Come on, get over here.
Get over here.
Oh, my God. All right.
Sheldon, say hi
to the nice coach.
Sorry, I've got
some stomach cramps.
It's all right, it's
all right, just keep it going.
Well, that was not at all
what I expected.
My heart's still racing.
I just looked a man in the
eyes and I shook his hand.
All the time I was thinking,
"I'm sleeping with your wife."
You know who does that?
James freaking Bond.
Okay, orange slices.
There you go.
Thanks, Michael.
Don't thank me,
thank Dylan's mom.
There you go.
Why would you throw
something wet at me?
You love it.
There you go.
Now, were those
for the team?
No. They didn't say "team,"
they just said "Coal Hawks."
I don't think those
were yours to take.
Well, then, it wouldn't
be the first time
I stole something
away from Coach Shane.
I just want to
go on record as saying
that I do not
condone this affair.
And I even went so
far as to force Michael
to confront
the victim of his behavior.
Did you talk to him?
I did.
You talked to the man whose wife
you're having an affair with?
Wow, that is crazy.
Was there a fist fight?
No, we just talked.
He's very nice.
And it didn't
change your mind?
It did not.
Michael, that's awful.
Isn't it?
Yes.
I'm awful, aren't I?
Yeah, that's pretty...
I'm an awful guy. Ooh!
How can you
live with yourself?
I am what I am, Oscar.
And I want what I want. And
right now I want a piece of cake.
From now on, when I'm hungry, I am
going to eat whatever I am hungry for.
That is
a dangerous game, friend-o.
Well, because
I thought that it was
a book about Anthropologie,
the store.
I don't know why you were in
that part of the bookstore.
Because it's next to
the baby section, okay?
Well, that makes more sense. You
should have said that at the beginning,
when you said, "I read a
book about anthropology."
I don't even know why
you're screaming at me right now.
I'm not screaming.
That's Meredith's cake.
It's her birthday.
I don't care.
I have an appetite for life.
Mmm.
God, that's lemon.
Good for you, man.
Good for you.
He takes what he wants.
You know what?
I think you're attractive
and I want to sleep with you.
What about Kelly?
You read my mind.
Is this a joke?
Yep.
It's hard to
live that way, man.
You gotta really not care what
people think about you, right?
I don't know how you do it,
Michael. I can't be that cold.
You'll learn, baby,
you'll learn.
I am an honorable man
and I will honor the contract.
But I don't have to
give her the good stuff.
Schrute sperm are strong, but they're
no match for a grown Schrute man.
Let's see what she gets.
Boss, we're out of paper.
Yeah, I noticed that.
Aren't you gonna add any more? Nope.
He don't give
an F about nothing.
I have got big balls.
I don't think
I'm gonna make it.
What about an
energy drink or something?
It gets in the breast milk. If I drink
it, Cece drinks it six hours later.
Well, it doesn't mean
I can't drink it.
Well, it does and it doesn't.
I probably
shouldn't tell you this,
but a lot guys in the
warehouse work multiple jobs,
so we have a place.
A place?
A restful location.
Talk to Glen, he'll
take you up in the lift.
You sleep in the warehouse?
Light bulb's burned out,
so it's dark.
And the heat from the backup
generator keeps it nice and warm.
Sometimes I think about it when
I'm trying to fall asleep at home.
But as far as the rest of the
office goes, it doesn't exist. Okay?
Okay.
Pam?
For your signature.
Okay.
Phyllis?
Okay, look at me.
Phyllis, look at...
Okay, that's...
All right, all right, you
know what? I'm sick of this.
I'm sick of the little
disapproving head shakes.
If you think that's going
to have any effect on me,
it will not.
I am going to leave right now
and go to a motel to meet Donna.
Why not your condo?
Because a motel is dirty,
and it is sexy.
Like me and like Donna.
And frankly, the stuff that we're
into isn't very condo-appropriate.
Michael, will you drop it?
Everybody's spoken their mind
and no one's changing their mind.
Okay, Morgan Freeman
narrating everything.
Do you want someone to stop
you? Because no one's going to.
Nobody better try to stop me.
Good.
I could have stopped him.
Are you warmed up?
No.
God, Angela, why is that
always my responsibility?
What did you
do to yourself?
Never mind.
Just... Never mind.
Well, it better
work. DWIGHT: Lt'll work.
Stop kissing me.
It's not in the contract.
How do I feel about
breaking up with Donna?
Good. Moral.
I feel proud.
Like a grown-up.
That was not easy because
I really liked her a lot.
I'm a little bit
emotional right now
because I know that I absolutely
made the right decision.
At the end of the day,
we have to do what's right.
And it was either
living with myself
or being happy.
And I picked
the
former.
Michael Scott?
Yes?
Do you want to make
a comment on the rumors?
Um...
I have done some
very bad things.
Things of which
I'm not proud.
I would like to
publicly apologize
to the coach
and the players,
and I vow to never
listen to my bodily
instincts ever again.
I'm talking about the Sabre
printers that catch on fire.
Oh! Okay, I was talking
about... What's going on?