The fundamentals of business.
"Mental" is a part of the
word. I have underlined it.
Because you're mental if
you don't have a good time.
You have to enjoy it.
"Fun" is in it.
"Fun"-damental.
Oh, right.
Get out.
I know, I know.
Yes, so, it all starts
with a handshake.
But you can't just go right to
the selling. You need small talk.
What topics can you
use for small talk?
Golf, stock market,
Dave Matthews.
Yes, what else?
Small things. Peas,
ball bearings, dimes.
No.
The weekend.
Yeah! That's good.
Come on up. Meredith, come up
here. Let's do a little something.
So, Meredith and I have
just started conversing,
and I will say,
"So, Meredith,
"how was your weekend?
What did you do?"
Well, I caught my son taking a dump
on the upper part of the toilet.
All right. He calls
it an "upper-decker."
Okay, okay.
God.
What you people don't know about
business, I could fill a book with.
Then do it.
What?
Write a book.
The Fundamentals of Business
by Michael Scott.
Over one billion sold.
More than the Bible. I'm
not surprised. Chapter One.
The businessman...
Mr. Grotti,
this is Michael Scott.
He's the person
you should talk to.
Hi. I'm sorry,
just a sec.
Erin, you're
supposed to be the gatekeeper.
Do you have any idea
how valuable my time is?
In your schedule, it just says
9:00 till noon is creative space.
I thought this
could be part of that.
Do you know how creative space works?
Okay, fine. Just cancel my afternoon.
You don't have anything in the
afternoon. It just says "free play."
Push free play till tomorrow morning.
Hi. Sorry, crazy day. You're
seeing how the sausage gets made.
Come in the conference room and I
will show you a finished sausage.
As a manager of business,
you've got a lot of pride.
Hmm.
But you also got a
lot of responsibility.
Yep.
None greater, perhaps,
than the need to be sure
that your small or large business is
secure in the event of a covered loss.
Okay.
There's nothing more
insulting to a great salesman
than having to listen
to a bad salesman.
It's like a great
basketball player
having to listen to a
bad basketball player.
Jim's gone
on his honeymoon.
So, I started borrowing
his office to fart in.
Then one day, I came
in and I just stayed.
'Cause this place is awesome.
It feels like home now.
Even better than my home.
My home sucks.
What do you think?
I think you're right.
Definitely looks
suspicious.
And his southern Italian
heritage raises some flags.
God forbid you should have
a fire in the warehouse.
Oh! Yep. Yeah. Definitely.
All that paper burning up.
Yeah, and the truck goes off the
side of the road, there's injury.
Mmm-hmm, I hear you. The truck.
You will be hearing
from me, Mr. Scott.
Okay, well...
I can be very,
very persistent.
Do your worst.
All right.
Would you look
at that, people?
What an unpredictable
world we live in, huh?
Thank you.
What happened in there? Nothing,
other than once again, I am just
thankful that I am a paper salesman.
Did he threaten you?
No, Dwight. Not everything is a threat.
Mobsters are.
There is no such
thing as monsters.
- He drives an SUV.
- I knew it.
More trunk space, or
should I say corpse space.
Okay, guys, I drive an SUV.
Does that mean I'm in the mob?
No, not that by itself,
but look at all the facts.
He seems like a mobster.
Wait, when did we start
talking about the mob?
The guy was trying
to sell me insurance.
All mobsters
have a front.
Sometimes it's
selling insurance,
sometimes it's waste
management or sanitation.
For the record, not all
Italian-Americans are in the Mafia.
I think he just seemed like he
was trying to sell me insurance.
Yeah. "Buy my insurance or
I burn your warehouse down."
Exactly.
He did talk about
a fire in the warehouse.
And he also vaguely threatened
me with testicular cancer.
All right.
Who else is here?
Pam and Jim are
on their honeymoon,
so there's not the usual
balance between sane and others.
Toby has mentally
checked out since June.
It's a very dangerous time. The
coalition for reason is extremely weak.
Oscar says
I checked out, huh?
Huh!
This is bad. All right.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Calm down,
calm down, calm down.
Ryan, you lived in New
York, what do you think?
Well, first of all, there's
no such thing as the Mafia.
Okay. What you have
are specific families.
What's the guy's
last name?
Um, it is Grotti.
Oh, no.
That is...
What? What?
John Gotti, you idiot.
It's a completely
different name.
So he won't get caught. DWIGHT: Yeah.
It's pretty close.
What are you
talking about?
What mobster would change his name
from Gotti to Grotti? It weakens it.
No, I disagree. "R" is among
the most menacing of sounds.
That's why they call it
"murder," not "mukduk."
Okay, too many different words coming
at me from too many different sentences.
Lock your door.
I'm not going
to lock my door.
Hello?
Jim, it's Oscar.
I'm so sorry to be calling
you on your honeymoon.
Oscar,
what is going on?
It's Michael. He thinks he's
being shaken down by the mob.
I don't know how you
usually handle this.
We're in
Puerto Rico, so...
Hey, Oscar. It's Pam, hey. Hey.
We're on our
honeymoon.
Pam, I'm sorry.
Unless someone
very close to us
is in immediate
physical danger,
you should not
be calling us.
You're right,
you're right.
All right. Okay, bye.
It's from Grotti.
He's following up.
Already?
This guy's persistent.
Okay. "I feel that
you will regret
"missing this great
opportunity to be in business."
That's bad. That's bad. Yeah. Yeah.
What are my options here?
Do I just ignore it or...
Yeah, right.
You heard him,
he's going to burn
the warehouse down
or run one of our
trucks off the road.
Okay, I'm calling
the police.
That is the stupidest thing
you could do right now.
No, he's right.
Cops can't do anything
until a crime
has been reported.
All right.
Not only that,
but if they find out you snitched,
you get a dead horse's
chopped off head in your bed.
You know what?
That's not going to happen.
That's an exaggeration.
- That's how it works.
What am I
supposed to do here?
When somebody threatens you,
you give in right away.
Okay, you need to buy insurance from
this guy and get him off your back.
I was thinking exactly the same thing.
No. Criminals are like
raccoons, okay?
You give them
a taste of cat food,
pretty soon they'll be
back for the whole cat.
Dwight. The only way to defeat a bully
is to stand up to him. Trust me,
I have bullied a lot of people.
I don't know. I don't know about that.
Wait. Let's hear him out.
This is interesting.
Here's what we do. We
meet him in a public place,
ask him to lunch
or something like that.
Someplace where he
can't be openly violent.
Okay.
Let him know
that you are not the typical kind
of guy that he can shake down,
that you're stubborn, that you
might even be a little bit dangerous.
I like this plan. I'd like to
officially withdraw my plan.
Hold on, hold on,
just...
No, no, no, no.
My plan is out.
We do it the hard way.
All right, I will meet with
him, but I'm not going alone.
Well, you're going to
have to. We'll be right beside you.
What?
All right.
What are you wearing?
Who's Pat?
If I'm going to back you up, I need
a weapon without drawing suspicion.
And I have to
justify it somehow,
so I'm a mechanic
with a tire thing.
Do you know
how to use it?
To change tires, no.
But, I mean, it's metal,
I can hit somebody with it.
Let's go, come on.
God. God.
Should I change?
You're wearing loafers.
Forget it.
Take that thing off
the table. Please.
Well, then I can't use it.
I'm just going to hide it.
Hey. The bathroom
checks out clean.
Nothing behind the toilet
except this roach motel.
No! God!
Oh, my God.
You'll never kill it that way. Guys.
You want to separate
the head from the thorax.
Guys, guys. Cool it.
There he is, there he is.
Hello.
Mr. Scott, hello.
Mr. Grotti, we meet again.
These are my associates.
Hi, Angelo Grotti.
Hi.
Hello.
So...
You got this table?
Yes. What's this, one
of them half-booths,
can't-decide-what-it-is
type of thing?
Well...
Waitress, we're going
to sit over here.
That's fine.
Okay.
Hello?
Hello, Mr. Halpert.
I'm calling from the Identity
Theft department at Capital One.
We've detected some unusual
activity on your credit card.
Oh, man. Do you think
it was stolen?
First, would you mind
verifying your home address?
Um... Yes.
383 Linden Ave.,
Scranton, PA.
And may I have the last four
digits of your social security?
Six-six-five-zero.
Well, Mr. Halpert, you're obviously
not in San Juan, Puerto Rico.
Wait a minute.
Yes, I am.
I'm going to go ahead
and put a hold on your card.
No. That... I...
I think that we should let the
criminal use the card a little longer.
Very funny, sir. We'll get a
new card out to you right away.
No. Have a nice day and thank you.
Shoot.
If you want to supplement
your coverage, we can do that.
If you want to replace your
current coverage, all the better.
Hey, you seem
like a nice guy.
Oh, he's not that nice.
That's true.
Mmm-hmm.
That's very true.
Okay, shut up.
Have you decided?
Yeah, I'll have the linguini,
red sauce on the side.
If the sauce does not come on
the side, I will send it back.
I want garlic bread,
toasted, not burnt.
If it comes burnt,
I will send it back.
Okay, then.
And for you, sir?
I will have
the gabbagool.
The what?
The gabbagool.
I don't really know
what that is.
You know,
gabbagool.
I don't have to have that.
What he's trying to
say is, gabbagool.
Guys, guys,
all right.
I don't really think
that we have that.
That's okay. Bring him the gabbagool.
I will have the
spaghetti with a side salad.
Okay.
If the salad is on top,
I send it back.
Why would you cancel
Jim's credit cards?
I usually can think
quick on my feet,
but they were so
fast on the phone.
This constitutes
identity fraud.
Oh, God.
I wouldn't last in jail,
Oscar. I'm not like you.
What's that
supposed to mean?
What, you don't
know about jail?
You would love jail.
Why would I love jail?
Because...
You would love it.
I don't think our company actually
needs any more insurance. So, I am out.
Look closely, Michael. I feel
there's a plan here for you.
Maybe we have
a plan for you.
How about you?
Maybe you can use supplemental
coverage of some kind.
Anybody can get hurt.
You always think it can't
happen to you, and...
Think about it.
Excuse me.
Sorry to bother you.
Are you a mechanic?
Yeah.
My battery's dead. I've got
my kid. Can you please help?
Yes, I can.
No, no, no,
no, come on.
I'm sorry, we're
having our salads.
Come on,
lady in distress.
Go, go.
Okay. Sorry.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate it.
Hey, do you
need any help?
I'm sure he can handle
a simple jumpstart.
Now, come on, sit down.
He's a good mechanic.
Sit down.
Where were we?
I don't...
He was trying to force you to
sign a policy. Okay, okay, okay.
So, we're choosing...
Okay. Yep.
Did you check out Dental?
All right, put it down.
Black goes on the red with
the... If we... Positive...
It being a motor drive,
it's probably down.
He seems bad at this.
You want to do this, junior?
I didn't think so.
I'm sorry, just had kind of a
long day at the mechanic store.
You've got
a leaky spark tube.
What?
So, your car's totaled.
You're gonna want to
get a refund on that.
Or my guy could do it, he's
great. But I can't do that for you.
I work exclusively
on motorcycles.
All right.
Now, if you could just sign
this letter of intent,
I'll bring this
back to my boss
and we can get
this in motion.
You okay, Pat?
Yeah, I was
just thinking
about how I had this car.
It was this Italian car.
And I was driving it,
and it kept
telling me how much
it needed oil, but I
wouldn't give it any oil.
And then, one day it exploded
and it killed everyone,
and that's what
I'm afraid of.
Aren't you a mechanic? Why
wouldn't you put oil in a car?
It was before my
technical training.
Don't do it.
Do it.
Don't.
Just do it.
Okay.
Don't do it.
Look, Mike, I don't know what
your friends are telling you,
but you have to
decide for yourself.
I mean, are these guys
going to take care
of your things
if you die tomorrow?
Yes.
Okay.
I don't understand. Why
would you buy a policy?
It's just the cost of
a cup of coffee an hour.
You were man enough to back
down, Michael. I'm proud of you.
I had to make
a snap decision, Dwight.
It wasn't a snap decision. You
were sitting there for an hour.
It was a lot of
snap decisions.
Do you know what "snap
decision" means? MICHAEL: Yes.
It means like this.
Just
get in the car.
Hello?
Jim?
Michael?
Oh, thank God.
How did you get this number?
Michael, we're on
a catamaran.
It wasn't easy.
I had to tell the hotel that
it was a medical emergency.
I chose a massive
coronary because
you told me that your
dad had a bad heart.
Listen, man,
I got a problem.
I think I'm in trouble with the
mob or a major insurance carrier.
That sounds bad.
Yeah, I know.
And you usually can get
out of stuff like this,
so I'm turning to you,
my friend.
I'm going to help you
through it, all right?
Okay.
All you're going
to need...
And then go to...
Jim. Are you...
And you'll be saved.
What? Wait. I didn't hear
a thing you just said.
Just... And then
you'll be saved.
No! God, I missed
the important part again.
No. Oh, my God.
And you'll be saved.
No, Jim.
Please repeat what you're
saying, I can't understand you.
Bermuda Triangle...
Please don't call again.
Jim?
Oh, my God.
Hey, question for you.
I recently purchased some insurance that
I can't afford given my present salary.
Is there anything
accounting-wise I can do
to sort of make
it all go away?
Accounting-wise, no, but phone-wise,
just call up and cancel it.
No, no.
Um...
What about this Cash
for Clunkers thing?
Just, no. No.
Okay. All right, well,
it was a thought. Thanks.
We have let Michael down,
and it's 85% your fault.
He's alive,
so you're welcome.
Not on the inside,
he's not.
Look at his life. Broke, living
in fear, no friends, dead-end job.
Yeah, some of that
existed before.
Not the living in fear,
that's new.
You're right,
that is new.
Yes.
He's got to stand up
to this Mafia guy.
Well, I don't see
that happening.
Me neither.
Not the way
things are now.
But what if Michael felt no
fear toward the Mafia guy?
Are you saying...
Yeah.
...that we surgically remove the
fear center from Michael's brain?
What is wrong
with you?
I am talking about convincing
Michael that the guy's not Mafia.
That seems
a little farfetched.
What, more farfetched than a
mobster walking into a paper company
for a low-level shakedown?
And that happened.
Michael, incredible
news. Grotti is clean.
No, he's not.
He's just good.
Nothing sticks to him. You still
don't understand how this works.
No, Michael, what
we're trying to say is,
we made a mistake
assuming he was Mafia.
I have a buddy who's a Fed and we
did a background check on the guy,
his background
is perfectly clean.
It's true,
he's clean.
I have a couple of friends still
on the force, checked with them,
ran his Fed friend up the flagpole
to make sure he wasn't on the take.
Turns out he's a totally lovely guy.
Sweetest guy on the force, really.
Class act.
Boy scout.
But Grotti acts like
he's Mafia, though.
He's trying to intimidate
you to close sales.
He's just
a pushy salesman.
And he made us all
look like chumps.
If there is one thing I hate
more than the Mafia, it is a liar.
I wish the Mafia would go
out and kill all the liars.
And bury them in my yard. And I
wouldn't tell the cops a thing.
Not that I would
be lying, per se,
but I would just get really
quiet all of a sudden.
This is
Grotti. This is Scott.
Oh! Great, Michael. I'm just
finishing up your paperwork right now.
Oh, really? Is that
supposed to scare me?
I thought
you'd be pleased.
Well, you thought wrong.
Because I am not pleased.
I'm actually kind of p.o.'d.
Why? I think you know exactly why.
Because you were trying to
scare me into buying insurance.
I don't get it.
How was I scaring you?
I think you knew exactly
what you were doing,
and frankly, I think you were
being a total and utter jerk.
Ooh, okay.
You suck.
- Okay. That's...
And I'm not going to buy
your stupid insurance.
That's good, let's wrap it
up. Okay. How about that?
The only person that actually
needs insurance is you,
if you show your face
around here again. Got it?
Look, Michael, when
we all calm down here,
maybe at some point
in the future,
you change your mind, why
don't you give me a call?
Doubt it.
Oh, man.
What a tool.
What?
Next time you look
in the mirror,
you're going to be looking at
a guy who stood down the Mafia.
No. What do you mean?
We just told you he wasn't
Mafia so you wouldn't be scared.
What?
You successfully
backed down the mob.
You made the Mafia apologize to
you. You made the Mafia be polite.
Oh, man.
I should be mad
at you guys.
But I'm not.
So, I looked him
in the eye and I said,
"Not today, Grotti.
Not today.
"And not tomorrow, and not the
next day, or the day after that.
"And you can tell
all your friends that
"if I see them,
then they are already dead."
I said something like that.
Very close.
Just to be clear,
he backed down
an insurance agent from
Mutual of Harrisburg.
Erin?
- Yes?
Coffee.
Okay.
Not from the kitchen,
Stop & Shop.
If it's not Stop & Shop,
I send it back.
Okay.
Large. If it's a medium, I send it back.
If it's an extra large,
I send it back.
How do you
return coffee?
Go.
Any questions?
Are you kidding me?
Hi, Pam. Is Jim there?
Listen, our credit card has been
canceled and we have to deal with that.
And I really can't handle the
fact that you're calling us here.
Okay, that sounds good.
I'll let you go.
Just tell Jim
that I said hi.
I will. I will, Kevin. I will
make that my top priority.
Cool. Okay. Bye.
They have no idea
what happened.