They're back!
Oh, yeah!
Woo-hoo!
- Jim and Pam!
How was Puerto Rico? Was
it so romantic? JIM: It was.
It really was.
Really was.
I'm so happy for you.
Puerto Rico
was awesome.
Oh, my gosh. The honeymoon was great.
We met this other couple at
the resort, Frank and Benny.
We hung out
with them a lot.
Frank and
Beans. Always makes her laugh.
Frank and Beans.
Is there someone there?
Who's there?
I hear voices.
Is somebody there?
Yeah!
Is someone here? I can't
see you because I'm blind.
It's Jim
and Pam, Michael.
- It is?
- Yeah.
They're back?
Pam.
Nope.
And, oh, Jim.
Hi, Michael.
I haven't seen you since my
accident that I had when I fell...
I fell into the pool
of acid, eyes-first.
Blind guy.
Blind Guy McSqueezy.
How do I describe it?
It is a character
I've been workshopping,
whose lack of vision gets
him into all sorts of trouble.
The women in my improv
class absolutely hate him.
So, what'd you
bring us?
Some candy.
What else?
That's it.
Oh, because you spent
so much on the wedding.
It's good to be home.
This conversation has
two items on the agenda.
Did we have a conversation scheduled?
Number one, do not leave
your things on my desk.
It's not some kind of personal
pen receptacle for you.
I don't care how high
they promote you.
Which brings me
to item number two.
I never formally congratulated
you on your promotion,
so I'd just like to
say congratulations.
Wow. That's really thoughtful
of you, Dwight. Thank you.
You're welcome.
I inserted a listening device
into the belly of the mallard.
Now I can observe Jim,
track Jim, and destroy Jim.
Just like in
the Bavarian fairytale.
Only this time the mallard
skins the toad alive.
And, of course,
in this version,
you lose the whole veiled
critique of the Kaiser thing.
I'm sorry to have been
bugging you all these years.
It's a real
handsome duck.
Mallard.
Okay, I'll get out
of your hair.
Hey.
We brought back some
Puerto Rican candy.
Coco-Leche. That's
my favorite. Awesome.
I'll leave it up here
so everyone can enjoy it.
Oh, let me just check
with Michael first.
I think it'll be okay.
I think it will, too, but I'll
just check with him, though.
Great.
Oops. Sorry. Oops!
I have recently
taken a lover.
Well, that's great.
Congratulations.
Who's the lucky lady?
Pam's mom.
What?
Pam's mom, Helene.
Remember,
from your wedding?
You're messing with me.
About what?
You did not have
sex with Pam's mom.
Oh, big time.
What kind of car
does she drive?
She drives a green Camry,
And the seats go
all the way down.
All the way down.
Oh, my God.
What?
Okay, never tell Pam,
and then, secondly...
Good. A pact. A pact.
Although, I may have
to break it tonight,
when Helene and I
tell Pam over dinner.
You all right?
Oh, my God.
Hey, Jim... Not now, Toby. My God!
Jesus. Get the hell out of here, idiot!
What did I do?
Okay, as far as dinner
tonight, cancel that,
and please,
for both of our sakes,
never, ever,
ever see her again.
I think you're
underestimating Pam.
I think more than anything,
she wants me to be happy.
No. Not more
than anything.
Okay. I...
I have a good thing with the
mom. Don't call her "the mom."
She's right on my way
home from work.
Then take a different
way home, man!
All right,
I'll take surface streets.
The last thing in the world I
would want to do is upset Pam.
Okay. So, we're good.
Yeah.
Can you change my dinner
reservations from four people to two?
Sure. Is it okay
if I put out some candy
that Pam brought back
from Puerto Rico?
Sure.
Thanks for asking.
Pam, we're all set.
Yum.
Frank and Beans!
So, what'd we decide
for Michael?
The bottle of rum or
the seashell alarm clock?
You know what, can I have
the weekend to decide?
Bottle of rum it is.
All right, shall we?
You know what?
I am really slammed trying to
catch up on everything here,
and I know that
Michael's slammed, too,
so maybe we should do this when
things are a little less crazy.
Come on, it'll take two seconds.
No, it...
Oh, wow.
That is amazing. I feel
like a real Puerto Rican.
Michael, you're all
set at Botticelli's.
I changed the reservation
to two people.
Erin, look.
Fun.
- Yeah.
Wow, Botticelli's. That
sounds like a special occasion.
Yeah, no,
it's nobody.
I don't know. I think
Michael has a date.
No. Yeah, I think you have a date.
I don't, I don't.
Come on.
Ah, I think we should just drop it.
Because obviously he doesn't
want to talk about it.
I don't deserve this, guys.
- Yes, you do.
No, I don't.
Just take the parrot.
Okay, back to
the old grind.
I was probably going to
break up with her anyway.
Oh! That's too bad.
Don't.
Pam, it is very
complicated.
There are a lot of
moving parts here.
Sounds complicated.
Yeah, but, I mean, if you
really like this person,
then you should
see where it goes.
You want me
to be happy?
Of course.
Part of the problem is she's the
mother of a close friend of mine.
Oh.
More than a friend.
A coworker.
Oh, gossip.
Who is it?
Who is it,
Michael?
Who?
It's okay.
No, no, no, no, no.
No. Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
No!
That could have
gone one of two ways,
but I never expected her to get upset.
You seem tense. Hey, you want
me to give you the chills?
Okay.
There's an egg on your
head And the yolk is running down
The yolk is running down
Feels good.
There's a knife in your back
And the blood is gushing down
Sleeping with Pam's mom.
Sometimes dinner.
The blood is gushing down
You know, I really would
have appreciated a heads-up
that you were
into dating mothers.
I would have introduced you to mine.
How could you do this
to me? He's my boss.
How many times have I
complained about him to you?
No, I am not being dramatic,
you are being crazy!
Who wants a hot chocolate?
Thank you.
So, Dwight gave me this
wooden mallard as a gift.
I found a recording
device in it.
Yes. So, I think
if I play it just right,
I can get Dwight to live out
the plot of National Treasure.
You need to be more upset about
this. She's your mother, too, now.
Your mother is sleeping
with Michael Scott.
Andy, can I talk
to you for a second?
Sure thing,
Tuna boss.
How may I be
of service to you?
I am going to need
your advice.
I was thinking of getting this
opera for Dwight's birthday.
What do you think?
This aria is a joke.
Really?
What are you thinking?
I was going to go
with this one.
Let me tell you something,
if you respect him at all,
you will get him
something better.
Nard-Dog, what was
that all about?
I know, right?
What were you guys
talking about in there?
Trust me, it would
only make you mad.
Due to a certain
recent incident,
corporate has asked all the
branches to come up with ideas
as to how we can better
communicate with our communities.
Is this because of the 60 Minutes
segment about working conditions
in our Peruvian
paper mill?
That was a hit job.
If you read the Dunder Mifflin
press release, it clearly states
that they had absolutely
nothing to do
with that particular
cancer cluster.
So, if there is a lesson
to be learned here,
and I'm not sure
that there is,
it is that in order to
help our communities,
we need to put other people's
needs ahead of our own.
And whoever comes up with the best
idea gets a $50 gift certificate
to the restaurant of his or
her choice.
Yeah.
- Good, good.
Okay, who wants to help the
world one step at a time?
All right, good.
Volunteerism is important.
Every weekend I volunteer
at the local animal shelter,
and they need a lot
of help down there.
Last Sunday, I had to put down
over 150 pets all by myself.
All right,
that's...
Paint a mural of Chicano
leaders. All right.
I have a way to make Scranton a
better place. You could leave it.
Okay, I'm out of here.
See you later, guys.
And stay out.
Bye-bye.
Okay. Oh, no, here's
an idea. Conservation.
I love it,
conservation.
Let's start by
conserving our time
and stop having
these stupid meetings.
No more meetings!
Anybody else?
Who else has an idea?
I have some ideas about
conservation. JIM: Yes.
Angela.
Thank you.
Please. Can you hold down the fort?
Hey, boo. ANGELA: Well, first
of all, I think that we could...
Why are you crying?
Yes, I think we should
look into that.
If you could just
speak up louder.
Well, for our profit and
loss... MICHAEL: No, no.
No, I'll talk to her. I will. No,
nobody talks to my baby that way. Uh-uh.
Yeah, I'll let you know how it
goes. All right. Bye, pickle.
- Who's pickle?
Pamela Morgan Beesly.
You need to apologize
to your mother right now.
I'm sorry, I was told
I had the floor. Yes.
Hold on, hold on.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
It's all good.
I'm not apologizing to anyone.
Michael owes me an apology.
For trying to find happiness
in the arms of a lover?
Don't call my mother
your lover.
Oh, yes! That's what
I'm talking about.
That is not okay, dude.
All right,
in my defense...
Disgusting.
That's messed up, man.
Yes, thank you.
Welcome to my personal hell.
You have no sense of boundaries,
Michael. Shut up, Oscar.
Hey, all right, you know what?
Clearly, I'm outnumbered here.
But can I just say
one thing? Please?
What is so wrong
about me?
I'm caring,
I'm generous.
I'm sensual.
Is it really so horrible that I could
possibly go out and find happiness?
Good luck, Michael. I hope
you find what you're looking for.
Maybe you're right.
Who are we to...
Shut up, Oscar!
What is wrong
with all of you?
He is sleeping
with my mother!
I don't think there's a whole
lot of sleeping going on.
Let's get back to
the matter at hand.
Whatever, you know.
Sleep with my mom, just
sleep with everybody's mom.
No, no, no,
no, no... No.
This is not... RYAN: Whoa! That's
my mom you're talking about.
I don't like
the tone here.
This is a place of business.
You are to listen to others,
you are to give
others respect,
and you are to keep your
personal issues out of it.
Oh, my God!
You are ridiculous!
Do not talk
to me that way!
I am your boss and I may someday
be your father, so get out.
You are never going to
be my father. You get out.
I hope that you are willing to
die in this office, because I am.
Me, too.
Hey.
Pam, how's your day going?
Pam, just for the record, I think
you're overreacting a little bit.
Your mom's old enough
to make her own decisions.
Oh, well, thanks, Oscar.
I was just wondering,
how would you feel
if Michael was sleeping
with your mom?
My mother's
in a wheelchair.
Well, he could still...
I'm sorry about that.
Could I just get you to sign
the second page as well?
Ryan, I have
to ask you a personal question.
Do you think that
I should get a fedora?
I don't think so, no.
Why? I think I'd
look really hot in one.
Where did you
get your fedora?
I'd rather
not say.
You think I'm going
to get the same fedora as you?
Hey, Dwight.
Shh!
Natural look. KELLY: I think
I would look really cute in it.
It has to go with the
persona that you already have.
Well, I think
I have that persona.
Where did you
get that mallard?
What the hell
is a mallard?
That!
Oh, Professor Damon D. Duck.
Jim gave him to me.
Okay, I gave that to him as
a gift. I'm taking that back.
If you take it back,
I'll scream.
I'll give you
five bucks for it.
Twenty.
Ten.
Deal.
You're so cool.
This reminds me, you owe
me three bucks for gas.
Hey, Toby, can I talk
to you for a minute?
Yeah, sure.
What's up?
I just wanted to apologize
for taking that tone
with you earlier.
That was uncalled for.
I'm sorry.
Yeah. That means a lot.
Thank you for saying it.
Can I sit down
for a second?
Yeah,
or pull up a chair,
or you can sit
on the shredder.
This is going
to sound weird,
but I think I may be the victim
of a hostile work environment
with this whole
Pam situation.
You should probably deal with
that outside of the workplace.
She brought it
into the workplace,
so I feel like it has
to be dealt with here.
Yeah. Okay, well, I
mean, I could talk to her.
Really?
Yeah.
Would you do that?
That's why they
pay me the big bucks.
You're a good, good guy.
Okay.
You know, I always knew if Michael
just took the time to get to know me,
we'd become friends.
Hey, Pam, could I talk
to you for a sec?
Sure. What's up?
Well, I was hoping that maybe in light
of everything that's happened today,
it would be a good idea
if you and me and Michael
head into the conference room
for some conflict resolution.
What's the matter? Can't
fight your own battles?
No, that's...
Maybe you should just take the
rest of the day off, you know?
Oh, would that make
you feel better?
I don't... I can't hear
your conversation.
You can tell Michael
that I'm not leaving.
Buddy, I think that you
can't make her leave...
Yeah, yeah, okay,
you're a jackass.
Hey, hey, you know what? You're
just as stubborn as your mother.
When you don't want to do
something, you just don't do it.
Michael, you're just her rebound!
You were right, Jim, I
should have listened to you.
Should never
have told her.
What? You knew?
Barely. I... I don't have all the facts.
Frank and Beans.
Okay, do you want me
to stop dating your mom?
Is that how we're going to
get past this? Because I will.
Hmm. Yes.
Well, that is not
going to happen.
Then why did you
even offer?
Because I assumed that
you want me to be happy,
because I want
you to be happy.
Michael, let me make
this very easy for you.
I could give a About your
happiness. Stop dating my mother!
You know what? I'm going to
start dating her even harder.
What's that
supposed to mean?
You know what it means.
Hey.
Shut it.
Yep.
I don't need to be
friends with Pam.
I have plenty of
female friends.
My mom, Pam's mom, my aunt,
although she just blocked me on IM.
What's-her-face from Quiznos.
I see her four times a week.
Dwight, you brought
the mallard back.
Well, I had to.
I mean, Kelly was not...
Hi, buddy.
I'm sorry.
A wooden duck?
Mallard. I put it in your
office in order to surveil you.
I was jealous that you
got the promotion over me.
Okay, just to be clear,
you're terrible at this.
And you're not equipped for
espionage. I'm equipped...
Stop.
Don't tell Michael.
I won't.
But you will wash
and buff our car.
Punishment fits the crime. I accept.
Good night, everyone.
Night, Pam.
Thanks again
for the rum.
Good night, Michael.
Good night, Erin.
Hey, Pam, can I see you for a second?
So, Dwight heard you were
having a really rough day,
so he generously
offered to wash our car.
Aw, he did that for me?
Yes, he did.
You know what was nice?
Night swimming in Biobay.
Remember that older couple whose
kids were also named Jim and Pam?
Yeah.
Say more nice things.
Well, we went on a Segway
tour, and we're awesome at it.
Yes, we are.
And Frank and Beans.
Maybe I'm overreacting.
Yeah, maybe.
But I don't think I am.
You're not, nope.
Nope.
Oh! Where did you get that hat?
I'd rather not say.
We have our high
quality 28-pound bond,
our heavier 38-pound bond, or our...
I've got eight
hours of this.
Of course I wanted Jim to find
the mallard. Make him feel safe.
Did you really think I would
put my primary listening device
in a wooden mallard?
I'm not insane.
Fifty-five pound cover
stock, which is the heaviest paper
that will still feed smoothly
through your desktop printer.