Yeah?
You wanted to see me?
Yes, Oscar, come on in.
Close the door if you would.
Thank you. Thanks so
much for talking to me.
Yeah, sure.
I'm going in
for a procedure today.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
It's routine. I'm just
a little bit scared.
I'm sure everything
will be fine.
What's the procedure,
if you don't mind my asking?
It is a colonoscopy.
Okay.
In your experience,
what should I be expecting
in terms of sensation
or emotions?
Is there anything I can do to
make it more pleasurable for me,
or for Dr. Chaudry?
Oh, my God!
My main concern, should
I have a safe word?
Yeah.
So, Michael, you think
you can give me a rundown
on the Buffalo
clients by Monday?
Absolutely. You know what?
I'll do you one better.
Sunday. Sunday night.
Okay. I will
get it Monday.
Hold on, big guy.
I'm going to put it in the mail
Sunday night, you'll get it Wednesday.
Okay. Jim, you want to
hit the conference room?
Sure.
Hey, good luck.
Oh, right, this thing.
I remember now.
What's this about?
This is just me and
David, if that's okay.
It's okay with me. He's
going to want me in there.
No. It's okay,
Michael. We got it.
Really?
Yeah.
All right. Do you mind
if I sit this out?
I have so much work to do, I feel
like I'm going to blow my brains out.
Okay. You got it.
Am I worried that Jim and David
are having a meeting without me?
No. Because we are
the three amigos.
And once in a while,
one of the amigos will
go off to the bathroom,
while the other two
have a secret meeting.
Hey, let me escort you to your desk.
Okay. It's just three or
four steps, but thank you.
Thank you. You and Jim are close, huh?
Yeah. I think the pregnancy
really brought us together.
Hey, what do you think he
and David are talking about?
What do you...
Um, I don't know.
Well, you said good
luck to Jim as he walked in.
Did I? Doesn't sound like
me. Not very superstitious.
If you're lying to me right now, Pam,
your baby is gonna
come out a liar.
That's how it works. They inherit
things through the breast milk.
Please don't talk
about my breast milk.
I just don't want
you to lie to me.
I don't want you to ever lie
to me. Have I ever lied to you?
Yeah.
I just don't
want you to.
I was rushing
to fill an order.
I put the ladder up to grab a box
of three hole from the top shelf,
next thing I know, I'm on the
ground, ladder's on top of me.
And that's how you
broke your ankle?
Yes.
Hmm. Interesting.
How did the ladder end up on
top of you if you fell off of it?
This doesn't concern you, man.
You need to walk away.
Oh, really? I'm sorry. I
thought this was a free country.
I didn't know we were
in Communist Sweden.
If we were
living in Sweden,
I wouldn't have
to worry about this
because we'd have
universal healthcare.
That's not... Okay.
Be quiet.
I'm talking about...
Hmm...
I will send this
off to corporate.
Make sure you hold on
to your medical bills.
Feel better.
Thanks, T-man. Later.
So long, Darryl.
Feel better.
He's lying.
He has a doctor's note.
From who? Dr. J? You really
need to investigate this.
People don't just
fall off of ladders.
Guy on my street
fell off a ladder
painting his house.
It was on the news.
Since when have you known
Darryl to rush to do anything
other than to come up here
for birthday cake?
"Y'all having birthday cake?"
That's not a very good Darryl. Please!
And how many foremen do
you know that pull boxes?
It just doesn't add up.
Well, we did a little
investigation, and Dwight had a good point.
The ladder didn't reach the top
shelf. I don't know if I believe it,
but I am a fan of the
hardboiled detective novel.
"I'll punch you
into mush, see?"
Uh-huh. Well, if he doesn't like it, you
can tell that s.o. B that he is fired.
Sorry, I'm going into a meeting right
now. I will. I love you, too. Bye.
Who was that?
Sorry about that.
What'd I miss?
Michael, we would like to continue
the rest of this meeting in private,
please,
if you don't mind.
I do not mind.
Yes, I do. No, I don't.
Yes, I do. No, I don't mind.
Catch you guys on the
flippity-flop. Oh, this...
Call waiting. Yeah?
Uh-huh. Well, you tell the
mayor he just lost six votes.
They've been
in there a while.
Yeah.
Can't be good.
No.
Think they're
talking about me?
No, I think they're
talking about me.
Yeah. That makes way more
sense. Okay. Thanks, boss.
What is Jim telling
him? That I can't handle this job?
That's bull crap.
That is bull crap.
Although it has been
chaotic lately.
Corporate shut down
the Buffalo branch,
which left us to absorb
all of their clients.
I will tell you, there
has been work every day.
Had to come in
on a Saturday
to retrieve... I left
my cell phone here.
Hey, Kelly.
So jealous
of your boobs.
Thank you.
Um, listen, I just wanted to confirm
that you're not
coming to the wedding,
which is totally understandable,
and more than fine.
Is Ryan going?
I don't know,
he hasn't RSVPed yet.
We invited everyone in
the office to our wedding,
even though we realized most people
wouldn't be able to make
the drive to Niagara Falls.
Which is why we're
having it in Niagara Falls.
Then Michael
told everyone
they could have Friday and
Monday off if they came.
So now, people have to decide if
they want to come to our wedding
or have to work.
Here's the deal.
I really want to go.
But I'm not gonna go
if Ryan doesn't go,
because it's kind of
a waste of time.
That came out wrong.
It would be awesome if you
could try to get him to go
because I'd really like
to be there to support Jim.
What can I do
for you, hoss?
How are your
sales doing?
How are my sales doing?
Busted.
You know, my numbers
are down a little bit.
And it's 'cause
of the economy.
You're not buying it.
You're good.
Okay, the truth is
I have been having trouble
focusing lately. I'm in this weird,
flirty, nebulous thing
with this cousin of mine.
And it's a total mind f'er.
Again with the cousin.
Oh, I'm sorry, Phyllis.
You explain
this email. Okay?
"Hey, Andy, let's go visit Grandma
and then get drunk together. Ha, ha."
Shh. I'm just trying to figure out
what's going on in that room, okay?
Wallace
had to show up
on the one four-month period
that I'm completely overwhelmed.
You know when they say, "It's
so crazy it just might work?"
Well, I don't believe that. I
say go for the airtight plan.
And that is why
I am having Andy
wheel me into
the conference room
inside a makeshift
cheese cart.
It is just elegant.
Be my eyes.
You got it.
What have we here?
Oh!
Hello.
Just backing up
and turning around.
Hey, we're
gonna do this...
It's not for you.
I took the liberty of preparing
for you a cheese platter,
which I will place here on the
eastern wall of the conference room.
Cheese platter?
From the Wisconsin region,
a nice, firm cheddar.
Also from the great state of
Wisconsin, an aged Parmesan.
Here you will find
a cheddar-style spread,
which has reacted nicely with
the air to form a light rind,
which I think you'll find both
challenging and delicious.
At that point, I would
recommend you take
a quick trip south of the border
to the great state of Illinois,
where you will find this
fine blue cheese dressing.
If I may be so bold,
it's a lot of fun
to let the goldfish
take a little swim
in the blue cheese.
All right, well, I should
go. Thanks for this.
You've given me
a lot to think about.
Please promise me you won't
do anything until we speak.
No, I won't.
All right. Hey,
thanks for taking the time.
Yeah. Appreciate it.
Thank you, Jim.
Erin,
is Michael around?
I think
he's around here.
Is that...
Hey, hey, hey.
You must have walked right
past me. How you doing?
Yeah. Could we talk in
your office for a sec?
Yes, definitely.
Okay.
It sounds
like a EMD P40.
Nah. That's a GE.
The P40 is much
higher-pitched.
You're into trains?
Have been my whole life. Wow!
I'm rebuilding a
turn-of-the-century steam engine
in my slaughterhouse.
That's so cool.
Yeah.
Wow! I'd love to take a look at that.
Yeah. It's just a
run-of-the-mill slaughterhouse,
but sure, anytime.
Well, you know,
because of the trains.
Wait, someone's coming.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
It's Darryl! Get down!
He's not using crutches!
Get the camera.
Start taping.
Drive!
Worker's comp, my ass!
I can't believe this.
Hey, you ass!
Toby!
You gonna eat all
that dog food yourself?
No, no!
Oh, man!
You okay?
Just drive.
Hey, Ryan.
Hey.
So, I just wanted to confirm that
you're not coming to my wedding.
Yeah, I might stop by.
It costs about
$75 per person.
Okay. I once had a glass of
Cognac that cost $77, so...
Can you just tell me now
if you're coming or not?
Yes. I'm coming
to your wedding.
Okay. Ryan Howard, yes.
Probably yes.
Kelly Kapoor, yes.
Are you sure you're okay with
these new responsibilities?
Look who you're talking to.
Just trying to figure out the best
way to utilize everyone's talents.
Well, I would say
that my greatest talent
is being the best
man, woman or child
to have ever run
this branch. Ever.
And what about Jim?
You think Jim is
someone who is ready
to move into
a management position?
Permission to speak
on the record.
Please do.
Jim is like Big Bird.
He is tall and yellow
and very nice.
But would I put him
in charge? No.
I don't think so. He... Big Bird
doesn't make the tough decisions.
If I was going to put someone in
charge, I would put Bert in charge.
Or I would put one of the
real grownups in charge,
like Maria.
Or Gordon, maybe.
I thought you liked Jim.
Very much.
Jim is my best friend.
But here's his
performance report.
Right here.
Now, this was
written by Toby,
who we all know is
extremely reliable.
"Constant office distraction. Spends
way too much time at reception.
"Antagonizes other salesmen.
Not at all what he thinks he is."
It's not very well written.
But you get the gist.
Is there anybody else you think could
run the day-to-day of the branch?
I could just continue
to run it myself, that's...
Jim had an interesting idea to
help you with this extra workload.
And it involved
you being promoted
to oversee all
northeast sales.
And then Jim would be
promoted to your position.
This was Jim's idea?
Mmm-hmm.
Wow!
Well, I'd have to talk to my
mother and my guy at H&R Block.
Okay. But, well, see,
here's the thing, though.
The plan doesn't work
unless we have someone to
replace you. I was hoping...
Plus, we have to worry about
Jim. He has another job offer.
We may have to replace him.
I didn't tell Michael because
I thought he'd try to help.
Example, he handed out Jell-O shots at
the 23rd mile of the Steamtown Marathon.
Jim, can you walk me down
to my car for a second?
Sure.
I can't help but feel
partially responsible.
Little pick-me-up. Those
are the best. Sugar rush.
When you were in the office
earlier talking to Wallace,
did I come up at all?
Well, we did talk about
how handsome you are.
Why don't we head into
your office and talk?
Okay. What did
we... God! We said...
I know there were
certain things we said.
Michael, look.
I'll just be honest with you.
Earlier today, I spoke with
Wallace about a promotion.
And I actually think
that talk went really well.
Mmm-hmm.
And then,
after he spoke with you,
for some reason, it felt
like things had changed.
Hmm. That's weird.
That's weird.
Kind of weirding me out.
Did you know that Lincoln's
secretary was named Kennedy?
Michael,
did you say anything?
Tell you what,
when you leave this office,
I'm going to call Wallace
and I'm going to tell him
that you should
get that promotion.
Really?
Yes.
You will?
Wanna do it right now?
Yes.
I tried to keep
Michael in the dark.
I should have known that he can
do just as much damage in the dark.
I need to see
your pupils.
I have to see if
they're dilating...
Toby! Dwight!
Is that them?
Definitely.
You come to my house,
bust up my trash cans,
call my baby sister an ass
and told her to eat dog food?
We thought that
she was you.
Why would you think
a lady is me?
Are you serious? Because
you look exactly alike.
Am I the only one?
- That's too far...
Are you getting this?
I mean...
I don't see it.
Here's what
I'm gonna do.
I'm calling corporate and I'm filing
a complaint against both of you.
Oh, Darryl.
Come on, Gwyneth.
Sad.
This is David.
Hey, David,
this is Michael...
Michael Scott here.
Yeah.
Just wanted to talk to
you about Jim Halpert.
I understand that he did
not receive that promotion,
and I wanted to see
what I could do
to nudge you in the right direction.
So, what, you're changing
your mind about Jim?
Absolutely not!
Like I said before,
Jim is fantastic
and he deserves this job.
Michael, it seems like
you're cutting in and out.
This is not what
you said earlier.
What... Here's the thing.
Jim is the best
man for this job.
I think you should
give it to him.
Well, it doesn't change what
you showed me in Jim's file.
What?
Well...
That was an anomaly.
That file had been falsified.
Toby Flenderson is doing drugs.
Michael, I really don't know
what's going on down there, but...
Oh, damn it!
I am getting pulled over for
talking on my cell. Damn it!
Hey, Darryl, look,
we're here to apologize.
We're cool.
- Wait.
They're using the lift as
their own personal elevator.
What?
He broke his ankle
climbing over the railing,
then he lied about it
because it was a misuse
of company equipment.
Case closed.
Stupidest thing
I ever heard.
Really? Then why is there
new wood only on one railing?
Let's just check
the security tapes, Toby.
Well, you know, I don't think
there's any reason to check them,
but I suppose if we wanted
to be really certain.
All right. Yeah.
Fine, so whatever.
Yes!
You really did it.
Now, I would like to file an
official complaint to corporate
because Darryl lied
on an official form.
And I'm telling them you guys
sexually harassed my sister.
No judge
is gonna believe that.
Okay.
Look, we could all file
complaints against each other
and just drown in a sea
of paperwork, but,
you know, we'll just
move on with our lives.
So, Dwight and Darryl came to an
agreement that they would both file
complaints
with corporate,
and now I get to do
all this paperwork.
We worked it out.
Hey, hey, Jim. It would make
me feel really good right now
if you would just punch me in
the face, all right? Just do it.
How many times
have I asked you
to put me up for
a branch manager job?
I never recommended you because
I didn't want to lose you.
And I didn't
want to lose Pam.
Now I don't want
to lose the baby.
So, instead,
you screwed me?
That's what she said.
No.
David Wallace
is calling.
We're kind of in the
middle of something here.
Should I tell him
you'll call back?
Yeah. No.
I'll tell him myself.
Let's both.
Hello?
Hey, Michael.
Yes.
You got Jim
there with you?
No, it's just us.
Actually, can you call Jim in?
I want him on this. Please.
Oh! Well, here
he is right now.
Come in.
Hi, David.
Hey, guys.
So, I spoke to Alan.
We had kind of an unconventional
idea, which I think is pretty cool.
But it only works if
everyone's onboard.
Well, just as long as it
means Jim becomes a manager.
We were thinking of having two
branch managers in Scranton.
Both of you guys
working as co-managers.
Jim would handle
the day-to-day,
and Michael, you would focus on
clients and big picture stuff.
Wow!
That sounds pretty cool.
I like that!
So, manager
and co-manager.
Co-manager and co-manager.
See, there are a lot
of moving pieces
and this is the only way
I can sell it upstairs.
Well, that might be a
little confusing for people
because they
know me as manager.
All right, hey, Michael, can
you pick up for one second?
Okay, look, I'm not going
to force you into anything.
If you're willing
to lose Jim, fine.
You just say so. We'll
find another solution. Okay?
Is that what
you want to do?
Okay, people, listen up!
- Okay, everybody.
I have an announcement to make.
Fraud was committed in... Whoa!
Do you have
an announcement?
I was making it.
Everybody, David Wallace
and I have talked,
and we have decided to promote
Jim to the position of co-manager.
Co-manager of what?
Of your butt!
And your butt, and your butt, and your
butt. All of Scranton branch butts.
What's happening
to you, Michael?
What's happening to me?
I am also being
promoted to co-manager.
We will be
co-managers together.
Jim Halpert, welcome.
Thank you.
Niagara Falls in October?
Hells yeah!
Do you think that you could
send in your RSVP card?
No. I'll just
tell you now. Easier.
Well, you have to
choose a food option,
and there's information in there
about directions and lodging.
I'll just have whatever's
fanciest, unless there's ribs,
and I'll just get all the other
information the day of. I'll text you.
You are going to text me
the morning of my wedding
to ask for directions...
Mmm-hmm. Right.
...and you will eat
whatever is fanciest?
Unless there's ribs.
Rude.
So rude, right?
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, my gosh. I have been
chasing people down all day.
It's incredible.
Pam, my bag was there.