Could you please sign
my expense report?
No way, no how. Expense
reports are a day-to-day item.
That is Jim's now. I am
exclusively big picture. Epic.
Sign this.
Uh-uh-uh.
Where's the please?
We're not animals.
Sign it.
No. Not without a please.
Idiot.
I have a complaint
about Jim.
That is not
big picture.
I would like to file a huge,
enormous, massive complaint
about the tallest guy
in our office.
Okay.
Jim won't sign
my expense report.
That is not...
Okay. Day-to-day.
That is day-to-day.
No. That is huge.
You're trying to trick me. Get out,
get out, get out, get out, get out.
I'd like to lodge
a complaint.
I'm sorry to hear about that.
Who is this about?
You.
Okay.
Just want to let you know I
take complaints very seriously,
so, when did
this happen?
One minute ago.
Okay. And how
do you feel?
Angry.
All right. Did he hit you? No.
Did you cry?
No.
Did you feel like crying? No.
I'm just going to write,
"Held back tears."
Wait, stop writing that.
That is not true.
If you stop crying,
I'll stop writing it.
I'm not...
I deserved that
promotion. Not Jim.
Oh, man, makes me want to put
him in a triangle choke hold
and force him
down to the ground
and just keep
pressing and pressing,
and then flip him over and then put
him in a hammerlock and he's gasping.
He's panting for
every last breath.
And the crowd is going crazy
and boom, I emerge victorious!
Eighteen thousand dollars
and a chance at the title!
Dwight, Jim wants you
to keep it down.
Everyone, now would be
a good time to freshen up
because I'd like
everyone to meet
in the conference room
in five minutes.
And I suggest that
you bring a snack
because we may be
in there for a while.
Michael.
Yes.
Can I talk to you in my
office for a second? Mmm...
Sure. But could I first
talk to you in my office?
Can I also be a boss?
Look, it doesn't
take a genius to know
that any organization thrives
when it has two leaders.
Go ahead, name a country that
doesn't have two presidents.
A boat that set sail
without two captains.
Where would Catholicism be
without the popes?
I have noticed
that we...
Welcome.
Thank you. I have
noticed we've been having
a lot of conference
room meetings. Mmm-hmm.
And I'm wondering if
perhaps those are a bit...
Disruptive.
Yes.
No. I don't think they are. I think
the meetings are very important.
Okay. Maybe we
should talk specifics.
Let's do.
Okay.
Yesterday we had
a meeting about planets.
Well, to be fair,
Jim, James... Jimothy.
To be fair, Jimothy...
That sounds weird.
Are you okay with
being called Jim?
I am.
All right.
Jim, to be fair,
the conversation
wasn't about planets.
Right.
At first, we were
talking about
introducing a line
of toilet paper.
And what part
of the human body
does one use
toilet paper upon?
So you draw a line from
there to the other planets,
and I think by the end, we all learned
a little bit about
how small we are.
Yes, I agree.
I just feel...
Because it's
a big universe.
And we're all just little
tiny specks of dust.
I just think that maybe they're
eating large amounts of the day.
You know what eats a large
amount of the day are naps.
You go to sleep, it's light
out, you wake up, it's dark.
That's the whole day. Where
did that day go? I have no idea.
You mean
on a weekend?
Yes.
How about this?
I think our goal should be
we don't have meetings unless
they're absolutely essential.
All right. No more
meetings this week.
Really?
You just agree to that?
I can be very
surprising.
What's going on?
I need to fit into
my wedding dress.
However,
I'm also pregnant.
You know, it's a myth
that women have to gain
more than nine pounds
in a pregnancy.
Look at these actresses.
Some of them lose weight.
Hey, did you guys register
for wedding gifts?
We did, but mostly because
people expect us to.
We're also accepting other
gifts not on the registry.
However much.
It's awkward asking people for
money. But we could really use it.
Why doesn't Crate and Barrel let you
register for a toaster full of cash?
Perfect.
I hate registries.
Oh, good.
My cousin makes the most amazing
romantic birdhouse mailboxes.
I know I shouldn't tell you, but you'll
still be surprised when you see it.
You're not registered
for a birdhouse, are you?
No, we're not.
Good. Good.
Mmm-hmm.
Okay. I thought
I saw people missing.
Yeah. Just focus grouping a product
expansion idea to these folks.
Got one of each.
Really?
Hey, Stanley, what was
the last thing Michael said
before I came
through the door?
Stanley, you don't
need to answer that.
Stanley?
"If you don't smell
this, you're fired."
Okay, Michael,
I thought we agreed
to not take up people's time
with meetings like these.
What do you mean
by "these" people?
Michael, this is a
conference room meeting.
Oh, hey, everybody, I think
that Jim has gone insane
because he thinks that my
office is a conference room.
That's not
what I meant.
Listen, Jim, no offense,
but when push comes to shove,
what I want is more
important than what you want.
I disagree.
What do you
guys think?
Can
I go back to my desk now?
Great. Guys, can I just have a
moment alone with Michael, please?
No, no, no, no. You
don't need to go anywhere.
Anything that Jim
has to say to me,
he can say in front of
these types of people.
That is not what I said.
And also,
I am co-manager,
meaning you are not
the only manager anymore.
I am also a co-manager.
That is not what
Wallace told us.
That's exactly what
That is not the way
I heard it.
I love rivalries.
Michael or Jim,
Paris or Nicole, Heidi
or L.C., it's so much fun.
But I guess if I'm
really thinking about it,
and answering your
question honestly,
I'd have to go with L.C. Heidi's a
bad friend and her skin is terrible.
It is one thing me giving
you the co-manager title,
it is another thing
you bossing me around.
I'm not bossing you around.
I'm trying to do my job,
which is sharing your job.
So maybe we should
just call David Wallace.
No, no, no. No! We will
not call David Wallace.
I will call
David Wallace.
David Wallace is on
line two for you guys.
Or David Wallace will call us
on line two. Why don't we just...
Hey, David. You got
Jim here. Hey, David.
This is Michael,
senior co-manager.
Hey, guys. I'm
calling because unfortunately
we will not be
able to give out
cost of living
raises this year
and I know
people expect it.
However, there just is only a small
amount of money for each branch.
So, we're leaving
it up to the managers
to decide how
to distribute it.
Got it, Dave. Sounds like your
classic big picture decision.
Which will clearly affect the
day-to-day wellbeing of our employees.
It's probably
a little of both.
Which is it more of?
Excuse me?
Hey, David,
I know that I am
very new at this,
but I have a very good
perspective on how things work...
Wait, I'm sorry. Michael,
are you texting me?
I thought maybe we could
talk after this is over.
Look, I need you both
to take care of this.
This is not going to
be a problem, is it?
Nope, not at all.
Not at all. Nope.
No, it will not be.
I am on top of it.
Very good.
All right. Thanks a lot,
David. Talk to you later...
Okay, you didn't
let me say goodbye.
All right, I am looking
forward to this.
You don't have to lie.
I hate the fact that we have
to do this together.
I think we work
much better separately.
When I am irritated and I look
at you, I don't see you anymore.
Right.
All I can see
is how big and gross
the pores on your nose are.
All right.
Let's get started.
Hey, why haven't we ever...
We have.
You know, there's no
easy way to do this.
I say we add 1.5%
to their paychecks
and don't say
anything about it.
Do you mean, like, break in,
in the middle of the night
and change the numbers
on payroll?
No, we can do it
during the day.
It doesn't have to be
that dramatic, Jim.
Okay.
You know what would help is a
pros and cons list for our options.
Jim, don't take this
the wrong way.
Are you going to take
this the wrong way?
It's hard to tell so far.
You use your brain
too much.
I'm sorry, are you
advocating that I use it less?
Sometimes the smartest
people don't think at all.
You just came up with
that. As I was saying it.
Yeah.
Okay, so for the 1.5% increase,
pro, everyone gets a little bit.
Con, you look
like a nerd.
Con, no one gets as much
as they did last year.
Pro, you get to share your pros
and cons list with the other nerds.
Pro, no favoritism.
Con, you unzip your pants
and you'll find
that there's a calculator down there.
I've been studying
Michael for years
and I've condensed what
I've learned into this chart.
How Michael
spends his time.
As you can see, we have
procrastinating and distracting others.
And this tiny sliver here
is critical thinking.
I made it bigger so that
you could see it.
Hey, Pam. I heard that you were
registered, but I didn't hear where.
I don't think we registered
anywhere. We just want cash.
Like money? Like,
you want my money?
Mmm-hmm.
Will you take a check?
Yeah.
Cool.
In the memo line, I'm going to
write, "To love's eternal glory."
Okay.
Wait till Monday.
Is this what I've become?
Materialistic? Shallow?
I feel horrible. Oh,
look! "Mrs. Pam Halpert!"
That's the first time
I've seen it in writing.
You know what,
the more I think about it,
the more I think we should
give it to the salesmen.
That will not
go over well.
Yeah, I know, I just
think it seems smart
to keep the salesmen
happier right now.
Of course, I know this
might come off as biased,
so you know what?
Let us...
Oh, my God,
are you going to make
another pro and con list?
I'm going to kill myself.
Well, I'm not going to let
you stop me from thinking.
No, I could not
do that, Jim.
I can see it in your
crusty little eyes
that you are going to make
everything perfect.
"If I could just
think this through,
"if I could just
think it exactly right,
"I can make this perfect.
"And then I can go
down every avenue,
"and every avenue
off of that avenue.
"And then another avenue..." Michael.
"And then another."
Look, you have
a lot of strengths.
Oh, I do?
Tell me what they are.
I think that you
are able to take
constructive criticism
very well.
Ha! That, I am not
known for that.
But there is a reason
why I'm here.
Yes, you went over
my head to Wallace.
No, it's because you also have
a lot of weaknesses, Michael.
Okay, well, why don't you
tell me what those are, Jim?
Why don't you
enliven me?
I don't think you're good
at making tough decisions.
Ah!
At thinking out the options and then
stating that decision very clearly,
especially when it's
an unpopular decision.
Okay. Here's a tough decision
for you, you suck. You suck.
Michael, wait. Is that
clear enough for you?
Maybe I'm here for a reason, because
I might have some good ideas, too.
I've been sitting out there
and I've been learning a lot
and maybe I can just bring
something different to the table.
Okay, Skippy, here we go.
Why don't you run yourself
out there and tell them?
You call it.
This had better be terrible.
Could I have everyone's
attention, please?
I have some tough news, so I'm just
going to give it to you straight.
Truth is we only have so much
money for raises this year.
So the simple fact is,
some people will get raises
and some people won't.
Now what
we've decided is
we are going to give those
raises to the sales staff.
Wait, seriously?
Look, you guys are smart,
so I'm just leveling with you,
just trying to treat
you like adults.
Thank you, Jim, for thinking
that we're smart people.
But I do not understand.
If we're such smart adults,
then why don't we get raises?
Excellent question,
genius.
It's because Jim wants
to give the raises
to his friends and the
people he sleeps with.
Ooh! Easy,
that's not it at all.
Well?
Really, what it is,
is about the money
the sales staff brings
in to the office...
What's going on?
Jim is only giving raises
to the salesmen.
What the hell? Why are
you being such a jerk?
Hold on, Kelly, would it help you
to know that Jim thinks you're smart?
No. How is that going
to repair Ryan's car?
This is ridiculous!
How can he do this to us?
Okay, Dwight,
you know what?
You'd be getting
the raise, so...
What about all these people?
How is it fair to them?
- Exactly.
- Totally.
We work just as hard as the
salespeople, we deserve raises.
Yes.
They don't get them
if we don't get them.
My kid needs shoes. You want to
tell him he doesn't get shoes?
Yeah.
Her kid needs shoes, Jim.
What the hell?
Wow. I'm just going to rewind
and back off a bit, so...
That was good.
Okay, all right.
Well, we all know
it's hard to be
a boss, right?
You know what? Look around you,
these are your best friends.
These are the people who
will open their hearts to you.
They all have
heart-ons for you.
And that is a gift.
So in terms of gifts, we should
be giving each other gifts.
Angela, yes, lend Oscar a cup of sugar.
This is... What are you
talking about? Michael!
We just need to hear
your plan for our raise.
My plan, a man, Panama.
That's not how that goes.
You're not saying anything. At
least Jim was being direct...
Thank you, Meredith.
...when he was telling us
his dumbass plan.
We would just like
to know what's happening.
Are we getting a raise,
yes or no?
All right, let me get this cleared.
Does everybody want a raise?
Yes!
All right,
everyone wants a raise,
so what we're going
to do is go into here
and we will not
come out until we do.
Again, that gives us
no information.
This isn't a game,
you know, it's our livelihood.
What about a raise
based on merit?
Rank each person
individually.
Mmm-hmm.
Piece of cake.
Ryan is obviously
the best.
Obviously.
Too bad he's a temp
and doesn't count,
so let's get started.
Are you making a...
Nope, I'm numbering the paper.
Just...
Yeah. I don't understand
how they can even
consider giving money
to some people
and not the rest of us.
It's not like we're not going to
see the checks, we're in Accounting.
I am so pissed
at this company.
And Jim.
Yeah.
Who said that?
I think it was Creed.
Yep.
It's going really
well, actually. Mmm-hmm.
Each Boston baked bean
represents half-a-percent raise.
We each got 24 beans,
so the idea is,
you place the bean
on the picture of who
you think deserves...
Who's that?
Toby.
Okay, he's not a part
of this, you know that.
Just wanted to draw
a picture of him.
Okay, your move.
All right. Who to pick?
Who to pick?
Here we go.
I will skip a turn.
Okay, you're going to still have
to play that bean, you know that.
I need more time.
Wallace sent an email
about a meeting next week,
he wants you
both to respond.
People are starting to notice
how terrible Jim is.
It's great. Eventually,
they will rise up and revolt.
My only hope is that they do
it sooner rather than later.
If the people here were
our Founding Fathers,
the Revolutionary War would
have been delayed 10 years
because Stanley Washington
was napping.
And Phyllis Hancock was
still signing the Declaration,
and Kevin Jefferson was
distracted by a butterfly.
Come on in. That's right.
Come in, feast your eyes.
They determine our worth
by putting beans on our faces.
What the hell?
Things were not this bad
when just Michael was manager.
Hey, what are you guys
doing in here?
What does a bean mean?
Why aren't there any beans on this
very old, frizzy-haired picture of me?
Michael,
what does a bean mean?
Jim?
I was just trying
to be unbiased.
What does a bean mean?
Someone please
explain it to Kevin.
Why can't you? My time is
just as valuable as yours.
Not according
to the beans.
This is how you make
this important decision?
There's no way that Stanley
gets more beans than me, that is ridiculous.
This is how it works.
It's not so much that I might
not get a raise, it's just demeaning.
Thank you. That is exactly... But,
by the way, I would also like a raise.
Yeah, I would, too.
Are we idiots?
What right does
Jim have to claim authority?
Is he as good
a salesman as I?
Is he as matronly
as Phyllis?
There are moments where
we can affect change.
For a few seconds,
every decade, we exist.
And these are those seconds.
Let us storm his castle.
Come on, tick,
let's get him, tock.
Let's get Jim. Tick, and drag
Jim out of his office, tock,
take his keys away from
him, tick, that's a clock.
The time is getting very
close. It's now or never.
What say you?
I say no.
No, I mean, what do you say to my plan?
Michael Scott...
Security guard.
Michael,
will you help us?
What does
a bean mean?
How you doing?
On a scale of one to 10,
I'd say I'm about a four.
What are you usually?
Six. You?
Usually a 10, but I'm
feeling like a zero.
I mean,
a performance-based raise
sounded like
a good idea, right?
I know, I know.
We tried to find
the fairest way to do it.
Yes, we did.
I just...
What?
Um...
Nothing. I just...
I used to have to do this part
alone. And it was the worst.
I have something
I would like to give you.
Michael, come on!
This isn't fair! KEVIN: Michael!
Michael's my only friend
left in the office.
Except Pam. I think.
She still upset?
Michael, you cannot
just keep avoiding us like this.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What's in here?
Gin.
Ooh.
Just
pretend we're not here.
Heard you guys are looking
for cash for the wedding?
Yeah, I mean, if it's
all the same for you.
Question for you,
would you guys rather have $100
now or $5,000 a year from now?
$100 now, for sure.
Because you just give me
$50 to cover the broker fee,
I put in $100 of my
own money, as the gift.
Yeah. No, no. The $100.
I'll just take the $100.
Instead of
$5,000 a year from now?
How sure is this?
The guy has an algorithm
to determine the winner of any
given college basketball game.
Don't tell Jim.