Look at that, huh? Nice!
I love cycling.
Andy, I feel like
a tourist in my own city.
I literally can't wait
to wake up every morning.
Okay.
She is a beaut.
Can't beat a horse.
A horse is a bike
that pedals itself.
Yes, it is.
Look at that, smooth roll.
Yeah.
KEVIN: You got it!
Lance Armstrong's bike.
Yes!
His ass was on
that seat? All right!
KEVIN: Nice.
No, Meredith, it's
not his actual bicycle.
But it is the same
exact model he uses.
I'm on Sheryl Crow's
side in that whole thing,
so I feel really
weird right now.
PAM: Michael!
MICHAEL: Oh, God!
Yes, I can ride a bike.
I take spinning classes
three times a month.
I think I know
how to ride a bike.
Are you sure you once
knew how to do this?
I did, yes!
I had those extra
wheels on the back
that support you.
ALL:
Michael! Michael!
Michael! Yeah!
All right!
PAM: Yeah!
Just steer more now.
Oh, my God!
Not the car!
No, no.
You never forget.
How do I look?
Amazing.
Normal. Ugly.
Well, I do the best
with what I've got.
Let's go.
All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait for me.
It's weird if I
come in slightly after.
We have a big meeting
with the chief buyer
for Frames Select, Steve Nash.
He's not "the" Steve Nash.
He's...
He's big, though.
He's kind of like
Scranton's Steve Nash.
Will you stop trying
to put it in terms
you think they'll understand?
It's condescending.
I'm not doing that.
I'm just explaining.
And who is this
"the" Steve Nash?
Phoenix Suns' point guard?
No.
No? Nothing?
No, Mr. Jock Hipster.
Well, I'm neither of
those things, so...
Oh ho.
Libby Dirketts got married.
Big, red mazel tov
to the Libster.
Ooh.
It says here Dan Becker
fell off the side
of Kilimanjaro
in a climbing accident.
It appears Dan's
Sherpa survived
to tell the tale...
Oh, my God!
What? Is Dan okay?
No, he died.
It's Broccoli Rob.
You know this guy.
I showed you his
picture on Facebook.
Yes.
"Some Vermont-based alums
can hear
'Broccoli' Rob Blatt, '96,
"in the state milk lobby's
new milk awareness song
Calci-yum,
"featuring
Phish's Trey Anastasio.
"Says Broccoli,
'Trey and I had a ton
of fun in the studio,
"'and I think you can
hear it in the song."'
Oh, that's great news
for your friend.
Yeah. Yeah. It's great.
You know, I forget about milk.
This is a terrific reminder.
I was the artsy musical one.
In Here Comes Treble,
I had four solos,
Broccoli Rob had three.
Right?
Go tell her we're here. You're
good with receptionists.
Ha.
Dwight.
Crap.
Danny Cordray
is the worst.
Well, by worst,
you mean the best.
The best salesman ever.
He works for Osprey
Paper over in Throop,
steals more clients
from Dunder Mifflin
than anyone.
So the situation
is the worst.
Also, he slept with Pam.
No, he didn't.
Tell them.
Nothing happened.
We went on a couple of dates.
He never called me again.
What? He never called you?
I thought you said
it just fizzled.
That's fizzling.
I mean, someone has
to start the fizzle.
Yeah, I thought
you started it.
No, I liked him.
For a couple of days.
Four years ago.
You know I have
a kid with you, right?
Aah!
I'm gonna
intimidate him.
Okay?
Okay, great.
I'm just gonna watch.
Watch this.
So anyway, she says,
"That is the biggest
penis I have ever seen."
And I said, "I know.
"That's why I brought you
to the penis museum,
"where tickets are $1,000."
Well, hello, Danny.
Hey, Dwight.
Good to see you. Jim, hey.
How are you?
I'm good.
What are you doing?
Well, I'm just here
for the coffee.
Like hell you are.
Dwight!
He's not just here
for the coffee, Jim.
Wake up.
Brainstorming
session is now open.
Sorry, sorry, sorry. Hello?
Hey, it's Jim.
Listen, this is important.
Are you busy?
Oh, hey. No,
I'm not busy.
What's up?
You are busy!
We're in a meeting!
What?
It's Jim, okay? Yes.
Listen, you gotta
get over here,
'cause we're
pitching Steve Nash
and Danny Cordray's here.
You need the big guns, yes?
Yes.
What'd he say?
What did he say?
The big gun thing. Stop.
I will see you in 10.
Bye! Hold tight.
Well, I know
a lot of you thought
that my sales
days were behind me.
And, to be honest,
so did I.
And the only reason
I got out of the sales game
was to be reluctantly
called back in.
You don't look reluctant,
Michael. You look
really eager.
No, I don't have
time for this.
Are you kidding me?
PAM: You don't?
No! Okay. All right.
Knockity-knock,
Don't knock back
Just kidding, you can knock.
It's your office.
Do you have a minute?
I'm very busy with
time-sensitive work.
Not to go all
Sherlock Holmes on you,
but I can tell by
the reflection in your glasses
that you're entering points
into weightwatchers. Com.
If you don't enter
them immediately,
you forget.
What?
I'm starting a band,
and I need you on keyboards.
Nah!
I play for pleasure.
This is for pleasure.
Wouldn't enjoy that.
I'm willing to pay you.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
How much?
60 bucks a session.
That's crazy money.
I'll take 40.
Yes!
There he is.
Oh, no, that's a male model.
No, that's him.
That...
Hello.
Michael Scott,
Dunder Mifflin Paper Company.
Danny Cordray, Osprey Paper.
Nice to meet you.
Three of you
guys for one sale?
Yeah, well...
We call it overkill.
Well, whatever works for you.
Anyway, all right.
All right.
Good to see you guys.
Nice to meet you.
Goodbye.
I could swear that
guy was a male model.
He's ready for you.
Oh! Thank you.
All right.
On the count of three,
it's show time.
Ready, one, two...
No, I'm not doing that.
I've been in show time
mode since breakfast.
You're not?
Okay, all right,
just forget it then.
Show time!
It's show time!
Never mind. Let's go.
When I knock on your door,
you know who it is.
It's Michael Scott.
We've been
together forever, and...
Michael,
I appreciate everything
that Dunder Mifflin has
done for this company.
You know what? You are
having some problems
with your loading dock.
Are you not? All right,
we're going to deliver
to you on weekends.
That's very generous, but...
And you know what
else we're gonna do?
I can't believe
I'm gonna say this.
We are going to offer
you our paper at cost.
I know.
I could get in a lot
of trouble for this,
so you'd better
shake my hand right now.
He's not kidding.
Shake it, shake it!
Michael, I'm going
with Danny.
Oh.
Thanks for coming in.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Jim talked too much.
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
Stop it. Just stop it.
We did what we
should have done.
We just got bested.
Why is there
a door close button
if it doesn't
even close the door?
How do I feel
about losing the sale?
It's like if Michael Phelps
came out of retirement,
jumped in the pool,
belly-flopped and drowned.
You know who we
always lose out to?
Staples, the big guys...
Osprey?
They're a small company.
They're smaller than we are.
What's our excuse?
How do we combat this guy?
Stanley, how do we combat him?
We sell better?
Okay. You know what?
You clearly don't care,
so why don't you just leave?
I would like to stay.
This pertains to me.
Why don't you go outside
and take a shot of insulin
and have a nap, okay?
Why do you always
assume I have diabetes?
I don't know.
Your frame, your build.
Why don't you have
a glass of apple juice
and tell me
you're not a diabetic?
See? I could tell
by the sound you made
when you stood up
that you have...
Okay. Yes, Phyllis?
I could try to seduce him.
Oh, my God!
I know how we can
learn his tricks.
What I'm about to show you
is of the utmost secrecy.
Is that your office?
Yes, Jim.
And with a little tweaking,
it becomes a different office.
We lure Danny to it
and watch him sell.
PHYLLIS: Oh.
I'm out of here.
This is weird.
You know what this is?
This is a stinger.
A what?
Like the movie.
I think you mean The Sting.
Paul Newman, Robert Redford.
They're bank robbers?
Nope. Different movie.
It's called The Stinger.
The Sting.
Your 2:00.
Thanks, hon.
Meredith was
the perfect choice
to play the head
of the company.
Her lunch break
lined up with our
appointment with Danny,
and... That's it.
That's really all
we were looking for.
Danny Cordray.
It's great to meet you.
Meredith Van Helsing.
Pleased to meet you.
Meredith Van Helsing?
Van Helsing was
a respected professor
before he was
a vampire killer.
Okay. But what is
he more famous for?
Shh.
You know this
isn't real TV, right?
Yes.
Please, Mr. President
If you wanna
Give hope a whirl
Bring our troops
Home safe and sound
Says this little girl
Please, Mr. President
Wait a second,
wait a second,
wait a second.
So, the song is
from the point of view
of a little girl?
Yeah.
But you're singing it.
Yeah. But I'm
using my falsetto.
No, that's not a good idea.
I don't see it as
a very good song.
Yeah, well, it'd
sound a lot better
if you actually
sang with some soul.
I never sing with soul.
That's a lie.
I could sing it.
I just was hoping to
maybe save your voice
in case we did
a novelty song
about frogs.
But my voice is unique.
Like Bob Dylan.
Okay, three-way argument
between a drummer,
a keyboardist,
and the front man,
lead singer.
Wonder who's
gonna win this one.
Two, three, four...
I'm gonna take off my coat,
if you don't mind.
It's just a bit warm in here.
Hello!
No, no, no. Don't.
People can't keep
their true natures
hidden for long,
and this guy is
smoldering like
a tire fire.
Testify.
Okay, he's not
that good-Iooking.
I don't understand
why everybody's...
Yeah, he is that
good-Iooking. Okay?
He's very, very handsome.
That's a great set of
shoulders you got there.
What is that, genetics?
Creatine?
Sorry.
Yeah.
Pull it together,
all right?
Stop looking at him.
I'm sorry.
You're here to
sell me some paper.
Well, actually,
no, Miss Van Helsing,
that's not why I'm here.
I'm here to meet you,
see if we'd be a,
you know, good fit.
What do you mean?
Oh, my God!
He's making her sell to him.
Bring our troops
Home safe and sound
Says this little girl
Okay. Honest
feedback time.
Oscar.
That's pandering.
And it makes me think
you think I'm stupid.
But do you think
it could be famous?
Like in a car
commercial or something?
Not really.
It's kind of weird that
a grown man is singing
from the point of
view of a little girl.
Mmm-hmm.
I feel like I can see
someone ice skating to it,
you know,
like in the Olympics.
I don't think
they usually skate
to such bad songs.
Rude. And not helpful.
Well, I really,
really, really liked it.
Well, that really
bums me out.
You're welcome.
Well, you should think of
this as a first date.
And I think it's
going very well.
How about you?
Real well.
Uh...
Feels more like
a third date to me.
Stay...
Shut up and let me do this!
You know,
what is with this desk
keeping us so far apart?
I've never been a desk man.
Always traveling on the road.
Come on... Why not? Uh?
Well, we'll get this...
Oh, man.
So, what's your drink?
You a vodka man? Me, too.
We gotta get someone else
in there right now.
You're an exec at
Pennsylvania Solartech.
That sounds fake.
What do you mean?
I told you.
You're an exec at
Stark Industries,
a corporation you
inherited from your father.
Will you stop?
Here's the story.
They need Meredith
somewhere else ASAP, okay?
Okay.
So you're taking over.
You just gotta
get her out of there
as soon as you can.
I can do that.
Then what?
Then make him pitch to you.
You gotta see what he's got.
Yes.
Exactly. You
can do this.
Okay, and remember.
You're not gay.
Stop it.
It's gonna be great.
Listen,
if anything else happens,
just roll with it.
Meredith, I...
Manuel.
This is Manuel,
my cleaning man.
He doesn't speak any English.
Manuel, cleano el window.
Give me the...
Who else we got?
Okay. You're a young
hotshot from
Stark Industries.
You've just
bought this company.
Meredith is fired.
It's a whole new regime.
He's gotta pitch to you now.
Okay, Stark Industries
isn't real.
I run Google.
Larry and Sergey brought me...
Great. Sounds awesome.
Just have him pitch to you.
Don't let us down.
Will do. Won't do.
Yeah, sure.
You smell like a Scorpio.
This is Esteban,
another cleaning man.
He doesn't speak
English either.
Esteban, el flooro.
You know what?
I may have parked my
car in a compact space,
and I hate when I see
others do that, so...
Danny, I feel
a real connection to you,
and I got to get real.
JIM: No. No, no, no.
MICHAEL: No, no, no, no, no!
I'm going in! I'm going in!
Michael!
No, Michael, stop it!
No!
Stop, stop! Oh, my God!
Okay. Stop it,
stop it, stop it.
Gross! Stop it,
please. Everybody stop.
Michael Scott.
I said stop.
Okay, Danny,
this is not
Pennsylvania Solartech.
This is Dunder
Mifflin Paper Company.
This is Meredith Palmer.
Pleased to meet you.
Don't... Stay away from him.
Please, just leave.
Get out of here.
Go. Forever.
Hmm.
I owe you a most sincere
and humble apology.
We were trying to watch you
to see your sales technique
so we could stop losing
so many clients to you.
Watch from where?
A surveillance
room next to this one.
Okay, so you set up
this fake company,
then you hired
this homeless woman
to impersonate an executive,
to spy on me
so that you could
copy my sales technique.
Yes. And it's the sincerest
form of flattery.
Or crazy.
Well...
I'm gonna go.
Okay. You know what,
it wasn't just me.
Jim and Dwight
are behind that wall
in the surveillance room,
and it was their plan,
as well.
No!
No, no, no, no.
Well, then, yeah.
All right, hey!
Good luck, guys!
Seems like you got
a great operation here.
No, we don't.
Here's... Here's my point.
Danny, listen,
you have to understand
that we are not
normally like this.
We just... We wanted
to know your tricks.
What do you mean, tricks?
There's no tricks, man.
I'm just a good salesman.
You wanna copy that?
You can't copy that!
You are, you are. You are!
Stop it, stop it. Stop.
You are a good salesman.
And because of that
I want you to work for me.
Sure. You seem like a fun,
professional guy.
So you will.
No!
Hold it, hold it,
hold it, hold on.
Hold on. Wait, wait,
wait, wait. Wait.
Danny, I want you
to look at me.
Do you want your
life to be better
or to be worse or
to stay the same?
Get out of my way.
Answer the question.
Do you want
a better life, Danny?
I swear to God,
I'm gonna hit you.
I didn't mean that.
I'm sorry. I'm not...
It's just, I'm very
upset right now.
I know.
I'm very upset!
I know, I know.
Do you want more freedom,
less freedom,
or to stay the same?
More freedom.
I can give you more money.
There's your better life.
I can let you come
and go as you please.
There's your freedom.
And you already
know Dunder Mifflin
has the best service
and the best prices.
But you beat us anyway.
Can you imagine
how well you would
do selling our stuff?
Everyone, may I
have your attention?
I would like to introduce you
to Mr. Danny Cordray.
He's going to be
joining us as our
new traveling salesman.
Say hello to Danny!
me.
Okay. You know what?
No. No.
This is not some sort
of construction site,
or all of Italy
where you can just go around
treating people like meat.
We are to respect him.
I respect him
because he
reminds me of somebody.
Can anybody guess who that is?
Josh Duhamel.
Yeah, I can see that!
No. No. No.
Somebody in this office.
He's like
a better-Iooking Andy.
Thanks, Kevin.
No. Me. Right?
Sort of like a little,
younger version of me.
It's hard to judge
ourselves accurately,
isn't it?
Michael.
Yes.
Can I talk to you
about something?
No, you may not.
It's about this
very announcement
you just made.
I said no.
Michael...
Michael, I think
you really want to
talk to him.
Okay, let's... All right,
all right. Let's talk.
Please don't
let him leave.
Don't leave.
Got you.
You hired him?
Guys, let me
ask you something.
Do you want your life
to be better or worse
or stay the same?
ALL: Stay the same.
Okay. Well, get ready,
'cause it's gonna get better.
It's not gonna get better.
He's gonna steal
all of our clients.
No. No. Wrong.
He would have
stolen your clients,
but you know what?
He can't now.
This guy used to
steal sales from us.
Now he's going to
steal sales for us.
Where's he gonna sit?
There's no more seats.
He doesn't need to sit.
He's a traveling salesman.
Look, I am not going
to exclude good people
from our staff
simply because they
are threatening to you.
And unless you have
a better argument
than that,
I suggest you leave.
Yeah.
Where's he gonna park?
There's no more
reserved parking spots.
Goodbye!
Songs about truth.
Yeah.
What's something
you really care about?
Reverse snobbery.
More universal.
Sometimes I feel like
life has passed me by.
Couldn't get
Out of bed today
Wish the alarm clock
Would go away
Nice!
Holy crap.
Are you kidding me?
You just made that...
That's amazing.
Go ahead.
Which me am I
Gonna be today?
I got a closet full of mes
Ha ha!
Am I gonna be the happy me?
Or the me that stinks?
Oh, my gosh.
We're almost
out of time.
How much for
another half hour?
Don't worry about it.
Wait. Seriously?
Yeah.
So we're just, like,
jamming as friends?
One, two, three, hit it.
Closet full of mes...
Oh, you know, funny,
your wife and I
went on a few dates.
Did you?
Yeah, way, way, way back.
I'm just kidding.
She told me about it.
Good. She was not into me.
Oh.
Obviously.
I don't even think
she called me back.
You snubbed her.
Dwight, please.
Let me handle this, Jim.
Drop the act, Cordray. Okay?
We all know that
you probably thought
that Pam was too "meh"
or thin without being toned.
But I wanna
tell you something.
She is one of the plain,
hearty women of Scranton
that make this city great.
And so what if she
doesn't wear makeup?
I wear makeup.
We like her better that way!
And you steal clients,
don't you?
Don't you?
Okay, that's different.
"That's different," is it?
Okay, thief.
You better check your
things, people. In fact,
where are my keys?
Oh. They're in my pocket.
False alarm.
Okay.
So you're gonna
be working here.
Uh...
I mean... Yeah.
Welcome aboard.
Thank you.
Hey, crazy. Um...
So, that's it?
You're just... You're fine?
It's after 5:00, Jim.
I'm not gonna take this home.
Pleasure.
Thanks.
This morning, Danny Cordray
stole a sale from me.
So what do I do?
I go out and I
steal Danny Cordray.
The sale that mattered,
I made. Boom.
Funny thing about it,
we don't even need him.
We already have
Packer on the road.
Crap. I forgot about Packer.
Star's in her eyes,
tongue full of flies
Would you like
to share my pad?
Croak, croak, croak,
Bullfrog in love
And I gave her the croak
That meant I love you
I'll be your croak monsieur
I'll be your croak madame
Your mama might've said
That bullfrogs are dogs
But I'm here to
Tell you that I'm a frog
Come and sit on my log,
You little pollywog
I find you
absolutely ribbitting!
Croak, croak, croak,
Bullfrog in love
Croak
Ribbit
Scoopty splash
Nice.