Everybody, can I please
have your attention?
Ryan and I have
a huge announcement.
Oh, my gosh!
PAM: Wow.
Over the weekend,
Ryan Bailey Howard
and I got divorced.
Sweet.
Free ring.
Divorced?
Just so you know,
it's totally amicable.
We're fine.
We don't need people
here to take sides.
The last thing that
we want is any
kind of drama.
Wait, I...
Can you back up?
What's the story?
We were having
a beautiful weekend
in the Poconos.
We were making
love constantly.
We saw the sun
rise, and Ryan
was crying a lot.
That's not
a relevant detail.
And in the morning,
we walked
by a chapel,
and we stopped suddenly,
and Ryan said,
"I don't think
I should be married
to you anymore."
Wait...
Sorry, when did
you get married?
Um, like, a week ago.
We got really wasted,
and it just felt right.
And you didn't
invite any of us?
We are getting
divorced, Andy!
This is such a raw time.
God, baby, you know,
with people's
reactions to this,
I wonder if we
made a mistake.
No, with the messed
up laws in this country,
I don't want to be
married until everyone
can be married.
You know what, Ryan?
I talked to the
other gay guys,
and we're okay with it.
We all agreed it's fine
for you to get married.
No. No, Oscar.
Not until everyone can.
KELLY: Ryan,
I changed my mind.
Okay, fine.
You know what?
This actually isn't
amicable at all,
and we actually
do need people
to take sides.
Who's on my side?
And who is on my side?
All right, bye.
Bye.
Let's go.
Just a minute!
How long do we
have to wait?
For what?
You broke up with
A.J. weeks ago.
Don't you have a
sales call to go on?
I don't understand.
I really don't.
I mean, we know we're
gonna start dating.
Why not now?
We don't know that.
Sure we do.
Why is it such a certainty
that we're supposed
to be together?
Why does the sun
rise in the morning?
Why do magnets
stick together?
Because everybody
says so. Everybody.
Michael, I can't keep
getting into a situation
where I date whoever
I'm working with.
Well, you could
understand that.
Yeah, I understand.
I just don't agree.
Well, you don't
have to agree.
Yes, I do.
No, you don't.
No, you can have
your own opinion,
and I can have mine.
MICHAEL: I have my
own opinion,
and my opinion is
to disagree with you.
He's gonna be
a lot of fun to drive
around in a car with.
Oh, you'll get
through it, hon.
Just make a
game out of it.
A funny Jim game.
That's it?
That's all I get?
Even after all the hard
work I put into celebrating
your talent today.
All right,
what'd you do?
Well, those
things that you
consider doodles,
I consider art.
Where'd you put it?
Where'd I put what?
Let's go.
Oh, sorry. I gotta go.
Say it. Where?
Okay, fine.
Three hints. One,
when you're getting colder,
you're really getting warmer.
The fridge.
Two!
You have a better chance
if you think Bob Vance.
The fridge, got it.
And the final clue...
MICHAEL: Let's go!
You know what?
Just think about it.
You'll be fine.
Bye.
ERIN: Holly is ruining
Michael's life.
He thinks she's
so special.
And she's so not.
Her personality is like
a three, her sense
of humor is a two,
her ears are like
a seven and a four.
Add it all up,
and what do you get? 16.
And he treats her
like she's a perfect 40.
It's nuts.
Cheer up.
We made a sale.
Just drive faster.
I wanna get back.
Well, I'm going
the speed limit.
Okay, fine.
My feelings don't
matter to you.
What matters to you
is your precious
speed limit.
Someone's in a bad mood.
No, I'm not.
I'm not in
a bad mood.
I'm not,
Jim. Hello?
Okay, fine, ignore me.
Have it your way.
Let's just talk
about you as always.
Sex different after
the baby, Jim?
All right, let me turn
on some music.
I need to pee!
No, you don't.
Yeah, I do. My
word against yours.
All right, well, we'll
be there in 10 minutes.
What part of
"I need to pee" do
you not understand?
I'm upset,
my bladder is full,
there is no
telling what I
might do right now
all over the inside
of your precious
little car.
All right. Well,
if I see a gas station,
I'll pull over.
Well, I hope
I make it.
Hello?
Hi, Jim, it's Helene.
Hey, Helene.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
Baby's fine.
She has a tiny fever.
I'm taking her
for a checkup.
Nothing to worry about.
Okay.
A tiny thing.
I locked her
in the car.
What?
She's smiling.
She's happy.
Oh, my God.
Jim, I don't have
a spare key.
Oh, my God.
Just stay there.
I'll be there in
one second.
Michael!
Excuse me, sir,
there's a... There's
a guy in the bathroom.
He's coming out,
but I have to go,
'cause it's an emergency.
Will you just tell him
to call the office?
Just call...
Call the office.
Thank you! Please?
Hello?
This is Pam.
JIM: Hey, it's me.
So, don't worry.
Everything's okay.
What's wrong?
Nothing,
absolutely nothing.
But you're not holding
a cup of coffee or
anything, are you?
Jim, what?
Uh, okay. So, Cece had
a little bit of a fever,
and your mom also
locked her in the car.
Oh, God. What?
No, no, no,
it's okay.
So, Cece's with Daddy
now, and she is laughing
and she's happy,
and we're on our way
to see Dr. Barbara.
Okay, so she's okay?
Yes, and your
mom got a very
well-deserved day off.
So, here's the thing,
though, I left Michael at
the gas station on Bennett.
Understood.
And his wallet and
phone are on the
seat next to me.
Got it.
I will put
out an A.P.B.,
otherwise known as
an "Ask Pam Beesly."
Did the phone
cut out?
Nope.
All right, just call
me after the doctor.
Okay.
All right, bye.
Bye.
I know, I know.
You have a phone
policy. I understand.
But this is an emergency,
because my friend isn't here,
and I'm worried that
he has been abducted.
No.
And...
No, he ditched you, man.
I saw him drive away.
There's no way
he ditched me.
that happened.
He's my... Okay.
May I please just use
your phone? Please?
Just make it quick.
Thank you. Okay.
I will make it quick.
I will make it very quick.
And you don't have my
numbers on speed dial.
Okay, what is it?
You don't know.
You don't...
You know what?
I could dial 411,
get Jim's number...
He left you here
on purpose,
all right? I saw it.
He just drove away.
MICHAEL: Actually,
this is good.
I am going to take
this opportunity
to go walk about.
Good, good.
No, get away.
No. That's enough.
Okay.
It's the gas station
on Bennett Street?
Yeah.
You know what?
Why don't you
stay and I'll go?
Oh, no, no, no,
I'll be fine.
It's kind of a sketchy
neighborhood, though.
I better come along.
Problem solved,
everyone.
Space Orphan and
Princess Nincompoop are
off to rescue Michael.
Unbelievable.
I'm going.
You drive. I got a
car full of fox meat.
Cute.
Very funny, everyone.
Who wrote captions
under my doodle?
I'm not even kidding.
They're pretty good.
Which one
in particular?
Yeah, which one?
Well, the first one
has a surprise factor.
"I'm a suck, suck,
suckity Sabre."
Booya!
But I suppose the
second one is the
better written line.
You suppose?
What's it say?
"I'm supposed to
be wearing red gloves,
"but my color cartridge
portal got jammed again."
Gloves.
Keep it real.
You guys, if I knew
you wanted to do
a caption contest,
I would have
drawn something
more challenging.
And I will take
you all down.
You?
I've been reading the
comics to my daughter
since she was
three years old.
Not once have I
used the real captions
to Family Circus.
That crazy family
is hilarious to her
for one reason, me.
It is on like Genghis Khan
wearing Sean John in Bhutan.
Yes. You guys,
I have the perfect idea.
Okay, it'll just take
me 10 minutes.
KEVIN: All right.
ANDY: I want to do it.
Male, Caucasian,
40s, black hair,
facial type, marsupial.
He answers to Michael,
Michael G. Scott,
Michael J. Fox, Mr. Fox,
the Incredible Mr. Fox...
Yeah, he just left.
Which way did he go?
Okay, hey, hey, hey,
let me answer this.
Stupid question.
He went back to the office,
obviously, which is that way.
Oh, really? You don't think
he walked by that bakery
just for the smell of it?
She's right.
He went that way.
All right.
Don't get a swelled
head. You're no
tracker.
Let's ride.
Hey, you guys.
Listen to me.
Don't get hung up
on just one girl,
because there are
a lot of other
girls out there.
Look over there. See?
They look cute.
You guys are
so beautiful.
You're so colorful.
I wish I could
understand you.
That's a metaphor,
I guess.
You are disgusting.
You'll never find love.
Do you think she needs
more time, or it's just
never gonna happen?
I'm being serious.
Seriously.
Dunder Mifflin. This is Pam.
Has Michael
checked in?
Oh, hey, Dwight.
I asked you
a question.
No, he hasn't.
Okay, bye.
No, wait. Hey,
while you're out,
could you pick up
some paper towels
and chocolate syrup?
We have ice cream,
so I thought we could...
Pam, this isn't
a shopping trip.
No.
This is a
manhunt/rescue mission.
Okay, I just... When
you're done, or any
time it's convenient,
I just thought
since you're out...
Pam, I'm obviously gonna
get that stuff for you,
so just shut up. God.
Okay, well, it wasn't...
No word from Michael.
Ta-daa!
Okay, it's two giant dogs
with two giant palm trees
on a regular-sized island.
Oh, I got one.
Yeah?
Yes.
GABE: Okay,
I'm sorry,
but I'm gonna have
to shut this down.
Unless we can all agree
to some ground rules.
It's either that, or
I can fax this to Jo
and let her decide
how to proceed.
Gabe, tell us your
stupid rules so we
can start the game.
Number one, and this
should be obvious,
no captions that
insult the company
we work for.
Number two,
no pop
culture references.
Seriously?
Wow.
I think we can
all agree they tend
to alienate those
who don't get the
reference, making them
feel like the other.
Wrap it up, Gabe.
Okay, final thing,
and this is a fun one,
instead of writing
the caption directly
under the picture,
let's all try using
Sticky Quips.
All right? New from
Dunder Mifflin Sabre.
Sticky Quips are fun.
They're safe.
They're handy.
I like to use Sticky Quips
as regular Post-it notes
when I'm in
a fun mood.
Not every day.
Go get 'em.
Start quipping.
Hmm.
Pam, I think I'm
gonna send you an IM.
Oh, okay.
Send me one, too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
put me on that.
PHYLLIS: Cc.
DARRYL: Ditto.
Hello.
I would like a hot
dog, please.
Now, I don't have any money,
so here is what
I would like to do.
I leave you here
with my watch,
and I come back later
and I pay for the hot dog.
I'm not a pawn shop.
Well, I understand that,
but this is a $45 watch.
Wow.
With that, I could
buy half the menu.
I can't just go giving
away hot dogs.
All right.
What do you do
with the hot dogs
that you don't sell?
Throw 'em away.
Well, okay,
instead of throwing
them all away later,
why don't you just
throw one away
now into my mouth?
No.
Okay. You've just
lost my business.
Hey.
Hey, you were
in there forever.
There's too many
brands. Where's Holly?
She wandered
off like an idiot.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Just changing my
cell phone plan.
Okay. Okay.
Here you go.
I'll take my free
stress ball too now.
Sure thing.
Here you go, Miss...
Okay, Fanny Smellmore.
Real original.
What?
You know what?
Say hi to Orville
Tootenbacher for me.
Tootenbacher.
Orville Tootenbacher,
that's Michael's
millionaire character that
farts popcorn.
Farts popcorn.
Of course.
He was here.
She's the key.
Amazing.
Holly.
Hey, where would
you like to go next?
Holly?
Are their egg rolls
really that big?
Oh, boy. That was yummy.
Thank you so much.
You know what?
I think I left my
wallet in my car.
Do you mind if
I run out and get it?
No problem.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
God! Okay,
you know what?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't have my wallet.
And I was...
I was gonna try
to dine and dash,
and that was stupid,
and I realize
I can't do that to
you fine people.
So, you can't pay
for your food?
Well, I can,
but I will have to
come back later tonight
and pay you.
But the point is I
did the right thing.
You did not.
You have no money,
but you dined, and
you dined so much.
Well, the number three
is not such a giant feast.
Mr. Choo!
Okay.
All right.
You know what?
You're trying to
steal food from us?
I am not.
I just have had
a bad day, and I...
Okay. I'll be back later
with the money. I'm just
gonna leave right now.
You can't.
We'll stop you.
Well, I think I can
get through the door.
Excuse me,
do you speak English?
We are looking
for a man,
Michael, this tall,
black hair, Caucasian.
It's Michael!
He just left.
You knew.
What?
No. Dwight asked if
I wanted an egg roll.
What... What are
you implying?
Uncanny.
Put a pin in that.
Which way did he go?
That guy,
when he leave here,
which way did he go?
We looking for him.
This way? This way?
This way? I don't know.
Do you know?
I think he was
heading downtown.
He's heading downtown.
So what, no one's
even gonna try?
Guess not.
Oh, come on.
My rules could not possibly
have been that oppressive.
You crushed
our spirits, Gabe.
Congrats. You're
a big man, huh?
Takes a lot to
destroy the creativity of
a whole group of people.
Hey...
Click the "X."
I'm clicking!
In the box.
I am clicking.
Woman, you've had
a computer for years!
Phyllis!
Too late!
Oh, huh, an IM
chat. Very clever.
I'll just print that out.
Come on, guys.
Grow up.
I don't want to
be your babysitter.
"Darn it, Bob, I told
you not to buy a
Sabre brand lifeboat."
Nice!
GABE: No, not nice.
Terrible.
Doesn't even include
the fact that they're dogs.
Do the next one.
"Wake up, Fred.
"The power cord on
your Sabre printer
shocked you into a coma,
"and you're dreaming
you're a dog on
a desert island."
Dreaming he's a dog
on an island.
Uh, excuse me,
excuse me.
How does the speaker
know what the guy
in the coma is dreaming?
Well, if you think
it's so easy, Gabe,
why don't you try it?
Um...
You don't have
to sniff my rear
end anymore, Bob.
I'm the only
one here.
That's tasteless, Gabe.
Tasteless?
Tasteless.
GABE: More tasteless
than this?
"Is that a palm tree,
or did Gabe get skinnier?
"Either way,
let's pee on it."
Ladies and gentlemen,
I think we have a winner.
Yes.
KEVIN: Yes.
Well done!
Whose is it?
Who wrote that?
Yeah. Who wrote it?
Please. It was easy once
I decided I wanted
the dog to piss on Gabe.
Where did he
go, Holly?
I have no idea.
Do you see a little
clown that you
wanna follow, huh?
Is there a little bird
that's chirping to you,
"This way, this way"?
I don't know.
Okay. Close your eyes.
We need you to think.
What is Michael
seeing right now?
Can you tell him
that we miss him?
Michael, we're
coming for you!
Will you stop?
There have been
a few coincidences,
that's all!
All right, then.
Someone propose
a plan.
Okay.
We fan out...
Not you, Erin.
Stop looking
at me like that.
Okay, look, let's just
go up somewhere high
and see if we could spot
him on the street below.
That is the stupidest
idea I've ever heard. No.
Tap into your common
mind, and tell us
what he would do next.
Look, I'm not playing.
I'm gonna go look for him.
Good. We
don't need her.
Right.
I can do this on my own.
I can think like Michael.
All right...
I'm deep below the
ocean's surface
in a submarine.
A torpedo's coming
right at me.
No. Damn it, that's
just my own imagination.
Maybe he's bowling.
Michael?
Hi.
How did you know
I was up here?
What are you
doing up here?
I got turned around.
I thought I could
see Dunder Mifflin.
Dunder Mifflin?
Yeah.
Wow!
I just miss
you so much.
I missed you, too.
Really?
Yeah.
Can I kiss you?
Okay.
Maybe that's not the
best one. Keep reading.
Yeah, it was.
Maybe it wasn't.
"Oh, thank God, I had
a horrible nightmare
"that I was stuck
in America with Gabe."
No, that's not the one
I was thinking of.
Keep going.
"I know what it smells
like, but I didn't
roll in anything.
"It's from listening
to all of Gabe's..."
"Isn't this the
perfect romantic
getaway, Erin?
"Sitting on a desert
island in dog costumes?
"I'm Gabe,
and I'm a weirdo."
"Gabe's mom.
Hmm, Gabe's mom?
"Wait, tall woman?
Looks like Gabe?
"Yeah, I banged her."
Yeah, there you go.