DWIGHT: I have the best
stocked survival shelter
in northeastern Pennsylvania.
But everything
has a shelf life.
So I must eat and
then replace everything
that's about to expire.
It's nice not to
have to plan my meals.
You're eating
eight-year-old tomatoes.
They're still good
for another week.
You know, I think I
might have some type
of cheese
in the back of my
fridge you might like.
I've got some cheese
you might like, too.
In between my toes.
DWIGHT: Hardy-har-har.
All right, picture this.
Snowy ash drizzles
from the sky.
A rabid pack of
dogs surrounds you
as the flame at the end
of your stick dies out.
There's only one
hope left for you,
the door to my shelter.
You pound. You beg.
"Dwight, please let me in."
But I ignore your cries
and do not let you in.
You want to know why?
Because of the sign
that says, "No pounding.
No begging."
No, because you
laughed at me.
Kevin will be eaten.
Pam will be taken slave.
Jim will be made
a warlord's jester.
Meredith will do okay.
Be assured this day
will come. It's just
a matter of time.
Could be one month,
could be two months.
Three months.
Could be.
Four months.
I see that happening, yes.
Eight months?
That's a realistic timeline.
Eleven months.
Perhaps.
Okay, wait,
now really think hard
about this one.
One year.
I could see that as
a very real possibility.
Four hundred and
ninety-four months.
I could see that happening.
Four hundred and
ninety-five months.
That's just...
I really
thought I was becoming
too much of a womanizer.
I realized I had shirts
in five different
women's houses.
Still not seeing
the problem there.
All right.
Truth is,
I got a couple love
bumps on my ding-dong,
so I was like,
"Game over."
MICHAEL: It was the best
of times. It was the
"awesomest" of times.
And now Packer
wants to come home.
And look who's here
to sign off on it.
My boo, Holly.
Hi.
You must be Todd.
Whoa, I'm sorry.
Michael, I thought
we were meeting
Holly today,
not Jennifer Aniston.
Very funny.
Okay, let's get started.
After you.
Okay.
Michael,
this'll be just us.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Just so you know,
he's at his funniest
when you've given him,
like, five shots.
Okay.
And it also helps if
you've had five shots.
I already have.
Why is Packer back?
Is Packer here?
Why is he
talking to Holly?
Don't know, don't care.
Michael loves you,
and your sales speak
for themselves. So...
Yes! The Pack is back.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I would like
to introduce you
to a man who
needs no introduction,
probably because
most of you have
done it with him.
Just kidding. He wouldn't
be interested in any of you.
In all seriousness,
Todd Packer is
a permanent salesman
at this branch.
And I would like to
invite you now to welcome
him with open arms.
Yes!
What?
It's great to
be among friends.
And until then,
you suckers will do.
Nice.
We got burned.
MICHAEL: You did.
You got burned,
because Packer's back.
Packer is turning in
his car for a desk.
He is turning in
his condoms for
a condominium,
although he's probably
going to have to use
condoms from here on out.
Holly. You approved this?
Yes, I did.
I think Todd's gonna
make a great addition
to the staff.
You did approve it?
Yeah.
What don't you understand
about the word "approved"?
It seems a couple
of you don't know
what the word
"approved" means.
I have very little
patience for stupidity.
Sorry we're late.
Gabe fell in the shower.
Such a klutz.
Yeah, and it took
the fire department
forever to get there.
Oh, my God.
Where did this
come from?
Who did this?
PAM: I got Erin
a new computer
because the one at
reception sucked.
I should know.
And I don't want to say
the other one was old,
but its IP number was one.
Right?
Thank you, Pam.
Oh, you're welcome.
My pleasure.
Can I do something for you?
I just helped someone out.
It feels good.
Nice.
You know, I cleaned
up our daughter for,
like, an hour at 4:00 a.m.
this morning, so...
So you know the feeling.
Special delivery for
Dwight K. Schrute.
I didn't order anything.
And I don't have
anything for you,
but I do want to talk
to you about something.
We have been
thinking about where
Packer should sit,
and we can't just
sit around waiting
for Creed to die.
Well, there's a lot
of seats in the annex.
So you wouldn't mind
permanently relocating
so that Packer can
take this desk here.
TODD: Thanks, man.
It would mean a lot to me.
I've been sitting here
for 10 years, Michael.
Well, I was there
for 12 years.
Plus, my name's
carved under the desk.
No, it is not.
It is too.
Where? Let me see this.
Right there.
Check it out.
DWIGHT: Michael, I don't
want to move desks.
MICHAEL: Don't be
a baby. We're...
Okay, there it is.
"Packer was here
and so was your mom."
Yeah.
Do I have any say in this?
MICHAEL: No!
No!
It's $20 to watch, Halpert.
Hey. Whose
dirt box is this?
That's our Zen garden.
What do you
growing here, bull crap?
Hey, Holly.
Hey. What's up, guys?
Don't "what's up" us.
You think you're
so cute with your
pretty blond hair.
Pull it back.
Why did you hire
Todd Packer?
PAM: He's seriously awful.
Michael's recommendation
was glowing.
And honestly,
he's been nothing
but nice to me.
That's how he gets you
to take off your panties.
Why are you nodding?
United front.
Okay, look,
we can't fire someone
because we don't like him.
Right. This isn't the
U.S. government.
What are you referencing?
Everything.
Do any of you have
any concrete complaints
about something he's done?
Well, I mean,
he humped Michael.
Well, if that's the case,
I guess I've got
to be fired, too.
Hey. Hey, you guys.
The Yarmouth
Regatta video is up.
Gather round. Check it out.
This guy's on
a full beam reach.
They're hiking out
like mad.
Luff him up. Luff him up.
Nice!
This computer's
a hunk of junk.
Hey, sailor,
come watch your
regatta over here.
Where did you get this?
Pam gave it to me.
This is a sick computer.
Gwen Stefani
has this computer.
Pamela.
Yep?
What does a guy
have to do to whom
to get one of them?
You have a computer, Andy.
Yeah, but if you
donated my computer
to Africa,
it would become famous
as the slowest computer
in Africa.
Okay, listen,
we just don't have
the budget for it, okay?
Reception needed
a computer, so we got one.
Well, Andy's desk
needs a computer.
And, I mean, it's just
kind of a coincidence
that I work there, but...
Yes, but reception
is a one-person department.
If I get you a new computer,
I have to get one
for everyone in sales,
for Dwight, for Stanley.
It would be crazy.
So something good
happening to Stanley
is crazy now.
ANDY: They're not
asking for one.
I am. I need it.
If you're just
handing them out,
I want one, too.
Phyllis, nobody's
handing anything out.
See? That's what
I'm talking about.
What, are you gonna
play mahjongg faster?
PAM: I'm sorry, Andy.
Hey, what's going on,
you guys?
Yeah.
Three muske-queers.
Mean, but good.
So, Todd, this must
be nice for you,
getting off the road.
You get to spend some time
with your daughter.
I don't know.
I love her and all,
but she's turned
into a bitch.
Most days she's great,
but some days she
acts like her mom.
Well, some girls
go through a phase.
Yeah. Your life
is so insane.
You should write a book.
Since when did you
learn how to read?
I do know
how to read, though.
Yeah. You know
how to read a menu.
This guy...
I... He's right.
I mean, I could
lose some weight.
Kevin, in sumo culture,
you'd be considered
a promising up-and-comer.
What the heck?
Why do you have
Erin's computer?
It's crazy, right?
Erin just
wanted me to have it,
so we switched.
What? Erin,
is that true?
I just thought he seemed
to really need a new computer,
and he knows so
much about that one.
Erin, it's not up to you.
This computer was
for reception, okay?
It's not yours
to give away.
Pam.
When I'm freaking out,
I just sort of step back,
take three deep breaths.
I'm not freaking out. Okay?
And then I ask myself,
"Is this worth
freaking out about?"
Andy, why should she
have your crappy computer?
That's interesting.
So you also think
my computer's crappy.
Switch the computers
back, Andy.
Seriously?
Seriously.
Pam, come on.
PAM: Now, please.
ANDY: Fine!
Please make sure
nobody is humping me.
If you're going
back to the annex,
could you take
these to Dwight?
I think the ants
are waking up.
They need to
start farming soon.
Thanks.
Best day ever.
So much is happening.
Question.
Should I get stripes shaved
into the side of my head?
No. No.
Please.
Did Todd tell you
to do that?
Yes.
Yeah, I thought so.
You love him, right?
You love him. I can tell.
I love you.
No, no, not me.
Him. What...
He's certainly opinionated.
If you're not gonna
take the ants over,
I should probably
just do it myself.
I'm going.
No. Are you jealous of him
because you think
he's funnier than you?
Honey.
I don't think
he's funnier than me.
He's funnier than me.
He's not funny at all.
So I'm less funny
than not funny at all?
Hey, oh-oh, I think the ants
are starting to eat
each other.
No, what I'm saying is
he's not funny, but
you're funnier than he is.
Okay, Bill Cosby,
Steve Martin,
Charlie Bit My Finger,
Michael Scott,
then all the way down here,
Todd Packer.
That's insane.
Honey, he's a jerk.
For Pete's sake,
it just needs to be done.
So you two are
married now, right?
Yeah.
That's sweet.
How's the sex?
Yeah.
DWIGHT: Hey, Packer,
I made you some
hot chocolate.
Why?
'Cause I want to let
bygones be bygones,
show you I'm cool.
You're the new guy.
It's cold out.
I made too much.
I got this awesome
hot chocolate recipe
from my wife.
That's a lot of reasons.
Drink it.
I think I'll pass.
The only hot
chocolate I'm into
is Vivica A. Fox.
Can I talk to
you for a second?
Here.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
So this hot chocolate
thing with Packer...
None of your business.
Well, you know you
can't actually poison him.
Right?
It isn't poison.
It's a laxative.
People take laxatives
all the time.
This is just a lot
more of a laxative.
Let me handle it.
I really think we
should join forces
on this one.
Really?
What do we think?
What would drive him crazy?
I know.
Here we go.
Pepto-Bismol in
his hot chocolate.
You have got to stop
with the hot chocolate stuff.
Okay.
I was thinking
maybe we could
jam his drawers
so they only
come out two inches.
Then, that way,
you can see
everything in them,
but you can't get at it.
Does Edgar Allan Poe
know about that one?
So sinister.
That wouldn't
annoy a person at all.
Where do you come
up with this stuff?
Okay. All right,
well, this isn't my best,
but call Froggy 101,
say that we're
the tour manager
for Justin Bieber,
and we're giving
away free tickets.
We give them a number
to call for the tickets,
and it's his number.
Who is Justice Beaver?
He... It's a
crime-fighting beaver.
Why don't you write
up your best 40 ideas
and e-mail them to me.
Can you do that?
Absolutely.
I'll e-mail you 100.
Okay.
Yeah. Write up
your list of 100, edit it
down to your top 40,
and I'll read it over.
Pam, can I talk
to you in private?
I don't know if there's
really a private place
in this office.
Well, I put a sign-up sheet
in the conference room,
and I signed us
up for three mods.
A mod is five minutes,
and it started two
minutes ago, so...
You did that?
Can we talk about
this in the meeting?
'Cause we're already late.
Okay.
Wow, when did
people sign up for that?
Mind if I close the door?
No.
What you did out there earlier
was totally un-cool.
Well,
what I was supposed to do,
let you walk all over me?
You humiliated me in
front of everybody.
Okay, well, I didn't
think about it like that.
It's just...
I can't do anything about it.
I can't replace your computer
unless that one breaks.
Well, I mean,
it's pretty broken already.
Well, if it breaks
all the way,
I can get you a new one.
Pretty sneaky, sis.
Hey, cats, we got
a jam session in
mods six, nine and 12.
There are 400 of these.
Yeah, I couldn't cut it down.
They're all good.
So good.
"Number three, eat a frog."
That sounds promising.
"Number four, eat a dog."
I don't know, from
a practical standpoint...
One thirty-five.
Did you like
one thirty-five?
"Eat a brog."
Maybe it's 'cause I
didn't understand it.
I just had a couple of notes.
Let me grab a pen and...
Damn it.
Just when we were...
Just when we were
getting going.
Allow all cookies?
Why, soitenly.
Pop-ups? Yes, please.
Bit torrent streaming
from a Somalian music website?
Yeah, why not?
I hope you don't get sick,
Mr. Computer.
Why are you doing
this to me, Andy?
Because I hate
your broke ass.
And a 76ers fan to boot.
I like that.
And you made Hank smile.
That doesn't happen often.
You're very charming.
You know what?
That is something that
you should take upstairs
and use on the people
that really matter.
Why?
I don't know.
Holly mentioned
that there were
some complaints
and that you had
said some things
about Kevin.
Holly said that?
Yeah.
She was laughing hysterically
the whole time.
I guess you said
something weird
about your daughter.
She asked me, Michael.
It would have been
rude not to answer.
You've been on
the road a long time.
And you've been
an outdoor cat.
And now you have
to be an indoor cat,
so you can't be peeing
all over the walls.
Michael, can I open
the kimono with you?
I've been on
the road too long.
But I want to connect
with my daughter.
And it's not right
to call her a bitch
in front of strangers.
No, it isn't.
You're right. I got to...
I got to watch my behavior.
Yeah, a little bit.
Don't give up on me.
I won't.
Okay. Everybody?
I need you to see this,
because maybe
there is somebody here
that you underestimated
who will surprise you.
Todd Packer is
going to apologize.
Kevin, front and center.
Come here.
I got a lot of numbers
here to put together.
Kevin, we know
that you are just
trying to save face.
We know that you are
hurt and embarrassed.
That's silly.
I should be
apologizing to Packer,
'cause everybody
knows that I can dish it
as good as I can take it.
Okay, sweetie, no,
you shouldn't be
apologizing to Packer.
That doesn't
make any sense.
You ready for this?
Are you ready for this?
Mmm-hmm.
Gentlemen,
start your engines.
I'm sorry if you were offended
by my comments earlier.
Well, like I said,
I wasn't offended,
but I'll stand here
for the big show.
Kevin, do you
accept the apology?
Don't do it, Kevin.
That's that fake
kind of apology.
Okay, go back to the annex.
This is textbook.
It's so un-cool.
Ryan does this to
me all the time,
like it's some offense
to have feelings.
Don't do it, Kevin.
Sometimes you overreact.
OSCAR: Michael, how is
this supposed to work?
Packer's gonna keep
saying terrible things,
and then he's just gonna
make half-ass apologies,
and we're back
to square one.
Okay. You want an apology?
Here goes.
Kevin, I am so sorry.
You are skinny,
and you're a genius.
Okay. That...
That was maybe too much.
Packer is a survivor
of divorce, Stanley.
Packer doesn't speak
with his child, Meredith.
Packer never lived up
to his parents'
expectations, Andy.
Angela loves pussycats.
Packer loves...
No, don't.
I was going to say "dogs!"
Okay, you know what?
This is over.
Apology has been issued,
and we're through with it.
Packer's going to be here
until the day he dies,
just like the rest of us.
So, listen, we have to
really scuff this up.
No, no, no, we can say
that the previous owner
was a neat freak
or an elegant old lady,
and she just kept it around
in case her grandkids
came to visit.
But they died,
and they never came.
I'm gonna make myself cry.
Andy, this is the
deal we made.
That's probably good.
That's enough.
We should break
this hinge maybe.
Let's not go crazy.
Well, thanks. Will do.
JIM: Absolutely. Now,
when you get down there,
Jo's a little bit forgetful,
so she may have
locked the gate,
but what you're gonna
do is, go ahead, hop it,
and just head
back to the pool.
That sounds weird.
JIM: It is weird.
Look at you. Perceptive.
Now I know why Jo's
kept her eye on you.
and check out
the Harry Potter World.
JIM: Whatever you want to
do in your spare time
is up to you.
Harry Potter World
is supposed to be fantastic.
Apparently, as soon
as corporate found out
I wanted to come
in off the road,
Jo offered me a cushy
new job in Tallahassee.
And here's the best part.
I'm a huge alligator nerd.
I can name you every genus,
every subspecies.
Also, I'm a huge boob nerd.
Check it out
and have a free
Butterbeer on us.
Keep the receipt,
and we'll get you back.
What are you doing?
This is a very
important client.
All right,
so just pack your bags.
And be sure to bring
those swimming trunks.
Bye, now.
Bye.
I cannot believe this.
You're sending
Packer to Florida? Why?
Because he's a jerk.
You gave him my desk.
Okay. So you're
tricking him into
flying to Florida.
This wasn't my first choice.
Jim had so many better ideas.
You have to tell him.
You have to tell him
what you did.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That is not in the plan.
That is actually
anti what we're doing.
He is my oldest friend.
I am going to tell him.
Wait. Why don't we
come up with a plan
that we're all happy about?
Yeah, that...
Pam, how is this
thing even any better
than my old computer?
Come on, Andy.
I mean, you said
you wanted a computer.
This is the best I could do.
Where'd you even
find this thing?
Like, in the corner
of the warehouse?
Yes, I found it on
a shelf in the corner
of the warehouse.
All right, well, thank you
for my garbage computer.
You're looking at
the new face of corporate.
Gonna put the "ass"
in Tallahassee.
Yes, about that...
Man, we got to go out
and celebrate tonight.
Well, I don't know
if that's a good idea.
The old ball and chain?
No. No. Nothing
like that at all.
Listen, I'm gonna
tell you something
that none of these
people have the stones
to tell you.
It's your girlfriend.
She's uptight.
Sorry?
I know this stuff can hurt,
but I wish someone
had said something
to me about my ex-wife.
All I'm saying is,
in about a month or so,
have you down to Florida,
introduce you to
all the local talent.
Sounds great.
Yeah.
It's gonna be so good.
MICHAEL: That is.
It's gonna be awesome.
I think you're really going
to enjoy it down there.
I'm sorry
about your friend.
No. He's an ass.
You are.
What are you,
wicked smaht?
No, you are.
Hoo-ah!
Saw Andy's new
computer you found
in the warehouse.
Yep. Lucked out.
Yeah, you really did,
'cause I know every
inch of that warehouse.
Yep. Super lucky.
Maybe you could
go back down there
and see if you can find
me some extra sick days.
Yeah.
You know what?
I think I saw
one sick day.
I think maybe I saw five.
Three.
I'm full-on corrupt.