Andy?
Attend the tale
Of Sweeney Todd
His skin was pale
And his eye was odd
Yes.
He shaved the faces
Of gentlemen
Who never thereafter
Were heard of again
He trod a path
That few have trod
Did Sweeney Todd
The demon barber
Of Fleet Street
Did you write this?
No.
Who did?
Stephen Sondheim.
Who is he?
Swing your
Razor wide, Sweeney
Hold it to the skies
Freely flows the blood
Of those who moralize
What the hell is happening?
We are the cast
of Sweeney Todd:
The Demon Barber
of Fleet Street.
We open in
a couple of weeks
at the Loose Screw
Playhouse, here in Scranton.
And today, just doing
a wee bit
of viral marketing, gov'nor!
ALL:
Attend the tale
Of Sweeney Todd
He served a dark
and a vengeful God
What happens then
Well, that's the play
And he wouldn't
Want us to give it away
Not Sweeney Todd
The demon barber of Fleet
Street
Wow!
Oh, that was amazing!
That was awesome!
I auditioned for this!
When did the cast list go up?
Like a month ago.
Really? They didn't call me!
Who am I playing?
Andy?
Two comps for milady
and her Gabe.
It's closing night.
Tomorrow we have to
give the theater over
to the Scranton's
Miss Fitness Pageant.
I am so excited,
but I just need one.
Gabe can't come. Sorry.
What?
Yeah.
That's awful.
Everyone's
gonna miss that guy.
Gabe is not coming,
which is huge,
because my plan
is to make Erin
fall back in love
with me tonight.
Women cannot resist
a man singing show tunes.
It's so powerful,
even a lot of men
can't resist a man
singing show tunes.
Oh, who else is going?
Everyone.
Gabe seemed to
think no one was going.
What kind of terrible
rumormonger is Gabe?
He is woefully
ill informed, all right?
Excuse me.
Everybody, you're all coming
to my show tonight, right?
Andy, what time's it start?
8:00 p.m. Sharp.
How long is it?
Hour and 45...
No, I can't make it.
They say that no one
can take your pride,
but the people who
cast Andy's play,
they took mine.
Jim, Pam, you guys
are in, right?
Oh, we wanted to, but our
sitter just fell through.
I'm really sorry.
Dwight?
No, thank you.
Last time I went
to the theater,
a man dressed as
a cat sat on my lap.
It would mean so much
to me if you came to
my show tonight.
I can't, Andy.
It's too hard.
That's...
I put everything I
had into that audition.
Do you understand that?
If it makes you
feel any better,
no one who auditioned
for the part of Sweeney Todd
got that part.
They had to bring
in a ringer.
This guy's, like, world class.
You should not feel bad.
I'm asking you,
thespian to thespian,
will you please
be the bigger man
and come to my show?
I wish I could,
Andy, but I can't.
I have plans that night.
I'm going to see
a friend in a play
called Sweeney Todd.
You're that friend.
I'm going to see your play.
Nice!
And scene.
Listen, I would like
you to take me to
Andy's play tonight.
Please, waste of time.
You know what?
Let's just knock
this out right now.
Disrobe.
Angela?
Don't like her anymore.
Not attracted to her anymore.
Just contractually obligated
to make a baby with her.
Give me the punch card.
No.
If you want to
punch the punch card,
you have to take
me to the show.
That is not in the contract.
Well, there's a lot of
gray area in that clause.
Do you want to re-mediate?
All right, fine!
I'll go to your little show.
But I'm not wearing a cape.
Thank you.
Dwight and I have
a contractual agreement
to procreate five times,
plain and simple.
And should he
develop feelings for me?
Well, that would be
permissible under
item 7C, clause 2,
so I would not object.
Hey. How are those salads?
It's my own fault...
My parents used
to scramble to
find babysitters
so they could take
my little brother
to do stuff.
I understand how
hard it can be.
I just... Tonight,
I mean, if you could...
We'll keep looking.
Yes!
Really?
I mean, who knows?
Maybe I have a niece
my family never told me about.
Oh, my gosh,
that would be amazing.
Yeah.
For a lot of reasons.
Yeah, I know. Niece!
Oh! Hey, guys.
You brought
balloons to a play?
I did, because I am
being the bigger man,
and balloons are
bigger than flowers.
It's nice, like Up.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Are you the guy
that did an entire
Law & Order episode
for his audition?
Nope.
Guys?
ALL: Hey!
Andy!
Hey!
You all made it.
Thank you so much.
You should
actually thank Erin.
She's the one who
agreed to babysit.
She's babysitting?
I really wanted to see
Andy's play, because
he's so, so talented,
but I've been trying
to get in the babysitting
game forever.
The 13- year-olds
in this town have
a complete monopoly.
It's almost like
a babysitters' club.
I understand.
This is, like, a huge
opportunity for her.
This is ridiculous.
You'd think they'd
discourage people
from bringing in balloons.
Hey, I think this guy
playing Sweeney Todd
is my plumber.
No, Darryl. This guy's
a world-class actor.
He doesn't daylight
as your plumber.
No, it's my plumber.
Says so in his bio.
It's his first play.
He didn't even audition.
Are you kidding me?
Shh.
If we don't
listen to the overture,
we won't recognize
the musical themes
when they come back later.
All right, I'm sorry.
God.
Attend the tale
Of Sweeney Todd
His skin was pale
And his eye was odd
He shaved the faces
Of gentlemen
Who never thereafter
Were heard of again
He trod a path
That few have trod
Did Sweeney Todd
The demon barber
Of Fleet Street
He kept a shop
In London town
Excuse me,
I think you may be
in the wrong seats.
What if none of
Their souls were saved
They went to their
Maker impeccably shaved
By Sweeney
By Sweeney Todd
The demon barber
Of Fleet Street
I feel you
Johanna
I was half convinced
I waited
Satisfied enough
To dream you
Happily I was mistaken
Johanna
Oh!
There's gum on the seat,
and now it's on my work skirt.
I have to go change.
Too bad I'm not gonna
explain anything
that you miss.
Oh, Dwight, just move.
Do they think that
walls can hide you?
His name's Andy.
He's a terrible salesman.
I am in the dark beside you
Michael!
Shelby Thomas Weems,
the director.
Hello.
I promise you that if
you keep auditioning
with a similar gusto...
Okay.
...we are going to
find a production
with a role for Michael Scott.
Okay.
Yes?
Yes.
Good.
Enjoy the second act.
You enjoy the second act.
Have a refreshment.
Thank you. You, too.
Thank you, thank you.
Come on, Dwight.
Why are you dressed
like a seed catalog model?
These are just my dirty
old gardening clothes.
They were all
that I had in my car.
Let's go.
Hey, Erin, it's Pam.
Hey, how you doing...
No, no, don't put Cece
on the phone, because
she can't talk yet.
Okay. No, I was
just calling to see
how everything's going.
Yeah? Yeah? It's good?
The play?
The play is kind of great.
I mean,
it's fun to hear Andy sing
in the appropriate setting.
No, he's really sorry
you couldn't make it, too.
Yeah.
So thank you so much again.
We're having a great time.
Oh, they're
flashing the lights,
so we should go in.
Thanks. Bye.
Okay, so we called,
and everything's fine.
Everything's fine.
We can relax.
Let's get our Sweeney on.
Then I go
Walking with you-hoo
You-hoo
I warm me bones
On the esplanade
Have tea and scones
With me gay young blade
I'll knit a sweater
While you write a letter
Unless we've
Got better to do-hoo
Anything you say
Think how snug it'll be
Underneath our flannel
When it's just you and me
And the English Channel
In our cozy retreat
Kept all neat and tidy
We'll have chums
Over ev'ry Friday
By the sea
Anything you say
Don't you love the weather
Just checking my e-mails.
See if I got any
last-minute "break-a-legs"
or "l-still-Iove-you"
type texts.
Doesn't look
like I got anything.
Maybe on my Facebook wall.
Unfortunately, in this
ham-fisted production
of Sweeney Todd,
the real terror
comes from the
vocal performances.
New paragraph.
Mr. Todd! Mr. Todd!
I found her!
You found Johanna.
That monster of
a judge has locked her...
üMUSICAL TONE
PLAYING ON CELL PHONEä
Locked her away...
üMUSICAL TONE
CONTINUES PLAYINGä
There's a little
bird fluttering around.
Do hope it ceases chirping.
How is that funny?
The bird continues to call.
Someone please
turn off your bird.
üMUSICAL TONE
CONTINUES PLAYINGä
Oh, for the love...
Turn your phone off!
There are signs!
Oh!
It appears the bird
was in mine own pocket
this whole time.
He's gone to sleep now.
I closed his beak.
What is the news
of my darling
daughter Johanna?
üMUSICAL TONE
PLAYS ON CELL PHONEä
You know what?
Let me just double check.
Make sure that bird...
Okay, good. It's off.
I mean, silenced.
I silenced it by killing it.
I've killed it!
I'm a murderer!
Just like you, Sweeney Todd!
See? It all connects.
Not that I know
you're a murderer.
My character
doesn't know that yet.
But I'm suspicious,
because of all the razors
that you have laying around.
but you're a barber,
so that's legit.
So there's that.
But...
A madhouse.
A madhouse?
Yes, a madhouse.
Johanna is as good
as rescued.
Where do you suppose
all the wig makers
of London go to
obtain their human hair?
Do you think...
So you think...
Fogg's Asylum, why not?
Sounds like Cece.
Okay, I think everybody
just needs to relax.
Oh, my God. Go, go.
Oh, my God.
That's really
irresponsible of Erin.
She's a terrible babysitter.
I just didn't think
you guys were
gonna see us.
We were just gonna
stop by and then
get some ice cream
and then go home.
Okay, this was
pretty simple. Right?
Why are you here?
All you had to do
was play with her
for, like, 30 minutes
and then put her to bed.
Then we were kind of
hoping that you wouldn't
touch her again.
Babies shouldn't have
ice cream, by the way.
I'm sorry. I just...
I really wanted to see Andy.
You guys made it
sound so un-missable,
and you set me
up with a car seat
and everything.
Well, the car seat
was to take her
to the hospital or...
But why would I take
her to the hospital?
You know what,
it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
Why don't I
just take her home,
and let you guys finish,
and then you should
stay out as late
as you want.
No, we're good.
Thank you, though.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Okay. All right, bye, Cece.
Okay.
All right.
Well, we're never
leaving the house again.
Not together.
That was more
horrifying than Nunsense.
All that singing
got in the way
of some perfectly
good murders.
Where's my car?
Come on.
Mmm!
Fruit is so much
better when it's dried.
I've already eaten,
like, 30 apricots.
Darryl?
Hey!
Didn't know you
were gonna be here.
How's the toilet?
Silent.
Look, congratulations.
Thank you.
I had no idea.
This plumber has pipes.
Yeah, good job. Well done.
You're the guy
who booed me.
Mmm-mmm.
No, there were a lot
of people booing you.
I wasn't one of them.
No, I saw you,
and you were the only one.
Get your eyes checked,
chucklehead.
Be cool, Michael.
I saw this guy kill
a bunch of people.
Good work.
Thank you.
You didn't have to boo him.
He was getting
a lot of applause,
and I just didn't
think it was indicative
of how people
were really feeling.
How would you like
it if we booed you?
That would never happen.
Okay.
I appreciate the feedback.
I don't like that at all.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I'm so scared!
Okay, kill me!
Just kill me! Kill me!
Blood everywhere.
Oh, no.
I'm so glad we're hanging
out again outside of work.
Yeah, me, too.
Okay, I kill you now.
Okay.
All right.
All right, let's do this.
You know, actually, Dwight,
I didn't realize how far
this walk was,
and I'm exhausted.
It's okay, I smell.
No. No, no, no. I think
I just want to go home,
but it's okay.
This can count as
one of your times.
No, no, no.
Contractually, we're
obligated to have sex.
Well, I won't
tell if you don't.
I will tell.
I will tell the mediator.
What...
What are you... Oh, okay.
Oh, was that in the way?
Get rid of it. Oh!
Good night, Dwight.
Good night.
These would have
been your seats.
Best seats in the house.
Lot of people think it
would be the front row,
but, actually, right here,
this is where
the speakers converge
and the sound just,
like, nails you right here.
This is awesome.
Oh.
Sorry. Oh.
Hi, Gabe.
Yeah, I just stopped
by Andy's cast party
to say hi to everyone.
Sure, I can pick you up
some soup. What do you want?
That's broth, Gabe.
Okay, I'll see you soup.
Okay, I have to go.
Thank you so much.
This was so much fun,
and I'm really sorry
that I missed your play,
but next time,
I'll be there.
Or here.
Right here, I promise.
Awesome.
Okay.
See you later.
Thank you.
This night was a disaster.
No, it was not a disaster.
It was weird,
but it wasn't a disaster.
I think we have, like,
a gift bottle of Irish Cream.
Yeah?
We could put that
in orange juice.
Get it.
Yeah?
Let's get our juice on.
Yeah.
PHYLLIS: Found him.
Hey, what's going on here?
Post-show blues?
Yeah, I guess
you could say that.
Yeah, I get those
every day after work.
Your show was
really great, Andy.
Interesting subject matter.
I'm surprised
you pulled it off.
It was like amateur hour.
It was an amateur production,
technically.
Oscar,
enough with the sass, please!
God! What is wrong with you?
Andy, listen to me.
Look me in the eye.
I thought that
you were awesome.
Stop just saying that.
I am not just saying that.
You can trust that I am
telling you the truth.
I booed someone tonight.
I have no filter.
And if I thought
you were terrible,
I would have booed.
And if I thought you
had done a better job,
I would be saying
nicer things right now.
But I thought that you
were exactly awesome.
No better, no worse.
Thank you.
That feels good.
I did not say that
to make you feel good.
I just said it.
Total integrity.
DARRYL: Andy,
sing us another song.
Thanks, but I feel
like a Ioner right now.
Come on, Andy.
You were the highlight.
Come on, Andy, seriously.
Andy! Andy!
ALL:  Andy!
Okay, all right.
I try to say goodbye
And I choke
Try to walk away
And I stumble
Though I try to hide it
It's clear
My world crumbles
When you are not here
I play it off but
I'm dreaming of you
I keep my cool
But I'm fiending
ALL:
I try to say goodbye
And I choke
Try to walk away
And I stumble
Though I try to hide it
It's clear
My world crumbles
When you are not near
My world
It crumbles
When you are not here
In the criminal
justice system,
the people are represented
by two separate
yet equally important groups,
the police who
investigate the crimes,
and the district attorneys
who prosecute the offenders.
These are their stories.
A dead body!
It looks like a classic case
of autoerotic asphyxiation.
Yeah, looks like everybody's
tightening their
belts in this economy.
üHUMMING LAW & ORDER THEMEä
Last time you saw the victim,
was he happy?
Last time I saw
this John he was...
He wasn't a victim,
if you know what
I'm talking about.
DIRECTOR: Thank you.
No!
That was just part...
I was just getting
into the first act.