DWIGHT: Uh-oh. Okay,
okay, nobody panic.
Listen up, listen up.
Everyone,
follow me to the shelter.
We've got enough
food for 14 days.
After that, we have
a difficult conversation.
My bad.
Space heater and
fan were both on high,
plugged into
the same outlet, so...
JIM: It's saying
the server went down?
Does anybody
know that password?
'Cause otherwise,
we can't do any work.
Uh, try "password."
Nope.
Try zero, zero, zero,
zero, zero, zero.
No.
Okay, now try zero, zero,
zero, zero, zero, one.
Okay, I'm not
doing every number.
Wait, does anyone
remember when
it was set up?
Uh, it was, like,
eight years ago?
Lord of the Rings stuff?
I don't know,
I'm just trying
to think of things
that were happening
at the time.
Everyone was getting
their driver's license.
Why don't we just
call the I.T. guy
who set it up?
What's the name of the guy
in the glasses, again?
Okay, moving backwards,
our I.T. guys have been
"Glasses," "Turban,"
"Ear Hair," "Fatty 3,"
"Shorts," "Fatty 2,"
"Lozenge" and "Fatso."
I think "Lozenge"
is the one
who installed it.
ANDY: I got it.
Try...
You know what,
it made me laugh
when I heard it,
but Pam got
really offended.
"Big boobs."
"Drama queen"?
"Nosy"?
You're typing
"big boobs"?
I'm trying everything.
Try "big boobs"
with a "z."
That's the password.
We're in.
DWIGHT: All right.
Wow.
DWIGHT: Yes.
The important thing is
this kept us secure, people.
Morning.
RYAN: How's it going?
Hey, I'm Wuphf.
I'm Facebook.
What's up, Facebook?
I sent you
a Facebook
message yesterday,
I still haven't
heard anything back.
You should've
sent me a wuphf.
A what?
When you send a wuphf,
it goes to your
home phone, cell phone,
email, Facebook,
Twitter, and homescreen.
All at the same time.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Wuphf.
Wuphf!
Wuphf.com!
Thanks, Erin.
Sure.
Hey, Pam. I don't
wanna be a lousy snitch.
Okay.
Ryan has been
using the color printer
for his business a lot,
and as office
administrator...
Oh, it's okay.
But it's not for...
Let it go.
PAM: Yes, I invested
in Wuphf.
It's actually
a really great idea,
and I can't believe
it didn't exist before.
And I know Ryan's
kind of a sketchy guy,
but hey, I married Jim.
I've done my part
for the nice guy.
Now I want a bedroom set.
I think an investors'
ski trip, frankly,
is the best idea.
It will be
a bonding experience.
I love it.
I was looking
at a trail map,
and I was thinking
that we should start
on a bunny hill,
because I've never
actually been skiing.
And then work our
way up to "Death Drop."
Great,
so we got our first offer
to buy the company.
You're kidding.
We could sell,
but why think so small?
We can just get
a couple more
people involved,
really do this
thing our way.
You and me, baby.
New investors are key,
though. That's actually
why I came in today.
Don't you work
here full-time?
Today, I was
thinking I would sit down
with a few of the people
who haven't invested yet.
Or we could do that
together, if that
sounds fun to you.
That does sound fun to me.
Awesome.
Oh, this is good hay. Yeah.
This is the good stuff.
Mattress quality.
Every fall,
growing up,
my Uncle Eldred
used to build us a maze
out of hay bales
for us kids to play in.
We called it "Hay Place."
Eldred called it
"Hay World."
Eventually, lawyers
were brought in. But...
That's all behind us.
Hay Place lives on.
Watch it, watch it.
Hello!
Welcome to Hay Place.
A place for hay.
Don't forget
to make a broom.
Oh, the petting zoo
closes at 2:00,
and the goat roast
is at 3:00.
Come on in, enjoy!
Hey.
I'm kind of in the mood
for a roll in the hay.
Roll in the hay, $5.
No, I meant...
Oh, our contract.
Mmm-hmm.
Yes, why don't we
meet at the usual spot.
Uh, I've got a half
an hour during lunch
in between the historical
reenactment of the
Dunmore farm slaughters
and the onion boil.
Perfect.
So... Excuse me,
get off of there.
Those are show bales,
not play bales.
All right, thank you.
I will send the
contracts over right away.
All right.
Whoo!
JIM: I am on the first hot
sales streak of my life.
I think it all comes
from feeding Cece,
because no matter
how much she resists,
I sell her
those carrots.
And let's be honest,
if I can make mushed carrots
seem better than a boob,
I can pretty much
sell anything.
Commission comes out to
zero.
Okay, well, it can't
be zero, Kev.
I entered the sale,
and I hit enter and I
said, "Dunh-duh-na-dah!"
I'm pretty sure
I timesed it right.
You met your
commission cap
last week.
So, from here until
the end of the fiscal year,
your commission will be zero.
What are you talking about?
We have a commission cap?
It's a new
corporate policy.
Is this job really
about the money
for you, Jim?
I mean, isn't this
where you fell in love?
A commission cap
takes away my
incentive to sell.
So, you realize
I now have no
reason to work, right?
When you're dealing
with a large organization,
sometimes you have to
put up with policies
you don't like.
I wish my gym
didn't allow full nudity
in the locker room.
Okay, some of
these old guys
walking around naked,
feels almost
passive-aggressive.
But I deal with it
'cause it's policy.
See what I mean?
Nope.
Nudity makes me
uncomfortable.
Okay.
My gym allows it.
I wish they didn't,
but it's policy. So,
I respect it, and I just
keep a low...
You know, I look away.
Think about your
commission cap
as a naked old man
in a gym locker room.
Excuse me,
everyone. Sex!
Now that I have
your attention...
You don't have
our attention.
Money!
I'm listening.
You had me at "sex."
Pervert.
PHYLLIS: You have
all of our attention
just by screaming anything.
That's good to know.
What do you want
to say, Michael?
Wuphf!
All right,
I've warmed them up for you.
You have the floor, Ryan.
How's everybody doing?
RYAN: Good!
Now, a lot of you
have already staked out
your corner of
the Wuphf empire.
Raise your hand if
I'm describing you.
Great.
STANLEY: Yes, I have a dream.
And it's not some M.L.K.
dream for equality.
I want to own
a decommissioned
lighthouse.
And I want to
live at the top.
And nobody knows
I live there.
And there's a button
that I can press,
and launch that
lighthouse into space.
For my current investors,
things are going great.
We already
have a buyer.
Really? Who?
Washington University.
I don't even want to
think about selling
until our numbers
get into the billions.
At least.
So, I've decided
to open up a second
round of investment
to friends and family.
Oh, God. Hold on to
your wallets, ladies.
Did you ever think of
Wuphf as an emergency
notification system,
like, for college campuses
with shooters or gas leaks?
No, no, Oscar, it's not
a digital rape whistle.
Wuphf is about fun.
That's right.
Fun, communication,
connection.
What's your
money situation?
Well, it's tight,
as with any start-up.
Sure, how long can you
sustain this without
a cash infusion?
We have nine solid days.
I love these questions.
Keep 'em coming.
I'm sorry,
nine days until what?
Bankruptcy?
Wait, Ryan,
so this could be
over by the weekend?
How long do you
think a week is?
No, not this weekend.
Next weekend.
We were gonna go on
the investors' ski trip.
I bought poles.
JIM: Well, since I have
no incentive to sell,
I've cleaned my car,
organized my desk,
and taken a multivitamin.
So...
What now?
Pam.
Okay, now I've tried
everything.
Did you prank Dwight?
No.
Well, you like that.
Yeah, it's not
as fun if I'm not
blowing off work.
I love you,
but I'm kind of busy,
so I need you to
figure this one
out on your own.
Oscar said Wuphf
only has enough money
for nine days.
Check this out.
All that color.
MICHAEL: Look at that.
Triple your
investment by January.
Anyone can just
throw numbers up
on a chart.
What are you doing
to make it happen?
Well, earlier today,
I was emailing someone
by the name of John Legend.
MICHAEL: There you go.
You have his email?
A lot of these
guys are just Mac.com
at their website whatever.
We get that guy wuphfing,
it's all over.
I want my money back.
Do not talk
like that, Stanley.
Ryan, just tell
us your plan.
Okay, all right.
I know what you wanna see.
I'll be right back.
Hey, kids,
was that fun?
ALL: Yeah!
All right.
I wanna go
on it again.
Oh, I bet you do.
You know what?
When I was a little kid,
they couldn't get
me off the hayride.
But it's gonna cost
you three more bucks.
Wow! This brings
back memories.
Hay stacking,
hay throwing...
And at the end of it all,
one lucky boy would
be crowned hay king.
I always wanted
to be hay king.
But the world
shines on Mose.
Where have you been?
I've been waiting.
Can we move this to
the end of the day?
No, I think you should
make time for it.
I found the needle
in the haystack!
Hey, congratulations.
Do you know
what your prize is?
I don't know.
Nothing. Life lesson?
Some tasks are
not worth doing.
Dwight?
Wuphf T-shirts.
Who wants one?
Just imagine that
you're at spring
break at Daytona Beach.
Here we go.
Okay?
Everyone's like,
"Hey, dude, what's up
"with all the hotties
in the Wuphf shirts?"
Or, "Hey, what's up
with that helicopter?"
"It's Ry from Wuphf!"
"It's Ry,
the Wuphf guy!"
"Yo, Ry from Wuphf!"
"He's up there."
"What's he dropping?"
"Wow, what's falling
on us, man?"
Wuphf condoms!
Fifty thousand condoms
out of the sky.
MICHAEL: Look at that!
He threw 'em
on the ground!
Look, this is
a marketing campaign.
You got nine days.
Let's say you
do get the money.
What are you
gonna do with it?
The first lesson of
Silicon Valley, actually,
is that you only
think about the user,
the experience.
You actually don't
think about the money.
Ever.
That sounds weird.
No, it's not weird,
Andy, and you
know what else?
We have an offer from
Washington University.
So, monetize that.
Are you guys
meeting about Wuphf?
You know that that
was my idea, right?
I said to Ryan,
"I try to call you,
"and you don't
have your phone.
"I try to I.M. you,
and you're not online.
"I wish there was
a way that I could do
everything all at once,
"and I could
just be like this
little dog going,
"'Ruff! Ruff! Ruff!
Ruff! Ruff!'"
RYAN: Baby, baby, baby...
KELLY: I think
I'm gonna sue you.
No, no, no.
I do, I do.
This isn't right.
I help you with your
things, and you help
me with my things.
KELLY: But I...
It's not right.
Is it any particular branch
of Washington University?
The Washington University
Public Health Fund.
W-U-P-H-F.
Oh, God.
They only want it
for the initials.
The domain name.
Yeah, they do.
I move we sell.
MICHAEL: What?
Yeah, sell.
Sell.
Get us out of this.
Have some faith
in this idea.
If everybody
wants to sell,
we sell, right?
I won't sell.
And you know what?
Ryan and I have
the majority of shares.
Isn't that right?
Yes. You alone do, actually.
I... Yes.
We're not selling.
I will not sell.
Awesome.
Do you mind if we
share this bale?
Sure.
There's no charge
to sit on the hay,
is there?
Probably.
I mean,
wouldn't you think
the $10 to
build your own broom
would include the hay
and not just
the instructions?
I mean,
I'm starting to think
this guy is just
trying to make money
off the holiday.
Yeah, instead of
"Hay Place" it should
be "Pay Place."
Don't laugh at me.
No, no, no, I wasn't.
I was just laughing
at your joke.
Oh.
"Pay Place."
Yeah, so we can celebrate
"Thanksgiving-me-your-money"
Day.
That's humorous.
Thank you.
KEVIN: You guys know
how to get out?
Hi, Michael.
Can't talk,
saving the planet.
Oh, we don't recycle.
We don't?
Well, why have I been
separating the trash
into whites and colors?
I'm sure no one
asked you to do that.
Eight years.
Listen, I know you
really like Ryan...
No, I won't
even consider it.
Michael, I...
I hate to say
this, but...
You know this special
bond that you've
always felt with Ryan,
where, like,
you're best friends
or you're his
mentor or something?
Right, yes, yeah.
Best friend/mentor.
Michael, I think
that that feeling
only goes one way.
And I think that
Ryan knows that,
and he's taking
advantage of you.
I think you are wrong.
And there are
a lot of other people
in this office who
have money at stake.
Other people
you care about.
You may be right.
I may be crazy.
Don't.
I'm just saying that
I think I agree
with your point.
Yeah, but in a jokey way
where you're
gonna start singing.
I thought it might
make me feel better.
Okay. Go ahead.
But it just
may be a lunatic
No.
Ooh, nice.
Wasting time,
here we go.
Hey, back off.
It's solitaire.
Hey, kid.
Hear you're
looking for work.
Talk to me.
How far can you
reach those lovely
long arms of yours?
Put 'em down.
How long can you hold
that pretty little
breath of yours?
Good.
Hey, Jim?
Are you distracting
these people?
CREED: We're working.
Can you at least
try to look busy?
JO: The moment Darla
put the cupcake
in her mouth,
her daddy pulled
her aside and said,
"You're too fat.
No one's gonna like
you if you're too fat."
The next time I
saw David Geffen
was at the Buffalo Club.
"I love you,
you gay bastard," I said.
"You gay bastard," I...
Gay ba...
Gay...
Michael,
how's it going, bro?
Good, good, bro.
Hey, thanks so much
for having my back
out there.
Always have your back.
So, any ideas on how
we can get over this
nine-day hump here?
I have nothing but
ideas. The thing is,
they all require money.
Nine days, though.
That's, like...
Look, I know I've
tapped you so hard.
Yes, you have tapped this.
Hard.
You are funny, Michael.
You... People don't
give you enough credit.
Maybe I could take
a second mortgage
on my condo.
Well, a lot of
people are doing that,
and there don't seem
to be any consequences.
And they say the rates
have never been lower.
So, you would think
that's a good
idea for me to do?
Think about this,
you and me on
our private plane,
flown by our
private pilot,
eating our private meal,
cooked by our private chef.
Yeah, well, we never even
have dinner now, so...
We totally should.
Tonight?
I gotta work on this.
Right.
What am I saying?
Rain check.
Yeah.
And now, by show of
applause, we will crown
this year's hay king.
All in favor
of Purebred.
Put your hands
together for
Mixed Bred.
And let's hear it for
Purebred.
We appear to
have a three-way tie.
I have no choice
but to pick
the hay king myself.
I pick...
Me! I am your hay king!
All hail your hay king!
Did I truck 300 bales
of hay to a parking lot
to rectify some
childhood disappointment?
Yes.
So, if I were to
call Dunder Mifflin
and ask for
Miss Angela Martin,
would I get
through to you?
You would.
And if I were to
call your house
and ask for your wife,
would I get
through to you?
My wife passed away
a few years ago.
How tragic.
Very sorry to hear that.
Thank you.
KEVIN: Help! Hello?
Oh! Help!
Consider it
a wuphf in person.
You're doing
the wrong thing.
You're gonna lose
Michael's investment,
you're gonna lose ours.
You got this crazy
opportunity to get
our money back.
Tell Mike to sell.
If you tell Michael
to sell, he'll sell.
I'm betting on myself.
It's a bad bet.
Hello?
Hey. It's an ambush here.
Nobody here
believes in
this company.
Will you tell
them they're wrong?
It's not that
we don't believe
in the company.
We don't
believe in you.
All those in favor
of selling, say "aye."
Aye.
Do not agree to sell,
which is to say nay.
What is wrong with you?
What happened to
you in high school?
Michael, are
you that blind?
I'm not blind!
I know exactly who he is.
He is selfish and
lazy and image-obsessed,
and he is a bad friend.
And he's also clever.
And he shoots
incredibly high, and
he may just make it.
But you know what,
even if he doesn't,
I would rather
go broke betting
on my people
than get rich all by
myself on some island
like a castaway.
And there is
no middle ground.
You're gonna lose
all of our money.
Only if he fails.
And you know what?
Ryan, I believe in you,
just like I believe
in all of you.
You have nine days
to save everybody's money.
Oh, that's a lot
of pressure.
I'm gonna need
some more time.
You can't have it.
Okay.
I won't let you down.
Angela? Angela!
The world sends
people your way...
Ryan came to me
through a temp agency.
Andy was transferred here.
No idea where
Creed came from.
The point is you
just have to play
with the cards
that you're dealt.
Jim,
that guy is an ace.
Dwight is my
king up my sleeve.
Phyllis is my old maid.
Oscar is my queen.
That's easy.
Give me a hard one.
That's what Oscar said.
Toby is the instruction
card you throw away.
Pam is a solid seven.
And yeah, you know what?
Ryan is probably, like, a two.
But sometimes
twos can be wild,
so watch out.
And I am obviously
the joker, so...
That's...
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Wuphf from Ryan Howard.
Decided to sell company.
Thanks, bro.
Hell of a ride.
Thank God.
Gabe Lewis.
JO: Now, listen here,
Gabe, you're too fat.
No one's gonna like
you if you're too fat.
I made some
changes to my book.
See if you like them.
Well, Jo...
Now, I love reading,
and I hate being
interrupted.
Shut up and listen,
you gay bastard.
Chapter one. I was born,
not into luxury nor poverty,
but into adversity,
and for that,
I thank the Lord.
My father was a man.
That's all we can know.
After I learned
to ride a bike,
there was no stopping me.
I would ride up
Magnolia Street
and down Azalea Lane,
which would later
become my paper route...
All right,
good night, Gabe.
Just wanted to
say thanks again
'cause I really
think I made
good use of my day.
...wherever I wanted.
I have always
been a fighter.
Sorry.
And fate has obliged me
with plenty of battles,
the first being a hard...