What about this one?
It's kind of badass, right?
It just seems kind
of crazy in a way
I might need right now.
I don't know.
Oh, that's not yours.
JIM: Stanley just
drank OJ out of my mug
and didn't seem to realize
that it wasn't his hot coffee.
So, the question
has to be asked,
is there no limit to
what he won't notice?
What's a seven-letter
word for purse?
Satchel.
No. Starts with an "H."
Handbag!
Hmm, thank you.
Shh.
All right, everybody.
Take a seat.
As you may have heard,
our branch on
the planet Jupiter
is up 8,000% in sales.
Hold up.
That clock is slow.
It is 5:00.
I will see you all
tomorrow.
Bye, Stanley,
love you.
So long, Stanley.
Night, everybody.
So, what kind of
statement are you making
with that costume,
Kevin?
Well, the statement
that I am making, Oscar,
is I kind of look
like Michael Moore.
Dunder Mifflin,
this is Erin.
Happy Halloween.
How can I haunt you today?
A lot of people are
really getting into
Halloween this year.
Pam's got a lot of
fun stuff planned...
Including a costume contest
and bobbing for apples
and a ouija board.
Oh! Boom!
Oh! Explosion!
MacGruber!
People are really into
the costume contest
this year.
Might have something
to do with the prize.
Maybe you've heard of it?
The 2011
Scranton-Wilkes-Barre
coupon book,
worth over
$15,000 in savings.
Stop.
Too late.
If I was the real
Scranton Strangler,
you'd be so strangled by now.
And if you're out there,
Strangler, you will
get caught.
By me.
Sounds like
someone's really trying
to convince us
that he's not
the Scranton Strangler.
To my chickens,
I'm the Scranton Strangler.
DWIGHT: Oh-ho.
That's very funny.
Looks like someone
decided to dress up as
old Dwight Schrute's mom.
What?
You're only one-third
as beautiful
and about
half her height.
I am supposed to be Olive Oyl.
And it makes more sense
when I'm standing
next to Popeye,
but Jim doesn't
wanna put his costume on.
I am Popeye.
I've never really
been a costume guy.
Even when I was a kid,
it just felt like
something I was too old for.
And then this morning,
Pam hands me
this little number.
No.
In case you can't read
my, my, my poker face,
We will be reviewing
our sales policies.
I have 10 seconds to
explain them or this
whole place blows up.
MacGruber!
Lame.
Why don't
witches wear panties?
Oh, here we go.
Because they need
to grip the broom.
Oh! Who likes to
water-ski on Lake Eerie?
No, wait.
Where does Dracula
like to water-ski?
Lake Eerie.
When our warehouse workers
make deliveries,
they're gonna be
encouraged to offer clients
extra products.
And then they will
split those commissions
with sales.
Wait,
so drivers are gonna be able
to sell paper on the road?
That is correct.
Has anyone started
calling you
Gabe-wad yet?
Not here, no.
Gabe-wad.
GABE: Okay, guys.
Fun is fun, but...
Blackula.
Dracula.
Oh, so,
and I almost forgot,
you'll find this
hilarious.
Apparently corporate
is going to have drivers
sell paper on
their routes now.
That's, like, exactly
sort of the idea
that you had.
Yes, I do remember saying
something like that to you.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I blew this.
You should have gotten
credit for that, man.
I'm just glad
we're gonna try it out.
Really? We're good?
We're cool.
Okay.
What's that
in your shirt?
Oh.
That's a ream of paper.
I thought you might hit me.
Darryl Philbin
is the greatest guy
in the world.
And you know
what I'd like?
I would like to have
all the racists
brought together,
and take Darryl Philbin
out to lunch,
just to see what
they're missing.
It's a great stick, right?
RYAN:
It's really good.
A classic.
I feel like you might win
the whole thing with that.
Thanks.
OSCAR:
Everyone realizes
this coupon book
is not actually worth
$15,000, right?
You'd have to spend $200,000
on crap you don't even need
to get $15,000
worth of benefits.
I'm not the only one
who sees this, right?
RYAN: No.
Well, sure.
No.
I get that.
Uh, excuse me,
everyone?
I wanna invite you all
to the Halloween party
I'm having at my bar.
You own a bar?
Public School,
at exit 11.
That's a great name.
You're hilarious.
A plus!
So, you're all on the list.
Hey, man,
can I get a plus five?
It's all guys.
Hey, what's the crowd like,
Danny? Our age?
Okay.
I don't think that
she would leave
Jim for Danny.
I don't know.
They're both handsome.
Pam is gonna choose
whoever has a scent
most like that of her father.
Does anyone remember
what her dad smelled like?
I think he...
Hey, hey, gang, quiet.
Here she comes.
Did you hear
about that Danny guy?
Heard he used to date Pam.
So, four years ago,
when I was in Stamford,
Connecticut,
and dating someone else,
Pam went on
two dates with Danny,
which was obviously
the greatest
love story ever told,
given how much people
are walking
on eggshells around us.
We were basically
Romeo and Juliet.
That's right.
Except where
Juliet doesn't have
that great a time
and Romeo doesn't
call back
after two dates.
Yikes.
But I've learned
to love again.
He's a cartoon sailor,
Oh! No.
And he looks so handsome
in his uniform.
No.
Please!
No, I'm not gonna... No.
Tuna! Tuna!
If you want us to
skip this party...
I don't care.
KEVIN:
I am never gonna forget
what Danny did to Pam.
I forget nothing.
I'm like an elephant
in that way.
You know what else?
This sucks for Jim, right?
But it also sucks for us
because we don't get invited
to a ton of Halloween parties.
Yeah. And like,
everyone's
gonna be there.
Stanley,
Phyllis,
Angela,
Darryl...
Creed's a maybe.
Creed's going?
Madge from the warehouse
just made her first sale.
Madge! We should
have been doing this
a long time ago.
Erin? Would you
please do me a solid,
and get Darryl Philbin
on the speakerphone?
Hello?
Hi, Darryl,
come out here, please.
I'm good.
You need to stop
being so shy,
come out here and embrace
who you really are, superstar.
This is embarrassing,
Michael.
MICHAEL:
Yeah, I bet it is.
You're gonna do
your job well here,
you gotta get used
to being embarrassed.
Well, let me put
my shoes on.
Hit the speakerphone button.
The speakerphone button.
Same button as
you hit before.
Same...
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Your call cannot...
Or sit on it.
This whole
delivery slash sales idea,
you know whose that was?
That was Darryl Philbin's.
He thought of that way before
the corporate fatsuits.
So, what happened?
I got in the way.
I said, "No,"
and it just stopped.
But then, corporate
comes up with this idea.
But you know what?
They need to know
that it was yours.
And I don't care
if I take a bullet.
We are going to
call them,
we are gonna put them on
speakerphone right now,
Oh. Oh.
And we are going to
straighten this out.
Screw corporate!
They probably
stole the idea anyway.
MICHAEL:
Mmm-hmm.
Uh.
Corporate stole nothing. Okay?
Darryl brought this
idea to me.
And then I told them,
giving Darryl full credit. So,
no need to
"screw corporate."
Everyone, let's give Darryl
a round of applause
as planned.
I'm a little peeved
at Darryl right now.
He went to Gabe
behind your back!
No, he didn't
go behind my back.
He went over my head.
He went over your head
to go behind your back.
What is taking
someone from behind?
No. Shh.
Michael, listen.
This cannot stand.
You can't have workers
going straight to corporate.
It makes your
job superfluous.
It was a good idea, though.
Yeah,
here's another good idea,
corporate chain of command.
We need to
strangle Darryl's idea.
Hey, Danny.
Hey.
I'm really sorry,
but we can't come to
your party tonight.
I was looking forward
to throwing some
darts with you guys.
You were?
Okay, well then...
I mean, maybe we
could do it like,
next Halloween?
For sure.
We're just, like,
totally caught in
the middle here.
What are you
talking about?
Well, Jim and Pam
basically begged us
not to go.
Jim and Pam really
don't want you to go?
They're really upset about
the whole Danny situation.
I'll talk to 'em.
Yeah, but do you know what?
Don't tell them that
we said anything to you.
Okay.
Okay? Or you're dead.
Kelly!
Great costume.
You cannot change costumes
in the middle of the day!
Pam, she's out.
If I'm out, I'm gonna
sue this entire company
for discrimination.
Guys, you're arguing over
a one-in-sixteen chance,
over a prize worth $40.
Fifteen thousand
bucks, Oscar.
Yeah, shut it,
Oscar. Pam?
This is an amazing prize.
I mean, I don't even wanna
give Pam a compliment,
'cause she's so, ugh...
But she did a good job.
I really want
that coupon book.
Garbage magnet.
God! Magnets are
interesting enough,
you don't need to
tart 'em up
with some design.
I can't believe this
doesn't make you mad.
What the hell are
they talking about?
Hmm. Kevin and Gabe?
Probably about the extremes
of the human physique.
Do you think Kevin
is going over my head?
I don't... Oh, my God.
Okay. All right,
all right, all right.
You know what?
That's inappropriate, Kevin.
I am your boss.
And if you have
something to say,
it goes through me,
and then I
take it to Gabe.
Chain of command.
Do you understand?
I am so sorry.
Oh, you're sorry?
I just thought...
What did you
just thought?
Well, Gabe asked me
if there were
any really cool
Lady Gaga moves
that he could do
for the catwalk.
And so, then I told...
All right.
I told him that there
was this one cool move
where she powers down
like a robot.
Okay.
Okay?
But I'm so sorry
that...
All right.
I didn't tell you first.
Well, don't let it
happen again.
You think that I would
let this happen again?
No way, Jose!
Um.
you, Gabe.
JIM: That is crazy.
We would never care
if Andy or Kevin
went to your party.
Look, I'm just glad
we can laugh about it,
because I was a little nervous
about coming to work here,
with, you know,
our history.
Oh, my gosh.
Everyone keeps blowing that
out of proportion.
It's not even a history.
Exactly.
It's not like
you guys had some
long relationship, right?
Big painful breakup
I don't know about?
No!
Two or three dates.
It was two.
Was it two?
I thought it was three.
No, we had plans
for a third,
but then, I don't know,
you never called me back.
So...
Oh! You can't
handle the truth!
Well, that does not
sound like me.
Yeah. It was, though.
That's what happened.
Uh.
Well, great,
I just wanted to make sure
things weren't weird.
Uh-uh.
Okay. This whole
going over my head gate
is making people act weird.
Chain of command
is crumbling.
Do you know
what just happened?
I just made Kevin cry.
And Gabe looks like Lady Gaga.
That's not Halloween.
Halloween should
be a day in which
we honor monsters
and not be mad
at each other.
I'm not mad.
Are you mad?
You went over my head,
and then you lied to my face.
So, my head and my face
have taken a beating.
Well, I'm sorry if it
seems that way to you.
Okay, that might help.
If you said "I'm sorry"
in front of everybody...
Mike.
...in front of me.
You made a bad call
and I fixed it.
So, I'm not apologizing.
So, that's it?
That's it.
Is it?
Yes.
Sookie!
Bill Compton
from True Blood.
How many freaking vampires
am I supposed to
care about these days?
Well, I guess you could say
I'm still in costume.
I'm a rational
"consumer."
Oh. Oh, yeah.
So, it's...
This stupid
coupon booklet.
Have you seen my costume?
I'm a rational "consumer."
Yeah, I heard you
say it to Phyllis.
That's a good line.
Okay, everybody.
After you walk the runway,
everyone has to vote for
who gets the coupon book.
And you can't
vote for yourself.
Pam, can you vote
for other people?
Hey, I gotta get in on this.
Hey, it's cool, man.
I work in the warehouse.
I'm cool!
I'm hip and I'm jive!
But I don't care
about nobody!
Do you know who I am?
Happy Halloween, jerk!
Still don't know
who I am?
I'll give you a hint.
I go over other
people's heads.
Michael, this is
a bad idea.
What's a bad idea?
Dressing up as somebody.
I mean, when has that
ever worked for you?
Never!
Okay, you know what, fine.
I'm not Darryl.
And thank God
Could you have for once
just let us enjoy a party,
instead of making it
about all your issues?
That's a warrior!
I present to you
the rational "consumer,"
as it were.
TODD: Slow, nice
and slow, honey.
PAM:
Angela as a nurse.
Don't... No,
slow it down.
CREED: There it is.
ANGELA:
I don't like your tone.
Look, they were sold out
of all the other costumes,
okay?
I think we all live
in the real world here.
Let's not pretend
to be unaware of what
sells in this office.
PHYLLIS:
What should we ask?
Hey, can I play?
Why don't you ask if
Darryl is a bad friend
who backstabs
people in the back?
We have one question
to ask the spirit world and
you want us to ask that?
He says no.
Uh, Darryl moved it.
You moved it.
No.
Hey, Dwight, you saw
Darryl move it, right?
Let's just say I saw exactly
what the two of you
wanted me to see.
I know how to
sit on a fence.
Hell, I can even
sleep on a fence.
The trick is to
do it face down with
the post in your mouth.
If you had one word
you would use
to describe Darryl,
what would
that word be?
ERIN: A...
S...
H... No!
Uh. E...
T.
An asset.
That's enough.
I don't think
it's gonna work out
the way you think.
I don't think
you get it.
Hey.
This is some party, huh?
When you work hard,
you play hard around here.
Even if you
don't work hard.
Oh, here's something.
Uh.
Why didn't you
ever call Pam back?
Serious?
Yeah. I mean, I'm not saying
that everybody has to
fall in love or anything.
I'm just saying,
but...
To, you know,
to not even
call her back is...
You know what it was?
I think she
gave me her number,
but then, her fours
look like eights and...
Could be.
But you also
called her the second time,
so you had the number right.
TODD: Halpert,
you looking for
someone to bang your wife?
No.
Okay.
You want to know?
I didn't call her back
because she spent
the whole date
talking about you.
She was obviously
in love with you.
Fifty-seven,
fifty-eight...
Wait, wait.
She hasn't moved in a while.
Erin!
Two! I got two!
I ate two whole apples!
I'd remember
talking about Jim.
That wasn't it.
Just tell her
the real reason.
Do you honestly wanna know
why I didn't call her back
on a date
over four years ago?
Hey, she had
a nice time.
It seems rude.
Well...
I did. Yeah,
and it's one
of those things
that's just gonna
keep gnawing at me.
Like, gnaw, gnaw...
"Why? Why didn't he?
I have no idea why."
Okay, honestly,
I didn't call you back
because I just thought
you seemed a little
dorky.
Hey, man...
Thank you!
Thank you. I got it.
Now I know.
You thought I was
a little dorky.
You know?
In the future, you need to get
Michael's approval on anything
before coming to me.
Thank you.
You're gonna miss out
on some good ideas.
Okay, well, obviously if it's
a really, really good idea,
then my door is open.
If they're good ideas,
I'm not gonna say, "No."
You said, "No"
to this one.
That's... Okay, I make
one mistake in 15 years
and you drag me
over the coals.
After everything
I did for you?
What have you
done for me?
Oh, well...
What have you
done for me?
Ed Truck hired me.
Jo promoted me.
Gabe listened to me.
All you've ever done
was say, "No" to me.
I have ambition,
and you kept me
at the same level
for years.
Dropping bombs, right?
This really make
you think, Michael?
Stop it. Stop. Stop.
We're thinking.
We're thinking about it.
GABE: Yeah.
You don't have to
point to the fact that
we're thinking about it.
Stop it.
Just let us think.
Okay, next time you
have a really great idea,
we will put it in a hat,
and then we will have Erin
pick it out of the hat
and let her decide.
I don't understand
the point of a hat.
You're right,
we don't need a hat.
I am not budging
on the hat issue.
Okay, we're gonna
table the hat question.
The best ideas are
gonna come to me.
I make the
final decision,
period.
Okay, we both reserve
the right to go to Jo
if we disagree with Gabe.
Okay.
DARRYL: Fair enough.
Why don't we simplify this?
Darryl brings it to Michael,
Michael brings it to me,
no one calls Jo.
Unless you and I
decide we wanna talk to Jo,
then we'll give her a call.
Cool.
Hey, sorry I left.
I'm sorry I was a jerk.
MICHAEL: Friends fight.
Friends fight.
What's up, man?
Sometimes it seems
like it was better
down in the warehouse,
you know?
When I was
a freshman in college,
I worked at
the student newspaper,
the Cornell Daily Sun.
This was at Cornell.
I had to write
an op-ed column every day,
"Bernard's Regards."
This was your
freshman year?
I started to ask myself,
do I have big plans here?
I didn't wanna become
editor of that paper, so
I got up
and walked right out
of Walter Bernard Hall,
and that's actually
when I heard
eight male voices
singing,
unencumbered
by instruments.
I was hooked.
So, is becoming
CEO of this company
your a cappella group?
Come on. We're going to
Danny's bar, Public School.
No, I got
some work to do.
I do have big plans
at this company.
ERIN: She...
It was fantastic.
Yeah.
It was like
a little gentle...
JIM: To be honest,
I still can't believe
he didn't call her back.
Who doesn't call
a dork like that back?
Oh! Wow!
Spinach in a can!
Power from spinach!
Ag, ag, ag, ag, ag, ag!
Oh, my hero!
PAM: Okay, everyone,
I've tallied the votes,
and the winner
of the Costume
Celebration Spectacular
and the Scranton-Wilkes-Barre
coupon book,
Oscar Martinez.
PHYLLIS: Who?
If I have to vote
for someone,
I don't want it
to be someone
who can beat me.
Shake things up.
I'm a Nader guy.
Best Edward James Olmos
costume I've ever seen.
Like, freaky good.