MICHAEL:
Kahlua sombrero, please.
All right.
So just you tonight?
Actually,
I'm meeting somebody,
but I'm a little bit early.
Leaving my company
after 19 years.
I'll drink to that.
I'm starting at
a company this week.
Oh, really?
To beginnings and endings.
And to middles.
The unsung heroes.
And to moms.
The moms of the troops.
Mmm.
Do not tell my fiancée
I'm drinking on a Wednesday.
I won't.
I don't know her.
Moving out to the 'burbs.
Actually, I'm moving
further than the 'burbs.
Moving to Colorado.
Colorado?
Yeah.
Sunshine State.
Yep.
Don't mess with Colorado.
No, don't.
Doing some skiing?
No, no.
I don't want to end up
like Sonny Bobo.
Well, that's just good
sense right there, yeah.
Everyone I know
who skis is dead.
You know what?
I would like to
try the luge, though.
Try it once, you're hooked.
That's my guess.
That's what I've heard.
I'm an Olympics nut.
Oh, yeah? Me, too.
Summer or winter?
Summer.
Knuckle. Actually,
I've got to come
around and give you...
Yeah, come on.
You know, it's funny.
I actually tried
to get an animal
Olympics going.
Really? What happened?
You know, life happened.
What are you gonna miss
most about Scranton?
Oh. Wow. The mountains,
where things are.
Mmm-hmm.
That's the way it goes.
Man, he is late.
I'm gonna call him.
Do you mind? I'm sorry.
No, no.
Where is this guy?
Excuse me.
Hello?
This is Michael Scott.
Yes, yes.
Hi.
You running late?
No, I'm here.
I'm at the bar.
I'm at the bar, too.
You are? What bar?
I'm at the bar,
the bar that's located
in the lobby of the hotel.
I do not see you.
How long have you...
I've been here about, gosh,
over half an hour.
Okay, yeah, me, too.
Sorry.
What are you wearing?
I'm wearing
a gray suit, red tie.
Are we both at
the right place?
Which place...
I hear your voice.
I hear your...
I see your lips moving.
I hear your voice
in the phone.
And that's... Man!
And...
Michael Scott.
Deangelo Vickers.
Wow.
That is insane.
"That is insane" is right.
That's the right term.
Bartender,
let's get some vodka
up in this cranberry
and one for my friend.
Here we go. Ready?
I am ready.
All right, here we go.
Well, this is it.
What do you think?
She'll do.
Oh, she'll do just fine.
I am very much
looking forward
to tomorrow. It is...
It feels like
the culmination of
a lot of hard work,
a lot of good fortune and...
We should write
a movie or something.
I'm serious.
Michael is leaving.
And apparently
they already hired
a new manager.
And we're meeting him today.
It's a lot to process.
Paperwork-wise.
Nope, it's not Ashton Kutcher.
It's Kevin Malone.
Equally handsome,
equally smart.
Okay, everyone,
as you know,
one of my favorite things
is fanfare for its own sake.
So without further ado,
let's all start clapping.
Presenting Deangelo Vickers!
Hi. Hello.
MICHAEL: Come on out!
Hello. Hey.
How are you, sir?
I'm well, sir,
how are you?
Uh, can I just say
I am so excited
to be working here.
Little bit about myself,
I love the American southwest,
for starters.
You may call them
Arizona, New Mexico,
Nevada, Utah.
I call them heaven.
I have a peanut allergy,
something I live with.
It's a part of me.
I've learned to cope
with it. What else?
I'm just as
comfortable at a ball game
as I am at the opera.
I was a...
Did I want to be
made manager? Sure.
A great opportunity
squandered? Absolutely.
A crushing blow? Yes.
Will I get over it?
Mmm...
No.
But life goes on.
Not for me.
I'll get that,
you guys. Don't...
No, I'll help you. Here.
You know, it's just...
You know...
Hi.
Hello. Hi.
Have we met before?
No, not officially.
I saw you coming out
of the bathroom earlier.
Well, I guess I'm gonna
go back to my cave.
Okay.
It was really
great meeting you.
And that is what
they call a meet cute.
So we talked for
like 20 minutes,
no clue it's Deangelo
the whole time.
It's kind of embarrassing.
No, no.
Yeah, that story
makes you sound stupid.
I happen to like
the hilarious high jinks
that I get myself into.
There he is, there he is.
Deangelo, I was just
telling them about last night
when we met.
Remember that?
That was crazy.
Let's see,
where's my replacement?
Where's the guy
I'm replacing?
I don't know.
Why don't I look
to my left?
I know.
He's sitting right there.
Well, that's what I was
just saying. That's...
That exact situation
is why I always carry
around a couple of these.
Just in case,
'cause, you know,
sometimes you need
to ID yourself.
Office funny guy.
Always glad to have
an office funny guy around.
ANDY: I wasn't even
trying to make a joke.
I guess I've always
been sort of quirky,
offbeat, a little twisted.
This is Jim and Pam,
a.k.a. Jap.
What started as an affair
has blossomed into
a family before our eyes.
Well, it wasn't...
It wasn't an affair.
Yes, it was.
But, no,
but we are a family.
We made that.
Cecelia.
DEANGELO: Oh!
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I have four kids
of my own.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, my gosh,
well, we just have the one,
but she poops for four.
Uh-oh.
Someone started off
on a good foot
with the new boss.
Yeah, they don't
ever talk about careers
that were made
because of unplanned
pregnancies. So...
Psst. Thanks for
meeting me.
Are you kidding?
I would come anywhere
to see a turtle.
Yeah.
Where'd you find him?
There's no turtle, Michael.
I just wanted to get
you here.
You know me
very well, Dwight.
That's because I'm your
right-hand man, Michael.
But I can't do it.
I can't do it again.
I can't be a right-hand man
to a whole new guy.
Now, I'm gonna
have to go online
and look at turtles
or else I'm gonna
be off the whole day.
I want to be manager.
I just don't understand
why I wasn't even
interviewed for the job.
I mean, what's wrong?
I'm totally qualified.
You were pushing for me.
That apple looks delish.
I do a lot of
portion control.
Try to keep my daily
caloric intake
under 1,200.
Deangelo, you're going
to starve to death.
So you decided
to have an orgy
and not invite me?
Come on. I call middle.
That's cool that you
like the southwest.
It's one of my
favorite regions.
"It's one of my
favorite regions."
Did I just sound
totally lame?
Oh.
I sounded good.
I love the desert.
It's one of my
favorite ecosystems.
Here's the great thing
about the southwest,
there is so much
more than desert.
Along the north rim
of the Grand Canyon
is a forest as lush
as you've ever seen.
Burned. It's lush, dummy.
Hey, Deangelo,
what do you think
about bald people?
I hate them.
Deangelo, I forget,
did you mention
you like politics?
I did not.
Because I was thinking,
you should meet my boyfriend.
He's a state senator.
I really think the two
of you would hit it off.
He's a great person to know.
Sounds very interesting,
thank you.
ANGELA: Mmm-hmm.
Dunder Mifflin. This is Erin.
Okay, let me transfer you.
Why do you use your name
when you answer the phone?
Oh, that's how Pam does it.
I just copy her.
She's sort of
a living legend.
Try it without
using your name.
Dunder Mifflin. This is.
Oh, yeah, I like it.
Dunder Mifflin.
How may I assist you?
Oh. "Assist."
I sort of like
the old way.
I just prefer it
without the name.
And I thought...
Okay. No, no, no.
I've got to start doing
some managing at
some point, right?
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
But if it's not a big deal,
we should just
do the old way.
And it really isn't.
Okay. That good?
ERIN: Yeah, okay, good.
Well, I'd like to
change it, actually.
MICHAEL: Well,
you know, whatever...
Yeah.
Whatever you think
would work.
What do you...
Yeah.
I think a change
would be nice.
You could do the old
way or the, you know...
Whichever one you want to do.
Mmm-hmm.
DEANGELO:
Change it.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, funny guy.
I have a little
midday lull here.
Make me laugh. Huh?
What do you got?
I can't even look
at you.
Here we go.
Okay...
What do
African Americans
call the...
What?
ERIN: Deangelo?
Yeah?
Did you order a barber?
Oh. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on back here.
Put a pin on that, okay?
I can't wait to hear
the punch line.
Finish the joke, Andy.
What do
African Americans call?
I don't know. Help me.
That is so bad-ass.
Just so hardcore.
Yeah, very cool.
Real power move.
Yeah.
I saw a hawk today.
It was just
sitting right there
on the overpass,
looking at me.
Shave me.
Well, this is going
to be funny.
Because it looks like
we're gonna be
shaving buddies.
Okay, all right.
I love it. I love it.
Michael, this is Reggie.
Hello.
He is the number one
Yelp-reviewed
shaver in Scranton.
It's not even close.
And this is Erin,
and she's going
to shave my face.
Here we go.
All right.
This is how we do it.
MICHAEL: Mmm.
Feels nice, doesn't it?
It really does.
This is luxury.
Here we go.
Okay.
Oh, that is nice.
You wanted to
talk to us, Deangelo?
Oh, yes, yes, please.
Cozy up there.
I just thought we could
have some rap sessions
with smaller groups.
You know, we don't
really do rap sessions,
we kind of do... God!
We sort of do
more of like powwows
and what-ups.
Okay, well,
powwows, then. Fine.
That's...
Hey, Deangelo,
my mom just sent me
this picture of Cece.
It is so adorable.
All right, wait,
but a little bit
of back story.
She loves dogs,
she calls them dadas...
Dadas.
...and what happens is...
You know what?
Enough about
your baby, okay?
I'm sorry.
Well, we were just...
I think she was
just trying to...
No, no, no,
I know what you're doing.
Just quit it.
I want to hear from
the rank and file.
How can I be
the best manager
for you all?
You know,
what can I do better?
Okay, you know
what, everybody?
There's... You have
to be honest here.
You can't say that everything
is perfect, right?
So, you know,
come up with something.
OSCAR: Well, Deangelo,
I'd say communication
could be improved.
People stopped
reading memos.
So everyone
marks them urgent.
Okay, you know what?
I mark it urgent "A,"
urgent "B,"
urgent "C," urgent "D."
Urgent "A" is
the most important,
urgent "D" you don't even
really have to worry about.
Okay, Michael,
can you stop talking now?
I have to do your lips.
Don't shave my lips.
What's up?
I don't mean to go off
on a rant here, but...
I wrote the perfect joke.
Topical, edgy, funny.
I saw this thing in the news.
Democrats want electric cars.
Republicans don't.
Right.
I'm thinking,
how crazy is it
that we got
a car debate going on
in a city known for gridlock.
Um... Let's not talk politics
in the office, okay?
I like you better
as the funny guy.
I wasn't taking a position.
It was just sort of
one of those things.
Now that's funny.
That's funny.
You walk much?
Yeah, right? I mean...
A little click.
Mmm-hmm.
Deangelo, this box
came for you.
Great, thank you.
That's my stuff. Yeah.
Michael, take a look
at this.
Need a hand?
Oh, that'd be great.
Thank you.
Hey, you know what?
This office sort of
has a perfect
fung shooey to it, and...
You know,
let's not go overboard
with the redecorating.
And I'm
still here, so...
Wow.
Right?
Ooh.
That's nice.
I still have to look
at this stuff, guys, so...
Oh, man. So this is
a 10-gallon hat?
Yeah, you like that?
10-gallon hat.
Technically, it only
holds about 3 quarts.
A little factoid.
Interesting.
MICHAEL: Deangelo's great.
I love the guy.
But I'm not sure
he's a good fit
for the office.
And also, I'm not sure
if I love the guy.
Cool, cool.
All right,
see you later, girl.
Hey, hey, hey.
No, I'm good. Keep that.
Hey, funny man.
What you got for me?
Make me laugh.
Let's see if
my favorite tea is in...
Whoa! Jeez.
That's hot coffee.
Drink some soap.
Eat some hand soap.
I guess this is my life now.
How do I become
a manager at Sabre?
Well, first things first,
thank you for coming
to me directly, you know.
I know you could
have called Tallahassee,
but it would have
just looped back to me.
So it's cool you
recognized my role here.
I left a message
at corporate.
There you go.
Get a recommendation
from Michael.
That'll put you
right on the short list
for next time
there's an opening.
Can't you just use
the recommendation
you already have on file?
What recommendation?
From when
he recommended me
to replace him.
Um...
I'm sorry.
I never know how to act
in these awkward
type situations.
Best whale watching?
Easily the West Coast.
If you're gonna
go whale watching
on the East Coast,
you might want to
bring a magazine called
West Coast Whales.
Snack time!
It's the witching hour.
It is the sandwiching hour.
Awesome.
PHYLLIS: Hmm. What you got?
PB and J. My mom's recipe.
Michael, Deangelo
has a peanut allergy.
Okay, I need a wide berth.
I need a wide berth
from those nuts.
What are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
I think Kevin wants one.
Kevin, here you go.
OSCAR: Michael,
this is serious.
Do you know what happens
if Deangelo touches a peanut?
What?
Michael, the last time
I was exposed to a peanut,
I was itchy for
three days, okay?
I had to take
baths constantly.
I missed the O.J. verdict.
Had to read about it in
the paper like an idiot.
Wait, so you
don't go into, like,
shock or die or anything?
No, Jim. Not
everything's life and death.
I want to feel comfortable.
Oscar, here you go.
Oh! Whoa!
You're getting nut
particles all in the air.
No one had
a problem with the air here
until you came around.
Everyone, mandatory meeting.
Multi-purpose room, now.
No, that's good.
You just stay in there.
Except for Michael.
Stay in there
by yourself, loser.
Nobody go in.
Nobody go in there.
Why?
Stay where you are.
Michael, this is insane.
No, it's not
insane, Oscar.
I've been here
for 19 years,
and just because
someone else is
called the boss,
you're gonna throw
it all away? No, no.
Listen, you're the one
who decided to leave.
Come on, he's our new boss.
You know we have to do this.
Okay.
Well, who needs them?
Looks like it's just
you and me, Dwight.
Correction.
Just you.
All right. Meeting,
multi-function room.
DEANGELO: Apology accepted.
Hold on.
Hey, Michael.
Michael, wait up,
hold up. Hold up.
Um...
So, for these meetings,
do you just jump
into business
or do you start
with some chitchat or...
I start with some chitchat
and maybe a couple of jokes.
And you might
want to develop
a couple of characters.
You know what?
You just...
You'll be fine.
Maybe, maybe not. 50-50.
You know,
it is too bad for this place
that you're leaving.
Bring it in. Come on.
Bring it.
Okay. Okay.
Why did you have
to be so damn good?
I... I'm adequate.
I'm half as good as you.
No, no, no.
Come on.
You are good.
They know it.
Come on.
I just didn't expect you
to get there so fast.
DEANGELO: Would you do me
a favor and enjoy this time,
okay? You've worked so hard.
Get your senioritis on.
It's Lake Havasu time.
I guess I've been
working so hard
I forgot what it's like
to be hardly working.
Okay.
What is the Native
American girl's name?
You'll figure it out.
DEANGELO:
Thank you, Dwight.
DWIGHT: Thank you, sir.
DEANGELO: Listen up...
Hey, Deangelo.
Want to meet Cece?
That's a cute baby.
Very cute baby.
Adorable. Very cute.
Thank you very much.
See? We knew it.
If he just met her,
he'd understand.
We're back in.
Ha.
Right?
I'm telling you, that baby
could be the star of a show
called Babies I
Don't Care About.