Sorry, mate.
Excuse me, mate.
What are you...
What are you doing?
English?
If you're taking the
mickey, you picked
on the wrong person.
Let me tell you that.
No, I'm not picking
on you at all.
You're English, correct?
Yeah, big time, yeah.
I'm working on
an English character.
Would you mind...
It's called
Reginald Poofter.
Oh.
David Brent,
my liege.
How are you?
Michael Scott.
Oh, bloody hell.
I do characters as well.
I got a Chinese fella.
Not politically correct,
but he's called Holy...
That's what it
sounds like.
"Herro! Herro!"
I do Ping.
"Herro. I'm Ping."
You can't do
that these days.
You can't.
I'm Ping! No.
No, no. And people
don't understand
that it has nothing to
do with making fun of
a different nationality.
No, no, no.
No, comedy is a place
where the mind goes
to tickle itself.
That's what she
said.
That's good.
Pleasure to meet you.
Where are you working?
Dunder Mifflin.
Any jobs going?
No, not right now.
Just let me know.
All right.
See you around.
Bye, bye.
What a nice guy.
Your first student is
here, Mr. Bernard.
That's actually
"Master of Ceremonies"
Bernard.
Last year,
I went to a seminar
called "The 10 Secrets
of Real Estate."
Turns out it was
just a ploy to sell me
timeshares in Idaho.
Cut to, you know,
I'm spending a
weekend in Boise,
terrible time,
super lonely.
But I get to thinking,
maybe I should put
on my own seminar
to lure clients.
Oh.
Hello, I am here
for the small
business seminar.
Michael?
Nein, I'm Greek!
My name is Mykonos.
Ooh.
Oh.
Wait, Michael?
Michael?
Okay.
I am the plant.
Every great seminar has one.
My job is to make
the speaker look good,
and I do this
through the techniques
of leading questions
and laughing at all jokes.
And the character, Mykonos,
is just a little added flavor.
Mykonos is loosely
based on another
character I do, Spiros,
who is more about the ladies.
Thank you so much,
Tuna Turner.
You are simply
the best.
Listen,
this isn't a favor,
all right?
This is a good idea.
We all win.
Go higher.
All right.
I get super flexible
when I'm nervous.
Wow.
Stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop.
Hey, Andy,
I'm really, really
sorry to do this to you,
but I have
a meeting today
that I totally forgot,
so I can't be a part
of this seminar.
No! What?
You can't do that.
You are a critical
part of this seminar.
You're the charming
warm-up guy.
I know.
If the seminar was
a meal, you'd be
the amuse-bouche.
You signal the flavors
of the whole night.
I'm really sorry.
I can't do it.
You can't. You can't.
I can't have
this go badly.
I'm a terrible salesman,
and I haven't been
making very many
sales lately, or ever.
This is my only
idea on how to
turn things around.
If it goes badly,
I might lose my job,
which would suck,
because this is the only
job I've ever been good at.
Will you let me
know when this whole
seminar thing's over?
What's going on?
Do you know that guy?
I just have a meeting,
outside the office.
Hey.
How are the marks?
What are some of your
small business ideas?
I was thinking we could
buy up a bunch of
abandoned mineshafts.
ALL:
That's great.
There's a big,
big future in that.
WOMAN: A lot of mines
in Scranton.
DWIGHT: Um,
what about you?
Uh, credit cards.
Uh-huh.
My company will act
as an inter-medium
for, like, 0.2 cents
off every transaction.
Wow!
Or something
with cell phones,
like, every time you
make a phone call,
I'd make 0.2 cents.
Or anything. Like,
any online shopping,
I get 0.2 cents basically.
Right. Okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
You promised us whales.
These are worms.
They're not worms,
Dwight, okay?
They're just people
with tiny businesses.
They're baby whales,
which is even cuter.
I'm out.
Stanley, you're
supposed to close.
I'm out, too.
What?
I already lost Jim.
Salesmen are supposed
to help each other out.
We're supposed to be a team.
We're no more a team
than the people
staying in the same
hotel are a team.
You know what
might be kind of fun?
I was thinking,
you know, Andy's having
a seminar today?
What if we went in
as a Greek couple?
Mykonos and...
Oh, I don't
know, Michael.
I'm not feeling
up to that.
Okay.
MICHAEL: Holly broke
up with A. J. last week,
which is the greatest
thing that has ever
happened to me.
To Holly, it's been the
worst week of her life,
and I know for a fact
that there was a week
for her in High School
when she got mono
and her first period ever.
Too much information?
That's what I thought.
But you know what?
Here I am using it.
If you change your
mind, why don't you
talk to Mykonos?
Is Mykonos Greek?
He sounds Italian.
Ugh. You're the fifth person
to tell me that today.
Maybe Mykonos ran away
to join the Italian circus.
Okay, yeah, like
a character history.
Good. Tom Hanks does that.
Yeah.
Is "JLP" a word?
"Jelp?" J-E-L-P?
No, J-L-P.
Like, "I Jlp...
I Jlp you!"
I don't think
that's a word.
I'm playing
scrabble with Gabe,
and I've never
won a game.
The winner gets to pick
the movie we watch.
I have won no games.
So far I've seen
The Shining,
Rosemary's Baby,
The Ring.
Not really my thing.
Although, I...
I do like the early
parts of the movies
where they have
a perfect family
and everything.
You want some help?
Really?
Mmm-hmm.
Yes.
K-A. "Ka?"
What does "ka" mean?
It means you're
playing someone who's
going to destroy you.
Why did you play "moo?"
Because I'm
playing to win.
I'm playing "moo,"
I'm playing "milk,"
whatever it takes.
Okay, but look,
you could have
hit "mood."
Would have played
a... A triple word.
Ah.
Like the cow
mood yesterday.
God.
Or moon.
The cow jumped
over the moon.
She's stuck on
that one thing.
You know it doesn't
have to just be cow
stuff, right?
Kevin, Jim dropped
out of my seminar,
and I'm just...
I was wondering if you
could replace him as
my charming warm-up guy.
Andy, I'm no Jim. I'm...
The only way
that I'm Jim is in
the movie version
when Jim sees what
his future would be like
if he never met Pam.
Hey, that's crazy talk.
I think you're great.
Then I won't let you down.
Pink.
Indigo.
Hi, Ryan, you
went to business
school, right?
Yeah.
I need somebody
to talk to this
seminar about business.
And?
Okay.
I don't...
I don't like committing
to things just like that.
So, no?
No, I don't like
committing to not
doing things, either.
That's just as big
a commitment.
Oh, baby.
What do I put you
down for, bro hombre?
Yes.
All right!
Yes, I'll do it.
Okay, thank you so much.
It's gonna be awesome.
And if I flake,
I flake.
What?
Kevin, you
open it up.
Yep.
Ryan, you come in
with your small biz
expertise, right?
And then Creed,
guest speaker
extraordinaire.
And then I come in
and just close all
the sales and stuff.
Okay, here we go.
One, two, three!
Team!
Creed!
Welcome everybody.
Awesome to see you guys.
My name's Andy Bernard,
but you can call me
"The Nard Dog."
Hi, Nard Dog.
I'm Lu Peachem.
Let's get things
started, shall we?
You guys ready to hear
from the Dunder Mifflin
business experts?
Good. Well, as you can
see on your program,
first up is a speech called,
"Don't just dream it, do it."
Yes! Please give
a big hand to
Mr. Kevin Malone.
Four, five.
Yes!
There are some people
who have charm
and some people
who don't.
Guess which type I am.
Charm type.
Dream big. Right?
So, what I
want you to do
And then double it!
Are you okay?
No. Yes!
Here.
Mmm-hmm.
I'm fine.
Okay, from here now.
The first lesson that
I'm gonna teach you,
right, is about
finding success.
And the key to
finding success is
to picture a winner.
Okay, so then,
what are you
picturing right now,
right this second?
'Cause the universe
is yours, people.
Get out of the way.
I'm really excited
to introduce you guys
to Ryan Howard.
He has achieved a
great deal in the last...
But perhaps no
achievement is greater
than his on-again,
off-again girlfriend.
What are you...
Who am I?
I'm Kelly Kapoor,
the business bitch.
It is important
to brand yourself,
so I have a couple
of things in the works.
The business bitch,
the diet bitch,
the shopping bitch,
the etiquette bitch.
I could sit here,
and I could tell you the
10 secrets of business,
and you would
have a great time,
learn a lot.
But who better
to tell you
than the Yale University
adjunct professor
in management,
Professor Scott Powell,
who I have on my BlackBerry.
MAN: Hey, Kelly Kapoor.
What a delicious surprise.
Uh, why?
Do you think you
could tell us the 10
secrets of business?
Um, there aren't
really 10 secrets.
Come on, Scott,
please. It's me.
Uh, all right. Well,
Uh,
I guess know your
market would be key.
Practice fiscal discipline.
That brilliant little bitch.
A little treat for
our old friend, Gabe.
Put that "Q"
right there.
Wait. Why?
Put the "Q"
there, sweetie.
I think
there's better...
Put the "Q" there!
Sorry I yelled.
You could have
just told us what
you were thinking.
There's no theater
in that.
There's no yelling
in that, either.
Well...
What do you do
in your free time?
Practice Olympics.
Do you like movies?
I like the
musical Grease,
or as we call
it, "home."
We have to try this
out on somebody.
Hello.
Look, you want
to order something?
She will have
a greekaccino.
I don't know
what that is.
It...
It's a very strong
coffee with milk
from a goat.
I can't
believe it.
It's a miracle.
She can talk.
No more brain damage.
No more brain damage!
I don't know.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our special guest
speaker will provoke you.
He will inspire you.
He is...
Creed Bratton.
Two eyes, two ears,
a chin, a mouth,
ten fingers,
two nipples,
a butt, two kneecaps,
a penis.
I have just
described to you the
Loch Ness monster.
And the reward
for its capture?
All the riches
in Scotland.
So I have one question,
why are you here?
Okay! All right,
ladies and gentlemen,
it is now time for
the rarest of things,
an actual free lunch.
There's sandwiches
in the back.
Certainly help yourselves.
We'll meet back
up in an hour.
I picked out our movie.
It's called Suspiria.
It pushes all
the boundaries.
All your preconceived
notions about what horror
can be, come crashing down.
When I win,
we're gonna
watch Wall-E,
where all the boundaries
of color are pushed.
GABE: It is hard to
explain why Erin is
doing so well today.
The only thing I can
think is Erin is living out
some Slumdog Millionaire
scenario,
where every word she's
playing has a connection
to her orphan past.
It's possible.
So what's your crazy
business pipe dream?
Well, I started my own
golf supply company.
Really?
It's taken off faster
than I expected,
so I came here
to learn about creating
manageable growth.
Phyllis?
Some of these
people are for real.
Hey, friend.
How's it going?
Oh, you know what?
Let me steep
that for you.
Thank you.
Hey, you
know what?
Good news.
We're back in.
Let's go sell some
paper, buddy. Huh?
Really?
Excuse me.
I got it. I got it.
Hey, do you
need a lozenge?
They're a bunch
of jackals.
What?
They left you
in the lurch,
and if they want
to jump in, it means
you're almost there.
You did this.
Bring it home.
Let me tell you what
you can do with
your offer to help.
You can table it
and offer it up
another time.
Just know that
I really appreciate
the gesture.
Hi. Hope you
enjoyed your lunch.
Welcome back.
Ooh, well, hello.
Welcome to the seminar.
Hey, man.
What's going on?
Maybe.
Only maybe.
We got it.
Wow, we got it.
Oscar, wait. I think
the victory would
be more meaningful
if Erin puts the
last word in herself.
Yes, Pam.
Yes, most definitely.
Yes.
No.
Although I must say,
I will have apoplexy
if you lose.
Do you understand?
Apoplexy is what
I will have.
Apoplexy.
Yes.
Got it.
Oh, Oscar.
Oscar?
I played "ape."
I just want to make
a point to that last
caller. I disagree.
I don't think it is the
running game at all.
I think we do have
to make a few moves
in this off-season.
Wow!
What a day, right?
Guess you guys are
probably ready to go.
And you got my
business card, so...
You know,
I like you.
I'm going to give you
my secret gyro recipe.
Come out here,
since it's a secret,
and I'll tell you.
All right, you have
to close right now.
Yeah, I'm getting to it.
No, you're not.
You're getting past it.
You have to close.
Do it. You can do it.
Yeah, yeah.
Andy, what's
the problem?
This is hard
for me. I'm a nice guy.
You know, Kelly
and Creed, Kevin,
they believe in you.
Don't let them down.
Don't let yourself
down, Andy.
I'm gonna go back in.
I'm going to stall
them for a little bit.
I want you to get
your head together,
and then come back in.
I want you to close.
MICHAEL: What is taking that
guy so long?
Psst!
You think
this thing's gonna
go much longer?
I don't know.
They're still in there.
Goodbye.
Stop.
Out with it.
Here's the story.
Tom Witashkin.
One of my best
buddies, actually.
And when they
were both in
the third grade,
Jim was placed in the
top reading group.
JIM: I was blue group,
so I was second from the top.
PAM: And Tom...
Was in green group.
And Jim's
mom suggested
that Jim spend time
hanging with the kids
in his reading group,
because she thought
that they would be
a good influence.
And that's what
I told him.
Right.
But how'd
you say it?
"My mom thinks
you're too dumb
to hang out with."
Okay, who would
like to purchase
this small business
package from me right now?
Yes, we got one.
Okay, the snowball is rolling.
Who else?
You can put it off
for a couple of days,
but I guarantee you,
eventually you're gonna
realize you need this.
So the only thing that's
gonna be different
is you'll be a couple
of days behind
where you would be
if you bought this
from me right now.
So who's gonna
buy one right now?
I'll take one.
Yes! Awesome!
All right, anyone else?
Sold! Anybody else?
Yes! All right!
Yeah, bitch.
ANDY: Good choice.
The rest of you
are dead to me.
You made the stupidest
decisions of your life.
No, no, no.
But it was a pleasure
meeting you,
and you've got my information,
so feel free to call anytime.
Hey, you think it's coo I
if I grab a soda?
Yeah.
Yep, absolutely,
go ahead.
Hey.
How's it going?
Pretty good. Good.
It's been a while.
It has been, yeah.
So you work here, huh?
Sales.
Must be a front
for some kind of
famous laboratory.
'Cause you're so smart.
Oh, man. You remember
that, huh?
Barely. I'm so dumb,
you know,
stuff goes in,
stuff goes out.
Not like you probably
remember every paper
sale you ever made.
Paper salesman genius.
All right, good catch-up.
Yeah.
See you.
Where's your jetpack,
Zuckerberg?
Andy.
I didn't think
you had it in you.
Well, I guess when
you looked in me,
you forgot about my balls.
They're on the outside.
Don't know how
you missed 'em.
Wonderful seminar!
Almost as good
as the day when
we first met.
You are the
love of my life.
Come to me, Necropolis.
Put your lips on
my lips. Come on.
Michael, I should
get back to work.
What? Come on.
It's time for grapes.
That was a fun day.
So, I won.
I know.
You get to pick.
Well, that's actually
what I came to talk
to you about.
I know how much you
want to watch Wall-E.
Yes?
So I got us
a compromise.
This movie is
called Hardware,
it tells the story of
a killer combat robot,
just like Wall-E,
that the government
invented to
destroy humans.
It's some of what
you like and some
of what I like. And...
Erin, I heard you talking
about movies before and...
Anyway, I just watched
this over the weekend.
I thought you'd
really like it.
There's a Shrek 2?
Oh, yeah.
See you tomorrow.
Nice guy.
Ooh.