We could get
Deangelo flowers.
No, you can't get
flowers for someone
who's in a coma.
They'll wilt
before he wakes up.
Yeah,
that's true.
Good point.
All in favor of the baskets
full of chocolates,
teddy bears and balloons.
Wait, wait.
All in favor
of the knapsack
filled with
canned goods,
chainsaw,
gasoline and emergency
radio in case he
wakes up post-apocalypse.
Nope. Baskets have it.
So as it turns out,
unless you're
a young child,
or a prison inmate,
you don't need
anyone supervising you.
People just come in
and do their work
on their schedule.
Imagine that.
People like us
allowed to sell paper.
Unsupervised.
And yet,
somehow it works.
Must be because
the stakes are so high.
Well, I really
appreciate the offer,
but I'm just happy
the way things are.
Okay. Thank you.
That was Jo asking me
if I wanted to take
over as acting manager
while they find
a replacement.
I told her I don't
wanna mess this up, right?
There's a consensus.
People are happy.
Dwight Schrute.
Yes, I would.
DWIGHT: Thank you.
Jordan, gather my
things from my desk.
Wait.
What have you done?
Mose?
You'll never guess
where I am right now.
Can't stay
there all day.
I'm coming.
Do I at least
get to go with you
in this fantasy?
You'd slow me down.
Dwight has been
acting manager for
three months now.
No, a week.
Just feels like
three months.
Let's see.
We all have to punch
into a time clock,
which is very old,
very strong,
and has the slot about
the size of a finger.
We were all given
new business cards,
big enough to
set us apart from
the competition.
Which is how I learned
that our titles are all
now junior employee.
Our lunch breaks
are staggered to
prevent wasting time.
Mine's at 10:30
and I find that
the first hour
of the day goes
by a lot quicker
than the
second seven hours.
Stop stalling!
Come on.
ALL: I pledge allegiance
to the Flag of the
United States of America
and to the Republic
for which it stands,
one nation under God,
indivisible,
with liberty and
justice for all.
...justice for all.
Amen.
DWIGHT: Excellent.
Morning announcements.
There's been a problem
with some people
sharing copier codes.
Your copier code is a
distinct 21-digit number
that is unique to you
and you only, okay?
Don't share it.
Jo Bennett,
our CEO, will be here today
for a high-level meeting
involving Gabe
and myself.
Ooh! About what?
That's on
a need-to-know basis.
I thought I needed to
know for your calendar.
General meet
and greet.
So I expect you to be
on your best behavior,
which means
none of you will
be insubordinate,
nor will you
foment insurrection.
Question.
If we've already
fomented insurrection,
may we be
grandfathered in?
Define "foment."
You define "foment."
DWIGHT: Please take
note of the new
color-coding system.
Ah-ha!
Oh, my God!
What is wrong with you?
Got you!
Why are you late?
It's none of your business,
actually.
It's very
medical and personal.
All right.
You stop me
when I reach
the diseased area.
In fairness, Darryl did
tell me that joke, so...
ANDY: I know, right?
Hey, Andy?
Yeah?
Can I talk to
you a second
about these client memos?
Sure.
ANDY: What's going on?
Are you still in
love with Erin?
What?
Because I am.
Andy, do you
like being alone
with me right now?
No, this is horrifying.
GABE: No,
I don't like
being alone with
me, either. Okay?
I have to get
Erin back.
Are you still
gonna date her?
We're just
friends, okay?
Do you promise that?
Yeah, fine, I promise.
We'll never date again.
Can we go
outside now?
No, just give
me a second.
I don't want
anyone to know
I've been crying.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What do you
think you're doing?
What's this?
What's The Fist?
It's just a
social club.
Like the French
Revolution or The Black
Panthers or communism.
It's just a club.
Guys talking.
You expect me to believe
that you're
starting a rebellion?
Nope, social club.
God, I hate
when everybody
calls us a rebellion.
Okay, you know
what? I would love
to join The Fist.
And we would love to
have you, but not today.
Unfortunately, it's a bad day,
what with
Operation Overthrow
and everything.
But I have noted it.
One.
Pam, I have to
show you this video.
You're gonna love it.
It's Beyonce falling
with a fart mixed in.
I will never be
happier than I am right now.
I will also
never be less happy.
I will be at my
current maximum happiness
for the rest of my life.
Because I am manager
of the Scranton
branch of Dunder Mifflin.
Acting manager.
No food now?
Someone has to do
something about Dwight.
He put some snacks
in the freezer for us.
You mean the frozen
mice for the piranha?
No, the blueberry
slurpy pouch.
Hmm.
He means the ice pack.
2:00 should
probably be okay.
I can either take
your number or...
I'm sorry,
this can't wait.
He's just
gonna call back.
Erin, I am in
love with you.
I don't believe
in much, okay?
in horoscopes. I don't
believe in Christmas.
I sure as hell
don't believe in God.
What?
Or maybe there's
a God, I don't know.
It's just not a guy
with a long, white beard.
Or it could be.
It's possible that that
is exactly what God is.
But for all of the disbelief,
I believe in us.
I believe in love.
You have made me believe
that for all of the hokum
out there...
Do we not
have voicemail?
Dwight doesn't trust
robots to give
us our messages.
Well,
it just...
It messes up
my rhythm, but...
I'm taking a break
from dating.
Gabe was a great guy
with so many
wonderful qualities,
but it was a challenge
being touched by him.
Wow, you've really
embraced the whole
Bond villain aesthetic.
Jim, Jim, Jim.
The gun is
a Beaumont Adams.
Jo collects them.
I thought we could have
some nice small talk about it.
And the piranha's
a rescue.
And the desk.
The desk is a replica
of Uday Hussein's desk.
I saw a picture in Newsweek.
Listen, I'm a very busy man,
let's get right
down to business.
Okay.
Jo is coming
later today.
I cannot have a
subordinate trying to
make me look stupid.
Okay? I need you to promise
me that you'll be on
your best behavior.
I promised other
people that I'd be
on my worst behavior.
And I gave them
my word, so...
Don't make
me fire you.
You can't fire me.
You're acting manager,
not office manager,
so you have
no firing powers.
Don't make me
pre-fire you.
You wouldn't dare.
Watch this.
You're pre-fired.
And when I'm promoted,
you'll be full-fired.
If you get promoted.
And if you haven't
fallen in love
with me by then.
What?
If I had thought that
there was a real chance
that Dwight would
be permanent manager,
I would have
pre-quit.
And you might be
saying to yourself,
"Well, that's pretty
premature to think."
But I always say,
"It's better to be
pre-pre-pre-prepared."
How you
doing, Jordan?
I'm good.
Everyone here thinks
that you're a joke.
They think that
you were hired because
of your good looks,
which won't
last long anyway.
As your pale skin
and severe bone
structure imply,
you'll age
swiftly and poorly.
Why are you
telling me this?
Now I want you
to find out what people
are saying about me.
Things they don't
want me to know about.
It's a holster.
Yep. Yep, yep, yep.
Looking good.
What a day.
Dwight, are you
carrying a gun?
The holster was a gift
from my great-uncle, Honk.
I don't know.
I guess he's saying
that he's proud of me.
Dwight, guns make me
really uncomfortable.
The gun is just
an accessory to
the holster, okay?
I can't walk
around wearing
an empty holster.
Why do you need to
wear the holster at all?
Why do you need
to keep wearing
those booby
shirts all the time?
Thank you.
You could put your
cell phone in it instead.
Hello.
You could put
a banana in it.
Why would I put
a banana in my holster?
In case you
weren't hungry now,
but you got hungry later.
Dwight, no gun, okay?
Don't make us call Jo.
Okay, all right, fine.
Everyone calm down.
Someone, get
me a banana.
Sorry I freaked
you guys out.
Andy!
Ow! God!
It's so loud!
My God.
There is a hardwood floor
underneath this carpeting.
Why would
they do that?
There's like this
crazy ringing going on.
I can't...
I can't find perfect C.
Okay, everyone make
a list of what's lost
for the insurance.
I lost a necklace,
a ring, a painting.
Hey, what happened?
Dwight went on
a shooting spree
and then he shot
Andy in the head.
No, no, no. All we
know is that a gun fired.
That's all we know.
No, that's not
true. Actually, we
heard a loud noise,
later a hole was seen.
No one saw the bullet
leave the gun.
Something's
definitely wrong.
I'll look on WebMD.
What are your symptoms?
Everybody,
Oscar found a reason
to look on WebMD.
Firewall.
I can't reach Jo.
She must already
be on the plane.
Okay, why are
you calling Jo?
I think I should
go to the hospital.
I'll go with you.
GABE:  No!
We really shouldn't be
without a receptionist.
Now more than ever.
DARRYL: I'll take him.
Thank you, Darryl.
What's wrong
with you?
It's my ear.
Yeah.
I should get
the accident report binder.
I've never used
the gun violence
forms before.
GABE: I'm gonna
keep trying Jo.
Okay, everyone,
conference room!
Right now!
Yee-haw!
Woo-hoo!
Howdy, partners.
It's me, Gun
Safety Dwight.
And I'm the
rootin'-est...
Look, obviously
a gun went off
under my watch
and I'm launching
a full investigation.
We all saw you do it.
Really? You did?
What hand was I holding
the gun in? What did
Andy's tie look like?
Navy blue,
little red anchors.
I have no way of
knowing if that's true.
I am supposed to collect
eyewitness accounts.
Who saw Dwight do this?
DWIGHT:
Okay, really?
Would you consider this
a terrorist incident?
I felt terrorized.
Come on.
Oh! There's a whole
other terrorism booklet
for that.
I just really,
really think
that we should handle
this internally.
Dwight, why is it
on us to protect you?
Because you guys
are my best friends.
And I mean that.
Managing you
for this last week
has been the
greatest honor
of my life.
And if you ruin this,
I will burn this
office to the ground.
And I mean
that figuratively,
not literally.
Because you guys are so,
so important to me.
I love you guys,
but don't cross me,
but you're the best.
ANDY: Hey.
We're back.
There he is,
our hero.
You look fantastic.
How you doing?
DWIGHT: Here, tell us
your war stories.
Well, I burst
my ear drum.
Doctor said it could
take weeks to heal.
Did they say
what caused it?
'Cause I know you
like putting Q-tips
deep into your ear canal.
Yeah.
How's your hearing?
Temporary deafness
in one ear.
It was both ears.
I couldn't hear
a thing Darryl
was saying
when we were in
the waiting room.
I was talking like this...
I don't feel
good about it,
but he just kept
calling himself
a gunshot victim,
and it got to me.
Dwight, I would like
tomorrow off so that
I can go on my
American Idol audition.
American Idol?
What? No.
Okay, I guess
I can just not go.
Do you guys
wanna hear my solo?
No.
? Why did my temporary boss
go on a shooting spree? ?
Okay, fine,
you can go on your
singing audition.
Okay, well,
then I want an
extra vacation day.
Pet day.
I want pet day
back, no dogs.
Put back everything
in the vending machine,
except the fruit.
I put everything back
in the vending machine.
Put everything back
in the vending machine,
except the fruit.
You have to get rid
of all your weapons.
All of them,
including killer fish.
Okay.
Is it my turn?
Oof. I'm on the spot,
I don't know.
Um. You know what?
I think I'm good.
Thank God.
No. When Jo's here,
can you work in
"Shagadelic, baby"
at least three
times in the
conversation? Oh!
And when I cough,
can you do jazz hands?
What's
jazz hands?
Fine.
What the
is that?
Oh, my...
JO: Hey, all!
Cornelius, Bobo,
have at it.
Nobody let my
dogs hump each other.
They don't seem to
know they're brothers.
Hello, Jo. Welcome.
Shall we begin?
Slow yourself
down there.
Just like a man, wants to
jump right into it while
I still got my socks on.
Jim Halpert,
the only man to
ever turn me down.
I don't know about that.
Just wasn't for me.
But let me assure you,
Dwight is firing on
all cylinders, right?
Well, they're some
pretty big shoes to fill.
I was sorry to
hear about Deangelo.
He was a good man.
It was tragic.
Well, what can
you do? Life.
ANDY: We have to
clean this up, now.
She had so much...
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Hope I'm not
interrupting anything.
No.
Hey, Andy, did you
tell Erin about our
conversation earlier
when you said
you would never want
to date her again?
Uh...
I just thought that
it was so interesting
that you promised that.
Did I say
that earlier?
Yes, I did.
Because you,
Gabe, were crying.
No, I was not.
And sobbing
uncontrollably.
Yes. Uh-huh.
You were in hysterics
and my maternal
instincts kicked in.
Is it actually
how I feel?
Yes.
Or no.
That is between
me and my diary.
Oscar, can you print
out last year's
sales statements?
Sure.
Hey, Dwight,
give me a back massage.
No, Kevin. Come on.
My back is sore,
Dwight. Massage it.
Kevin, not now.
Hey, Jo...
Okay, okay.
No, under the jacket.
You're
kidding me.
Oh, God, what
am I touching?
It's moist.
KEVIN: I don't
feel anything.
DWIGHT: It's wet.
Push harder,
Dwight.
I can't.
I can't
push harder.
Go a little higher.
There.
There you go.
No, higher.
I can't...
Higher.
Oh, my God.
There we go.
How's that?
Knead it.
Knead it
like a pizza.
I'm kneading it.
KEVIN: But don't eat it.
Okay.
Dwight, walk me out.
Let's talk soon.
And stay on top
of these people.
You've got
to admit it,
it's nice to have
a little power, eh?
How's it feel?
Jo,
I accidentally fired
a gun in the office today.
What?
I am telling you this
because I care too
much about this job
to be blackmailed
into doing it poorly.
All I've ever wanted
is to be manager here.
And if you feel like
you cannot promote me
over this one accident,
I understand.
But if you think that
extortion is worse...
Shooting is worse.
Are you kidding me?
It's not even in the same...
You shot a gun?
What is wrong with you?
It was a Beaumont Adams,
if that helps.
Beaumont Adams
is a girl's gun.
That just makes
it plain stupid.
I take full
responsibility.
Who else would
be responsible?
Pam made me put
a banana in my holster.
You shot a gun off.
Okay, did I
make a mistake?
Yes.
Do I regret
the decision
that I made? Yes.
Stop asking yourself
easy questions so
you can look like a genius.
Got it.
I love you, Dwight.
But you don't
fit this job.
Jo, please.
No. No, child.
I will...
No.
It's over.
Now I've got to
find a replacement
for my replacement.
You three are my
search committee.
You're in charge
of finding me
my next manager.
All right-y?
Yeah.
Till then,
we need a
new acting manager.
Now who's got
the most experience
in this office?
Uh, well...
We probably don't
wanna go just
on seniority.
Who is it?
Hey, Dwight? What's up?
Shut up.
Okay. Well...
You do know that Jo
was right to take the job
away from you, right?
There's no debating that.
But I will say,
in your one week,
every single one of
the orders went out
on time
and I think that
is shagadelic, baby.
Four,
one,
seven,
one.
Another one?
Yes!
Seven...
Could you turn
the volume down
on the beeping?
Six, nine.
Shut up,
Oscar. Eight.
Nine first,
put the nine.
Nine.
Eight. Five.
Thank you.
Three,
zero,
zero, again.
Zero.
Okay.
Four.
Six.
Nice.
Two, one.
I hit three,
I hit three instead.
God!