The Sabre Code of Conduct
outlines the governing principles
key to establishing and maintaining
trust with our employees, clients
Oh, my God, kill me
Hey. All right, obviously
we all want to die,
but we have to get through this,
so Gabe, go ahead. It's okay
Oh, is it...
Is it okay with you?
Because if it's not
you work for me, so
Comply with all
applicable laws
regulations
policies and contracts
governing our business
Be honest, fair...
I'm going to do it
...trustworthy in a your business
activities and relationships
Treat one another...
Oh! I'm going into labor
Okay. She's going into labor!
Oh, my goodness
Make way, everybody
I know it's wrong to
fake going into labor
just to get out of things
but sometimes,
it's necessary.
I'm going into labor
But should I
have corn dogs or
I'm going into labor
Okay three reasons you are
wrong about True Blood.
Number one
I'm going into labor
Here we go
Hey, guys, you can't keep
saying you're going into labor
Everyone knows
you're full of it.
Yeah - It's not fair, you guys.
Pitiful.
- So stupid
Never cry wolf
Okay
Okay.
Oh. Oh! Oh, my gosh
Oh, my God, Pam
I'm really in labor
This is happening
Okay, guys
Okay.
Here we go.
We'll see you
How do you feel?
Drive carefully!
Good luck
Bye!
- Good luck
False alarm
What? They took
another client from us?
Okay, bye
Man, business is war
Customers, clients,
it's like a war out there
I am a leader
but you can only inspire people
so much in a place like this.
So today, I'm turning
the inspire factor up to 10
With a little help from my friend,
America's bloodiest battle
Why even read business books?
We should be studying war.
Going to places like
Gettysburg Where is that?
It's right here in PA
Ah
Well, we should take a field trip
there I mean, that would be so cool
I wonder if that
bus downstairs is
Okay, Andy. We get it
It's a trip to Gettysburg
That sounds super inspiring
I'm in!
Gettysburg? Hmm.
Could be interesting
Second most northern
battle in the Civil War
Actually, it is
the northernmost
Ha
The Civil War history industry
has conveniently forgotten about
the Battle of Schrute Farms
Whatever I'm over it. It's
just grossly irresponsible.
Charge
Well, this could be fun
Yeah, well, the bus
has free Wi-Fi
and I made special low
sugar lunches for everyone
And is anyone
kosher or halal?
What's the halal option?
Dates, tabouleh
and bagel with cream cheese
Out
You know, it's the same as the kosher
option There's a lesson in there.
I mean, I can't force you
to go, you're not my slaves
Thanks to Gettysburg
But who's coming with me?
I'm in
I'm in, too.
I guess I'm a sucker
for historical fiction
Anyone who's not going
you're dead to me.
You're uninvited
I don't want you to come
But FYI,
there will be leftover
turkey and pesto
sammies in the fridge
Yes
One for you
Cool, thanks
And one for you
Oh! You missed your head
There you go.
Phyllis, think fast
All right, guys, a little
foreplay before we do it
Fans of Ken Burns' Jazz will most
certainly enjoy The Civil War.
You know, I just got
Limitless on my iPad
I bet I could
get it on the TV
Oh, isn't that the one where
the guy becomes limitless?
It's just not appropriate If we were going
to visit Bradley Cooper's birthplace
I'd be the first one suggesting
that I'd be rooting for it...
Limitless, Limitless, Limitless,
Limitless, Limitless!
All right
all right, all right
Here
Like it?
- Oh by the picnic table?
Then you've got to
get the fire pit.
I can't get a fire pit
I have two babies.
But the fire pit is a no brainer.
Oh, hi there.
Hi, Robert. Hey. Um, how are you doing?
Good to see you again.
Where is everyone?
Where is Andy?
Andy took some of
the other people
on a corporate
retreat to Gettysburg
Well, I was hoping to talk
out some ideas with Andy
But what we have
here is perhaps better
By not going on the trip
you've shown
you're the free
thinkers of the office
Robert, you've got your sheep
and you got your black sheep
And I'm not even a sheep
I am on the freaking moon
So, here's what we can do
Game changers
Changes to the game
such that the game
can never be played
the same way again
Everyone,
brainstorm some innovations
Don't be afraid to
get weird with it.
Meredith
Excited
Okay
You guys, get excited
Movie's almost over
All right, we're here
Limitless can wait.
Fun fact. In France
they call Limitless
"The Man with
Many Capabilities.'
Whoo-hoo! Ladies and gentlemen
the 1800s await you
We can watch
Limitless on the way back
I got Source Code
on the way back.
Whoo
Where are you going?
Visitors' Center. Going to grab
a map for the memorials, right?
We're not going to the Visitors'
Center We're not tourists.
No, of course
we're not tourists
We're just people that aren't
from here who are taking a tour
Yeah, the sign says
"Begin tour here.'
Unless you're going on
the very specially created
and meticulously researched
Andy Bernard Tour.
After Chancellorsville
Lee brought his army up the
Shenandoah Valley right through here
They stopped in this field for a
picnic which they called "lunch.'
Yeah
but I'm confused
Total deaths
belongs to Gettysburg
But when you're talking about
DPA, that's deaths per acre
Uh-huh... nothing beats the
Battle of Schrute Farms
Oh, DPA sounds way more important...
Oh, it is
And you should read some of these
letters that the soldiers wrote home
I mean, it makes
the Battle of Gettysburg
sound like a bunch of schoolgirls
wrestling over a hairbrush
I'm telling you they're heartbreaking,
too So beautifully written.
Dwight, what are
you telling this girl?
The truth
Stop filling her head with nonsense, okay?
She doesn't know any better
Oscar, I'm so glad
you just got here.
I would have
believed everything he said
No, no, no. You're filling
her head with nonsense
You and the history books
I'm telling the truth!
Interesting
Yes, thank you
All of history has
been whitewashed
Really? Why don't you tell us
the real history, Gore Vidal?
Okay, I will.
I don't know who that is
but I'm going
to tell you this
He's a historian
Gettysburg was very important
Credit where credit is due, okay?
Big mad props to Gettysburg
Was it, however, the most
northern battle of the Civil War?
Yes, yes
Not by a long shot!
Yes
No
No, it was not
Was it the second
most northern?
What?
Sure! I would cede it was the
second most northern battle
Erin
Was it the northernmost?
No! Get out of here, Oscar
Get out of here
I am so eager to hear your game
changers Let's dig in, shall we?
May I go first?
Absolutely
Raw fish. The disgusting
food from Japan
that Americans
would never want to eat
Now, we can't
get enough of it
From movie stars to construction
workers, sushi is what's for dinner
Let me throw another idea
at you Origami. What?
The crazy art of paper folding
from that's right, Japan.
Don't you wish you
could go back to 1980
and open the first sushi
restaurant in Manhattan?
We can do that with
origami,
it's the sushi of paper
This idea hasn't gripped me
What else did
you come up with?
I had to memorize
the presentation, Robert
and it took a long time
to build the swan, so.
That was bad
If your woman is like mine
I bet you come home to hear
the same thing all the time.
"This paper is so hard
It scratches.
"Why can't there be
a paper just for me?'
Well, now there is
It's pink
scented and silky soft
Now, you can watch the game and she
can write a letter to her sister.
The situation you described returning
home to a wife complaining about
her paper being too masculine is
not one that I'm familiar with
In the African
American community No.
Thought it was worth a try
That's fascinating
Tell me what's the significance
of the peach orchard, though?
Well, that's a great question
Actually, some of the most
Excuse me,
I've got a question for you
Can you tell us about
the Battle of Schrute Farms?
Oh, I haven't
heard of that one
Really?
Okay, follow-up question
how much are they paying you
to keep your mouth shut?
I apologize for my friend. And for the
Republicans who are cutting your funding
We don't need to
bother this poor gentleman
I know exactly where
we're going. Giddy-up
Tallyho
Are you Lincoln?
No, no, I'm
Apparently, I bear a passing
resemblance to Abraham Lincoln
It makes it kind of
hard for me to go to places
like museums,
historical monuments
elementary schools
I don't see it.
Chelsea, give Mr. Lincoln your
hat so I can take a picture
Okay, quick
Hey, Lincoln's starting
Oh, no. No, no, no, no. I'm actually
with a tour group myself, so
Hello, I'm Abraham Lincoln
Some people call me
the "Great Emancipator, '
but you might know
me from the penny.
Okay, you know
the test booklets
that they give out
in all the schools?
I was thinking that we could
put a coupon in the back
that people
would mail in to us
And as, you know as I
tell it, I don't like it
Unless, of course you are
responding to it I am not.
Um, excuse me, I'm going
to go to the bathroom
At this point
when you're this pregnant
it's kind of
like senior spring
The other day, I spit my
gum out on the carpet
Kevin. You've been quiet
I'm curious to know
what your game changer is
You know how
in the vending machine
they have the chocolate chip
cookies in the A-1 spot?
They do that
because they think
A-1 is the best spot
for the best cookie
But the real best spot is D-4
Right? That's where
the eyes go.
So
Cookies. Cookie placement
Yeah. But not just
the cookies, though
That was just a for instance
Who else agrees with Kevin
that we're wasting facilities,
manpower on our underselling products
when we should be pushing
our top performers?
There you get consensus
Okay, we are
now on a planet where
Kevin is the most
creative person around
and I am just some
good looking guy.
I just don't understand
It's 1865, victory is ours
I have saved the very soul of our
nation and yet, happiness eludes me
Oh, perhaps a trip to the theater
will enliven my spirits.
No
So, another thing about oatmeal cookies.
Who even wants them?
I mean, I've seen
Toby eat one like once
but other than that
forget it.
Interesting
So what is Dunder
Mifflin's oatmeal cookie?
What is the product
that no one wants?
How about that
two-hole punch letter?
Only the lawyers want that punch
at the top, and they use legal
That's the oatmeal cookie.
Fantastic, Kevin, fantastic
Thank you
By the way did we leave
all the food on the bus?
Let's talk about food for a
second Food for thought.
Yeah, that's what I
had for breakfast,
and I think that's
probably why I'm still hungry
Hunger. Hunger for victory Hunger
for honor, hunger for pride
Hunger for hamburgers
Hunger for
chicken chimichangas
Right, Darryl?
That's good
Exactly. Now, do you know what the
Civil War soldiers were hungry for?
Pride. Now, each
battalion had its own flag
and they guarded these
flags with their lives.
Colonel Harrison Jeffords
of the 4th Michigan Infantry
saw his flag
being carried away
chased it down with
nothing but a sword
fought tooth and nail at the
foot of that flag until he died.
He wasn't about to
let them have that flag
Pride. Right, guys?
I commissioned this flag for
Dunder Mifflin It cost me $200.
Only $200?
We are a branches on this tree.
And from the tree comes paper
We're all part of a business
but business is war
What's that I hear?
Oh! A rebel paper company
is coming to take our flag.
What's going on here?
Whee-hoo!
Come and get it! Who's going to get
the flag? Who's getting it? Whoa, hey
Don't look where I am look where I'm going.
Jerk right, jerk left, jerk
Andy, this is inappropriate
People died here, man
Get the flag, get the flag
Come on, Big Tuna.
What are you going to do about it?
We've got a flag right here
Whee-hoo
Spangler's Spring
is a mile this way.
Oh, wow. So, that's two miles if
you incorporate the walk back
It's... I mean, come on
Oh, I don't think I
should walk anymore
All I had for
breakfast was oatmeal
yogurt, coffee,
orange juice and toast
Two poached eggs and then that
half a sandwich on the bus
I can't
All right, fine
You know what?
I guess this place
just hasn't rubbed off
on you the way
that I hoped it would
I'm still going, and I'm
not going to ask anymore
I'm not even
going to look back
I'm just going to
assume that you're with me
You said you weren't
going to look back.
And why is BlackRock
suddenly the paragon by which all
hedge funds must now be compared?
Yeah, I don't know
Right? I mean,
you're an accountant
those bogus prospectuses
must drive you insane
Yes, I am an accountant
Dwight, this is one
of the archivists here
I thought maybe
we can consult him
Really?
Yeah.
Well, anyone employed by the
Gettysburg industrial complex
is certainly going
to want to keep quiet
about the Battle
of Schrute Farms
Schrute Farms, did you say?
That is a fascinating little
chapter of the Civil War.
You've heard about it?
Yes! Ha Prepare to be
refuted Go on, come on
There you go
Families
and sweethearts back home
waited desperately for
letters from the front.
"Dearest Mother, I'm sorry it has
been so long since my last letter.
"It is three months since I
arrived at Schrute Farms,
"and I fear I may never leave this
place alive. Melvyn Fifer Garris."
Hallowed ground
But the battle at Schrute
Farms was no battle at all.
It was a code used by pacifists
from both Norte and Soute,
who'd turned
the Pennsylvania farmhouse
into an artistic community
and a refuge from the war.
You have to understand,
poets, artists, dancers,
these kinds of men
preferred peace to war.
These delicate, lovely men
found a place of refuge
among the Schrutes
of Schrute Farm.
Amidst the macho
brutality of war,
this was a place where dandies
and dreamers could put on plays,
sing tender ballads
and dance in the moonlight.
I like to think of Schrute Farm
as the Underground Railroad
for the sensitive and,
well, fabulous.
Wow, this is so much better
than the story you made up.
I've seen enough
You're right, there should
be a monument to this
Never trust a cookie
with a woman's name
Pecan Sandy.
Lorna Doone. Madeleine
Oh
They'll just break your heart
Kevin, you are
Robert, I hate to interrupt but I
would love to pitch you one last idea
I call it the Big Mac idea
What? No
Big Mac idea.
Sounds encouraging
It's really, really good,
Robert Let me explain
No, this is not fair
This is my idea.
He's trying to steal it
because he's jealous of me
Well, what is the idea?
Every time you buy a Big Mac
you set one ingredient aside
Then, at the end of the week
you have a free Big Mac.
And you love it even more because
you made it with your own hands
You know what? Now I remember
That was your idea
That is 100% your idea
Oh, my
It was just actually
cookies the whole time
Damn it
Hey
You guys came
Where's everyone else?
Back at the bus
We were locked out
Phyllis is sitting on the
ground eating a dirty sandwich
Yeah, I asked
the bus driver to lock it
because our stuff was in there.
I guess he follows orders
Yeah, sorry everybody else didn't
come I think they're just tired.
With holes in their
shoes and their dysentery
Even without an audience
you're still at it.
What are you talking about?
Our office has a disease,
and it goes by many names
Sarcasm, snark, "wisecracks.'
You take things
that people care about
and you make them feel lame
about it with your jokes.
That's what you
did with this trip
Andy, this whole
idea of our situation
being just like war
it's just not true
We just work at
a paper company
and you're our
regional manager
And guess what, man? You
don't have to prove anything
We like you as
regional manager
Andy, if you don't believe me
take a look at what's on my head.
I'm wearing a very pink hat
I've been getting weird looks all
day, because I'm pretty sure
"DM does GB means
something kind of sexual
But guess who's wearing them?
All of us.
Just for you, man
That's huge
You don't like the hats?
They're terrible
I hate myself
They just didn't turn out how I
wanted In my head, they were cooler
But they do look weird
The world
will little note
nor long
remember the fight that
Jim and I had
here at Gettysburg.
And that's good,
because I was basically wrong.
I wanted my team to be like this
army and I was their general
but I guess it's
really just more like
they're people who work in an
office and I'm their manager
Yeah, that's really probably a better
analogy Now that I think about it.
Abe and Mary are
seated watching the show
Oh, Mary, this is wonderful
Okay, Mary, stop your
scolding. I'll be quiet.
I need her like I need
a hole in the head
Mmm. Oh
Bang!