Okay. Bye
Everyone, stop what you're
doing I have terrible news
Dwight is
no longer with us
What?
He's gone, damn it
He's been promoted to
V.P. of Sabre Retail
and he's staying
in Florida forever
So, he's alive?
Yeah. That was him on the
phone He sounds wonderful.
Well, the way you said it made
it sound like he was dead
How could I have
been more clear?
He had a massive
stroke of good fortune
and he is now in
a better place.
If Dwight's not coming back does
that mean we can open his treasure?
You guys we've gone over
this there is no treasure
When the team
left for Tallahassee
Dwight told everyone
not to touch his treasure
Don't touch my treasure
Okay? You understand?
Obviously he wants us to obsess
about it There's nothing in there
Which is obviously what he
would want us to think,
making it the perfect
place to hide a treasure
Oh, God, I'm Wallace Shawn
in The Princess Bride.
Wanted us to realize
that this conversation among
friends is the true treasure.
No, no, no
I am dying to
know what's in there
Yeah, I know, Oscar. We all are.
But nobody's going to open it
You'd have to be insane
Hi. Hello
Now carefully open the box
It's a photo of all of us
Oh, that's so sweet
A dart?
Are you kidding me?
Who would put a poison dart Well, I
mean, I don't know that it's poisoned
God, I'm glad
he's okay though
Kind of sounds
like he deserved it
opening another man's
treasure and all. Wow
Well, Mister Ball it's been a
pleasure Now, give my regards to he
All right!
Well swung by VIPVP
I am loving the chemistry
between you two
Dwight is going to be
working alongside me
We are a regular Archibald
and his man George
Trick! There's no such thing
It's not even a real English duo
Ah
I just made you look like the Goat of
Dover. And that doesn't exist either
You think you're excited?
You should feel my nipples
Pong
Oh, that reminds me Little
something from all of us.
Oh, my gosh. Thank you, Jim
That's so thoughtful.
Fore! Oh, yeah
He doesn't even care
This is the last time
I'll ever see Dwight.
It's a weird feeling
It's, um...
What's the word?
It's not "bittersweet.'
It's "sweet." Yeah
Hey, man.
Selling cookies for Jada
You want
the same as last year?
Would if I could
and I can so I will
Put me down for one box Don't
care what it is. Dealer's choice.
I'll put you down
for shortbreads
Damn it
Knock, knock. Hey
It's Sasha's
first year in the troop
so I'm selling
cookies for her
Anyway, would you
like some?
No. No
What?
I've been selling here for
five years This is my spot.
You can't claim territories This is
the only place I interact with people
Why can't you sell it
at your church or barbershop?
Or chess club?
You know what? It's your first
time we'll split the office
You can have Sales the Annex,
Creed and I don't know.
I'll just take Accounting
That's it?
Yeah. Well, okay
Thanks, Darryl
Okay, great
All I need is Kevin.
Dude buys more cookies
than everyone combined.
And then some.
When I first started selling cookies,
he was a relatively thin man
Not a thin man, mind you
Relatively thin.
Hey, Lucy, I'm home
Babaloo
Here, let me help
so busy at the store today
Really good cheese nibbles
Irene hired me as
her live-in helper
We met at
the store launch.
I told her I was moving here
and I needed a place
and it just
sort of made sense.
I basically do
everything for her.
I run errands, I do chores
around the house.
I cook and clean.
Honestly, I don't know
how she survived without me
When can I introduce you to my grandson?
He's a wonderful swimmer
Shallow end, deep end
He does it all
Well, today might be
kind of tough, Irene
I have to talk to
my old boss, Andy
and tell him I'm
staying in Florida
Oh! What kind
of tea is this?
Oh, I boiled some Gatorade
Oh
Oh!
In England, they put the holes a
little bit to the right you see.
We'll just chalk it up
to cultural bias.
If I may
Try holding the putter you
know, with your wrists here,
and your thumbs here
Oh
That's right
Your little finger
Would you like to
buy some cookies?
Cookies, eh?
Mmm-hmm
Hmm
Oh, the spring time
thinks that it's the best
And fall time
Cold time has
kind of a strut
And Valentine's
thinks that it's the best
But gather round, peeps
I'll tell you the truth
Nothing beats the cookie
season That's the truth
It's not
a scratch and sniff, Kev
I know. But sometimes you
still get a little something
Hey, you tricked me
You just wanted Kevin
You're new to the game.
You learned a lesson today
See you next year, sport
No, no, no, that's not fair What if
Kevin wants to buy cookies from me?
I do
See?
That doesn't mean anything Kevin,
do you want to buy cookies from me?
Oh, I definitely do
Huh. Hit the road, Jack
No, you hit the road, Jack
Hey, guys, come on
Don't fight over me.
Why don't we split the order?
It's only fair
No, wait, no. I'm buying.
I make the rules
I actually do want
you to fight over me
wined and dined
and sixty-nined
Ugh
Metaphorically sixty-nined
Ew! Perverts
No offense, Oscar
Hop in! We have places to be!
No rest for the wicked
All right
so I guess this is it
Well, Jim, I just want to say that
we haven't always gotten along
And, at times, I've even
hated your guts, but
Bye, bye. I win
Good-bye, Dwight
Robert! Race you to the
clubhouse Gentleman's bet!
Whoo-hoo
Well, he's
Florida's problem now
Oh, let Dwight
have his fun.
Today will not be his day
What's that?
I'm going to
tank the Sabre store
at the presentation
to the board
I thought you
liked the store
No, the store is lovely
You created a wonderful space
to showcase our product line
Great job. Cheers
Thank you
But there's a reason we sell our
products online and over the phone
Have you ever used
Sabre electronics, Jim?
They're cheap,
they're unintuitive
The Sabre store
would work
if we adopted
the carnival mode
of leaving town once
everyone's wise to us
Wow. When you put it that way, I
guess it does sound pretty terrible
I couldn't just kill the project from
the start Jo Bennett endorsed it.
Shame, though.
I did like Dwight
Robert, I'm going to win! Ha-ha!
I'm the gentleman Suck it!
Bravo, Dwight
Very good!
Shame
DWIGHT
The math is simple, folks
Deeper market penetration plus greater
visibility will raise Sabre...
To the power of two
How did that look?
I'm not just
saying this,
that was the best
thing I've ever seen
Told you
When you guys do that whole
"power of two" shebang
how about I pop up also?
Say "power of three.'
Actually you know what?
Yeah, that actually works
You'd spin off right
I'd spin off
You know what?
That is a great idea
Cathy, write that down
and print it out
It's going to make some
really good toilet paper
All right.
There he is
What are you doing here?
I thought I got rid of you.
Can I just talk to you
for one quick second?
What? Your stylist
ran out of messy spray?
Um, actually, it's for your
own good I think we should...
You want to do
something for my own good?
Turn around,
walk out that door
Do not stop until
you get to Scranton
Find my cell phone charger mail
it back to me and then go to hell
Nice. Hey, Halpert, anyone ever
tell you you look like Wooly Willy?
Silence
I'm just trying to
I know what
you're trying to do
But your face does look like
the guy from Operation.
It's the same guy.
That's the joke I made
Different guy
You know what
I just think
you should know
That you look like
the world's tallest hobbit
Well, I tried. You saw it
So, it's on the record.
Can you help me? I'm trying to
make a video chat with Andy
Just open the program
and type in his username
Can you just do it?
You type in your password
Erin, one, two, three
That's a terrible password
And you don't
make a video chat
You video chat.
All right
Hello.
That's so weird. There's
something wrong with my laptop
Oh
Now mine's broken
Hang on.
Oh, there we go
He said "I did like Dwight"?
He's going to fire him.
No, no, no, I think it was more like
"I liked him,
but I don't anymore
"because he did a bad job so I'm
definitely going to yell at him."
Robert doesn't
talk like that.
You have to stop Dwight
from doing this.
He will not listen
Did you actually
try your hardest?
Yes. My pretty hardest
Look, you haven't dealt with
him in a while, all right?
He's like Super Dwight
It's like he's been bitten by a
radioactive Dwight or something
Stanley, back me up
Don't talk to me
Stanley's very upset
that we're leaving Florida
but he would back me up
If Dwight's about to get
fired, you have to tell him.
Just get the words out,
that's all you can do.
Okay. All right
What's a skinny guy like Toby
know about cookies?
You can't trust
him to understand
the wants and needs
of the thick man
Maybe Toby from
two years ago.
Yeah
That's true
If I have a question about
my cookies at midnight
who am I going to call?
Darryl Toby's probably
in bed with some model.
Thank you
I'm not going to comment
on my personal life
Look, I need this. Okay, your
daughter is a pretty little girl.
Let her go door to door
You think people are going to buy
cookies from my chubby daughter?
Ooh
Baby, if you're watching this you're
not chubby. You're beautiful.
Daddy's just got to
sell some cookies
And we're also going to exercise
more It's going to be fun.
Oh. You know what you
have to do to decide?
You need to make them do things
for you and buy you things
Or have them sing that song that
the frog does in Looney Tunes.
Make them kiss each other
Make them kiss me
Ew
Yes, this is, too, tan
This right here.
No
This is a tan spot.
I don't buy it. And that is a freckle.
That is not a tan, okay?
I'm going to have to inspect it
in person when you get back here
I want you looking totally
Puertorriquena when I see you.
Well, Andy,
I'm not coming back
What?
I have a job here.
I work for an old lady.
Hello.
Andy?
Yeah, that's awesome
That's great
Oh, baby, telephone
And tell me I'm your own
Okay, this is tough
because Darryl,
you sang better and
you danced better
but Toby has that indescribable
quality that makes a star.
I think I've
reached my decision
I've decided that you guys are
going to keep doing things for me.
No, no, no, no
It's not worth it
No
No, it's not worth it?
That's too bad
Because I was feeling
particularly hungry this year.
Yeah, okay, so what?
You buy 40 boxes?
Hungrier
50?
You're not
talking triple digits?
Oh, yeah
I'm talking triple digits
Again
Hello, ma baby
Hello, ma honey
Hello, ma ragtime gal
It's show time
Dwight
You again? Gosh, I keep throwing
you away you keep flying back
You're like
an Amish return stick
Okay, great, listen
listen to me.
No, no, no, no
Will you just let me
tell you one thing, please?
Yes, you may tell
me one thing Great
Wait, do you want to borrow money?
Listen to me
Robert is going to
veto the Sabre store
Jim, come on
Dwight, he's going to kill the store.
Mmm-hmm.
And then I'm pretty sure
he's going to fire you for it
Wait he's going to kill the store
and he's going to fire me?
Yes
That's two things
Dwight, please
Nice try, Jim.
Your pranks have
never worked in the past
and they're not
going to work today
Okay, first of all
they've mostly worked so
You know what? You might
want to get to the airport.
It's going to take you a long
time to get through security
with all those
beauty products Bye
Dwight, come on
Nothing is going to stop me
That is the mark of a great man
Unstoppability
Dunder Mifflin, the farm Mose, all those
things vanish in my rearview mirror
Now, if you'll excuse me I
have a date with destiny
And from what I hear
she's a
Help! Help
Gross, don't lick my hand God,
why is there so much saliva?
All I had to do
was think about pie
and my salivary glands
did the rest.
Gross! What?
What? What? What?
Oh, God, Jim!
Oh! My appendix
I'm sorry
My wound hasn't healed yet.
I'm so sorry I'm sorry.
Oh, man. I'm so sorry I forgot.
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Where the hell is he?
I cannot do this without him
He's not picking up
Looks like
Shnoot's a no-show
Guess he wasn't vice
prezzy material after all
But I am
Put me in, babe
I've got the info down backwards,
forwards and doggy style.
I'm your man
Right.
Let's begin then
Ladies and gentlemen
allow me to introduce
the vice president of Sabre
Retail, Mister Todd Packer
What's up?
What are you doing?
I'm just dealing
with Erin's stuff
since apparently
she's not coming back
and she didn't
bother to tell anyone
We knew.
Ryan told us
Ryan, why didn't you
tell me?
Thought you
checked my Tumblr
You never update it
Well, I updated it
Does anyone else
think this is weird?
Like, kind of
uncool, actually?
To leave us without
a receptionist?
We'll find
another receptionist
I mean, that's easy
We'll be fine
What are you doing?
I'm just trying to.
Get up. Get up
Okay. Okay
All right? I'm not
going to let you by.
Then you know what? I'm going to
just have to run right through you
Okay
What are you doing?
Are you really revving up?
You know that doesn't work
Jackie Chan
Go
Hi, this is Alex.
And this is Sam.
"Kevin can't come to the phone right
now because he's busy with us.'
Perfect
Now people w think I'm
doing hot girls all day
They might think
we're drag queens
Yeah, I don't know why you picked
names that were also guys' names
Okay, now who do I ride to
the kitchen like a pony?
Don't make me be
your pony, Kevin.
Forget it, man
What do you mean?
I'm out. So is Toby.
This may be wrong
but there's a limit
to what I will do
for my child.
Yeah.
I have my dignity, too
another man's horsey
No, guys, stop! You
have to sell me cookies
I'll do anything
Hello, my baby
Hello, my honey
I'm even going
to kiss Meredith
Mmm
That's so good
What are you doing?
No, no, no, no!
This ends now
This is dangerous.
Thunder slam
No
Anything else you
need to talk about?
Nope. That was it
Once again,
it's show time
What baffles me is how you could
take a perfectly good idea
which the great Jo Bennett
rightfully signed off on
and then, utterly
botch it in execution
If I may speak to that
I have only
been vice president
of this project for
the last half-hour
so the man you want
is Dwight Schrute.
I don't see Dwight
He clearly had
the infinite wisdom
to stay as far away from
this clown show as possible.
Whatever you do,
do not blame Todd Packer
It is not his fault
Blame his upbringing
His parents
The society that would
mold this idiotic creature
Fire the employee, yes
But not the man
You may not
cancel his soul
That was never
on the table.
Are you kidding?
She's the queen of the
whole frigging magilla.
And yet, Todd,
it's you who's fired
Wait, I can't get fired
I'm an institution.
Company for 20 years
How many of you have
been here that long? Huh?
Hey, hey, they're back
Hi! Oh, my gosh!
Look at you guys
Dwight, what are you
doing here?
I thought you were
supposed to be in Florida
Yeah, the crazy thing
about that is, um...
Wow, you look great.
Did you lose some weight?
Thank you. For someone
who actually noticed this
no, I didn't lose weight
but I started using my makeup
to contour my face
to look skinnier.
I actually put on
five pounds
Hey, good to
have you back
Good to be back
Hey, stranger
Hey
Oh, I missed you
I missed you.
Oh
I'm going to Florida
to get Erin.
Forgot to turn off my email
It's crazy, right?
It's just when she
said she was leaving
"You're about to
close four tabs,
"are you sure you
want to continue?'
Yes, I am sure
Ah! Slow computer