Hello, my name is Oscar I'm an
accountant in Scranton, Pennsylvania
and I am gay
And I'm here to tell you
that, yes it does get better
When I was younger
What? What's he doing?
He's searching out
younger gays.
No, it's just a way
to tell young people
no matter how hard
it gets for them
there's a brighter
future ahead
With you
No matter how hard it gets for you...
Kelly, seriously, I...
Just keep chatting I'm just
checking my makeup in your webcam
Do you not own a mirror?
Webcams make me look the way
I look in my fantasies.
I know, right? What is it? You
always look so good in those things.
I'm throwing out
all my mirrors.
Okay, as you can see
at a dynamic workplace
Being gay is a celebration
of life It's a simple...
I'm sorry. I just
can't sit idly by
and have
the gay youth of America
misled by
some reductionist
I'm not misleading
...pep talk
Sexuality is a spectrum
It's a paradox to think of any
sexual activity as normal
It gets better, but it also
gets vastly more complicated.
Hey, Robert? That guy
he looks just like you
Damn it! Kevin. God
You okay, Robert?
I'm fine
Put some ice on it
In any case,
it gets better
Maybe not much better
but better.
It hurts
One, two, three
I wanted to give a nice gift to
the tenants in the building.
At first I thought,
"Muffin basket."
Then I thought, "What's even more
precious to people than muffins?"
Can you just
smile, please?
Their own children
Hey, everybody
Just a few hours left for the
free family portrait studio.
Darryl, we'd love to see
little Jada come by
Angela, why don't you
bring by your little angel?
No, thank you
Jim, you've got
those two cute kids
We sure would
love to see them
doing this, Dwight
Last week, I may
have gone too far
I'll explain it quickly
Basically I found out where he
gets his clothes dry-cleaned
custom-ordered the same suit
made with tear-away Velcro
and you can
fill in the rest.
What?
Damn it, Jim
Now he's trying to get me to
bring my children into work
I think it's fair
to be cautious
Let me get this straight
you lost all of it?
All your winnings
$150,000?
You mean to tell me
no one wanted
an energy drink
for Asian homosexuals?
They did not
You've got
half-a-million of these?
Well, I've got to try it I wouldn't
Oh, come on.
What's the harm?
Hmm
What flavor is that?
The coconut's pretty subtle
Come on, man. Can you just
give us a yes or a no?
I don't know, man. You all
quit with a lot of confidence
came up in here dancing
and everybody was...
Ooh! Hold on a second
If I were Val, I would
break up with Brandon
Then I would date
the hell out of me
I wouldn't give in
to me too fast,
let me buy myself some
nice dinners and such
When I finally did give in
I would go crazy on myself
Hi, guys
How's it going, man?
I'm... I'm good
Thank you. How are you?
Great, yeah. Good
Oh, how the mediocre
have fallen.
Oh, God
Look, I'm not here
to get my old job back
I'm moving on
Just wanted to come in here
and literally beg you
for something, anything
water the plants.
No, you don't
Clean the toilets
Pull the poop
out of the toilets
Not even a thing.
Just please
Andy. Andy
Please give me something
Why don't you clean
the carpets for today?
Thank you
Well, you're...
Up you get, then
Pick yourself up
There it is.
Thank you
You don't need to
Good, good This carpet's
overdue for a good mopping
Is a mop the most efficient
too to use on a carpet?
Yeah, it is, actually
I can't hold
it in any longer
Because I convinced
David Wallace
to buy Dunder Mifflin
back from Sabre
and at 3:00 today he's
going to walk in here
and reinstate me
as manager
Family picture
Pam. No
What? Honey, we talked
about this.
No, we talked about
not bringing them
into Dwight's photo
studio/trap.
Yes, and then we decided
that was crazy.
No, we decided it was crazy
not to worry about it
No, we settled in a much
more rational place
remember?
No
We decided that there's no way
Dwight would harm a child
But are you 100% sure? I
don't think any of us are
No, no
Nope
But it's free and we'll
keep our eye on them
Yes
Yes, that's
And we will make sure that
Dwight doesn't do anything
Okay
...C-R-A-Z-Y
Wait. C-R-A-Z
Great, right up there
Yeah
Yeah.
You sit right here
one time.
There you go
Okay.
All right, why don't you
just give him to me?
Oh, great. Thank you
Perfect
This is great, excuse me
You ready? There you go
Okay.
All right, let's do it
I'll just stand here then
Yeah, just keep your eye
on Dwight Okay, yeah
Sir, could you
look into the camera?
Let's do it
Shoot it. Great
Sir.
Up here
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jim, right here right here.
Okay. Good
Oh, so that's it?
That's it
See, that wasn't so hard
Cute kids
Thanks for coming.
Hello, Erin.
Hello, everybody
What, why? Hi, honey.
What... How are you doing?
You know,
my office got a call
that they were shooting
family portraits right here
And if there's one thing every
politician instinctively understands
it's a good photo op
Okay, you're going to go
through the hallway.
Here's a map And if you get
lost just follow the blue line
Thanks
Well, well, well,
Senator Lipton. Welcome
Angela.
Dwight
Nice to see you
May I hold him?
Sure
No. I am going to hold him because
I haven't seen him all day.
I think that Dwight
is doing this whole thing
to get a sample
of my baby's DNA
to prove he's the father
Which is impossible
Because the Senator is the
only man I've ever been with
Did you see that?
What do you think
about that? See?
See that ducky?
Okay, hold on
a second, folks
A few of the baby's hairs
are out of place
Oh, thank you
No, no, no
I like the baby's hair
the way it is.
Really?
This is getting more and more
delicious by the minute.
It's go time
Hey, Nellie. I made... I made you
Well, I don't
want any soup
But it's really good
Oh! Come on, Andy
Ah
I know this is going
to be a great payoff
A delicious moment
But after you're manager
some of these images are
going to be hard to shake
Well, but it's
Just calibrate.
Okay? Calibrate
Okay, here we go
Oh, you know what? I don't want
to throw a wrench into the works
but I want everything
to be perfect
and the baby's fingernails
are just bothering me.
Uh-uh. Leave us alone
with the fingernails
Okay, great.
Suit yourself
Although
aren't those
excess skin cells
in the baby's cheek
distracting to you as well?
Dwight! We're fine
Oopsie! Did somebody
make a poopsie?
I'm just going to take
him out and change him
just for a second here
He defecated
Ooh
Oh
Stinky
A lot has changed
since you all left, okay?
You're going to have to
jump through some hoops
And the new foreman is here
Now, she's one of the best
we've ever known, okay?
So I need you to show her
your utmost respect
Make sure that
she feels welcome
and at home, okay?
Can you do that?
That's some pretty blatant
complimenting you're doing there, man
I don't even talk to her like that.
- Uh, Brandon
You would?
Yeah.
Sounds like you're trying
to hit on my girlfriend
Calm down. He's not
Yes, I am
Just so everyone's
on the same page.
So you really
think she's going to
leave a guy who owns
his own restaurant
for a dude who ate his own restaurant?
Brandon.
Good slam
Thank you, Biggie
Good luck to you
Oh, and have
a burger for me
Okay, shall we
take a few more?
I think we have all the shots
we need Thank you, Dwight
Okay, here we go
Yes, here we go.
No, Dwight! Give me
the diaper Dwight!
Is this what
you were looking for?
Huh? Huh?
Andy, we wanted
to talk to you.
A lot of us are very
concerned about you
You're dirty, you stink of booze,
you're limping inexplicably
I just want you guys
not to worry
because old Andy's
going to be just fine
No, no, no see, this is
what we're talking about
I mean, what was
that accent?
And last time I checked you were
drunk and now you're not drunk
No, unfortunately
it's true
He's been a nightmare
and the worst part is he's
been taking it out on me.
You hit her?
- What?
No, no
That is not the deal
Calibrate
He's not hitting me, but he's
been verbally abusing me
That is
not true, either
That's also total...
Everyone please relax
I think you're going to
like this surprise guest
Happy birthday to Gabe
Oh, get out,
Skeleton Man
someone to talk to
Huh?
Hold on
I'm just going to... Hello?
Hey, what's the scoop?
Are you close?
What? No, no, no, no, no, no,
no You have to come now.
Traffic clears.
No, next Friday
That's not going to work
Okay, yeah, okay
Damn it
Well, this is not going to be
quite as delicious as I wanted
but I do have a very tasty
announcement for you guys.
Not only am I not
a lowly janitor,
once again
Guys, I got
my old job back
Oh, boy
Oh, Andy
I'm not crazy I convinced David
Wallace to give me my job back
David Wallace hasn't
worked here in years.
Okay, yes
I see the confusion
at the fundraiser
He is now
a multi-millionaire
because he sold
his toy vacuum "Suck It'
to the U.S. Military
Andy, come on, man
I... Okay, I get how
that sounds crazy.
Andy, nobody's calling
you crazy, Andy.
We're your friends, Andy
Stop saying my name
No, he's not making this up.
Thank you, Erin
Andy tells me about seeing
David Wallace all the time
But have you ever
actually seen him yourself?
Oh, my God. Wait
Erin, come... Come on
You know I've been
talking to David Wallace
Do you see David Wallace
in the room right now?
Operation Phoenix is a go
Just get the car ready
Okay, you look at me
like you're adoring me
and I'm going to
look at the camera
like I don't even
know you're there
But I do adore you
Andrew, it's time
for you to go home
You're better than this
Yeah, I know
Everyone is
better than this
Because this is the worst
thing I have ever seen
Why did they add coconut?
I miss original.
Hey.
- Hey
Hey, guys
Hey, guys, long time
David, what are
you doing here?
Is it true you're
buying the company?
Okay, I guess
the word is out
Please keep this a secret but
yes, I've been talking with Andy.
What? I thought
I heard my name. What?
I'm the new manager?
I'll get to that
in a second, Andy
But it's
It is me? Right?
Yes
as we discussed
What?
Oh, my God
It's very possible
Probable.
Wow. From janitor
to manager?
Yep
It's quite a Cinderella story.
From M-O-P to MVP
There's an official
announcement A few details...
From total loss
to total boss. I mean
Can we expect
any payroll interruptions?
Now that is
a great question, Stanley
Right now I think
all your operations
or most of your operations are
pretty much down in Florida,
so the shift back
I was so looking forward
to that and it did not go
as I thought it would
So we're not going to be
a part of Sabre anymore?
Actually nothing is going to
be a part of Sabre anymore
Jo Bennett's planning on liquidating
the rest of the company
Oof!
Wouldn't want to be a Sabre
employee right about now.
I'm actually the CEO
Ah
I didn't realize
you were standing there
Hey, my friend, trust me
This is for the best I never
understood that corporate mess
Well, okay.
Well, great to meet you
Likewise, I'm Bob
Bob Kazamakis.
Pleasure
I'd love to give you
a little rundown
on what I've learned
about this place.
That's very
gracious of you, Bob
Please
I guess I better
take off these dirty rags
and figure out how to be
a manager of this place.
Perhaps your
year of experience
managing this branch
will come in handy.
Gosh, I hope so
No! God, Mose. God
Hi, Angela
Get out of the car
Get out!
Where is he? Where is he?
I'm not supposed to say
Yes, tell me!
Tell me where he is
Mose! Damn it
Where did he go?
Mose, get back here
See that smile
Jump in here
Come on
Looks like I might get my
delicious moment after all.
May I say one thing?
It would be rude of me not to let
you say whatever's on your mind
"The quality of mercy
is not strained.'
No
"It dropeth as the gentle rain from
heaven upon the place beneath."
Do not bring Shakespeare
into this
How dare you play
the "Bard Card."
"It blesseth he who gives
and he who takes.
"'Tis mightiest
in the mightiest.'
one mother *
delicious moment.
Is that too much to ask?
If I were to
hire you back, if
what do you think
you would do well?
Special projects manager
That's my background.
Doing whatever I want
All right, you sly bastard
when can you start?
Okay, everyone
with Bob
and since I am going to be CEO
now, there'll be no need for him
Ouch! That's got to hurt
But he is going to make so much
money from the liquidation,
he's going to be
freed up to do
something much more important.
What?
David has generously offered to
donate $1,000,000 in matching funds
to a cause
that's very dear to me
So for the next three years
I'll be traveling overseas,
concentrating all of my efforts
on educating, mentoring
some African, some Asian, but
mainly Eastern European women
I had no idea
how pervasive
this problem was until
Bob explained it to me
Oprah Winfrey's
Leadership Academy
and other schools like it while
wonderful, end with high school.
I want to see these girls
right through college.
Especially the gymnasts
They've lost so many years
of crucial education
to perfecting their bodies
Muscle groups the rest
of us can't even fathom
Gymnasts? You're going to
seek out uneducated gymnasts?
Yeah. So I'm hoping to identify
some truly exceptional women
who show great promise
Well, Andy, it's been fun
Hmm
It's been a great year
Hello
Where is it?
They're testing it now
How long does it take
to get the results?
Seventy-two hours
You're going to wait here?
Yes
Dwight, I can't do this
Dwight
Hey
Senator Lipton.
Hey, how are you?
You didn't call
Um
Well, the issue
that concerned me
You know what
this is about.
Call