This is Pam
Oh, my God, are you sure? Okay,
okay, we'll be right there
Everybody
The balloon is falling
- What?
There's this balloon
that has been floating
in the rafters of the
warehouse for, like, ever.
And
Okay, it's not it doesn't sound
cool you just have to see it
Well, I guess it doesn't
look that cool either
But it's been up there
a long time,
so it's become
a pretty big deal
Wow. It's the end
of an era.
You did
a good job, buddy
Now it's time
to come home
I remember when that balloon went
up there I was still with Gil
We were so happy
When that went up there
I had hair like Rapunzel.
How long do you think
it's been up there, Kevin?
I just remember pushing aside
my silky bangs to say,
"Look, a balloon.'
My Warcraft clan was
still on speaking terms
My kid didn't
have a face tattoo
of going back to school
And I was still
just a paper salesman
This has been fun, Pam Thanks
for calling us all down here.
Kill the balloon
Kill the balloon!
Hey
So they accidentally gave us an
extra egg sandwich this morning
Who wants it?
- Ooh! Right here
Right here! Pick me
Allow me to solve
your problem then
Nellie
Mmm
Ugh! That is disgusting
Do you call that a King
James breakfast pie?
What brings you to town?
Certainly not the Harry
Houdini museum What a nobody
"Oh, look, some Hungarian just
found their way out of a sack,
"let's build a shrine.'
No, I've come
to work here.
What?
How could Robert transfer Nellie
here after the Sabre store debacle?
She stinks of failure
The fact that she could
show her face around here
is an embarrassment
an identical situation
Robert did say you'd be joining us.
Welcome, I'm Tony
What?
Okay, I made a mistake I
thought it might go unnoticed.
But, I'm Toby
You messed up
saying your name?
It happens, okay?
So let's just find
an empty desk for you
and I'm sure Robert will be
with you as soon as he gets in.
That one looks empty
No. It's Andy's office
Oh, is it?
I have one simple
philosophy in business
if the seat is open
the job is open.
It's how I came to briefly
race a Formula One car
The three slowest laps
ever recorded.
Another beautiful day
in Tallahassee.
Good morning, Alonzo
Good morning, Erin
How are you?
How's your family doing?
Bye
Look at this place. Five rooms
and I get to clean them all
That's right. I'm a
maid for an old lady
Her grandson's staying with us,
too, because he ran out of money
Listen to me,
bragging away
Nellie
Robert
How are you adjusting
to life in Scranton so far?
So far, so good The water pressure
in the hotel is marvelous
It is astounding what a difference
that can make, isn't it?
Mm-hmm
Now, let's find you something
fun to do here shall we?
Oh, I've already found it
a natural next step
It fits like a glove.
We have a manager
Do you really?
Because it is 10:00
I've been in this
chair for an hour
and no other manager
has come and sat on my lap
Excuse me has anyone
seen Andy this morning?
Yeah, that's weird He's usually
here by now Right, guys?
Hello?
Andy, it's Robert
Why aren't you at work?
Hey, Robert, I really wish I
could come into work today
but I'm super sick.
Please come to
work immediately
Okay, I'll try to come in,
even though I'm really sick
with the Florida flu
He just hung up
on me mid-sentence
I'm in Florida to get Erin
As soon as I heard she wasn't
coming back to Scranton,
and drove straight down
until I hit the ocean.
My heart is my map
Turns out Tallahassee is about
two hundred miles inland,
so I overshot a good amount
But still, not bad
for a heart map, right?
Ew
Thanks a lot, BP
Not much we can do about this
until he gets here.
Can't you do
something about this?
Sometimes the flowers
arrange themselves, Jim
Right
What is going on,
and where's Andy?
And what is going on?
Erin, you got a package
ERIN
I'm in the bathroom
Where's the postage? I mean
there's no shipping label
Did you wash your hands?
Yes
Here I am, signed, seaped,
delivered I'm yours
Andy, what are you
doing here?
It's great to see you
Ah
Uh, I am here to take
you back to Scranton
because I love you and
I want to be with you.
Where's the ring?
Hmm?
Where's the ring, Lancelot?
Would you guys mind if we
talked privately for a second?
Sorry, Glenn
Um
Andy I am so happy to see you
but I'm not
coming back with you
GLENN Why won't she go with him?
I don't know. Maybe it's
because he's not that handsome
Hey
Don't listen
So what is going on?
That does seem to be the
question doesn't it?
"Hey, this is messed up, bro.
Who is this weird lady?'
So, who knows what's going on?
Anyone?
You, yes, wait. I am very
good intuiting names
Is it Chumbo?
A cross between "dumbo'
and "jumbo
with a hint of "chubby.'
It's not a name
So no one can tell me
what's going on?
Well, let me
illuminate things for you
We are getting to
know each other
"But why, my lady?'
Because I am
your new manager
Robert, is Nellie
our new manager?
This is an odd situation
But it's very interesting
how it's playing out.
We live in this world
of routines and rhythms
Kevin ate someone's lunch,
Phyllis has a new necklace
Who is this woman?
I came in here simply trying to
get to know you learn your names,
maybe have someone teach me
the company song.
And what I got in return
was nothing but disrespect
You leave me no choice
but to get to know you
in a more intimate way
Hot tub party?
Performance reviews
How can you give us performance
reviews if you don't know us?
On first impressions,
so I recommend smiling
It goes a long way with me
Erin, you really
nailed the hotdogs today
Thanks. I've been reusing the hotdog
water, so it gets more flavor.
It's only going to
keep getting better
So, Andrew, how does your skinny
brunette girlfriend, Jessica,
feel about you
visiting your ex-girlfriend?
Well, we're not
really dating anymore
so basically, I mean I just have to
cross a few t's and dot
a few I's you know.
So you came to get me but you
still have a girlfriend.
I think you should leave
young man
All right, technically yes. I am
still technically dating Jessica
But when I realized
that I wanted you back
and I drove down here
and I didn't want to stop
until I saw you
You didn't even stop to pee?
Gross!
Any luck?
No, he just keeps letting all
the calls go to voice-mail.
Please leave a message
for Andy Bernard
Include your name...
Oh, you're doing so good! Oh, my
God, you're Superman over there
You should take it
It's probably your girlfriend
wondering where you are.
Nope, It's just work
Not important
You know I can really
feel this in my quads.
Getting stronger
You really wouldn't feel those
kinds of results after one session
Just let it vibrate
It's fine.
You could put it
on silent.
I don't think
it does that
Just go to preferences
then click...
Proctology
Andy?
Jim?
Andy, where are you?
I'm home in bed
I've been in bed all day
He's here in Tallahassee trying
to turn my life upside down.
What? You're in Florida?
Andy, Nellie Bertram's
trying to take your job.
What do you mean
take my job?
Like, set up camp
in your office
and is calling
herself the manager.
Okay
Jim, I really appreciate
you looking out for me
but I'm not coming home
without Erin
So, I'll talk to you later
Guys
We cannot do these
performance reviews okay?
If we go into them
you're basically
accepting Nellie
as your manager
And trust me You do not
want her as your manager
Trust you?
The way Pam trusted you to provide for
her so she wouldn't have to work?
Dwight
should she be our manager?
I wouldn't let her
manage a celery farm
Those who can't farm
farm celery
And when was the last time Dwight
and I agreed on anything ever?
All right
let's get going
First up, it is the woman with the
beautiful fingernails and the tiny feet
Phyllis
Nellie, I'm sorry,
but I don't feel comfortable
being evaluated by
someone I don't know
Oh
Okay. I understand. Let me show
you how these are going to go
Dwight
I refuse to be judged by
someone that I do not respect
I lost respect for you
in Florida.
If it was up to me,
you would be in jail forever
Dwight, I have
completed your evaluation
You're getting a raise
What?
Dwight, you carry this company
on your massive shoulders.
You are our Atlas
and for that do you not
think you deserve a raise?
There's no limit to
what I think I deserve
Then you accept it?
Five percent, no less
Absolutely not
Seven percent
Six percent
I know my worth
Raise isn't real
Money isn't real ever since
we got off the gold standard
So, Phyllis, now you know
the rules of the game,
do you care to have a go? I'm fairly
certain you're going to like it.
Phyllis
Pam
So, Phyllis, I have been
very impressed with you.
Really?
Oh, yeah
The way you conquered your
fear and came in here,
and now the way
you sit there.
All very impressive
Um
Are you aware that Nellie
is giving out raises?
Yeah, she gave one
to Dwight, Phyllis
Let me guess,
you want one, too
Take the family
to Disney Town
Land! World
It's not that I don't want Well,
yes, I guess I'd take a raise.
That's not what I'm saying
That's not... Sorry.
Jim, I told Andy to come in
and yet he is still not in.
By contrast, Nellie Bertram
saw a vacuum and filled it
of her business experience
or her relationship
with Jo Bennett, my boss
Jim, would you prefer a nature
metaphor or a sexual metaphor?
Oh, God, nature, please
When two animals
are having sex,
one of them is communicating
a message to the other.
Nothing is
This isn't very helpful
You're going to want
to hear the sexual metaphor
Was that not the
All life is sex
And all sex is competition
Mmm-hmm
And there are no
rules to that game
That wasn't so perverted
now was it?
Was that it?
No, that wasn't bad
My point is there is one person in
charge of every office in America.
And that person
is Charles Darwin
In the end, doesn't he
decide who the manager is?
No. I would have said no
Hmm. Let's see. Review, review,
review Yes, good stuff.
Here you go, have a raise
Oh, great
and take these raises,
what are we saying?
That it's okay for someone to
just take someone else's job?
Shouldn't work like that
No, you know what?
Nellie's right.
That is exactly
how it should work
Darryl,
this office is mine now
No.
Yes
Yes. Sorry it's too late, I'm here.
This is mine. Back off
Ow! Ow
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow
Well fought!
I accept the outcome
Touch me and I'll sue
I've heard that's
amazing when it works
Yeah. If I had my own
Andy, I care about
you and I think...
Sorry. You go
No, go ahead
Well I was just
going to say that
if I had my own fountain
it would be two frogs
and they're spitting
into each other's mouth
It's just stupid. What
were you going to say?
Andy, you broke my heart
Do you know what it feels like
to be constantly rejected by you
and to have to watch
you date someone else?
You broke my heart, too
You broke my heart more
recently and more often.
And I think at some point in my
head it just sort of clicked
that we're not
meant to be.
I'm so sorry that we have not loved
each other at the same time.
So, Pamela, I'm going to
start this review
not by telling you
what you lack
but rather asking you
what it is you want
Really? Okay, we
Um
I like consistency in the manager's
position No weird silent coups
Stuff like that
I'm easy
That's not
really what you want
What you want is a good night's
sleep, working mother of two
Whoa
That's kind of condescending Would
you say something like that to Jim?
Does Jim
have to breastfeed?
Did Jim carry around those babies
for what is it, 12 months?
Be honest Does Jim really
get up in the night?
Well, I mean, the only reason he
doesn't is because I'm breastfeeding
and Philip
doesn't like a bottle
You must be exhausted
Fancy a nap?
No
Go on. Have a nap
Lie down right here
There's a blanket in here
Dreamt I could breathe
underwater like Jacques Cousteau
No one will know
I'll wake you up
When you wake up,
you will earn more money
I think you're amazing
You know that, right?
Go on. Say it,
"I'm amazing.'
I'm amazing
Erin, I think you're making
a big mistake right now
Andy is a nice boy
Really? Because you've been kind
of a "B" to him all afternoon
I was protecting you because
I thought he was no good
But I can tell
you really like him
And he's willing to
lose his job for you
In this economy,
with Europe on the brink
Irene what would
you do without me?
We're not your concern
sweetheart
Besides, Glenn's
going to sue Home Depot
Why?
He got his foreskin caught
in some lawn furniture.
Jim, time for
your review.
No, it's not, because you
don't really work here.
Why are you so
staunchly defending
your friend who
has abandoned you?
Wouldn't you rather come talk with
me maybe, definitely get a raise?
See, that's the thing
can even give raises
Jim, have you ever heard of a
character named Tinker Bell?
Yes
I'm Tinker Bell
No
I'm a magical fairy
who floated into your office
to bring a little bit of magic into
your lives to give you all raises
And we are grateful
But here's the thing
about Tinker Bell, Jim
everyone has to believe in her
or she doesn't exist.
And then she dies.
She dies
Now who here
believes in Tinker Bell?
Let's see it. Show of hands!
I do
Come on, everyone
All right, guys, stop
How?
Come on,
Jim, you're killing her
We believe
Look at this
wonderful recognition
of Nellie's leadership I believe!
That did not go
how I wanted it to
Ugh
I have a whole ton of Erin's
favorite food for the drive back.
Eggplant parm
It's biodegradable
Animals will eat it
Andy, wait! Andy
Andy, wait! Andy, don't go
Andy, I love you! Stop
Oh. This is the wrong Prius
I don't love you.
Erin
I'm sorry.
Andy
Let's get out of here
Okay.
Let's go
Wait, we have to go back
and get your stuff.
No, I don't have
any stuff.
Like your toothbrush and stuff.
I don't have one
You don't have a toothbrush? No
How do you not
have a toothbrush?
I just there's
always one around.
You just use whichever
one is sitting there?
Have you ever heard
of buying a toothbrush?
Of course,
I own my toothbrush
I grew up poor. I had little
formal education, no real skills.
I don't work
especially hard
and most of my ideas are either
unoriginal or total crap.
And yet, I walked right into a job
for which I was
ill-prepared, ill-suited,
and somebody else already
had, and I got it.
If you ask me, that's the
American dream right there
Anything can happen
to anyone.
It's just random