Erin, hey
In two minutes, I want you
to come into this meeting
and tell me that I have a
really important phone call
I'm not going
to take it
because I want him to know how
important the meeting is to me
Who's calling?
Nobody
Just say that I'm... Just make
it up that I have a phone call
And then I'm going
to refuse to take it
You're not going
to take it?
Just make up
a phone call.
It's not
a real call
Just make it up
Oh, okay. And then
come in and tell me.
Okay
It doesn't matter
what it is.
You're not going
to get it, though.
I'm not going
to take it.
And then he's
going to be like
"Wow, this is a really
important meeting."
Copy that.
Okay
Okay, so
tell me exactly
what kind of deal
you are getting right now and
I'll tell you how we can beat it
Well, we've been
going with
Andy?
Yeah?
You have a very
important call
I'm sorry, I'm with a very important
client It'll have to wait
Are you sure? It's
really, really important
There is nothing more important
to me right now than this meeting
Really? Because
your mother is dead
Oh, my God
I don't think she's dead
She's dead.
She was hit by a bus
She's not dead
This is exactly
the kind of thing
my mom pulls
This isn't one of those
times It's the police
They said it's the worst
they've ever seen
Andy, I'm really sorry
about your mother
My deepest
condolences
You must take
this call. It's...
Yeah, line one?
Line two
Okay
Hi
It's Darryl.
Erin told me to pretend to be
a cop and say your mom died.
Oh
Gosh
Dude.
Thank you, Officer
Look, man,
this is a bad idea.
Did she have
any last words or
Really?
That is messed up, man.
Make sure that your client
gets the best deal possible
You're a bad man,
Andy Bernard.
That is so Mom That stuff
can come back and get you.
It's called karma. You do
not want to be messing...
All right
but thank you, Officer
I've got an uncle...
Erin, please hold
all my other calls
Where were we?
Hey, Cathy
Hi
How's it going?
Everything make sense?
I think everything
is under control.
Great
You should sit down.
No, I'm fine
No, I should go
fill out my paperwork
Okay
That was just me
Pregnant Pam
And I make sounds
much worse than this
We know
I'm training a temp to be my replacement
while I'm on maternity leave
I should have
mentioned I'm pregnant
You probably
didn't notice because
it's impossible to tell
because I'm so small
But yeah, I'm pregnant
Oh, come on
Hey. Asking for a friend
do you happen to know
if that new girl is single?
Doubt it
Yeah. Me, too
You doubt it?
What's that?
Why do you doubt
that she's single?
Honestly, I have no idea I just figured
we'd save her from Ryan, right?
What are you
doing with my lunch?
I'm delivering it
from the fridge
It's like a porno. "Hey,
did anybody order a pizza?'
It's not pizza
Yeah, and we're not
about to make love.
I just thought
maybe you'd want
to eat lunch at
your desk today
so that during lunch
we could go down
to the warehouse and
bang out a few tunes
I like the sound of that
Is Kevin here?
You tell me
So word on the street
is she has a boyfriend
Well, he's probably
a drug dealer
That's the best way to
land a hot girlfriend.
You just
You get her hooked on blow
It's going to be nice
to have just like a
healthy, young, fit presence
in the middle of the office.
Yes, aesthetically
speaking, strictly
Yeah
She adds a nice presence
- Good energy.
Yeah, it's going to
be nice to have
someone hot at
Pam's desk, huh?
No, no. Not even
I'm kidding
Oh, my gosh, you guys She's
obviously super cute. I get it.
But I'd like to point
out there is 50 pounds
more of me to love
if that's your thing
Pam, you look more
beautiful now than ever
Radiant
Thank you, guys. Really,
thank you very sweet.
Yeah, you have
this sexy glow.
Well, it's one of
the most common fetishes
Really? Well,
thank you all
You know, it's not just pregnant
women who don't get their due
You know who's gorgeous?
Helen Mirren
Yes
Yes, have you seen her
in a bikini? Amazing
What would be the hottest thing
ever is a pregnant Helen Mirren
Ooh
Okay, okay.
Okay, no, no, no.
This is disgusting. Do you
realize what you're saying?
The hottest thing ever would be
a 66-year-old pregnant woman?
In this case, yes
No
There are universal biological
standards of beauty and attraction
And you are purposefully
celebrating the opposite of them
to mollycoddle
a pregnant woman
No, we're not. No
Yes, you are
And another thing Helen Mirren
was born Helen Mironoff
That's right, you're fake salivating
over a Soviet-era Russian
Nice scatting, man
Thank you. I think I said "doop"
instead of "boop" at one point
Not bad, fellas.
You're better than you look
Hey, screw you
Hey, Robert.
Are we meeting early?
Just taking a stroll
What exactly have
I stumbled upon here?
Well, we're all musicians and
we play together sometimes.
You're a band?
Thank you
We're called
Kevin and the Zits
That was never agreed upon
I miss being in a band
Miss no more
What do you play? Join us
I have a tambourine
Tambourine? You know
I'm the CEO, right?
CEOs don't play tambourines
Tambourines are for girlfriends.
I play harmonica. I think
I have one in the car
Great
Nice.
Guys, Robert is
going to be a zit.
Again, never agreed upon
I had totally given up on hanging
out with Robert California
and now he wants
to be in our band
And when you're in
a rock and roll band
with somebody,
you're bonded for life
Usually that life
is short and tragic
That's okay, right?
Yeah, even cooler
We all got to
go sometime
Hey
Helen Mirren. Hot?
Yeah. Super pretty
Huh
What about Cathy?
The temp?
Yeah, do you think she's hot?
Nope
I'm not asking
if you're into her
Just objectively,
do you find her attractive?
I'm telling you I don't
You don't find
Cathy attractive?
No, I don't
No, I'm not going to tell my
nine months pregnant wife
that I find her replacement
objectively attractive.
Just like I'm not going to
tell my 2-year-old daughter
that violent video games
are objectively more fun
It's true but it
doesn't help anybody
Look at her
Even I want some
fries with that shake
Okay. I don't.
So are we good?
That's just absurd
Yes, because
she's hot, right?
Her breasts are large
her waist is small,
her reproductive health
in ample evidence.
Facial symmetry, come on
The thing about pregnancy is
people treat you differently.
Like you're
a kid, almost.
They lose all
sense of boundaries.
They start acting weird, telling you
things that clearly aren't true.
I know it sounds nuts
but I think Dwight
is the only one who's
telling me the truth.
Dwight, am I hot right now?
Why would I or anyone else think
that you're hot right now?
I can't impregnate you
and that's the driving
force between
male-female attraction
What about before?
Was I attractive before?
Eh.
You were at your most attractive when you
were 24 with a slight gradual decline.
And a steep drop off when you got
pregnant for the first time.
Gradual recovery and
Well, now obviously
you're at an all-time low
Hmm
I think Jim's lying to me about
not being attracted to Cathy
You think Jim's lying?
That's so cute
I know he's lying
5 bucks if you can
get him to admit it
Done
I never touch
a pregnant woman
Yeah, that's
the Dwight I need
If we're going to work together,
we need some ground rules
Okay
Rule one, our only
loyalty is to the truth
I think so. Okay
Rule two,
we stop at nothing
What is that...
Is it... Well, okay
Rule three
Don't fall in love
Yup. Good
We're going to
bust this guy
Honesty is very
important to me
So important And then we
will destroy the man himself
Let's just see how we fee
when we get there.
Well, you came to
the right person.
You have to follow
your intuition, Pam
You don't want to end up
like Elin Nordegren
Actually, what am I saying? You wish
you had her life. No offense, Pam.
None taken
What have you got?
It is called the Matchmaker
Test and it is very powerful
Basically, we have Pam
ask Jim which
of his friends he would
set up with Cathy
If Jim picks
a really hot friend
then we know
he thinks that Cathy's hot
Hmm
Hey, you found us
You guys sound
great, man.
Darryl, Andy, Kevin, this is
Curtis Dorough local musician,
and the officiate
at my wedding.
Local musician?
Local legend.
I used to come hear you
play every week
at the Deerhead
Dude, you're on TV
You're the sportscaster
on Channel Seven.
Go, Eagles
You do that on TV
You guys mind
if they join us?
No.
Yeah, sure
Guys, I've got some
instruments right here
Hey, why don't you
and me play those?
Yeah?
Okay, this is awesome
What shall we play?
Maybe we should warm up
with some scales?
Midnight Rambler?
Yeah.
Midnight what?
Have you heard about
the midnight rambler?
Hey, this is crazy
Hey, I was talking to Cathy
Turns out she is single.
Oh, I stand corrected
I thought it might be fun
to set her up with someone
Any ideas?
Oh. You know who might be good?
Mike Tibbets.
Mike Tibbets, really?
Hey, who's this
Mike Tibbets guy?
What kind of
car does he drive?
Not his mom's car
Yeah, because his mom's car's
probably not a Nissan Z.
Touché?
Kelly, calm down
I mean, I guess
he'd be okay with hair
Okay, you should see
if he'll get hair plugs
I don't think Jim
cares about his hair
Yeah, but I do, Pam. Okay?
It's called
being a nice person
I don't see what's
so ugly about him
He's got the broad
face of a brewer
Jim's on to me
Hmm?
Yeah, Jim barely
talks to Mike.
We had to go through
like two levels
of friends to even
find his profile.
Jim picked someone
just unattractive
enough to shut me up
without tipping it
Just ugly enough
to have deniability
Yup
Mike Tibbets is like the most
boring looking guy I know.
So if that was for the Matchmaker
Test, I think I'm in the clear
If that wasn't for
the Matchmaker Test then
Cathy, he's a really
nice guy.
Well, Jim may be
lying with his words
but he can't
lie with his body
I'm going to write
something mean on his wall
No, Kelly, don't
The male reveals attraction
through unconscious and
involuntary physical signs.
The puffing of the chest
Mirroring
Increased blood flow
to the crotch
I say we start there
With the crotch?
With the crotch
Whoo
Psst
We're not here.
Who said that?
Exactly
How'd I get
this long triangle?
Okay, just shut up
Is he puffing out his chest?
I can't tell.
It's unnaturally sunken
Busted. He just was
mirroring. Did you see that?
No. Maybe he just
said something funny
Jim has no discernible sense of
humour, Pam. You should know that.
I think he's just
making her laugh
Time for me to find out
Why is he making
her laugh so much?
Just going to
walk over here. Whoa
I'm slipping and falling! I'm stumbling.
I need something to grab onto
Hey, are you okay?
I'm fine
Dwight! Dwight
I'm totally fine
Yes?
What? Jim?
Sorry about that
Cramp. I'm just
Dwight
Why?
I'm sorry,
I fell down, Mr. Balance
Leave
Does your husband
ever have soft erections?
Because if not I just grabbed
a very soft penis for nothing
Why was he making
her laugh so much?
Hey, I'll just be a second
Yeah, take your time
Okay.
That line from Zoolander.
Mmm-hmm?
It was from a deleted scene
so we were both right
Told you
Do I hand in
my expense reports
to a particular
accountant or
Oscar, Cathy
has a question
Sorry, I'll just
go ask Oscar
Yeah?
You okay?
Why won't you just admit
that she's attractive?
It's kind of annoying
that you won't say it
Okay, what can I do
to make you believe me?
Well, Dwight had this idea and
I thought it was kind of crazy
but maybe that's
where we are now
She called it crazy? Man
That's insulting
All I did was
propose a makeshift
lie detector test.
Monitoring his
blood pressure, pulse
perspiration and
breathing rate.
Yeah, it's nuts But I don't
know what else to do
And she called it nuts?
Seriously,
that was hot
Feel like you and the
newsman had a groove going
Did you know that Lisa
toured with Chaka Khan?
Are you serious?
From Star Trek?
Hey, you caught
some of that?
I caught it
What, you don't like the Blues?
I might enjoy seeing
you guys play the Blues
Well, we are playing
We're all playing together.
These are our jam buddies
It's a jam session We go
where the music takes us
I think the music
left without you.
Come on
Stop shoving me
"Stop shoving me Stop
grabbing my penis.' Grow up.
Take off your jacket
and take a seat.
When it lies, the human body
exhibits many telltale signs.
Really?
This could all go away
if you just
tell me the truth
Are you all in line?
Why don't you go check out
the sympathy cards, old man?
Now I'm going to ask you
just a few simple questions
Wait for this to
constrict. Here we go
Is your name Jim Halpert?
Sì.
Wait, that's it? That's the
question you're going to ask him?
We have to start
with a baseline question
to establish
what the truth is
You have to share
the machine with others
Well, that's
what they taught me
in my 19th
century kindergarten
Okay, Dwight, come on
You can go first.
Jim, are you serious?
You know what? This reminds me,
Cece needs a new toothbrush
Maybe we could
switch instruments
Yeah
'Cause my body's
starting to get bruised
Yeah, maybe everyone move one
instrument to the right.
We had to leave because
of creative differences
Yeah, they kind of
had a specific sound
that didn't really
fit in with our thing
Guys, this means they're
Kevin and the Zits now
No, man. We are
Well
I know, I know
Okay, you're done
I have a new
heart, you know
Do you really
Tin Man? Okay
Where were we?
No, I'm not worried.
Because this lie isn't
for me, it's for Pam
And when she gets her body
back and her confidence back
yes, I will tell
her the truth.
That
I had feelings for a co-worker
today that I haven't had in years
In my defense,
he was grabbing my crotch
fairly aggressively
at the time
Do you find
Cathy Simms attractive?
No
Yep, he's lying
See. Was that so hard?
I am not lying
Really?
Pam, are you really going to listen
to his stupid homemade test?
I would listen to
my homemade test
because your husband
is definitely lying
In fact, he's lied about every
question even his name.
Who are you, really?
Wait, what?
Look at the numbers. Every single
time it's come up 150 over 100
Your husband is
a pathological liar
Jim, you have
high blood pressure
He is definitely
attracted to her
Doesn't your dad have
high blood pressure?
Yeah, but I don't smoke
When was the last time
you went to the doctor?
I don't know. It's important
to go every month
and get your
prostate checked
You can do it at
home by yourself
with your finger
You just stick
Okay
Dwight, stop
I'm not kidding. I mean, I need
you to take care of yourself
What would we do if
something happened to you?
Okay, easy. Trust me
I'm around for the long haul
It's not really your choice, though, is it?
Death waits for no man
Okay
Come on, let's go
I want to call your doctor
Doesn't it worry you in the slightest
that Jim is not his real name?
Just go home
it doesn't matter
But the
Hey, Cece? s toothbrush
Thank you
Ooh,
baby, I love your way
Every day
Want to be
with you night and day
And day
Ooh, baby, I love your way