Hey, Jim Stanley's back
from the hospital today.
Can you sign his card?
Oh, great
"Glad they didn't mix up your
tonsillectomy with a mustachectomy."
That's not good
Oh, because your jokes
are all hilarious
It's nice.
It's funny
It mentions his
tonsillectomy and makes
a funny little joke
about his mustache
Stanley doesn't
have a mustache
Yeah, he does
Pam, hit the brakes Stanley
does not have a mustache.
I think he has a mustache
Okay, Phyllis sits
across from him every day
Phyllis, does he
have a mustache or not?
Oh, I don't know.
Now I think he doesn't
Phyllis,
what are you talking
The whole card
depends on this
Okay, the man's
worked here for 25 years
How can none of us
picture his face?
Because we come
here to do our jobs
We don't stick our noses
in other people's business
Okay. Which one of these
looks more right?
Neither of those
looks like any person
that has ever
existed or been dreamt of
in the history
of human insanity
That said
the one on the left
Guys, that's the elevator
What if it's him?
Okay, quick,
who says "mustache"?
Yep
Who says "no mustache"?
Ah!
Hey!
He does have one
Yes
Welcome back, Stanley.
"Good morning, Robert, '
says no one
because our receptionist
is in Florida.
Pam
Oh
Is this a video conference you're having
with "Drake featuring Swizz Beatz"?
Um, no, I was just
having a cup of coffee
kind of warming up
for the day.
People, you should come
to work already warm
9:00 to 10:00 a.m. is the most productive
potential that human beings...
Sorry! Sorry, everyone I'm late
but you are all here, so no
harm done at a by my lateness
Nellie, really, 9:50
Oh, here's
what happened.
7:46, my alarm clock goes off,
I hear it, whack the snooze.
Nine minutes. Buzz,
off it goes again, whack
Seven more times I did that
Buzz, whack, buzz, whack.
By the time I got up,
it was 10 minutes ago
No will power
That is my curse
I've never believed will power
was very important in a woman
would have shown up
to work
nearly an hour late
for no reason.
Oh, I assure you
I would have done
I did And I'll keep doing it
No, no, there's something going
on some stress in your life.
Well, yes, there is the whole
moving to Scranton nonsense
Thirty boxes arrived yesterday from
England and two trunks from Florida.
Then, I have to
move into my apartment
in this dreadful,
God knows where it is
backwater,
suburb of a suburb
and I mean no offense,
but are there
a lot of Irish people
living around here?
Yes
- Oh
No offense
None taken
Actually, Nellie, this monologue
you're delivering is very offensive.
Ooh! Ay caramba! The natives
are getting restless.
Who's a native?
Excuse me, the tone here
is getting quite hostile
I would appreciate it if
you would keep that stuff
on the basketball court
What does that mean?
Okay, okay
If you'd let me finish
Or the squash court or
the supreme court Hmm?
Nellie?
Yes, Robert
You're clearly under a lot
of stress with the moving
and the work situation
you've found yourself in
Yeah
Let's help her out
shall we?
Go above and beyond today
to show her some of that
warm Scranton hospitality
Jim, Dwight, take the day
Help Nellie move those
boxes into her new place
Why Jim?
What?
The rest of you, let's throw a
party at the end of the day
to welcome the newest member
of our little community.
I'm sorry, we're throwing
a party for someone
because they're
being horrible?
I'm sorry.
We're taking work time
to move someone's personal
belongings into their new apartment
I'm still not sure why
this woman is even here!
Why is she here?
Two crazy kids on
the journey of life
Going to Pennsylvania
On the road with
my new girlfriend
But first, a small pit stop to break
up with my current girlfriend,
who is at her parents' cabin
in southern Pennsylvania
Oh, that must be nice
Mmm-hmm
It's a beautiful place Great
place to let her down easy.
Oh, no, no I meant that must
be nice to have parents.
Oh. Hmm
Time to have a little kiss
No
Mmm. Sorry, right
No kisses until the
breakup is official Yes
I believe in that
Yes, so do I
I think that's important. That is
important. Bummer, but important
Important.
Mmm-hmm
I can't believe he's making
us throw a party for her
She's always late
she's always rude
It kind of makes me want to
throw a really bad party.
Yeah
On purpose
Phyllis
We should do it right
here in the break room
Ooh
Order carrot cake
And Jessica
just so you know
this is way more about my love for
Erin than anything wrong with you
Well, Andy, I'm upset, but you did
this in the best way possible
and I knew you as a lover and
I'll remember you as a gentleman.
Okay. That was one
minute and 10 seconds
Consider it nailed
should try it again
This time
worst case scenario
Okay, here we go. Jessica, I'm really
sorry. I just need you to know
What?
I just need
you to know
What? I didn't
sleep well last night
Ow
Nellie, that reminds me do you
want this chair in the bedroom?
'Cause I don't think it's
going to fit through the door
Don't listen to Jim. Have you
ever seen him play Tetris?
"Oh, I think I'll just
use this line horizontally
"Oh, I have no idea
what a gift this line is.'
That was one time
I will get the chair in. Watch the
great "Schrut-ini" work his magic
Oh, no, really? Magic, no,
no, no let's not go there
No, nothing is more
repellent than magicians
Bunch of grown men
waving wands
pulling bunnies
out of body crevices
Magicians are repulsive
Next topic
Excuse me, one second
Hi
- Hey, what's up?
Oh, nothing, just hauling
some cube with Dwight.
Hauling cube
That's moving boxes
We just came up with the
term to make it sound cooler
So, we're planning
this party for Nellie,
and we're going to
make it really bad.
It sounds like
every other party
No, we're going to
make it like a prank
like order bad food, give her
this passive-aggressive card
Oh, hire a magician
What?
Trust me
Okay.
Wow, there's a lot of cars
here This is just weird.
Andy. Hi, what are
you doing here?
Hey, Lauren
look at you.
I'm just on my way back
from this business trip
thought I'd stop
and say hi to Jessica
Aw
Why is Erin with me?
That's a great question
She is my co-worker and she needed
a ride because she totaled her car
Oh, God
So I'm Erin
Yeah, this is Erin
Hi. Nice to meet you
Well, Jess went out for a run
but she'll be back soon
Mmm-hmm
Hey, ladies,
Andy's here
Okay, Andy, that is
a bachelorette party
This is Jessica's friends and they've
been drinking during the daytime
Should we go?
Yeah
You know, we had such a quick
window to make this work.
I think we should
probably just
Oh, Jess look who stopped
by after his business trip
Andy, hey
are called
presidential-sized in England
a "Tweeter" account
Yes, you should
Ooh
I have to see
these shoes.
Oh
Who is this guy?
There's the two of them
taking a hike
I'm guessing he's
some kind of friend
Boyfriend
Here's the two of them
kissing at a beach
and kissing at
the Eiffel Tower
I'm guessing he's some kind
of close romantic friend
Like a boyfriend?
You read my mind.
Yeah
Whoa. Here's one with
his face whited out.
Hmm
Maybe someone threw
a pie in his face.
New theory, he's a hated
Italian politician
Better theory,
this is her ex-boyfriend
and they went through some
kind of painful breakup
Oh
- Nellie
so sorry,
we were just
discovered Benjamin
That's what I call my box
full of photos of Henry
Why not call...
Shh
God, we owned
this flat together
Then one morning just
like that, he was gone
He ran off with a waitress
at our favorite restaurant.
That's awful
What kind of restaurant?
Dwight
afford the flat myself
So I sold it at a loss
Ah, but what's 10 years
of bliss down the drain
compared with the thrill of starting
over with nothing and no one?
I'm so sorry These must
be very painful memories
If it would
help you to forget
in the brain stem
with this candlestick
Thank you. No
Look, Jim, Dwight, please,
don't tell anyone about this
No, no, of course
Just one quick question
was this Halloween or
God, no
That's the most embarrassing
thing of all of this.
What kind of fool gets her heart
broken by a bloody stage magician?
You know what, Pam? I was thinking
maybe we should change course here
Let's give up on
all this mean stuff
What? No. No. I just
had this brilliant idea
Everyone loved it.
You don't have
a copyright on pranks
at this than you
No, that's not Jim, could
you give us a hand?
Absolutely. Yeah
Call it off, Pam.
Call it off, okay?
It's way more complicated
than you think.
Cancel the magician.
Trust me.
Oh, okay.
Okay, I will
That's a great idea
Yeah. Okay
Pam, we have a great idea.
- Listen to this
We're going to have the
fluorescent lights flickering.
It's going to
make everyone sick
Or what if
Okay.
...we discuss the idea of doing
the party totally normal
Like, not mean
Just a regular party
Not mean
I knew she'd crack I wanted
to leave you out, you know.
We're in far too deep We can't
change course at this point
What are you talking about?
Of course we can
What I mean to say is
we don't want to.
Toots, we're not stopping this
train, so get off the tracks
Suck it
Andy
It'll be fine. Just act natural.
Do you want a gummy penis?
No. I'll just have
some gummy bears
These are delicious
But they're penises
And we come to Matthew
the guy who was
with his old girlfriend
basically the whole time
we were together
Oh, no
Eww! That seems gross
at first blush, right?
But relationships are always
more complicated than you think.
Know Matthew's history
with this other woman
Maybe she saved his life
I don't know
rush to judgment
about Matthew
Maybe we don't
pop that one.
No. Pop it
Pop it
Hey
Sorry It's kind of a mad house
Oh, Megan
You are one of the good
ones, Nard Dog. Aw
No, really.
Where's my Andy?
He's out there
Are you going to
sing for us?
Well, you guys are doing a pretty
good job with the scary yelling, so
That's not like you That's not
like you Come on, sing! Sing
By yon bonnie banks
and by yon bonnie braes
Okay, they're almost here
What?
Come on! If you guys
are going to be mean
can't you at least
be subtle?
Oh, in the warehouse
we'd use code names
for people we
wanted to talk about
Andy was "Jelly Roll.' Mike
was "Dennis the Menace.<'
Ryan was "Douche Bag.'
Hey, that's not a code name
That's just an insult
Plus, everyone would
know who you meant Yeah.
No, that's a great idea.
Yes, let's have a code name
How about "Mondays"? I hate Mondays.
Mondays are the worst
Nobody's named Monday
Hey, how about we go with "Pam"?
Simple, easy to remember
Because there's someone
already here named Pam
Shh. Here she comes
Hey
Welcome to your party
Everybody, get comry now This first
song's over a half-hour long.
Best gig ever. They asked
me to play only originals
I said, "Have you heard my originals?
They're terrible."
They said, "Even better." I said, "I get
it. It's an ironic party for Nellie.'
Maybe we should just go
No, I got to do this
Hey, Jessica
can I talk to you?
Uh, yeah, sure
what's up?
Maybe we could
talk in private
Yeah, what is it?
Well, first,
let me just say that
done with the
sort of ugly bits
that we can
stay friends
You're breaking up
with me?
Uh
No. No
You always do this.
You twist my words around
Part of me thinks we should
just end this right now
Oh, my God Are you
leaving me for Erin?
You said she wasn't relationship
material, and she wasn't as good as me
But it's her, isn't it?
Whoa
That... No
Okay, you want honesty?
Super honesty time
I'm gay.
What?
You did not, Kenny
You invited me to
go shopping with you
I like hanging out with you
You're a cool guy.
Which proves my point
that I'm gay.
JESSICA
Andy, you're not gay
and you seemed
pretty excitable.
Well, I was faking it.
I had to fake it every time
with John Stamos
doesn't make sense
Well, I mean I was
good at hiding it...
It's fine, Andy
we were going to get
married or anything.
I'm just upset for now
Understandable, and I'm
really sorry I really am.
So, we should probably go
This humble
but sincere effort is
all for our valued new colleague.
Excellent.
To Nellie Bertram,
you are a most welcome
and friendly presence
at our company
Cheers
Why, thank you.
Pam, on the other hand
is a most unwelcome
entitled and unfriendly
presence in our company
Cheers
Nellie is terrific
but to be honest
every day, I imagine how happy I'd be
if Pam died.
Oh, well, I feel that as
someone who knows Pam
only a little bit enough, a good
amount not the most, though,
she is misunderstood
and that maybe there's
some stuff in her past
that you guys
don't know about
that's a little
messed up and probably
makes her such a
torture to work with.
ALL We hate Pam! We hate Pam We hate Pam!
We hate Pam
So we've established
No
...that you guys hate Pam
Do you ever wish she
would just disappear?
Oh
That was a really
rough scene
Right? Rough scene
Yeah.
At least we can kiss now
Oh, yeah
You know, that stuff that I said
about you to her, that's just...
You know, I was dating
her at the time.
Yeah
Yes, of course
Ugh
Yeah
Probably from
seeing that turkey
Oh, yeah
When we drove by the farm
Always does that.
Are you Nellie? I think
you're my volunteer.
Come on
over here, huh?
No, I'll do it. I will volunteer
No, Nellie should
No, I'll do it.
Oh, big guy, huh? How's the air up there?
Watch out for birds
All right, let's
do some card magic
Now, what I want
you to do is,
I want you to pick a card
just by looking at it.
Do not say what it is
It's the four of hearts
Oh, no, it's
Looks like we got a guy from
another country here, huh?
No hablo el cardo, senor?
All right, the card is picked Now,
sir, will you please shuffle the deck?
You didn't just do that
on purpose, did you?
Why is Jim treating
the magician poorly?
Little known fact about me
before I was a magician
at a rope factory
Not true because
that's not a real place
But I never could seem to
figure out those knots
That's not a real knot When you
pull on it, it disappears.
What the hell?
All right Where's Phyllis?
Who's Phyllis?
Look, this is really uncool, okay?
I put on a clean show here
Okay, scram, wizard
What?
You heard me
Wow. Nellie I'm sorry.
If I'd known
Jim and Pam
would use this party
as an excuse to
abuse a magician
Well, I thought
it was quite fun
In fact, I think they're brilliant
employees in their own way.
Don't you see
what I see?
Interesting, yes.
No, yes, I see that
Great work, team
Great party
You think this
is a great party?
This cake has vegetables in
it like a salad bar, Robert
How do I get this
taste out of my mouth?
What? Why are we
one thing.
Oh, hello
Hey, everybody
look who's here
What are you doing here?
Hi. Super duper honesty
time, I'm not gay
In fact I'm so not gay that
I'm in love with a girl
Her name is Erin Hannon
and she is right there.
She's sweet,
funny and beautiful
and total
relationship material
Why the hell did
you come back here?
Go away
Get lost
Get out
Okay.
You're done! Get out
Bye, guys. Go. Go.
You ruined my party
Who does that?
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, run away
Run away
KENNY
You're disgusting
I can't believe
you're not gay
Yeah,
get out of here
Don't come back
Uh-oh.
You don't even
know how to drive
Loser! Nice car
Hey, Hank
Yes, ma'am.
I thought I was very specific about
you not letting up a magician
Yes, ma'am
I got my eyes open
Well, turns out he
actually made it up there.
What? That ain't right
Yeah, he came and went
Wait a minute, you said
it was a magician, right?
You don't think he could have used...
It couldn't have been
Let's just go
Good night, Hank