Oops. A little help
Wow, your hair
is really thinning
Standing is proven to be
healthier, increases productivity
and just looks cooler
Picture someone
doing something heroic
Now, was he sitting
or standing?
Not counting FDR
Every second you sit there
is an hour off your life
Look at all of you
I feel like you're
in a suicide cult
No, no, no. You're
way off on that one.
Are you really
comfortable standing there?
I tried one of those, and I just
couldn't find the sweet spot
Hey, guys, let's just all admit it, okay?
Dwight's better than us
He had the guts
to stop sitting,
and he's never, ever gonna
go back on it, right?
That's right, Jim
Hey, man
Hey
Taking a
load off, huh?
No. Putting a
load on, more like
Good luck with that
Last thing I need is luck
Thank you so much
What are you up to?
Oh, look out
Just... What are you doing?
Think fast. Ha ha
Give that back Come on. Prank
That's real creative
You know what you're
right It's not my best
'Cause you could
easily just bend over
and pick that up
right?
I could. I just don't
feel like it, loser
Because you're sitting?
Standing
Okay.
Don't
Because you're sitting?
Standing
You know
I have to do this
I know
Whoa
Andrew Baines Bernard
I think you could
just do Andy Bernard
Andrew Baines Bernard
I love filling
these out 'cause it's like
Oh, I'm taking a test
but I know the answers
In four seconds, my wife is going
to be coming through that door
I told her she
could work here
Under no circumstances
can that be allowed to happen
There you are, honey
How on earth did
you miss the elevator?
What was that?
I don't know.
He wasn't talking to me
But if I were you,
I wouldn't hire his wife
That's why my foundation
the Dream For
A Wish Foundation
is gonna put them
out of business.
They're not gonna
know what hit them
Everyone, I'd like
to introduce my wife
Mrs. Robert California
Mrs. California
this is everyone
Hello.
Hi
Welcome.
Call me Susan, please
Last night at dinner,
Susan and I were talking
about her returning
to work.
So she's here today
to see if there's a good fit
Something tells me it
just might work out
This is Andy Bernard,
the regional manager
Hello. Nice to meet you
Hey there.
It's a pleasure. Welcome
Thank you
Andy, would you
be so kind
as to show Susan
around the office,
introduce her to
various departments
find a place
where she'll shine?
I would love to,
but I have to be
completely honest
with you guys.
We're 100% staffed up
Andy, let's see if there's a
good fit first then we'll talk
All right.
Knock, knock, knock
You don't have to say
it if you're doing it
Remember how you said
that you were looking
for a place in the office
to do calisthenics
and aerobics?
Ah, weightlifting, yeah
Well, today's
your lucky day
I have opened
in this very office building
Dwight Schrute's
Gym for Muscles
Want to take a look?
I'll take a look
Your path from
obesity begins right here
I've been meaning to join
a gym For my health.
I used to say I wanted to live long
enough to see a black president.
I didn't realize how
easy that would be.
So now I want to
live long enough
to see a really,
really gay president
or a supermodel president.
All the different
kinds of presidents
Obese people in my office
building are a drain on resources
Chairs wear out faster
It takes more freon
to keep them cool
They flush the
toilets more often
Plus, their massive BMs
bust the rivets on my pipes
But a gym turns
fat into cash.
All right, the DM
Express is pulling out
All right, well it was really
nice to meet you, Brian
Ah, it's actually Ryan
Oh, Ryan.
Yeah
Bitch
We will start
here at Erinville
Hi
Reception
Your classic
one-man operation
Although, I was
watching a movie
and Meryl Streep
had two secretaries
I was watching a movie and a bunch
of apes took over San Francisco
Just saying
Two secretaries could convey
a sense of importance
and success to our clients
Certainly worth exploring.
Wouldn't you agree, Andy?
I'll explore exploring it - Good
Seems like you have
this under control,
so I'll just duck out and run
the company for a while.
Okay
Okay, next stop
on the tour, sales
Here we go Station
stop Jim Halpert.
Oh, boy, our resident
truth teller Uh
All right, have at it
Let her rip.
What do you hate
about this place?
Well, it's sales,
so you have to be able
to live in the
world of rejection
Maybe you do
Hi, I'm Dwight
Sales is really not so
hard, okay It's paper
We have it,
and they want it so bad
they are willing
to pay for it
Jim?
Well, it's not that easy
It's kind of
sometimes difficult
It's the second-easiest
job in the world
Being a mom
I love shopping.
And sales is just
the other side of that
That's true
You know, if you joined
our sales department
you would be working
very closely with our
department head,
Mr. Dwight Schrute
That's me
Dwight, why don't you tell Susan
about some of your hobbies
Oh Mmm-hmm Survival skills.
Ranking of animals
Maybe over a beer
after she's closed
her first sale.
Well, make that a red wine and
I'll tell you my animal rankings
How am I supposed
to pull this off?
The entire office is being nicer to
her than they've ever been to me.
What I wouldn't give
for one of Phyllis'
classic room-clearing
farts right now.
Ready?
What do you think?
Huh?
Umm, no
No. This is not a gym
This is like a
scene out of Saw V.
You haven't even
looked around yet
Look
Gravel bucket squat yoke
Right?
Hmm
Dedicated phone
book ripping station
You ever cut tin before? No
Five yards in and your
forearms will be on fire
Plus, I will buy
the tin back from you
that you cut for
two cents a yard
Now, let's go
over membership
I'm gonna need
the first month's
and the last month's
up front for $49 a month
But every third
month is $59 a month
But the fourth month is a
discount month at $19 per month.
Obviously, you know
how a gym works.
So you know I'm not gonna
pay money for this
You want people to
come to your gym?
Make a real gym
Darryl
accounting might
be a good fit
because I really
clicked with Oscar
and I do have some
experience with bookkeeping
But we already have a surplus
of accountants as it is
customer service
um, HR, even.
Those are fully
staffed as well
Are you telling me that there's
no one in this entire office
that could use
an extra pair of hands?
Yes
I am the CEO, and I am telling
an employee of mine what to do.
Let me beat around
the bush for a second
Our chairman of the board has
some very strong feelings
Robert, it's all right.
This is very uncomfortable
Obviously, there's no place for
me here, so thank you for trying
Why don't we
just let it go?
No.
Absolutely not
Andrew, there must be
something you can do.
There must be. Think
Well, there are
a lot of considerations
It's not a bad thing
to have the CEO owe you one
All right
Well, then, welcome aboard
So what happens next?
We get you over to HR and then
get you set up with accounting.
Hang on
Hello?
- Say "hello, grandma."
Hi, gam-gam
Hold one finger up to Susan.
You'll just be a second.
You numbskull!
You were given
a very simple task.
More clear with you.
Now say, "Are you
taking your medicine?"
Are you taking your med-meds?
Why can you not say
exactly what I tell you?
Undo this. Undo it.
You didn't say good-bye
to your grandmother.
We promised we'd
never say good-bye
Attention! I am
now accepting memberships
for the Dwight Schrute
Gym for Muscles
First 20 members
can take advantage
of our "pay what
you weigh" promotion
All I need
is another gym.
As if I don't
have enough drama
We have a gym at home
It's called the bedroom.
Who's spotting who?
"Don't use the bike
in the corner,
"that's Bruce's.
Jeremy says...'
Enough. Oscar, enough
Kelly?
I have these sneakers
which are basically just like
a gym for your feet, so...
That's okay. I know
how to build a business
You gotta bet the
black people to do it
to get the white
people to do it.
Then you gotta get the black
people to stop doing it.
One step at a time
Did you bring your
passport with you?
Who walks around
with their passport?
Well, I do
Always ready
for adventure
Have you had any?
No
Hey, guys
So Robert doesn't want
his wife working here.
So now that she is,
we have to drive her away
Andy, if he didn't want her working
here, then why did you hire her?
Oscar, it was a mistake
But one that can be fixed by
all of us being mean to her.
How can we do that?
She's simply wonderful
This is all pathetic
How mean are
we talking about?
It would be great if
she were gone by lunch
Erin, you're up. Find her a place
to work but not too comfortable
Got it. I know exactly
which stapler to give her.
Here you go
Um, do you think it
would be possible
to move to that
desk over there?
Because this seems a bit cramped,
and I don't have a computer
Well, that's a sales desk
Yeah. You need to be over
here with us accountants
Just sit here
and be quiet
And if you have a question
just raise your hand
But I'm gonna save you some time,
sweetie, and give you the answer now
No, I don't think
we should be trying
to make this
place seem unpleasant.
I think we should
let this place
just crush her
spirit by itself
what it's doing
That's Gerald
Oh, wow. So cute
Oh, that is so cute
Oh, he's so tiny
Is he in a ladle?
Yeah, he's in a ladle
That's adorable How on earth
did you get him in a ladle?
He did it himself
Is that ladle
stainless or
Oh, stainless
Williams Sonoma
Excuse me, waiter
there's a dog in my soup
It's not that
kind of ladle
Very cute
Let me see.
Just the battery
on these things
I'm sorry,
I've gotta recharge this
Last time I had a job
I remember I hated
the boss' wife
Of course, she was
married to Robert.
Your employees don't
seem to be taking to me.
Andy
Andy, could you
step in here, please?
We'll fix this
What is going on?
Please
Ah, Andrew, my wife
has brought up an issue that
requires your attention
So, if you'll excuse me
I should step out,
get to the ATM before that homeless
man sets up camp for the night
Okey-dokey, artichokey
You hate it, don't you?
Do you not want me here?
Why would you say that?
It's okay.
I understand I'm not
sure how I would fee
about having the boss'
wife work for me either
It's not that exactly
But it is something
Let's just say that if you
don't want to work here
I am totally
prepared to respect that
Why would you not
want me working here?
I don't know
what you're going through
My husband can be a very
difficult man to read, can't he?
Yes
The dude is an enigma
So he is mixed up
in this, isn't he?
Got it
What do you
think you're doing?
Getting my sweat on
I build you this
temple to the human body
and you're lifting
what, five pounds?
I just did, like,
35 minutes on the treadmill
I was watching you. You want to
know how long it really was?
No
Eight minutes!
Dude, I'm gonna be
here all week, right?
Five days a week. I figure I'll start slow
Is that the same philosophy
you apply to buffalo wings?
I want you to bring that same
buffalo wing passion to this gym
I'm gonna make you
look like Lebron James
It's Lejon Brames
That's what I said.
Yeah
Get it right I know.
Cameras
Still here. Terrific
Andy and I had
a great conversation
And I just want
to let you know
that I am not going
to be working here
Well, that's a shame
It just was one of those things...
Is it?
Because we
talked about it
and it seems like that
might be what you want.
Which is fine
Where did this come from?
Did Andy say that?
No, he did not
But I could tell
he was struggling
to understand what
was expected of him
What's the struggle? He made a
great call hired a great person
You sure about that?
Absolutely.
No games?
No games
Because Andy seemed to think
there was some information
he was not able
to share with me
Enough of this I
mean, real Enough
It's gotten way out of hand
Andrew, this is my wife
Whatever privacy you were trying to
protect between us, I thank you for
But it is not
welcome right now
Just be honest
Andy
Yes
Why do you keep
looking at my husband?
Andy, just answer
the question.
No games?
No games
Okay
of funny, actually.
Robert storms in
and he says
"In four seconds
my wife's gonna be in here
"I told her she
could work here
"Under no circumstances can
that be allowed to happen."
You lying son of a bitch
Tell my wife you're lying
That's not true, is it?
No, it's not
I tell the truth
most of the time
and I was just telling the
truth about your husband
Jim knows. He was there
This is preposterous
Robert
Let's get Jim in here.
Where's Jim?
He just rolled out
and crawled out
Can you call security tell them
to keep an eye out for him?
Time to settle this
Wait, wait, wait
Hold on, hold on
Just real quick.
Real quick, open... Okay
That's weird
Well, he's gotta be
around here somewhere
Ow! Ow
Ow
Creed, I was never
here, all right?
Okay. What about
your friend?
Oh, boy
This is my gym, my rules You do
exactly as I say no questions asked
Yeah, I'm gonna
ask questions,
and I might not
do what you say
First thing, we're gonna
stretch the pelvic bowl
Ready? Get down on the floor
Okay, I'm not doing that
Really?
Too embarrassing
for you? Huh?
You wish that every exercise was
strutting around the gym like the Fonz?
Well, how do you think
the Fonz got so cool?
He stretched
his pelvic bowl
Darryl joined
Looks that way
Nice pelvic bowl. Deep
Hello, Jim
No, no. No, no, no
Don't. Damn it, Tuna
So, I think you know
what we want to know
Do I?
Yes
I know. I do
Jim, I've had enough
of your unhelpfulness
I'm not really sure how I can
For God's sake,
did Robert tell you
that he didn't
want me working here?
That's the thing
See, I didn't want to get in the
middle of this Still don't.
But here's something
I feel that maybe,
if we take a step back
this is a simple case of
anxiety to work with a spouse
I think we've got
ourselves an answer
No That makes complete
sense, right?
Thank you all for a
wonderful day Perfect!
Jim
Yes?
Answer the question
please.
Want me to tell you.
To be really honest,
my wife works here
And I love it
She literally
makes me work harder
She makes me smarter. She makes
me remember why I'm here
And between us she's on
maternity leave right now
and I would love to leave
this room and see her face
but it's just
what I'm thinking
All right. Thanks
Yes. All right
Uh.
Yeah
Thank you
Andy
Hey, Mrs. California
Hey. I'm sorry about the
position you were put in today.
You know, honestly we all
wanted you to work there
Except for him
Especially me
Yes, I thought we
really hit it off.
Yeah
Well, different circumstances
Who knows?
Maybe after all
this settles down
Totally
It's a date
Hmm?
You're nothing!
You're so weak
You call yourself
a man? Huh?
This doesn't help me I don't
respond to that kind of strategy.
Okay, fine
Finish your set on your own and
never come back to my gym again!
Dwight, come back and spot me
All right, I'll help you
But first, you gotta
tell me what your goal is
What do you want?
To push this bar up
No! Because if that was the case,
the bar would be up by now
What is your goal?
Help me
What do you want?
To look good for Val
Val Kilmer?
I don't buy it
that doesn't make any sense
Wow
I figured out your goal
I am gonna make you the buffest
dude Val Kilmer has ever seen