Hey. So we saw
a new billboard.
Yeah. Pretty cool, huh?
What better way to announce
our new slightly lower prices
than with an ad campaign?
And what better face for an ad campaign
than our new regional manager?
How'd it look?
You've seen it, right?
No. Andy, somebody defaced it.
What? How?
Morning, Stanley
There's this thing that people
tend to do with billboards
How do I put this?
If there's an opportunity for a graffiti
artist to work in a phallic shape
interacting with the
artwork, it'll happen.
And Andy gave them
that opportunity.
Erin, how long did we order
those billboards for?
Six months
Oh, God.
I need you to call
the billboard company
great billboard. Funny, edgy right up to
the line without crossing it. Loved it.
Which one did you see?
Washington Street
The one with like 20 dongs on it.
Okay. Don't be gross
What's going on? Somebody
defaced the billboards
we just put out
in an inappropriate way
That's funny
Wait, from the photo
shoot with you and me?
Yeah, Dwight
No. No
No, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no. No
Schrute Farms
is very easy to find.
It's right in the middle of
the root vegetable district
If the soil starts
to get acidic
you've probably
gone too far.
Just give us the address
we'll look it up online
It's simpler this way.
It's really not
Now stated arrival
time is 3:00 p.m.
I don't get the reason for this party.
Yeah. What's the reason?
What's the reason, Andy?
What's the reason?
It's just a garden party Sheesh!
You don't need a reason
to throw a garden party
any more than you need a reason
to throw a birthday party
It's a garden party
You don't need a reason
A few other super simple reminders.
No burping, no slurping
When eating, take small bites and chew
thoroughly with your mouth closed
Yes, Darryl?
What happens when
we're done chewing?
Do we spit it out on the floor or keep
it in our mouths the rest of the time?
I get it. I'm being
a little overbearing
But I promise to be
under-bearing for a week
if you guys just
all step it up.
Andy, we understand basic table
manners We're not children.
Yeah. It's just
a picnic
This is not a picnic, Phyllis
It's a garden party.
There's a grill in the
warehouse I could bring
Oh, ew Please don't.
Not a barbecue
It's better than a barbecue It's dignified.
Quieter. There are rules.
How is that better
than a barbecue?
What's the dress code for this?
I'm glad you asked
Connecticut casual
Any chance Connecticut casual
is Pennsylvania business?
I.E., this is what
I'm wearing to your party
guys, my family just threw a garden party
to celebrate my brother's promotion.
It was a huge success
Check it out.
There's a video online
Heartwarming impromptu
father/son duet
Oh, yeah
Yeah. Oscar
you showed me this
I've seen this.
That's not you
Yeah. Who's the sausage?
It's my dad
and my brother
I would have joined in
but this melody
doesn't really support
another harmony part, so
Check it out
That's my brother's boss
Look how psyched he is
He's having an awesome time
Ah
And did Robert California
get an invite to your party?
Yeah, of course I mean,
yeah I think he did
Why didn't you just say this was
to impress Robert California?
I cannot believe that Andy is throwing a
party like this just to impress the CEO.
Classic Gabe move
Hey, Andy, how about you don't
steal my business strategies
and I won't dress like my life
is just one long brunch
See you all there at 3:00
p.m Connecticut casual
Remember your manners
and have a wonderful time
And please refer to the map
Stay off of the web.
Thank you
So, we've typed in
the address.
Now let's take a look
at the street view
They don't warn you when the
cameras are driving by Ah.
Why do you keep reading
that garden party book?
I mean, how hard are
finger sandwiches and tea?
There's so much
more to it than that
I've been wanting
Schrute Farms to break into
the high-end event hosting
industry for some time,
and this party is
a great opportunity
Plus, I've got
a secret weapon
Only one copy
in the world,
and some sucker on the
Internet sold it to me for $2
I'm actually really disappointed
in how poorly my book is doing.
I've only sold one copy
Is there anything you wish you'd
done differently to avoid cankles?
Nope
I've already gone up
another cup size.
The senator
is grossed out
When do you start
feeling it kick?
Cece was around 22 weeks
but Philip was much earlier
Philip?
Oh, my gosh. Yes But don't
say anything, okay?
It's after my grandfather
Philip is the name
that we're using.
It's after my favourite cat
Oh, wow
Funny. It's after
my grandfather.
It's after my cat
Andrew, I picked up two possible
gifts to bring this afternoon.
One, a pot of marmalade.
Ooh, that sounds great
That is what you want then?
The marmalade?
Sure
You don't want to hearthe otherone.
You love marmalade?
I'll hear the other one
It's a basil plant.
You know, the marmalade
sounds great.
I also mentioned the marmalade to my
sister, and she's very interested.
Then the basil will be fine
Well, you clearly want
the marmalade.
Gretchen, I need
another marmalade.
All right.
Hey, where do I park?
I'm the valet.
You have to give me your car, I'm parking.
I can probably park it myself
I'm the valet. You have
to give me your car.
It's probably okay
that I park...
No. I think it's
probably better that I
I'm the valet.
You have to give me
It's a finicky car Get out of your car.
Get out.
Have a good time
at the thing.
It's a little tricky.
You might want to
Mr. Ryan Howard
"Chapter Two. Announcing
guests as they enter
"is the height of decorum
"The more volume displayed the more honour
is bestowed upon everyone present."
Stanley Hudson
and his mistress Cynthia
James, Pamela
and Peepee Halpert
How's it going over here, guys?
Andy, stop hovering
You're being
really annoying
Didn't mean
to bother you, Mable
"Mable, Mable
if you're able,
"keep your elbows
off the table." Wow
Mr. and Mrs. Walter
and Ellen Bernard
So you all work
with Andy?
Well, technically, for Andy
Technically for Robert
California He's our CEO.
I thought you
were the CEO
I don't know how
you got there
You said you were
running the company
This branch
I'm the regional manager
Yes. Well, that makes
more sense.
Are you a
regional managers?
Did I throw this party to impress
my parents? That's crazy
No, if they wanted a garden party,
they could throw one themselves.
Which, as a matter of fact,
they did last week.
They threw one for my baby brother,
and it was totally amazing.
But I couldn't care less.
Can I introduce
you around now?
Yeah, we don't have too long
We have theatre tickets.
What are you
going to see?
Moneyball.
It was
Walter Jr.'s choice
MRS. BERNARD There he is. What?
Bro-nard
I didn't know you were
going to be here
I wouldn't have missed it
Okay
Ahh
I'm Walter. I'm Andy's
younger brother
Hey, how you doing?
I'm Jim.
Tuna, right? And this must
be your lovely wife, Pam
No
Hell no
She wishes. No, no, no no, no.
No
Sir, I need to be able to feed
all the guests I understand
Excuse me
Set that down
Present yourself
"Chapter Four One of the
host's most important duties
"is as dance master.
"A proper courtly dance sets the
tone for the entire afternoon."
Ladies and gentlemen
may I present
Robert California
Hello, Andy
Welcome
Thank you
Hey, I want you to meet
my first bosses
Mom and Dad
Yes. Hello. Nice to
meet you Pleasure.
Andy, where shall I put
your basil plant?
I thought you were going
to bring the marmalade?
No. I'm certain
you said basil.
This is not funny, man
Let me down.
I think this thing is broken. It's not
broken, Kevin This is how it works.
It's so pretty today
It's getting chilly
Yeah. We really
should be leaving
Yeah. Um
It'll be weird if the boss-man
didn't make a toast, so hang on.
Everybody, I just want to take this
opportunity to thank you all for coming
and to raise a glass
to my amazing staff
Toasts are great.
I mean, you toast somebody
they toast you back
It just goes round and round
That's my favourite part
about toasts, the reciprocity
Let's hear from you guys.
Who do you want to toast?
Yeah, I'll say something
I think we should be
acknowledging our boss
because none of us
would be here without him
Robert California
To Robert
- Yay, Robert
I cannot believe I didn't think of
toasting Robert. Get in the game, Gabriel
Why are you talking
to Stanley's mistress?
I would like to toast
someone who isn't here
but who will be
in just four short months
Welcome to the world
Philip Lipton.
Aww
I also would like
to toast Philip Halpert
who's due even sooner
May he be a good namesake
to my grandfather
who I promised as a child
long before tonight,
that I would one day
name my son after him
To Philip Halpert.
To Philip
All right
She just always has
to copy anything I do
It's the Ford Taurus
situation all over again
I'd like to make
a toast to the troops
Here, here
Yes
All the troops
Both sides
I think
we should toast
Ladies and gentlemen
the Last Supper.
"Chapter Nine The tableau
vivant is not only welcome
"but expected entertainment
at any garden party."
Andy?
I think that we should
acknowledge the man
who has led us to such
a profitable quarter.
To Robert California
Yeah
I would also like to toast Robert
California Mr. California...
You can't triple
toast somebody
At least not until
we hit everyone once
I'll say a few words if that's
all right with you, Andy
Yeah
You people say I led you
but it wasn't me
You want to toast the man
who led you to success,
but the boss is irrelevant
Andy and I produce
nothing We do nothing
We sit in our offices
and demand,
"I want this and that right
now" like petulant children
You know the difference between
a crying baby and a manager?
One day the baby
will grow up.
But without you, Andy and I would
be sitting in our dirty diapers
waiting for someone
to change us, wipe us
I should be toasting you
thanking you,
for allowing me to have the
easiest job in the universe.
Cheers
- Cheers
To Robert California
From the moment you entered our
building and our hearts, you...
Some of you know that we have
an Internet star in our midst.
Mr. Walter Banes Bernard, Sir
please report to the stage.
I'm eating, Andy
Come on
Okay. All right
Okay
Yes Yeah, what do
you want to do?
Well, how about one of our
classic father/son duets?
Oh, whoa.
You sure?
Really?
It's a little tricky
Saying I love you
Is not the words
It's too high. It's high but
it's not that high. Really?
Right. It feels strained
Yeah. Just take it down.
Saying I love...
Saying I love you
Here. Just give it to me.
Yeah Yeah
Okay
Something like
Saying I love you
is not the word...
You don't come in yet
...I want to hear from you
It's not that I want you
Not to say
but if you only knew
More than words
Is all you have to do
to make it real
Is anyone filming this?
Seriously. Erin!
It's either taping
or calling.
What would you do
If my heart was torn in two
You know what?
Walter Jr. is here
Why don't you come up and join us?
- Yeah, no
No, come up and do something with me.
I don't know, Pop
I'm just having a good time getting
to know Andy's friends here
Get up there and sing
or I will cut your larynx and
you'll never be able to sing again
Whoo! Come on
Come on
Give them what they want
All right. This old thing
I don't even
May the good Lord be with you
Down every road you roam
And may sunshine and happiness
Surround you when you're far from home
And may you grow to be proud
Dignified and true
And do unto others
As you'd have done to you
Cheers! All right
What's going on? Cheers, cheers.
Get your own guitar
Sorry. Please hang
up and try again.
I am so cold It's because
you didn't bring a jacket
My first love is beet farming,
but it's a young man's game
Whoever heard of an old beet farmer?
Forget the beets.
Concentrate on the hosting
I can spend a considerable amount of
money having my birthday party here
Really? We have a number
of birthday packages
The Pewter package has the
least amount of goats.
It's not no goats
it's still 10 to 12 goats
depending on the
availability of the goats
Now the goat package, obviously, has
the most goats What were you thinking?
Of course I am not
interested in goats
Why would you spend so much time
going over the goats with me?
I can get you
exotic meats
Hippo steaks.
Giraffe burgers
We'll talk
It'll all be goat
Hello, Cece Halpert
This is Andrew Bernard
I'd very much like to speak with
you about your paper supply needs
That wasn't even
my worst sales call
Hi
What was that display?
I don't know.
I just thought
if I could throw
this great garden party
and show you how respected I
am that you'd be proud of me
Andrew
I know
I know that you're
proud of me.
I'm not going to tell you
how impressed I am
that you're a manager
of some rinky-dink branch
of a paper company
in Scranton, Pennsylvania
How long are you going to
go on needing my approval?
You're a grown man. Don't act
like a little boy who needs...
I think if I had
parents like that,
I'd be trying to convince everyone
all the time how great I was, too
Guess we found Andy's
Rosebud Rosebud?
It's a reference
to Citizen Kane.
Something that explains why a
person became the way they are.
I know Citizen Kane. Rosebud didn't
explain why he was how he was
It just represented what was important
to him as a child, that he missed.
Different school of thought.
Let's just agree to disagree
No. You're wrong
Are you sure?
Yeah. I'm too hot anyway
My body has somehow become
acclimated to southern Italy
Isn't that strange?
I've never been there
Oh! Ah. Well
Yes, that's nice
Thank you
It was a nice party. The setting
was a little strange. The food
Sandwiches were dry
Bye, Tuna
Bye, Pam
Hey, everybody
I'm going to leave
and I just wanted to say
I'm really sorry
Cheeseburger
or hamburger?
Um
Cheeseburger
Nard-Dog
Thanks, Oscar
What are they doing?
Closing ceremonies
Nice touch
I think I left my wallet in your house.
Who cares?
Right here
Mr. James Halpert
Keys. My keys
Stop forgetting things. I didn't
forget them They're right here.
Mr. James Halpert
I'm so sorry.
I think I forgot the
What
You idiot
Ooh
Mis...
Mi.
What are you doing?
Hey, I have a question
Who do you think is really the
best salesman in this office?
Stupid question, obviously
Mr. James Halpert!