Hey, Angela
you wanna see
a picture of Philip
wearing those little
booties you got us?
So cute
Hey, you guys wanna see a picture
of Gerald wearing galoshes?
He refused to go out in the
rain until I bought these
Now, going out in the rain
is all he wants to do
Oscar thinks having a dog
is just like having a baby.
News flash,
if you didn't carry
it around in your
belly for nine months
it isn't your kid
Exactly
Unless you adopted
of course.
That is where we disagree
Hey, are your little
dudes crawling yet?
No. Three-month-old
humans don't do that
My Philip is crawling
Angela is such a liar
It's maddening
Exactly, that's just
like crate training.
All night long
Well, count yourself lucky
Wait until you have two
That's two sleep schedules,
two naps that don't coincide
I mean,
you'll never sleep again
No one said
you must have two
Like her genes
are so important
The world just needs more
Pam-Jim DNA Thank you, no.
No, thank you
Check this out My brother
just got a new sailboat
He has no idea what he
just got himself into.
There's nothing harder
than taking care of a boat
Am I right?
Unbelievable!
Unbelievable
It is the end of the day.
It is the end of the week
We managed to fill
40 hours, somehow
That's not bad, is it?
That's great
Pretty good.
Well, thank you
this is very helpful feedback
Dwight, I am still not
ready to name the V.P
That's not what
I was gonna ask
Gosh, you jump to conclusions
Come on, I know. You've
got so much on your plate
it's right now you're like
"Oh, what's more important Dwight's
question figure out who's the V.P
"Dwight. V.P. Dwight. V.P.'
Dwight. V.P. Dwight. V.P
Can we at least eliminate those
that are not in the running?
Free them up to focus
more completely on the menial
Like stacking
and sorting, or
Catching butterflies?
That's a hobby.
Unless it's for food
Theater
A waste of time.
Dragging?
That's just a verb
Dragging sticks
Yes. Nice. Perfect
All right, I'm gonna eliminate
three people right now.
Okay? Just. You three. No
Not good enough
English people's main use today
is judging American talent.
"You're crap.
You're wonderful.'
They're mean,
but they're incisive
Everyone meet in
the hotel bar at 7:00
I'm not allowed to
say it's mandatory
So let's just
call it compulsory
I'll be there at 6:00
Ugh. We're gonna have one of
those crazy nights aren't we?
Maybe we'll see
the real Talla-nasty
we've been
hearing so much about
Talla-nasty. Very clever
Thank you.
Wait, wait
You think she
invented "Talla-nasty"?
No, no, no, no
Cathy? It's been
great, fun, normal
gonna be hanging out
with Stanley on this trip
but he's turned out
to be kind of a loose cannon.
My friend and I
are new here in Tallahassee
Would you like
to get a cocktail?
Maybe go out for a little dancing?
Beautiful day, no?
Okay, everybody.
5:00. Work day's over
Put your pencils down,
and bring 'em back up
Because now, the late
night work jam begins
Yes! The conference
room is set up.
I've got pens, I've got paper
I've got a whiteboard!
We are good to go
Say what?
Good to go!
Stop it
Andy
Tonight, we're staying late
to service the accounts
of the people who
went on the Florida trip
Yes, of course
we could have just
been doing this
the whole time,
but someone dropped the ball
Ball droppings
can be beautiful
For example, when it turns an awkward
soprano into a rich, full tenor.
Jason Bourne
would kick Bond's ass
Jason Bourne has
no support staff
his own government's
out to get him.
Genghis Khan could
take 'em both down,
'cause he's not
afraid to kill children
What? It's true
He would eviscerate
babies and hang them
from poles
outside of the villages
Okay, drinking game The count
of three, take three sips
That's a stupid game I got a
great drinking game Okay?
Everyone, empty your pockets
Whoever has
the most seeds is the king
whoever has the least buttons
is the hunchback.
What happens if
you're the hunchback?
Oh, you get kicked
How many buttons do you have?
Forty. Always
Can I see?
Sure.
So I get to kick you now
No, they're not transferable just
'cause I handed them to you.
Well, that's how I
played it in college
College rules
And he lost at
his own lame game
Ooh! Double meaning
The game was lame and now
he's lame from the kick.
Quick wit.
Thank you
a glass of your oakiest
chardonnay, please.
And I will have a waffle
With your maple-iest syrup
Sorry, no waffles
Okay, just forget it then
Forget it. Forget it?
Waffle?
A hotel waffle.
I know what I wanna eat
Is that crazy?
No
I'm moving down here
you know
Oh. No, I didn't know
I'm young and I can
And if I can't,
I'm still pretty young
You come with me We're
gonna get you that waffle
Why would Erin confide in me that
she's staying here in Florida
if she didn't want me to make some
sort of last ditch, nothing-to-lose
Kelly Ka-who run at her?
Hey
Watson Carpet & Tile
One order
Order reference
number 00983-126
Eight cases
Bright White Inkjet
Paid
I'm dying
Processed
And delivered.
Sometimes I get so bored
I just wanna scream
And then sometimes
I actually do scream.
What the situation calls for
Hey, I see what you're doing It's
futile The V.P. position is mine.
Oh, please, you're through
She's going to give it to me as
I'm giving it to her tonight
The cowgirl has
chosen her saddle
Well, saddles
...sometimes fall off
Especially if you don't
properly cinch the girth
What? That's a joke, right? You
see the way she's all over me.
If anyone's having sex with
Nellie for personal gain, it's me
And I'm not joking at all
If you don't tighten your
saddle you may fall off.
Who is ready for dinner?
"Oh, I bet it's pizza or tacos
or something stupid."No
I went south of
the border for this
and then I went
south of that border
and we have ourselves
a Jamaican feast, man
If I wanted Jamaican food
I'd just hire
a bunch of
bodyguards and go there
Additional trivia factoid this
food comes to us through Val,
and our server is none other
than Brandon her boyf.
Hey
How you doing, guys?
Jamaican, huh? I just read
about the elections down there
Crazy stuff
Oh, no. I'm not
actually Jamaican
Terrific
What's up, man? I'm Darryl
Oh, Darryl
I heard about you
You doing good?
Oh, yeah
You must be doing real good
since you're * my girlfriend.
Whoa
Dude, you didn't tell me
you were * Val High five!
I'm not sleeping
with your girlfriend
Brandon, what the he
are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me I know what's up.
Honey, I am not sleeping
Hey! Hey.
Let's get back to the food
Brandon, tell us about
these delicious-looking goops
Hope you all like goat
Goat
Blow in my ear.
All right
Like I'm on the beach
A seagull
And a wave crashing
A wave crashing
Oh, that is lovely
All right, that's
gonna do it for me tonight
Have a lovely evening
Hey, how's it going?
Good. The heating system, though,
in my room is all messed up
It's like 90 degrees
in there
Maintenance is working on it
Can I hang out in here?
Uh... Yeah, I'm just
watching basketball
Okay. Yeah.
Okay
Cool
Is this March Madness?
I love March Madness.
Oh, no. That's not this.
Because that's in March
This is just the NBA
professional.
Miami Heat, actually. So
LeBron James
Yes
Nice, good word association
Impressive
Oh, please
anyone can tie a knot
The real skill
is in untying it
Thornwood Wholesalers
One order
I read the texts
you sent to Val, man
That's messed up
Is this spicy?
No, baby girl.
It would be messed up
if I didn't find anything
But I did, so
I'm pretty sure if
Darryl sent Val a text
it was about some paper
emergency or something
At midnight?
It happens
Like, a hospital needs
more napkins for surgery
You guys, we're not gonna
settle anything this way.
I think we just need to be
grown-ups here. Thank you
I think we're gonna
need to hear those texts
Kelly, remember how you wanted
to go home before?
No. There's no way
in hell I'm leaving.
Something interesting
is happening here
For once in my life I am staying here.
Darryl, read the texts
Yep? Coming
All right Hey. My minibar
is oddly out of rum.
We have plenty
Oh. Hello.
You wanna watch the game with us?
We're watching a game
The Heat game
It's just a game.
Got it. Good night
Careful, Jim
it gets easier and easier
No. No, no. Stanley?
Stanley. Stanley?
Stanley. All right. Hey
You know. Just bring
back those bottles!
Huh. The lights
are still on.
Yeah. They keep
them on, 'cause it's
less expensive than
turning them on and off
I like how guys just
know stuff all the time
Girls know a lot
of stuff too, okay?
And nobody
knows more than you
Especially me
Hello, waffle iron
Hello! What do
we have here?
Okay, so the recipe
says we need
a mixing bowl,
a measuring cup
Get down
It's the fuzz
Do you want us
to get scolded?
Shut your beautiful,
beautiful mouth. Please
"I got too much ice cream
you want some?"
"Getting my fry on.'
Boring
"The moon is huge tonight.'
Gosh, the moon one's damning
Yeah, sorry
That's regular text talk
You forgot one
"You're such a great friend.'
With the dots
"You're such a great friend
dot, dot, dot, dot, dot.'
Five dots, Darryl?
Are you kidding me?
Okay, 'cause three dots means to
be continued four dots is a typo.
But five dots means
"Whoa, do not
make me say what I
want to say, baby
"but if I did it would blow your
mind dot, dot, dot, dot, dot."
See? Yes, thank you, sister
Brandon, Darryl and me
that's ridiculous
Right?
Yeah
Totally crazy. Puts me in an insane
asylum just thinking about it.
I'm stranded on
Shutter Island over here
You look like Ed Harris
If they stretched
him a little bit...
You wanna see a picture of me
trapped under a tree?
Uh.
Excuse me
What? Not now. I'm busy
I'm sorry, I thought you'd want to know
that I saw
a bedbug in my room.
But never mind.
Sorry to interrupt.
Wait, wait, wait, wait
Bedbugs?
Oh, no
Freak, I need a favor
Well, then you have to call me
by my name Gabriel Susan Lewis
I've gotta be gone
for a few minutes.
You make sure that Packer
does not sleep with Nellie.
What's in it for G.S.L.?
You really want
Packer as your boss?
Got it
If Jim has bedbugs,
that means they're everywhere
I can't risk them coming
back to Schrute Farms.
Our biggest attraction is our
200-hundred-year-old mattresses.
Where did you see it?
In the bed
Well, I haven't seen anything
We gotta find it
before it eggs.
Jeez
Describe it
Brown, shiny, painful bite
Could be a bat weevil
Describe its mood.
Did it seem sleepy?
Stressed, but to be fair
it was a tense situation
Fair enough But after it bit
you did it run away fearful?
Or did it walk away smug
self-assured?
So smug. Like he thought
it was funny. Like this
That's a bedbug.
Yeah
Everything's a joke.
I know
Check your hair
God! It's so greasy You
should just shave all this
Just check it
You are clean. Okay
The one thing a bedbug thrives
on is heat and carbon dioxide
I am gonna generate myself
into a human trap
When I jump into the bed
you are gonna
cover me with
the sheet immediately
And then,
we'll see who's laughing
All right
Yeah
Cover me
Is this really necessary?
He knows what he's doing
Let the bedbugs bite
God! I feel so gross
I have to go take a shower
All right
then I will catch you later
What do we do now?
We wait
Come to Papa
No
No, I wasn't bitten
Okay, well, maybe it's not
warm enough in here
It's plenty warm
And I was farting continuously
under the sheet
creating a kind of a
greenhouse effect. Come on
If there were any
in here, they would
have imbedded
themselves in me
You know what?
Maybe they just ate
No, you're good.
Clean bill of health
Besides, I gotta
get back downstairs
I left Packer alone with
Nellie for way too long.
Okay, well, they're
fine, they're adults
No. That's the problem
Packer is trying to bed Nellie for the V.P.
job, unless I do it first.
Is that really how you
want to get this job?
Such a chorus girl
Okay, Dwight? Dwight?
Dwight, Dwight, Dwight
Uh.
Is "crazy" gone?
Oh
They don't make these cords
in boot cut anymore!
Aw
Pathetic, huh?
A real man swallows his vomit
when a lady is present.
Hey
Yep, one Death by Chocolate
one Bananas Foster.
Okay, cool. Thanks
Wait, this is why I
exercise like a fiend
Feel. Seriously
Okay. All right
I'm really sorry. I just have to say it
I'm married
I'm very happily married
Oh, my God,
what are you thinking?
Um
How little do you
think of me?
I'm sorry, I feel like
maybe I misread things
Okay. Let's just
go back to watching
Can you without running to the
other side of the room all night?
Yes. I can. Uh
All right.
I'm really sorry
I think we'll just
We'll just watch
You can watch, not watch
whatever you wanna do.
Take another shower I don't care.
Okay.
Whoo
Hey, Darryl, you okay?
She's got a boyfriend
Play it cool, man
She'll come around
No, you should go for it.
Mmm
I mean, nothing would've
happened with me and Jim
if he didn't put
himself out there
Yeah, but my friend Jim would
tell you to play it cool
My husband would
tell you to go for it
Hey. Hey
This is fun
A lot of fun.
I know. Can I give
you a compliment?
I'm really impressed
by how much you've grown
Since I met you
it's like night and day
You should move down
here with me Yeah?
We could be roommates
Really?
We could get a dog
we could go to R-rated movies
And who knows, I mean
you're a guy, I'm a girl.
Yeah
Maybe in six months, we'll see.
Six months
Okay. I'm in love
with Kelly
Put your forehead near mine and
see if you can read my thoughts.
Okay
Seven, one, one
Nine No, no, no not numbers. No
No, okay. Try again
Okay
I'm still getting numbers
Seven, one, one...
Is anyone around here thinking
the numbers seven, one, one?
Please stop. Okay?
Dwight, give me
a key card to your room
Meet me in seven minutes
for some one-on-one time
Wait, the numbers
There you go
I will see you in seven
Seven minutes
Nellie, wait
Let me write my room
number on the card
Win at all costs.
Don't respect women.
These are the tenets p was brought up
with, and they have served me well.
But my ancestors never worked
in corporate America.
They were farmers,
and before that, hunters,
and before that, time travellers,
and before that, me again.
At least that's
how the legend goes.
The point is, they never had to
worry about how they got ahead.
They just had to put food on the
table and not alter the past
1434-967, paid
It has been processed
It has been delivered
That's it, last one
Andy, this has been
an amazing night. Epic
Cool down fiesta
begins right now
I got decaf coffee
No way
I've got Romy and Michele's
High School Reunion.
Hey
Can we just like
never talk about it again?
Sure
Okay, thanks.
Hey, just so you know
me and you,
I don't think that's ridiculous.
Dot, dot, dot, dot, dot
All right. Now I think
it's time for you to go
What? Jim
I thought we talked about
this You're cool, right?
Cathy! Go
Where's the bug?
Awesome
Stand back
Stop it! Oh, my gosh!
That burns! What is that?
It's a compound of chemicals I
pulled off of the maid's cart.
Oh, my God!
Dwight, there
Oh, God! Stop it! Stop it
Big one! Big one
Stop it
Nice job, I think
you got him.
You can't stay here
this place is a biohazard
If I were you
I'd just bunk with Cathy
Second best Bananas
Foster I've ever had.
Yeah, what's the first best?
Dwight?
Hello? Dwight?
Is that Nellie?
Don't!
Are you in there?
On under your door
Hello?
Oh, look at that
The light went off just as
I said the light went on
Hello? Dwight?
Dwight?