Back orders and you
never called them
Can you believe this?
There's a dog in the car.
You can't leave a dog
in a parked car!
Snowboarder, it figures
Do snowboarders
hate animals?
I bet this guy didn't
leave his weed in the car
Okay, we have to do something because
this is incredibly dangerous.
Oscar, it's not
that hot out
A car parked in the sun
is like a toaster oven.
Well, we don't know how long
the driver's been gone
and it's not
in direct sunlight
So what, Andy? You want to
just let him die, you scumbag?
Here, I'm going
to get in my car
When I start dying, I will
honk the horn three times
That means
save the dog
Okay
you know what?
I'm going to give him
something to drink
Come here, doggy
Come on
Dwight
at least aim it
There you go
Here, doggy.
He's not even trying Come
here doggy, come on.
We're losing
cloud cover.
Don't try to get in
on it now, Michael Vick
Hey, hey, hey
Vick did his time
This guy's been gone long enough.
He's lost his right to a window.
Get back, buddy
Get back
Oscar, what are you
What... No, hey
All right
Yeah
Nice job, Oscar
And one
for good measure.
Yeah
So, who's going
to take the dog?
Why would we
take the dog?
What if he jumps out
the window and runs away?
Jim, he's not
going to start...
Stay, stay
Nein. Sitz!
Gut.
Oscar, what do you want to do?
This is kind of your deal.
You want a dog?
There we go
that should do it
Yeah, it's good.
It'll work
Nice job
Bye, poochie
Bye, doggy
Bye
What's that come to? Like,
what did they each win?
Oh, man, it's gotta
be over $100,000.
Yeah, before taxes
That's still
a lot of money
The warehouse crew won
the lottery yesterday.
$950,000.
And then they quit.
And no one else
can focus.
This is it.
This is all
on my shoulders.
I'm the one who has to tell
everyone to get back to work
I'm the one who has to tell Darryl
to hire a new warehouse crew
I'm the one who has
to say those things.
Hello?
Justine.
Nice surprise.
How you doing, baby?
No, no, no.
I didn't win
When I got promoted
I stopped...
What?
Yeah, Glenn won
You want to call him?
Yeah, you should call him
Congratulate him
That would be
What?
His number is
in your old phone
Oh, you know what?
I might have it right
Whoops.
When I worked in the warehouse,
I was part of that lotto pool.
They won
playing my birthday
What really interests me is the
group dynamic of six people
winning the lottery
This will not
end well, right?
Yeah
We're looking at
at least one suicide
and one weird sex thing.
At least
I don't even know what
I'd do with all that money
I know what you'd do
with all that money
"Hey, Pam Let's buy expensive
bathrobes and hug.'
No, I'd probably buy a big
piece of land in Maine
build a house
work in town.
Somewhere I could
bike to or kayak to.
I'd either bike to my job
at the kayak shop
or I'd kayak to my job
at the bike shop.
And then on the weekends
would you hacky sack
back to reality and spend time
with your wife and kids?
Whoa, Saucy I thought
you liked Maine.
I think we should get
a townhouse in Soho
Soho's mostly lofts
but okay
And then, every morning
I'd walk out onto my terrace
and I would breathe in
the inspiration of the city
You know, and just gather
ideas for my painting
Oh, God
And then my
handsome husband
Which, ideally
would be me.
Would bring me
a flavored coffee
Stop. I'm a barista
in your fantasy?
Well, in your fantasy we're
Stephen King characters
I don't know
about Stephen King
Get a divorce
I think I would
keep working
And for my salary, I guess I
would take like, $1 a year.
Obviously, I wouldn't
come in till noon
And I wouldn't do anything
I didn't want to do
I mean, I'm getting paid $1 a year, okay?
You can chill
Are you kidding me?
Guys, if I have to ask you to
get back to work one more time
I'm gonna change my tone
To down here, like Mr. T
And this would get
seriously annoying
I feel sympathy for the jerks who
have to listen to this all day
Darryl
How we doing on
the new warehouse guys?
I don't know
What... Do we have
new guys?
No
Are they on
their way over?
I haven't hired anyone
What? No warehouse guys?
I have an important order
that has to go out by 5:00
I e-mailed you about it
I'm not checking
e-mail till lunch
Four hour work week
This is kind of
time-sensitive
I got it. I'm doing it
Andy, this is a seriously big order.
I can't lose this client.
All right, well
until we have a new crew
let's get some volunteers
for warehouse duty
Who's in?
As long as you guys
don't need me up here
I think we'll be fine
No, we don't.
Really? Nobody's going
to help her?
Is chivalry dead?
Are you volunteering?
Of course, I would
But my hip
I would kill
to be at 100%
Jim, how about you?
Yeah. I mean
as the strongest person in
this office, I guess I should
Okay, no, no
That... You are
so not... Oh, God
False. Andy,
I will volunteer
Great
And Kevin
Good old Kevin.
He'll do anything
Well, guess what?
I will not do
a good job.
Thank you
Sure.
Wait, wait.
What's this?
Oh, sorry
I thought it was a
guess-your-baby's-birth-weight pool.
It says "lotto pool'
right on top.
Yeah, and I said sorry
Oh, come on
You really think I'm going
to have a 14-pound baby?
When did I get so fat?
You look awesome
I didn't hire anyone,
if that's why you're here
Where are we
in the process?
I have a file
of applicants here
I just gotta open it
look at it,
interview a bunch of guys
hire some of them.
So I say we're in the early
stages of the process.
Did you go out celebrating
with the guys last night?
They guys did invite
me out to celebrate,
but I decided
to just stay home
Eat a bunch of tacos
in my basement
You do have
a fantastic basement
I did
I did have
a fantastic basement
Now it smells
like tacos.
You can't air out
a basement
And taco air is heavy
It settles
at the lowest point
Right. Um
Well, how about we take
a look at some applications?
This guy wrote his
in green ink.
That's pretty cool
Check it out.
Hey
There you go
There he is
That is not Darryl
I don't know where Darryl is
I suspect, probably,
our Darryl is inside
of Fat Darryl.
Okay, 300 boxes
of 20-pound white
That's 75 boxes per person
So, that's not so bad.
Negative
Three hundred boxes for me
zero for you chumps
Deal with it
Nice
Oh, oh, oh
Damn
Yup
Welcome, everybody
My name is Andy, and this
is my other brother, Darryl
What? No Newhart fans?
Okay
Darryl, how do we usually
kick these things off?
You mean, what did we do the last
time the warehouse won the lottery?
Your old crew
won the lottery?
Does anyone have experience
shelving, storing keeping track...
What do we use?
The Dewey Decimal System?
Wait, wait. So, all
the old guys quit?
Oh, yeah
Well
One of them, Glenn is starting
one of those fat camps
where he steals your kid
in the middle of the night
Madge and a couple other guys
might start a strip club.
But on a boat
And Hide is investing in an energy
drink for Asian homosexuals
Could you guys
give us a minute?
But stay close
You're all doing great
Maybe grab a coffee
or if there's any donuts out
you can split one
You know they're for everybody
so people get fussy
You know what?
Just have a donut
Do you want to talk about this
not-winning-the-lottery thing?
I don't
You sure? 'Cause you keep
talking about it, so
Nope. I'm good
I'm here.
Let's find some warehouse
workers Good, great.
Then, can you say things that aren't,
like, a huge bummer to everybody?
'Cause the more I talk the
more they're going to realize
I don't know
what I'm talking about
Okay
We need you, okay?
Okay?
Yeah
All right
Ah
What's the problem?
Grunting is scientifically
proven to add more power
Ask any female tennis player
or her husband
I didn't feel anything
All right, thank you
for coming back in again.
Now, we're going to ask you a few
questions Darryl, you have the floor.
Why do you want
to work here?
I need a job
It's not a good reason
Good
Keeping them honest
Don't just take the first
job that comes your way
'Cause next thing you know it's 10
years later, and you're still there
You could write
your obituary tomorrow
It's not going
to change.
Are we scaring
them straight?
I hope so
Think about
this carefully
There's better lives
than this one.
I've never been lucky
And I'm not talking
about the lottery
I'm talking about stuff like
developing a soy allergy at 35.
Who gets a soy allergy at /5?
And why is soy in everything?
Nice, right back
where I like you
Can you make 10 copies
of this for me? No
Why not? What
are you doing?
Buying lottery
tickets online
Everyone wants to be rich but
nobody wants to work for it
You came in
at 10:30 today, right?
Okay, I'll just
do this myself
Is everyone licensed?
Like a driver's license?
No, warehouse license
Masters in
warehouse sciences?
I feel that Darryl has talked
about a license of some kind
Is this a joke?
No. Not joking.
This is real
Painfully real, what
is happening right now
Okay, I'm not going to
make it I'm turning back
There's gotta be
a better way to do this
This is literally how
they built the pyramids
Well, they whipped people
which was helpful.
But you're right. We should be
able to find a more efficient way
of moving boxes
than Madge or Hide
Yeah
Not that they're
not smart people
No, no, very smart
Theirs is more of a
physical intelligence
I'd go with that
Like baboons
or elephants.
Not that, don't
Guys, when I was a kid my
sisters used to butter me up
and slide me across the
linoleum floor of the kitchen.
It really made
them laugh.
It's a great idea, Kev
I don't think
it applies here, though
So, maybe we just
Yeah, we move stuff
and have fun.
Kevin
doesn't apply
Right, my mom
You need
to drop it, okay?
They hate it
I like it a lot but they
hate it so drop it.
Does anyone get distracted
easily by bubble wrap?
You'll be dealing with lots of
bubble wrap, obviously. Um...
How much longer
is this going to take?
Did you hire them?
No, because
they all left.
What do you mean
they left?
I mean, after you bailed
I got confused and
frankly, a little weird
And the stuff that you said
certainly didn't help
Then I think you
should fire me.
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to fire you
Yeah, just put me out
of my misery.
Okay, this is weird.
I don't get the joke
No? Okay
I don't want
to be here anymore
Fire me
So Darryl says
to me, "Fire me, '
but what he really means is
"I'm going to say something really weird,
try and figure out what it means."
So I say, "No,
you're not fired.'
But what I really mean is
"I've no idea what
you're talking about
"But I'm going to go ahead
and hire some people
"for the warehouse and hope that you
eventually start feeling better."
I really hope that's
what he and I mean
Attention
Does anyone know anyone who
could work in the warehouse?
We can pay
Come on, Oscar
Who's the most jacked guy
in all of Scranton?
Like your wildest
fantasy guy?
Bulk or definition?
Definition
Bruce Kenward. He hangs
out at Planet Fitness
Are those just show muscles
or is he really strong?
Oh, he's plenty strong
It used to be Reggie Winters
out at Gold's Gym
But he moved away
And then it was between
Bruce and this guy, Dean
But Dean got fixated
on his calves,
and, uh
And his triceps
went to hell.
So, I've been thinking
after we win the lottery
we take our winnings...
Our fake winnings
And we move
to the South of France
See... No, there's plenty
of bicycling for you.
I think that's where they
do the Tour de France
It is, yeah
I mean, I just don't know
why I'm compromising
if it's my fantasy
Because in my fantasy,
it's Maine, and you love it
Because I'm never going to act
like that, even in your fantasy
Nope, you're doing a great job
of it in my fantasy right now
Hey, idiot, what did
Erin want again?
A hot chocolate tea
Gideon, you are
a PhD candidate
studying America's diminishing
blue-collar workforce?
North America
And "diminishing" is a little reductive,
but, sure that's the headline version
Great
Well, it will bring a fresh, new
perspective to the warehouse.
FYI, Wednesday through Friday I have
a pretty full teaching schedule.
Oh, cool We'll figure that out.
Also, FYI
I don't technically
have a hearing problem
But sometimes, when there's a lot of
noises occurring at the same time
I'll hear them
as one big jumble
Again, it's not
that I can't hear
Because that's false, I can
Um, I just can't distinguish
between everything I'm hearing.
Got it. Duly noted
You
coolest tank top I have ever seen.
Where did you get that?
Made it.
So cool
What a cross section
we have here.
It's what I love
about interviewing
I get to meet
all these people
I wouldn't ordinarily meet,
or know or even talk to.
Message in a Bottle,
The Postman...
Kevin Costner
Kevin Costner, yeah
So
I found this grease
And then I remembered that you
thought it was a great idea.
You did say
it was a great idea
I heard you say it
So it's not
the dumbest idea
It's not the
greatest one...
But the fact remains,
we gotta move these boxes.
And it's clear we're
not going to carry them.
So sadly, it's the best
idea on the table. Exactly.
Hey, I think we're
ready to get this...
Jim?
Is he okay?
He'll be fine
Surprise! Your new crew
Would you just
fire me, man?
Hey, why? Because you
didn't win the lottery?
How am I supposed
to make you happy?
You want to make
me happy? Huh?
Yeah
Give me your job.
Haha. What? I'll do
it better than you
I earned it,
I deserve it
I got passed over
God knows why.
Reasons I cannot
and will not understand
The job was mine, Andy
Everyone said it was mine
Make me manager
or fire me.
I'm not going
to give you my job
It's my job
I earned it!
And here's the thing You
weren't even next in line.
I asked about you
I saw your file
You have a history of
being short with people
and you hired Glenn
your buddy,
to replace you
in the warehouse
He was under-qualified
They saw that.
Also, Darryl, FYI
I already told
this to Andy
but you should
probably know
I technically don't have
a hearing problem
It's just when there's a lot of noises...
Nate. Please.
Thank you.
You have no
business education
You were going to take classes under
Deangelo What happened to that?
He died
He didn't die,
his brain died
And my brain is still
very much alive
And I'd be happy to give
you business classes
How come you haven't
asked me about it?
What was...
What was the last
I'm having a
No part of this has
anything to do with you
I didn't have time
because of my daughter
But you had time
for a softball clinic
And a Mediterranean
cooking class.
Hey, I'm not going to tell you this stuff if
you're going to throw it back in my face!
Hey, here's the thing
Jo saw something in you
She loved you.
She gave you a shot and
then you stopped pushing.
She noticed
Okay
Okay, what?
Okay, don't fire me
Okay
My future's not going to be determined
by seven little white lotto balls.
It's going to be determined
by two big black balls.
I control my destiny
I do
I'll put some
guys on tonight
The best of your bunch
and my bunch
I'll tell you now, though it's
going to be mostly my bunch
Yeah, that makes sense
Okay, good
All right.
Are they here?
What is going on?
Oh, hey, guys
Why is the forklift
in the wall?
Why is
the truck empty?
It's not totally empty
Is that grease
on my floor?
Okay
I can see why you're angry.
You're coming into this cold
But believe me a lot of
thought went into this.
And did your brains tell you to
ruin these boxes with grease?
Okay, Darryl
Listen, and then
you will understand
The boxes were ruined during
our first trial testing.
So now, it's cool 'cause we
found another use for them
Okay, all right
That's... Look, all we were trying
to do is we thought we could come up
with a more efficient
way to do things.
And?
And we did.
I don't know
Jim, tell them
what it's called
That's all right
No, Jim, tell them
what the name is
Doesn't matter
Se침or Loadenstein
that's stupid.
Tell them why
it's called that, Jim
That's okay, we're good
No, Jim, tell us why it's
called se침or Loadenstein
Porque es muy r치pido.
Okay, you know what?
It's been a real busy day.
What do you say
we put all this away?
Let me see it
It's in beta testing
Get the thing, go
Lube it up.
Kevin, start mopping
Uno, dos, tres.
Yeah. I lost my client
I already won the lottery I
was born in the US of A, baby
And as backup,
I have a Swiss passport
I would spend
a lot of time
launching my true crime podcast
"The Flenderson Files.'
Duh-buh-bum
Flenderson Files
We came
to an agreement
We're going to live in a
stunning pre-war brownstone
at the top of a mountain
Right, it's city
and country combined
Just a subway stop away are the
best museums in the world.
And I can fish right from the
window of Pam's pottery studio
We can chat
any time we want
Just like now
It's too bad the schools are terrible,
but what are you going to do about that?
What are you
going to do?