Oh, for god's sake
Planking is a very stupid
and dangerous trend
Basically you lie like
a plank in weird places
That's it.
Sometimes you get run over
Welcome to the Internet
Planking is one of
those things where
hey, you either
get it or you don't
And I don't. But I am so
excited to be a part of it.
After you
my good sir
No, I insist
The search committee
finally decided,
after a lot of deliberation
on Robert California
for the manager position
Who took one look
around and left.
He drove down to Florida and
convinced Jo to make him C.E.O
C.E.O. Her own job
He talked her
out of her own job
and I don't really know
how someone does that
but anyway then the
position was his to fill
and he chose
It's unbelievable
True. I may have
been tee second choice,
but I was the first
choice's first choice.
And about Dwight,
have some resentment
about not getting the job
so I sat him down
and we had a talk
And I told him, "I need a
really strong number two
"I want you to
be my enforcer.'
Smart, right?
Very smart
This has got to stop
Hey! Kevin
Yeah, at first I was
really disappointed
But I've got a great daily
routine going right now
I've upped my karate
to eight times a week.
I've added boxing at
lunches and on weekends,
I do kick-boxing three times a
week, Krav Maga four times a week,
an hour of meditation
every morning at sunrise,
and again at sunset.
So yeah
I'm doing great
I'm going to need
some help. Pam?
Oh, yeah. Pregnant
Right here.
Little Michael Scott
Nope. I told you I
don't like that joke
It is a boy.
We found out early
Much different
the second time around
And I have to say
it is nice not being
the only pregnant
woman in the office
Look, it's "little
pregs" and "big pregs."
Wait, when did we start
calling each other
Isn't it amazing the
difference in our sizes?
Well, I am a few
months ahead of you
I'm having a child with
my husband the senator
And Pam is having a child
with Jim The great salesman
Hoist him aloft
Come on, Darryl, lift
Lift, Darryl
Come on, man
Yeah, I wanted the manager job,
but I got something much better
This soda
This is mine
It might be easier if you take a
deep breath lift from the knees,
and shove it
up your butt
a new thing this summer
I act like I'm telling
someone how to do something.
A long description
and then I say...
And shove it up your butt
It's stupid,
but it's my thing now
No one should be
planking at all.
Thank you. Yes
Dwight my enforcer, my number
two can you take care of this?
Say no more
Kids, don't try planking
it's dangerous.
Especially with me around
Are you watching
that commercial again?
Why do you keep watching it if you
know it's just going to make you cry?
Because everything makes me
cry so what's the difference?
This dog he just wants
to protect his bone
He's got a bank vault
That's a start.
Not enough, though
All right
The new C.E.O. works out of the
conference room about half the time
but whenever he takes a break he does
these weird walks around the office.
And you never know who
he's going to zero in on
for these really
intense small talks
You just hope
it's not you.
And yet you hope it is
you, too It's strange
Here we go.
Hello
Robert California.
Let's have a conversation
Describe your day so far
Well, I woke up and
When you recount your day,
never say you woke up
It's a waste of your time
That's how every day has begun for
everyone since the dawn of man.
Very smart
Suddenly, I was awake
and I...
Hey, Robert We have that 9:30 A.M.
casual chit chat scheduled
I emailed you about it last eight
to confirm. And again this morning
First item on the agenda
can I get everyone
an extra long
Columbus Day weekend?
Item number two,
connect with the guy
Robert California,
what does he think of me?
Don't know
Super care.
Number three, time permitting
we lost our biggest client.
Pam. Pam
Past! Pam.
Jim
Can I call you right back?
Thank you very much.
Okay
What is this?
The Friday before
Columbus Day, thoughts?
What are your thoughts?
Just making chit-chat
Kind of a medium year
for women's soccer, no?
What are you looking at?
It's nothing
It can't be nothing
Yeah, it can't be nothing.
It's just a list of our names
split into two columns
What?
Okay, just wait one second all right?
I will copy it
Do you have a pen?
No
Okay. Um, I'll take
a photo of it.
Dwight, can you
throw me my phone?
Nice catch
If he comes out
distract him.
We need a warning signal
We don't need
a warning signal, Kevin
We can see him right there.
- We do.
Don't need a...
Warning! Warning Warning!
Warning! Warning
Phyllis!
Phyllis
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
One, two, three
Thanks, guys
Okay. Which side
of the list am I on?
Left
Yes
Why are you...
How do you know?
Really great
list of names, guys
Thank you so much
Good work.
No, actually, that was
in Robert's notebook.
He left it at reception
and we photocopied it
Oh
Okay. I don't want
any part of this.
Maybe it's the list of people
he's going to fire.
Okay.
It's not that, Pam
You know I was
thinking it reminds me
of those lists
Dwight used to make
This is if we were a
on a cruise ship
and had to divide
into life boats.
And this is if we
were on a cruise ship
and had to divide
into life rafts.
Here's something "Who would eat
who in an Alive situation?'
No. That can't be it
I gotta say
it kind of seems like the left
side is the side to be on
Me, Jim, Dwight, Darryl
no offense, Pam.
Excuse me?
Shh. Pam, come on Don't
be such a right-sider.
Did you guys figure it out?
We couldn't crack it
Go in there, just ask
the man what it means
He'll know that we looked
at his private notebook
Come on Just say you saw
the list by accident
I'm already working on this
Columbus Day thing for you guys
And it's starting
to stack up.
It feels like a lot
One thing at a time
Yeah, that's all you had to do
today is ask about Columbus Day?
Yes. For god's sake
Andy, yes. Come in.
What's up?
Weird thing.
Totally awkward
But you left your notebook
on the reception desk.
Great. Thank you
And it was open
and people saw this
and they're just kind of
going nuts and, like...
What is this?
...wondering what it is
It's a photocopy
from your notebook
You read my notebook? And
photocopied it and distributed it?
No. They did. And they asked
me to ask you about it
Please
Oh
Here's what it is
it's a doodle.
What?
Some people doodle at work
when they let their mind run
They draw houses, penises
funny how the houses
are always colonials
and the penises are
always circumcised
Don't you think?
Well, I doodle too but I'm not an
artist so I draw words and lists
That is fascinating
And by the way
I am so glad I asked
People were just sort of...
Did you just move my name?
Might as well have
been sketching a cube
Okay, Robert's in the annex
everybody think quick
What do these
groups have in common?
Maybe we're supposed to do
it with people in our group.
That's not it
People in
the other group
Mmm. Still wrong
Stanley, you do puzzles
all day What do we got?
Well, you take the first
letter from each name
assign it a number
add them all up,
and shove it up your butt
Thank you, a little
much needed comic relief
But we really need to
figure this out, guys
It's alphabetical
No, it's not
Here's how we find out
Let's line up and
compare the lines
see if we learn
anything, okay?
Left-siders over here
right-siders line up over here,
face each other
Match up by height
and relative weight
Let's just size
each other up here
And left side of the list
attack
Wait, wait, wait,
stop, stop!
Will you stop?
Dwight
Don't do it
What are you doing?
Stop!
Warning! Warning! Warning
I'd like to invite the following
people to join me for lunch.
Jim, Dwight
Angela, Darryl
Kevin, Toby
Phyllis, Oscar
That's great.
Let's do this, guys
All right. Well,
I will see you in a bit
Hey, it's nothing
all right?
I'll text you
when we get there
I'll let you know
what's going on Okay
No. No dog video
Okay
Okay.
See you, guys
Well, we should a
be really excited about
our very own pizza party
Pizza party Pizza party.
Pizza party.
Jim, your daughter Cecelia what
does she think of the Street?
The street?
Sesame Street.
Oh. I didn't know
anybody called it
She likes it a lot
She loves Elmo
Elmo, God save us the Elmo era
Right?
Sesame Street was
created to reflect
the environment of
the children watching it
Complete self
absorption of Elmo
is brilliantly
reflective of our time
Ours is a cultural ghetto
Wouldn't you agree?
Yeah. She does like Elmo
Cultural ghetto?
Totally agree
Completely
Apt. Apt analysis, Robert
The thing that I like about
Elmo is the tickling
I don't know
I was in the wrong...
I'm... I'm sorry
Just picture me back there.
I was never here
Great group
Pizza party.
How is this a pizza party?
Well, why don't you
ask me again
when the five pizzas
get here?
Yeah, well,
that's just pizza
You need at least one other
element for it to be a party.
Okay. Have you guys
ever had margarita pizza?
What's that?
Fresh tomato with a dollop
of mozzarella cheese.
That's pizza
That's regular pizza
You know, I fee comfortable enough
now to ask you this question,
what made you
pick this group?
I just think
you guys are winners
and I wanted to
have lunch with you
Okay
Aw.
What about the other guys?
Losers? Come on.
Oh, I don't know
Come on. Come on
I guess I think
they're losers.
I knew it
Yes
Probably shouldn't
have said that
Whoo-hoo
Ah-ha! Their interpretation
of margherita pizza
Fans of classic pizza
will be psyched.
A text from Jim
"This is getting very weird
Will explain later."
Text from Kevin
"Suck it, losers.'
RYAN Okay, not to point out
the glaringly obvious,
but doesn't the fact
that lama in this group
make anyone feel just
a little bit better?
Oh, this crust is sharp
and sort of funny
and I could do those
cute little cartoons
and everyone who came
through here was like,
"Who's that receptionist? I like her."
Now I'm just a fat mom
Yeah, and you take one look at
me and you're like, "Oh, loser."
Come here, Pam
Chins up, okay?
Bad joke
Look around this room
Does this look like a group of losers?
Seriously.
Oh, god
Oh, hey, guys
we had so much fun.
We had marguerite pizza
We all hung out and got
to know each other better
How was your lunch?
It was excellent.
Good times
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, we did.
It was the best time
And you know what? Now it's
over back to work, everyone
You too, Andy
I knew it.
That everyone
was wrong about me.
My parents, my teachers, my
friends the doctors, everyone.
Well, that was
certainly an odd lunch
Is everything all right?
Yeah, I'm fine
Just take the
casserole out of the
Loser
Take it out of the refrigerator,
put it in the oven
It'll be fine Just leave
it in for 20 minutes
Loser
When I was a salesman
I could just be like,
"Not my job, not my prob I'm going
to the warehouse to polish my knob."
Metaphorically, of course
But now,
it is my job and my prob
Hi, Robert
Can you come out here, please?
It's really important.
Clarify something
Some people here
are under the misconception
that some people
may be considered
let's say top tier
and others would
be second tier.
Thank you. Great
I said winners and losers Is
that what you're talking about?
Oh, that might That actually
might be what I'm thinking of.
Can you clarify that?
Let me tell you some
things I find productive
Positive reinforcement
negative reinforcement
Honesty
I'll tell you some things
I find unproductive
Constantly worrying
about where you stand
based on
inscrutable social clues
and then inevitably reframing
it a in a reassuring way
so that you can get
to sleep at night.
No, I do not
believe in that at all
If I invited you to lunch
I think you're a winner
If I didn't, I don't
But I just met you all
Life is long,
opinions change
Winners, prove me right
Losers, prove me wrong
Well, I guess
that's that
No
No. No
Andy, don't go in there
I'm going in there
I know that every time I talk to
you things just seem to get worse
But you don't know
these people, and I do
And if I let you work
with faulty information
well then I'm not doing my
job as regional manager.
So, please take this pen
and change your list.
I'm not going to
change my list, Andy
And I don't use
ballpoint pens.
Well, then I w
make a new list for you
Stanley, you may think
he's a lazy grump
but did you know that he has the
most consistently high sales numbers
of anyone in this office?
And you may think
he's hard to love
but did you know
that he's in not one
but two long-term
romantic relationships?
About the sales figures
Meredith Palmer,
supplier relations
The word "no,"
not even in her vocabulary
And just to show you
that I'm being fair,
you had Gabe in
the loser column
Good call
Pam
easily the most creative and kind
person I have ever worked with.
Jim, shut the door
This is just gross.
Shh
Erin Hannon, the receptionist
and my closest confidant
A winner if
there ever was one
Are we done?
Yes
No
The Friday
before Columbus Day
we're going to
take a half-day
So that everyone can get a
jump on the long weekend.
You want a three-and-a-half
day weekend for Columbus Day?
Yes, I do
And you are aware that
Columbus and his legions
committed genocide against an entire
civilization of Native Americans?
Hey, guys
so Columbus Day, we got
that half-day on Friday
We get that every year
Well, you got it
this year, too.
Good night, Andy
Good night.
Bye
Good night, Andy
Good night
Night
All right, I'm going
to go warm up the car
Okay
Okay.
You dropped something. Jim?
Okay, I know I've been
crying easily today, but
I mean, that's just
pretty killer, right?
I mean,
maybe it's stupid
No
It's wonderful
I'm going to frame it