Phew! Wow. It is raining
cats and dogs out there.
Holy moly
Phyllis says the same 12
clichés every time it rains.
So, I promised everyone that if
she says them all by noon today,
I will send out
for hot chocolates
So how was the drive in?
Nobody knows how to
drive in the rain.
You don't say?
Yeah.
You know the roads are actually the
slickest in the first half hour?
I think it's the oil, it comes to the surface.
- I agree
Ooh! The plants are
gonna love this. Yeah
PHYLLIS I actually sleep
better when it's raining
Tell me about it
Time's almost up. How many are left?
Just one.
"This weather makes me want to stay
at home, curled up with a good book.'
Phyllis, this rain, does it make
you want to be doing something?
What do you mean?
You know, like, aren't some things
just so nice and cozy in the rain?
Hey, come on Lots of things
are cozy in the rain.
And that's noon
Exactly!
Sorry about that
everybody.
Hey, Phyllis would you
like a hot chocolate?
Ooh, I'd love one
I'm going out to get
two hot chocolates
the rain would make me
want to stay at home,
curled up with
a good book
but everybody's being
so nice to me today.
I'm really happy
being here
My girlfriend's back and
there's going to be trouble
Hey, la, hey, la,
his girlfriend's back
my girlfriend's back
A month ago, I walked
out of this office
positive I was
never coming back
I probably shouldn't
have emailed everyone
telling them exactly
what I thought of them
Hey, Erin, thank you
for the nice email.
Yeah. I don't get emotional
a lot but that was...
I'm just glad to know I had an impact
In other news Erin and
Andy are back together
Crazy story
Yes
down to Florida,
she was not expecting it
totally swept her off her feet.
Right? Yeah.
How long
was the drive?
It's like a day and
a half each way.
But when I got there, I went right
up to the house, and I was like
Day and a half? My lumbar
would be killing me.
You should get this lumbar
support cushion thing my dad has
What's it called?
Um
Not Easy-Rest
That gas must've cost
a pretty penny, huh?
Well
he's got a Prius
How many times you fill the tank?
Three, four?
What does gas
cost down there?
Lumbar Buddy
Oh, yeah
Lumbar Buddy.
Tell you what,
I'll email you the story
It's a real
tearjerker, though
So read with caution
Anyway, I know it's
the end of the day.
We just wanted to
stop by and say hi
And then later on, we have
a reservation at Patsel's.
Miss Lumbar
Hey, Kev
Yeah.
Nice sweater
Thank you
Nellie was nice enough
to give it to me
She's sweet I just
wish there was pockets
What happened
to Old Salty?
Nellie let me
bobble-ize him
His name is now
Captain Mutato.
I've written quite a bit
of X-Men fan fiction.
Captain Mutato is
half-man, half-mermaid
So he can fight
crime as a man
and make love
as a mermaid.
Most of my writing
involves the latter
Okey-doke
Yes?
Whoa
Well, you must be the famous Nellie
Bertram I've been hearing all about
I am the famous Andy Bernard you
have been hearing all about.
Oh, yes I just want to thank you
for jumping in and
minding the store
during my temporary absence
You are most welcome
Anyway, now that I'm back I would
love to have my office back,
whenever you get a chance. No
Obviously we'll figure
out the logistics
of moving all of this
stuff out of here.
But, you know the sooner the
better Get back to normalcy
Mmm. No
Thank you
Okay
Wait. Uh
When I showed up here
there was no manager
It's like when the Americans
showed up at the Moon
Nobody was there
So they planted
their flag,
and it's their
moon now, isn't it?
Nobody likes it but it's
America's bloody moon
Just lay him in his crib
and then bicycle his legs
And then after
Jim quiets down
you do the same thing
with your baby.
But if he keeps having
problems, just give me a call
Oh, my gosh
thank you so much
But seriously, we don't
want to bother you
any more than we already have.
That's it
It's no bother.
You guys are our friends
Ravi, our amazing
paediatrician,
was asking us if
we knew any girls
and I said, "I know
the perfect girl.'
Yeah. Because Kelly is
Indian and Oh, that's it
Race had nothing
to do with it.
I just knew they'd
be good together
Why?
Kelly has been
a handful in the past.
But she's had
a bad influence.
She's like an addict, and I
just had to get her clean.
Get lower
Next, I'm going to set up
my sister with Darryl.
Okay, we get it
What? I think they'd be good together.
Really?
Um, also, little tip,
never shake the baby
Sorry, just to be clear, you're
saying do not shake the baby?
Don't shake the baby
A lot of times parents get
frustrated because the baby's crying
and they shake the baby
and you got to...
You can't do that
Don't shake our baby
Yeah.
Okay, I'd never
heard that before
Oh, my God
So, thank you
Yeah, I'm glad you said
something Me, too.
Kelly and I broke up and she
can do whatever she wants.
And her new boyfriend
seems awesome,
if you're into
Indian people
I'm not
And that's
when I realized
if you're gonna put a
thermometer in one end,
you'd better put a
lollipop in the other.
Hey, I'm sorry Is this a
workplace or a Starbucks?
Because I was under the
impression it was a workplace.
Maybe I'm
the crazy one
No. No, we're sorry.
Come on, let's go, Ravi
Also, since when do we have
guests here without clearance?
Hey, um
What's the deal with this guy?
He's really into Kelly, huh?
Yeah, they're
really great together
Makes me wonder
if I made a mistake
No, no, no. Come on I think you
guys are both happier now, right?
You're single. Plenty of
girls to date, right?
Yeah
Maybe we weren't right
together but it's weird
I'd rather she be alone
than with somebody.
Is that love?
That's about it, yeah
Well, Nellie picked up
the slack around here
while you were trolling
the Florida beaches for ta
like some college student
on spring break.
I had to tell Erin
how I felt
Andy, I appreciate
your romantic quest
and in an age before the
telephone or Internet,
or written language
that would be compelling
But there are five six
devices in this room alone
that would have let you tell her
that without ever going to Florida.
We live in
amazing times
Yeah, I know
I screwed up
But I always do
whatever you ask of me
and this will never
happen again.
And if Erin decides she's made a
mistake and returns to Florida?
At least she knows how I feel,
and I would not follow her.
What if she were kidnapped by a
gang of Albanian human traffickers?
Like in Taken?
What?
Yes, of course
if she's taken.
That's what I'm talking
about By Albanians
I would stay
in this office
Wow, okay. I'll
remember you said that
Nellie
you've been terrific
in your interim capacity
but Andrew is
the rightful manager
so if you would just
give him his office
No.
I'm sorry?
This is what I was
trying to tell you.
I'm not accustomed to
people saying no to me
Well, Bobby,
get accustomed to it
because then it feels so good
when they finally say yes.
You're both adults
I'm sure you can
figure this out
between yourselves
desire to influence
a business decision
So, I find it best to
recuse myself temporarily
until I've had
a chance to make love
and then go back and analyze
the situation rationally.
Buffett operates
the same way.
I want to order the zebra
rug for my office,
but can you dye it
entirely black?
No, I still want it
to be a zebra.
Well, I'll know
Because they're
ridiculous creatures
They don't know
what they are.
Phyllis says J. Duffy's
might be more our speed
And if we want even the option
of drawing on the placemats...
of an anger problem
Got me in some trouble
a couple years ago.
When I see him
start to get mad,
on his arm like this
It reminds me to just
check out and relax
There's also a lullaby they used to
sing to me when I was growing up.
The state of Pennsylvania
is watching over you
No need for parents,
the governor will do
It's really nice
The General Assembly's
like a mom and a dad
...had
about a trespasser
Yes. Right this way
Because they are idiots.
Big, stripy, horsey idiots
What you don't... Hey
Hank, please remove
Nellie from my office
Hank, thank God
you're here.
This psychopath keeps
barging into my office
It's my office
Well, she's sitting
there like a manager
And you're standing
up here like me
But maybe it's a little
more complicated than that
I'm going to
count down from five
and if you're not
out of my office
I'm going to
dock your pay $100
Five, four
You can't dock my pay
Three, two, one
Congratulations,
you just lost $100
Really?
Angela
dock Andy's pay $100
On it
Great Five, four,
three two, one.
Angela, please dock
Nellie's pay $100.
Hmm?
Is she responding? Hmm
Angela? Do you want to go again?
Angela!
Let's go again
Five, four, three
two, one.
Oh, she's counting again
Look out.
Angela, $200
- Got it
Seriously, Angela?
I know what,
let's go $10,000
Five, four You're
just saying numbers.
It's meaningless.
Three
It's literally like
Two, one
There you go
Hey, we're going to
have a nice hot date
What are you guys
talking about?
Charlie Rose I don't know who that is
Guys
He has...
Guys, come here
What are you...
Come on
Where are we going?
Okay. Do you guys want
Andy, you should
not stand there.
The warehouse guys
pee there all the time
Ew
Okay. Do you guys want to
be part of something huge?
I'm already a member of the
largest club there is.
Non-churchgoing
Christians.
You remember in
the movie Rudy,
when the player comes
into the coach's office
and he throws his jersey
down and he's like,
"I'm not playing
without Rudy.'
And the coach is like,
"One guy. No big deal.'
But then every player
comes in, one by one
and they all throw their jerseys
down for Rudy. Remember that?
Yeah, I remember that
So, how amazing
would it be
if you guys all
did that for me
with your own brand new
Dunder Mifflin jerseys?
Hey, guys
Gross. Gross, gross
You don't need to go
while I was journaling,
and they reminded
me of you.
Those are from our weekend
at the time-share.
Yeah, the fractional
ownership property
We took this one right before
we got in that huge fight
God, I don't even remember
what that fight was about.
You were being
really bratty about
where we would
go out to dinner
but all I remember is how pretty you
looked taking those pictures of me
Anyway, if you want to
order prints of your own,
Yeah, that'd
be cool. Thanks
I'd like that
You were so annoyed that I
was taking that picture
Someone's into my abs
Sorry
You have doubles of this one, I
could probably just take one
I really want both
I am seeing a side of Ryan
that I have never seen
since the last time
we were broken up
with Kelly Kapoor
And I don't know how I'm going
to feel tomorrow or the next day
or the day after that, but I do
know that right here, right now
all I can think about is spending
the rest of my life with her.
Again, that could change
Hey. So, last night
was so not a big deal
Oh, yeah,
I was just tired
We both were
Yeah.
Plus I was definitely
not my normal sexy self
No. Are you kidding?
You were so sexy.
Just the thought of you last
night like, crazy turns me on
It just didn't last night
But you were so dang doable
Even though we didn't do it
Well, it's not like we can't do it
again when Whenever you're ready.
Uh, yeah. We are sexing it up tonight.
I don't care what you say
No. It will be consensual
Whether you like it or not
Sounds good
I'm gonna do you
Not if I do you first.
Oh
But really
it's not a big deal
Yeah. I know it's
not a big deal.
Oh, hey, instead of lunch do
you feel like going shopping?
Are you serious? Yes
That would be... I can't
Can you believe this?
Hey, can you believe it? Nope
Hmm
Oh, do you want that dress in
every size and every color?
Yeah, it's free returns
getting along
with Ryan again
He's so sweet He pointed
to my latte and he said
"Kelly, that would be
the color of our children.'
God. Yeah, he's so great
Remember how it felt when
he cheated on you, though?
Which time?
I am not going to let Kelly
throw her life away on Ryan
And it has nothing to do with
access to my pediatrician
Why you would even ask
or were going to ask
Because I feel like
that question was coming
But, you know, whatever
Ask me anything.
When you lost the
manager job Yes?
...did it affect you
outside of the office?
How?
I don't know what
the technical term is
Penial softy-osus
Erin, I am so glad
that you trusted me
You came to the exact
right person for this.
No, I have never once experienced
anything remotely like that.
Ever, ever. Never
Okay?
Okay
Washington Monument
Eiffel Tower!
Okay
Colossus at Rhodes
Hey! I hear you've been
badmouthing me to Kelly
All I did was remind her that
you used to treat her badly
Well, that's your opinion and it's
her opinion, but it's not my opinion
If you have something bad to say
to me, Pam say it to my face
Fair enough. Um
a very good person
And forgive me, but I feel like
I've said this to you before.
Well, a lot of people would say that I'm
a better match for Kelly than Ravi is
Come on, Ryan, really?
Ravi's way better.
For Kelly?
Yeah.
Man, you're insane right now
Ravi's the whole package.
I've never met Ravi
personally,
but I'm going to
go ahead and say
just having known you
a short while, Brian,
that I prefer Ravi, and again
I've never even met the guy.
Kelly, look around
Nobody believes in us
Nobody
Ryan, just stop making a scene
in front of all my friends
Kelly, I wrote you the
most amazing love poem.
But I can't even read it.
My heart couldn't handle it
Oh, come on... Oh, no,
no, no read it, please.
No, it would cause
me too much pain.
Read through
the pain. Be strong
This poem would
crush you.
God, Ryan, go away She found
herself a beautiful boyfriend
Yeah, man, he's
absolutely gorgeous
Please leave her alone
You see, Kelly?
Our love scares them
It screws up their
cookie cutter world
Do you guys think
he's right, though?
Do we live in a
cookie cutter's world?
Absolutely, but it's
not the point. God
One of Toby's eyes is getting smaller.
So there's that
Gabe bragged about having an extra
ticket to the air show this weekend
and Meredith said she was interested,
and then Gabe said immediately
that his friend might
be taking the ticket,
so I'll keep you
posted on that.
Every day, I brief Nellie on
what's going on in the office.
Most of it's irrelevant
But a good informer doesn't
judge what's worth passing on.
Oh, and Andy lost
his masculinity,
so congratulations
on that.
What do you mean?
Erin made it clear to me
that he was unable
to perform sexually
last night.
By contrast, I went to sleep
with an erection so large
it was like I was
wearing no blanket at all
but you just
demolished him!
I'm little bit
jealous, actually
Reduced him to a mere ant
I just wanted to take the
man's job not his manhood.
Are we good?
Everybody got a jersey?
I still think it's weird
that we're just doing Rudy.
Like, not a spin on it
we're just doing it.
What about The Dead Poets
Society?\ Much better movie
What? Get your movie
rankings right, dude.
Why can't we just do
whatever movie we want?
'Cause I was gonna
do a Spartacus.
Oh, I wanna do
a Spartacus.
I am Spartacus
No, I am Spartacus
Hey, guys, we're doing Rudy, okay?
So get ready
Okay, I would like to invite
everyone into the conference room
Sure. But first,
there is something
No, that's not important
Conference room, now.
You can't
call a meeting, so
But I would like
to have a meeting
in the conference
room right now,
so come on, guys let's get
in the conference room.
Thank you. Good
Thank you for
coming to my meeting
Appreciate it
Okay, if you would like to take
a seat, we can get started.
Can't do it because I got
to run a meeting, so
Wanted to talk to all of
you guys about importance
and know that each and every one
of you is vitally important
Andrew, not everyone here is important.
And the word is "impotence.'
Which is important
in its own way
so if you'd just like
to take a seat, Andy
Take a man's job,
but leave him his balls
Margaret Thatcher
said that, probably
Don't know. Don't read
Didn't see the movie.
So, Nellie wanted to have
a meeting on impotence.
Have to run it
as impotence is a concept
as foreign to me
as baba ghanoush
Something to do
with eggplant
That's all I know
This meeting is not about any
one person in particular
It is a human problem. It's
not just a human problem
Flounders frequently
experience impotence
especially when converting
from male to female
and then back again to male
- Really?
Nellie, does the "person" affected
by this want us to help her
in any way in particular?
Oh! Oh
It's not me. No, no
I've never had any
problem in that arena
And I have been
with several older men
How old?
Jinx, buy me some Coke
Dwight told me
about it earlier
Dwight?
You promised
Dwight couldn't
get it up for Nellie?
No, no, no, no, no
it's not me.
I'm going to prove it
right here and now.
What are you doing?
Stop that, Dwight
Stop that, stop it
Fine, it was me. I couldn't I had
a problem with Erin last night
Happy?
My mind last night
and I didn't perform
Okay, it happens
to plenty of guys
It's usually not followed by a giant
workplace discussion and an interview
Every guy in this room has been
touched by this affliction. Tuna?
D-Dog
Um
I'm terrible at math
overweight
You're in great shape A lot better
shape than I am tell you what.
It seems Andy is the only
one with this problem
Fascinating
what the problem is
Erin doesn't even like sex
Remember? You said it feels like
getting tackled by a skeleton
Chumbo, come on, help me out Any
problems with Little Chumbo?
Tip top shape
Stanley
No. Mmm-mmm
Creed, you are
1,000 years old
Haven't heard any complaints
Wouldn't care if I did
Okay, so
Actually, Andy
we've experienced it
What happened?
A couple of times.
A couple of times?
Jim, maybe you could tell us
about one of those times.
Yeah. Get it out there
- Yeah, Jim.
Um
Uh, yes, that time
that it was very late
Uh.
We had had sex so many times
already I was exhausted
Okay, stop. I could barely
see I was very drunk
If it makes you
feel any better
I never had an orgasm
until I was 42
And then when I did,
it lasted until I was 44
Forty-three was just
I've read, and I don't know
anything about this personally
but they say prostate
stimulation can help.
Ugh
This is just a This American
Life I think I heard
No, that's absolutely the case.
I know, right?
You know my rectal electro-ejaculator
is rated for bovine use only
but I could let you rent it
Andy, why don't you tell us about
the best erection of your life?
Or does anyone else have any remarkable
erections they'd like to share?
Wow. Oh What are
we talking about?
Toby, doesn't HR
have some rules
against talking about
this kind of stuff?
Erin, HR is a joke. I can't
do anything about anything
The most important thing to remember
is do not stress about this
Stress just makes it worse
and then you stress more
and that's a vicious spiral
come in today
Dad, don't think
of it as a demotion
just think of it as a
promotion to a lower level.
I don't think you have to
tell your friends anything
It hasn't been
decided yet.
Erin, on the phone memos you're
writing the date American style
Month, day, year. I prefer
it day, month, year
Small, bigger, biggest
Oh
Sexual innuendo
not intentional.
Shut up. Shut up, liar
"Sexual innuendo
not intentional!"
I am sick of
your dumb opinions
and if you don't like the way
that I take phone messages, here
Take them yourself
Our sex life is none
of anyone's business
And Andy is the manager
Not Nellie
Stop protecting me! I'm a man!
I can protect myself
This is misdirected anger
and I'm sorry!
I don't mean to
lash out at you
There's a lot coming up
right now all at once
Dad, go to he
I'm taller than you
Okay, just calm down
You are not the manager
I earned that job!
Chosen after Robert
was chosen and quit
Andy, why don't you
just take a seat?
Why don't you
take a seat, idiot?
Why don't you take
all your stupid memos?
And your stupid pens
and your dumb caramels
And your stupid face
And your stupid office
Ah! Ow
He does not
like that wall
Maybe we'll get sent to
anger management together.
That would actually be cool I'd love
for you to meet some of the guys
Andy, Erin
you can join us now
What do you like
about Ryan?
Ryan keeps up with all
the latest technology trends
And he's very honest with me
about when I put on weight
And he has the soul
and the body of a poet
Mmm
Ravi's hotter
and looks are subjective,
but there's no
question about it
Yeah, but I'm just worried
that I'm only
attracted to Rav
because he looks exactly like this Calvin
Klein model that I'm attracted to.
Who cares? That's fine
When I was your age, I had to
choose between a Ryan and a Rav
and I chose the Ryan
And if I hadn't,
I wouldn't have my kids
You'd still have kids
Better kids. You've
got to go with Ravi.
Here's my advice Figure out
what your heart wants.
And if it's not Ravi,
change it. To Ravi
why this is
a dilemma for you
He has, like,
this je ne sais quoi.
He taught me that
Ravi makes me
incredibly happy
And Ryan puts me
through so much drama
So I guess I just
have to decide
which of those is
more important to me
Andy, we're going to go
with Nellie as manager
and put you back
on the sales team
we'll all laugh
about this incident.
I already think
it's kind of funny
No
Excuse me?
I'm saying no
Well, you can't say no
No
Oh. Boo
Holy crap
Boo! Boo! Boo to you Pam, you
are toxic You are toxic.
Kelly, I have a few things to say
to you, but please don't interrupt
Yeah, but you do
a lot, so just don't.
Thank you. I know that I
haven't always treated you
the way that you
for whatever reason
feel you deserve
to be treated
But I want to marry you
Kelly Kapoor
Maybe not today, maybe not
tomorrow but some day.
And probably
Barf! Oh! You suck
What is your problem?
Hey, can we turn this back
around quickly please?
Can we turn this around quickly?
This is very important to me
Turn around
Can we turn this * thing around, please?
Thank you.
She don't want to turn around.
Thank you
Kelly, I can't promise you that
we'll always stay together,
I can't promise you that I'll
never cheat on you Nor should I
Modern marriages aren't built that
way Men aren't built that way
There's a very interesting
article I can email to you
But I can tell you this,
even if the odds are 50-50
that we'll break up
within the week
Ryan
Will you roll
those dice with me?
You mean so much to me
But I love Ravi and I
choose him No, you don't
No, you don't
still be friends
Can I have a hug?
Oh. Ew
Well, it's good to see
Kelly is maturing.
Oh, God
Look, Andrew, we can discuss
the specifics of the job.
No
It's the apology. I really have to insist
Stop saying "no."
No
Andrew, if you say "no" one
more time you're fired.
So, is there anything
else you want to say?
No
I can't describe it. I just, for
the first time in a long time,
Here.
But you hurt your hand. I got it
Right now?
Yes
You're not the
least bit curious
to hear a poem straight
from Ryan's soul?
Not at all.
Can we go?
"Kapoor and Ka-desperate
he watches.'
Second line! "He is a
drifter out to sea."
"And when the Indian Ocean calms
one speck of white remains
"in waters cold
and Kelly green.'
It's just so dumb
But when he describes himself as
a child lost on a life raft...
Ryan can never know