Approved
Chef from South Park. It's genius.
Just some chef.
I've decided to pre-screen all of
the Halloween costumes this year
I have three simple rules
don't be offensive
don't be cliché
and don't take the first
two rules too seriously
The gorilla from Rise of
the Planet of the Apes.
Huh?
The one who
sacrifices his life
Whoa! Oh
Spoiler alert It's been
out for ages, man.
Costume vetoed
Uh.
It's... Somebody's
already called that
Who? Kevin has a gorilla
suit you could borrow.
This is ridiculous! Why can't there
just be two Kate Middletons?
Guys, I know, I mean I
wish there could be too
It's like I can't choose
They're both
amazing, it's just
Look, I stayed up all night and
I watched that g. D. wedding
and then I came to work and I made
everyone else watch it all day
Meredith wasn't even here
Because I was there
You're the people's princess!
Diana was nothing!
I thought you were
at your sister's funeral
What I said was "My sister's
funeral is this weekend.'
Didn't say
I'd be there
Why is it such a shock
that I follow the royal story?
Warms my heart thinking
about them two kids...
...doing it
Can I maybe
squeeze through?
Here you go
There we go. Thank you.
When they talk about app the nice
things about dating a co-worker,
they don't mention
one of the best parts.
After you're done dating, you still
get to work together every single day
Jim, put it on
Put it on, man
I don't know if I can.
Come on the Three Amigos
Three Kings.
All right
I know, I know, I know. But
Darryl and Kevin needed a third.
They bought me
this jersey. I said no
Kevin started crying, so
I am Chris Bosh.
If you get into season
one, you know, really
Oh, my God, what the he
is wrong with you?
It's called a costume
What are you? Some kind
of Jamaican zombie woman?
Ryan, will you please tell her who I am?
Whoopi Goldberg.
Has no one here heard
of Kerrigan, from StarCraft?
Queen of blades
It's all Toby's fault
Every Halloween,
I tell him the same thing
You can't bring weapons
into the office.
And every year he says
the same thing.
"As soon as I get my weapons
back, I'm going to kill you."
But there I am at
Thanksgiving alive, you know?
I'm a lucky turkey
Everybody looking good?
This is the best we can do?
I'm not judging. I think you
guys look great, I just
...want to make sure this
is the best we can do
I just got a text
from Broccoli Rob. "Boo!'
It scared me
And then I got this text
from Robert California
"Looking forward to Halloween
party Expectations are high.'
Scared the *
out of me
G'day, Pameroo Could you
shoot this off for me?
Yeah.
Australian accent
What are you doing? I just
wanted to see how you do it.
If you're doing
something I don't
Are you That Andy
so hot and cold
One day he's like,
"Fax these documents, please.'
The next he's like, "Pam, you fax them.
Who cares what Erin's feeling." Right?
Oh, Erin
Pam
how would you rate me as a receptionist
on a scale of one to three?
Um
Two?
It's like the second to
last thing I wanted to hear
No, I mean
you're doing great
and Andy put you in charge
of the whole party, right?
Yeah
Yeah.
Send completed. You are the
best in the biz. I can't deny
Bob and I are doing this
Scranton haunted walking tour
I always wondered what kind
of people went on that thing.
Hey, if you go
by the Banshee Pub
tell the Man in Black
I say hello
What happened, Pam?
Okay.
When I was 22, I worked there and
everybody said the place was haunted.
I didn't believe it until
one day before we opened
I look up into the mirror
you know, behind the bar?
And I see this old man
dressed all in black,
but when I turn around
there's no one there.
So, I tell the cook my story
Wait, they have food there?
...and he said
"That's what everyone sees
That's the Man in Black.'
No. My wife does not
believe in ghosts
Hey
Oh
This Man in Black thing What
do you think that was about?
What do you mean? Was it
like trickery in the lights
or maybe you were so primed
to see it then there it was
I saw a ghost
Mm-hmm
What I'm saying is, like do
you ever wonder what it was?
It was a ghost. I told you
this on like our first date
Yeah, I had just told you about the
day that I met the Blue Angels.
I figured you had to top it I
don't know what to tell you, Jim
but I saw a ghost
Hey
Uh-oh
Looks like we're under a Jack attack.
- Yes, Andrew.
And you, on this day of
fantasy, are a labourer
Yes Everyone, this
is Bert, my son.
Bert, this is
a paper company
Hey, Bert
Hello
Can I use a computer?
I need to check a hurricane
Here, use this one
All right
Oh, look, pin the word
on the witch
How did you know
I was bringing my son?
I didn't. It was for us
But he can play.
Berty Boy, would you
like to play this game?
That stuff's for babies
Perhaps this party will
awaken the baby in all of us
Wow. Who shot our grownup
party with the kiddy ray gun?
We're still getting it set up
It's going to be really cool
Extraordinary.
Did you plan this?
Well, Toby and I did, yeah
And I overheard and thought "Hey,
that'd be fun don't mind if I do.'
If you turn out the lights
we'll do a little dance
One, two, three
Dem bones, dem bones,
dem dry bones
Now we're the skeleton crew
Delightful.
Thank you
Now then
how are we today?
Fine
Great.
Just fine, Kelly?
Everything all right?
Mm-hmm
You feeling fulfilled
in your life?
I guess
You guess? So there is
something you want that you
do not have
Try not to think
about it
Because it's too
terrifying to imagine
Now we're cooking
What is it, Kelly? What is
this great fear of yours?
Never marrying Yes. Dying
alone, that is very scary.
And how are you, Toby?
So great
Oh, I put those up. I know.
I'm taking them down.
I almost wonder if putting
nothing on this wall
is more Halloween-y
I don't know
about this, guys
Andy put me in charge of
the Halloween party, so.
Well, Andy sent us
in here, so which is it?
Oh
So can we speak our minds now? Or
are we still sparing feelings?
Because I hate
all of this.
Very low pressure
in the Sargasso Sea
Warm air from South America
Cold air from Greenland All signs
point to the perfect storm.
Perfectly mediocre
What are you, anyway?
I'm a Jamaican zombie woman
Leave me alone, ghoul
If you had some really big
wings with blades on the end
you'd kind of look like
Kerrigan from StarCraft.
Damn it! I am Kerrigan from StarCraft.
I've been censored.
If you're going to be a
Zerg, at least be a lurker
Not some girl. Kerrigan is
ruler of the Zerg swarm
Yeah. She also has boobs.
Yeah, but no nipples
Hey
Hey, what's up?
November's sure creeping up, ain't it?
You can't stop that month
Hey, what's the jive with Angela and
Phyllis helping with the party, you know?
Um
I just thought you could
use some help, you know?
'Cause Robert came in and thought
the party seemed a little kiddy.
And I guess I agreed
And maybe we could
mix a little more 13
into the PG.
But that's it?
There's nothing
about me or I?
Can we talk about it
at the end of the day?
I got a call
I got to make a call
Yeah, sorry
Yes, we can
Yes. I don't know
Mm-hmm
Gabe?
Sweet Erin
I'm throwing the Halloween party and
I just want to amp it up a little.
I think it could use
some extra pizzazz
Okay. Where does
Gabe factor in?
Remember that Halloween
party you took me to once?
The one where I started crying
as soon as I walked in
and I didn't stop crying?
Yes. Lars and Takako's
Okay, well let's say that I
wanted this party to be a tiny
tiny bit like that one
just more adult,
more scary and sexy
I will make this sexier
than you could ever imagine
No, just scary. If we wanted
ideas for scary stuff
No, that'd be scary
What are you thinking about?
All right, let me go get it
Pam Halpert
Hey. It's Jim Halpert.
I was wondering if you wanted
to see a movie tonight
'cause I've read a lot about
this really great documentary
Is it called Ghostbusters?
It's called Ghostbusters.
It didn't look like that
He didn't have
a buster sign around him?
Why don't you draw him? Why
don't we see this old man?
Okay. Yeah. Fine,
I'll draw him Okay.
I ain't afraid of no ghosts
Whoa
Mm-hmm
Dwight, are you eating a stick?
It's a root, idiot.
Okay
Everyone hates you.
That's really rude
I don't tell you hurricanes
suck even though it's true
What do you like, tornadoes?
Try influenza
Yeah? What's the vaccine you
could take to avoid a hurricane?
Open up a newspaper.
Look, a hurricane's coming
I suppose you're going to tell me
the scariest animal is a shark.
Try box jellyfish
What are we talking about?
I was talking about my wife and
how she believes in ghosts
Then we had a little debate and then
Meredith said that she believes in them too
You seem unimpressed.
Ghosts don't scare you?
I'm only scared of real things,
like serial killers and kidnappers.
Not things that don't exist
like ghosts or mummies
Mummies are real There
are mummies at museums
Yeah
You prank
It's true. They've
been preserved for
thousands of years
They're all over.
Why on Earth would a
museum put a mummy in it?
A little
witch's brew?
I grew this party
up real fast.
Get out of here, little kid party.
Nobody loves you.
And clean up your room Grownups
are going to use it later
The party looks fun
doesn't it?
Everybody seems to be in
there having a great time
So maybe now would be a great time
for me to pop back on the computer
I'm using it. I'm about to
play StarCraft with him
You serious?
Yeah, I'm serious
Hey, hey. That's funny
Okay.
Loser
Pam, do you think anyone's going to
notice I've worn this costume before
when I wasn't pregnant?
You know I guess nobody would
believe it still fits.
Hey, guys, I'm
an Oscar Liar Weiner
Oh, my God
Party's tight, E Fog is cool.
Thanks
It's on medium
Perfect
It really looks great
You did a great job
Oh. So we don't have
to have that talk?
We should still
have that talk
Maybe you could come by
my office at like 4:45?
Cool
Okay.
Okay, everybody,
be prepared
to be scared
Okay
The Cinema of the Unsettling
is a growing film movement.
The most well known film in the
genre is an hour long shot
of a squirrel
with diarrhea
Okay. Ew
Is that my grandmother?
What's the story?
- There is no story.
Yeah, seems like
there isn't a narrative.
Maybe the filmmaker realized that
even narrative is comforting
What the he
is going on here?
Okay, I think
we've seen enough
You can turn it off now
- Yeah
Yeah, kill it. go ahead
and turn it off.
Thank you - How'd
you get in my car?
Where is this from?
That is so upsetting
That was awful
Robert, I apologize
I'm sorry. I got confused
I heard that you
wanted to make the party more adult
but I think I know what to do now
This game is called
"Pecker Poker.'
It's the game of cards
that gets you hard.
What we have here is a
classic misunderstanding.
Why didn't you simply
ask Andy to clarify?
Asking is a very
easy thing to do
The two of you are
obviously very close
Oh, I see. This no longer
seems like my business
All I knew is that
you wanted to have a talk
with me at the end of the day
and I got nervous, so
You were going
to talk at the end of
I'm not here
Did you think I was
going to fire you?
No, I wasn't
I'm sorry This must be
really uncomfortable for you
I'm never uncomfortable
Okay
Erin, I think you know
I've been dating someone
Sure
And it's getting
a little more serious
She's never come by, so
And she's never called here
Unless it's your mom
No, I didn't want her to call because
I thought it would be weird, but
now it's weird
that she's not calling
Two dates?
Three dates?
Thirty-one
Wow
I'm so happy
for you guys.
Um. Let me know
when you get to 40
I'll see you guys
I should go
I just don't get it, Pam
I mean, you're a rational
person Thank you.
Jim doesn't let me wash his NFL
jersey during the playoffs
How is this any less logical?
Careful. Whoa
First of all, it's not like I think
that's going to help the Eagles win
Really?
No.
That is just a bunch of people
participating in a collective thing.
And maybe the Eagles will hear about
it and want to play better. It's not
Exactly.
Thank you
Go! Get up there
right now.
Got it
Dwight
You want to attack, or let them come to us?
Your call, B.
Unleash the hell storm.
- Dwight
Nice
Dwight
Got 'em. Go
Is she Asian? I don't know.
She's from somewhere, I bet
Maybe from the forest
Forest?
Did Andy say his girlfriend's
from the forest?
I don't know, Phyllis
Maybe she's from the city
Looks terribly real
doesn't it, Creed?
No
Are you scared of snakes?
You don't live
as long as I have
without a healthy fear
of snakes, Bobby.
Yeah, I guess sometimes I have
nightmares about being buried alive.
Honestly, Jim gives
me the creeps
What am I up to?
Like a few years
down the road, Cece says
"Mom, there's
a ghost in my closet.'
Now you say one of two things One,
"You're just having a bad dream."
Or two, "Let's go see
what it wants."
I'm not going
to freak her out, Jim
Okay I'm not going
to lie to her either
Oh, come on
When I was a boy,
there was an empty house just
up the h from my family's
It was rumored a man
committed suicide there
after being possessed
by the devil
One day, a young woman, Lydia
moved into the house
with her infant child.
That very night Lydia was awakened
by a loud heinous hissing sound
She walked to the nursery and
there in baby's crib was a snake
wrapped around baby's neck
squeezing tighter and tighter
Oh, my goodness
The crib was full of dirt,
baby struggled to free
itself from underneath
reaching and clawing
gasping for air
Embalmed bodies rose
from their sarcophagi,
lurching toward baby
For they were mummies
No.
Amongst them was a man
Tall, slim.
Jim
Almost instinctively
she turned to her husband
"Wait," she thought
"I don't have a husband.'
For Lydia and her husband had had an
argument one they couldn't get past
Each night they slept one inch farther
apart until one night Lydia left
It was about this time she lost
herself in imaginary worlds.
She had quit the
book club the choir,
citing something about
their high expectations
Her lips slowly
grew together from disuse
Every time she wanted
to act, and didn't,
another part of her face
hardened until it was stone
And that fevered night
she rushed to the nursery
and threw open the door
"Baby, are you okay?"
Baby sat up slowly
turned to mother
and said
"I'm fine, bitch. I'm fine.'
Fear plays an interesting
role in our lives.
How dare we let
it motivate us?
How dare we let it into our decision
making? Into our livelihoods.
Into our relationships.
It's funny, isn't it? We take a day a year
to dress up in costume and celebrate fear.
Toby. Hey, Bert. Want
to see the dance?
Dem bones,
dem bones, dem dry...
You're fired
What?
You heard me.
Pack your things
What? You can't
Gabe? Are you
I'm the CEO's son
Pack your things
You're done.