No, no, no
no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no
no, no, no, no.
No
Okay, fine
Ryan, is something the matter?
Yeah
Smokey's dead
Smokey the Bear?
Smokey Robinson, Pam
He died like
an hour ago
I guess I'm the
first to know
Wow, that's terrible
I really liked him.
Oh, you liked him?
That's nice.
Did you like when he changed the course of
American music like, two or three times?
Did you like that
Tracks of My Tears
is maybe the last true
love song ever written?
I'm glad you
like him, Jim
devastated right now
Well, I second that emotion.
Huh?
I know a few of his songs,
but what were his big ones?
Oh, God, Nellie.
What wasn't his?
Tracks of My Tears.
Yeah
God, so many, Nellie
No, no, no
Tracks of My Tears
and what else?
What are some more?
What's one more?
Okay, I'm not I'm not playing
this game, Pam. Not today
I don't think you love
Smokey Robinson.
All of this to prove how
deep you are about music
Okay, I'm sorry that I'm not a fan
of Jason Mraz or the Beatles.
You don't like
the Beatles?
That's not the point
Eleanor Rigby?
Paperback Writer?
You always think you have time to
see these legends before they go.
What was I so
busy doing?
It says here the Smokey
Robinson dead thing is a hoax
It's on CNN as of
two minutes ago.
Okay, well
That's a relief
Wow, look at that
Says he's actually
playing State College
That's only three
hours away
Oh, my God, Ryan
that's perfect.
You have to go
Tickets are
250 bucks.
$250 is nothing to the world's
biggest Smokey Robinson fan
Yeah
Who's opening?
Paul Anka
Paul Anka?
How can they make the Smoke Man
play with someone like that?
Okay, you could just
show up late, though
How much is parking
like, 30 bucks?
That's not what Smokey
would have wanted
Does want
Tears of a Clown. Don't
call me a clown, Pam
You're better than that
Looking good, RC
I feel like I'm
being strangled
like I'm at some erotic
asphyxiation sex club over on I-84.
The Red Room, say
or Dominick's
Robert, the Senator was going
to wear dark brown tonight.
I'm sure it'll be fine
My husband is sponsoring a fundraiser
tonight for local dog shelters
Robert California bought
two tables for everyone here
These people were
lucky to get seats
because it is going to be a who's
who of the northern 22nd district
but there is a distinct chance
that we're all about to be killed
Well, as long as you don't
want to alarm people
What's going on? There's a
disgruntled ex-employee
sitting in his car
in the parking lot
Oh, that's Andy.
He's just hanging out
That's how workplace
tragedies always begin
A middle-aged white
male "hanging out."
Call the cops
Dwight, I don't think he's
going to hurt anybody
How do you know? I mean, why
do you think he's there?
What kind of weapon he has
Could be a knife
could be a gun.
Could be a series of guns, all
lined up to shoot parallel
I'm going up
to the roof.
I'm going to bring my
gym bag just in case
Everybody told me if I moved
to America I'd be murdered.
Hey
Just wanted to say hi and hear
you say everything's normal
Maybe videotape you saying that so
that everyone upstairs can see?
We think you
might kill Robert
What?
Because he fired you, which means
apparently you're living in your car now.
Guys, everything
is fine.
I'm just here to pick up Erin.
We're going to the fundraiser
Great. That
sounds good
Wait, what?
You're going to the
fundraiser tonight?
That's going to be weird
Why would
that be weird?
It's going to be
super weird.
He just fired
you last week
Andy's just coming
as my date
Hey, I hear you I hope you're right
It just seems like it's going
to be really, really weird
Come in.
You really redid
Andy's office, huh?
Yes, cut out
the clutter.
Very simple,
very minimal
I need you to sign these.
We got a shipment going out
How are things in
the warehouse?
You could go downstairs
and ask them.
The warehouse
isn't downstairs
Is it?
Who knew, right?
L
Tonight could be the
night that Darryl and I
go from casual work friends
to actual good friends.
The only thing standing in our way is
the contempt he seems to feel for me
Robert, the Senator and
I wanted to stop by.
Hello. Robert.
Robert, how are you?
And say hello
- Hello.
Did anyone order a blast from the
past with a side order of sexy?
Hi, Andy
Oh, man, this is weird
Andrew
Oh
Want to shake
my hand, huh?
Because I want to
shake your body
Where.
Where do I look?
It's been so long since I
did one of these things
Okay, all right
What's the question?
How am I doing? Umm
Great
So, how's the talent?
Grey suit over there
is sending a signal.
Downstairs is receiving
Is that Gabe?
Ladies
How come you look so
decent all of a sudden?
Yeah, normally you
look so stricken
Well, I'm embarrassed
I had to give up
my hair gel
because it was giving me
this angry rash on my scalp
And I just gave up
on this low-protein diet
that I was doing
for eight years, so
Ladies seem to like it, plus I'm getting,
like, half as many bladder infections
Wow
Yeah.
Wow You ladies look
very pretty as well
Thanks
Why is it that things are
their most beautiful
in the autumn of their lives?
You had to say that
Sorry. Sorry.
Thanks
Yeah
Creed, I just bid $20
on six jujitsu lessons
No one's
raping this guy
Well, I don't
want to get raped
No, it was my idea to
not be raped Oh, well.
Wait, you think that
jujitsu classes cost $22?
If you're going to
play guess the price
you might as well try
and be halfway accurate
$180
Whoa
Dwight, I don't think
you understand.
You guess the price
you win the prize
Have you never been
to a Quaker fair before?
God
So, Dwight doesn't
understand silent auctions.
Guy in the office. Huh?
Because up until now
we didn't have one
What haven't I been doing?
Gosh, just today I was working on
this rock opera that I'm writing
although it feels more like I'm
receiving it than writing it
Wow, that's
exciting
But until you firm up the idea, you
might want to keep it between us
The hero lives in
this dystopian future
and he flies around in a spaceship
that's shaped like a treble clef.
And he has to sing his heart
out to destroy all evil
Sounds like you're
doing all right.
A little better than
all right, actually.
Really good
Have you thought about
getting into photography?
Are you kidding me?
'Cause I'm way into it
What are you
taking pictures of?
Children?
Yes
Homeless people?
'Cause in a way
they're more real
...than the rest of us!
The rest of us
This guy's
having a breakdown
You know, Oscar, I really had no idea that
you were so passionate about animals.
My dog, Gerald is my life.
Really?
Well, if you want to
get involved, call me
This is my cell
I'm more likely to
pick up at night, say
after 9:00
Excuse me
This confirms three things
I'm right about the Senator, I
still got it and poor Angela.
Got the flowers.
That piece is
so predictable
Daffodils in spring I wonder what's next
mistletoe at Christmas?
Yeah
Oh! It says, "You're welcome
to take this home.'
Oh
Sweetie, you don't want that Even
in your house, it's a little much.
Have you ever been
to our house?
Not exactly,
but I know the Flats
I'm going to say what
everyone is afraid to say
Phyllis is a bully
A big, beautiful bully
And she is not
getting that centerpiece
Step in right
away and start
Bobby, Bobbo
You're a rock
opera guy, right?
You like rock operas
Well
You've got to check out
this thing I'm working on
It's really cool
There's this character
Thomas Oregon
and he wants to destroy all
the guitars in the world
because he realizes that music is
the one thing he can't control
So, Thomas Oregon
is an evil figure
Evil
Although he's
humanized at the end
because he weeps uncontrollably
and pees in his pants.
And the hero
who is that based on?
Me, I guess
We're flying so high
we're cracking the sky
Going to fly out of this
dome My girlfriend and I
Hey, jabroni,
show some class
She's right, Andy
You're being a jabroni
You're being a
Thomas Oregon
Andrew
I think this may have
been a bad idea.
Why don't you let me
pay for you and Erin
to go out to a great
romantic dinner tonight?
Don't need you to pay for me.
I'm doing just fine, thank you.
Why don't you quit
harshing our mellow?
Andy, you should leave
Now
Excuse me
I would like to purchase two
seats at another table, please.
I'm sorry. The tables are
sold as complete units.
Then I'll take a table
Okay
And a high five
Let's do that again
Well, I just give a
dollar to every charity
That way, you get all the
mail, all the calendars.
You can't believe how much
you get just for a buck
It's also nice to know
you're making a difference
Jim and I give
to the Red Cross
Are you sure you
ought to be giving?
I mean, with your
financial situation
Excuse me?
You ladies are as tangy as the salad
dressing over there. I love it.
Oh, yes indeed
When
Whoa
Whoa, whoa, whoa
Forgot a few salads
When
I stumbled into a
very dramatic situation
Here, let me move this
so you can see him.
Pam
Pam.
Yeah
Angela's husband
just hit on me.
Oh, my God I know.
Wait, what? Come on
We were talking
about animals
He gives me his
cell phone number
He was just dying
for me to have it.
Okay, Oscar, I'm not saying
you're not dreamy because you are
but isn't it possible that he
was just schmoozing a voter?
Well, if you would have
seen the look he gave me
He wanted to rock
more than just my vote
Okay
What was this look?
Whoa
What happened? Did he do it?
Are you
Twice. For real?
Okay, guys. Not every glance
means something, all right?
Life isn't Downton Abbey.
Life is Downton Abbey.
Here's what
I'm going to do
I'm going to go over there
I'm going to talk to him
And I guarantee you he gives out
his cell phone to everybody
How much do you guys charge for
one full-year gym membership?
Thank you
It's $475
Like candy from a baby
That's the third time you've
asked me about my strategy
It's called "Guess the Price, '
strategy's in the name.
Simplest game since
"Touch the Rock."
Three-time champion
Almost four, but
I touched the wood
Hey
David Wallace?
Andy Bernard?
Hey, how are you? How you doing?
I'm great.
How are you doing? Are you
still with Dunder Mifflin?
No, got canned last week
Oh. I'm sorry
to hear that.
No, best thing that
ever happened to me
That's the attitude
to have.
You know what? When I got
canned I was lost, right?
I poured myself into this ridiculous
vacuum for toys called Suck It.
Yikes.
Yeah, exactly, right?
Then suddenly
out of nowhere
the US Military bought the
patent from me for $20 million
Point is,
forget those guys
Okay? Move on
Good to see you, Andy
Call me a lay man, but I wish
there was some real food here
You know
like hamburgers
or Oreos,
or a pizza pie, or
What's another food that we like?
Tacos
What I wouldn't give
for a big mess of tacos
Tacos.
Right now
some tacos.
Brilliant
If you loan me
some money
Yes, I can do that
For two tacos we
probably need about
what, $20?
Or $25? 20
30.
$30
Yes, yes
I've never eaten a taco
I'm not entirely sure
what they are.
As long as they're not slimy, and
please, God, don't let them have eyes
So?
Boom
This is interesting
Mm-hmm
What is interesting?
He gives his cell
out to everybody
Or you proved that
he thinks you're gay
He doesn't think
Jim is gay.
A gay man would not leave the
house wearing those shoes
A gay man wouldn't leave the
store wearing those shoes
Hey, you bought
me these shoes.
Wait a second
where's the centerpiece?
So I threw it in the garbage.
Really, Phyllis? You didn't
just put it in your car?
Nope
Which garbage?
It's not there anymore.
A man emptied the garbage
into a bigger garbage
and then I heard someone say
they were locking the garbage
You are out
of control, Phyllis
Come on, sweetie. We both
knew how this was gonna end
Before we bring out
our guest of honor tonight,
we are very proud to introduce a great
philanthropist, and a great guy,
Robert California.
Thank you.
Why do we love dogs?
Want me to tell you why?
There is no answer.
Our love for them
confounds reason.
Do you believe this guy?
The State Senator Robert
Lip\ton loves dogs.
He asked me if I loved dogs.
You know what I said?
Yes.
Not a joke. That,
that was not even a joke
Bella here was a
therapy dog for 10 years.
When her owner passed away, she came
to this organization for placement.
But people don't often
adopt older dogs.
So Bella and 11
heroes like her
are being cared for by
our generous volunteers
because, frankly,
nobody else will.
Of those dogs
Andy, that's very
kind, but...
No, no, no This guy can
talk and talk all he wants
but it's not that
complicated.
Andy, why don't we discuss this...
No, no, no. It's about
being there for someone after it's become
inconvenient for them to be around
Hello, everyone.
I'm Andy Bernard
and I am going to take
that bitch home.
That is a female
dog reference.
This bitch
understands loyalty
Sassy human reference
Thank you.
I will take Bella
Aw
And every single
one of her friends
Oh, God
This way
Hope you all learned
something Okay.
Huey's going to need his
medication once every 90 minutes.
You can administer it orally,
but he's going to puke it up
So other end's best
Don't split up Daisy and Mojo
because Daisy will start to...
I was going to say bark
but it's more of a scream
I'm so ready to love
all of these animals
This one's even bonding
with me already.
A therapy dog.
He apparently thinks you're in
some kind of emotional crisis.
Stupid dog
If you would like to talk about this
some more, my door is always open
So here's my office number
and my cell number.
Thank you.
Okay
Well, it looks like he
really did just want
to talk about the issues
I'm sorry, Oscar
No, sorry about what? There's
nothing to be sorry about here.
No, I'm certainly not disappointed that
Angela's husband wasn't hitting on me
I'd have to be a
monster to root for that
A lonely, aging monster
Tacos were on sale
Eight for $3
Oh, great
Okay
Oh. Oh. Oh
These tacos
Mm-hmm
Mmm
Uh.
Mmm. Oh
Huh
Mmm
Well, that's hit the spot
Um
Very savory
What do you do with
the crispy holder?
Here, let's try this again
Here, don't put
your finger in
Yeah, just hold it like that.
Hold it to the side
Right
Lean it to the side.
Look at me, like this
She's trying
The winner of the three-day
trip to the Skytop Lodge
is Dwight Schrute!
Yes
The year-long membership to
Scranton Bikram Yoga is...
Dwight Schrute!
Oh, yes
Yeah
A one hour appointment with the "Kissing
Magician" goes to Dwight Schrute.
Oh, yeah
Well, I think I can save
us all some time.
Dwight Schrute has
won every single item here.
Thank you very much
All I had to do was look up
the prices, idiots. Suck it
Well, Dwight, yes, you certainly
are a record breaker.
Your donation is the largest
we've ever received
at over $34,000.
Speech
Come on. Speech, speech
Thank you.
Wow, I can't tell you
what an honor it is
to support this
thing.
And obviously that amount of money
is no concern to me whatsoever.
But I want to ask
you something.
When did it become
all about the money?
When did it become about
the flower arrangements?
And the white
wine spritzers?
Hmm?
And all the dinner rolls?
You people should be
ashamed of yourselves.
How many courses did
we have tonight?
Two? Three, maybe?
If you chose the pudding.
These tables tarted up
like Victorian whores.
Let's remember we are all here
for the dog society.
He's what's important,
whatever his name is.
Not any of this.
So that is going to be
my donation to you.
Thank you and good night.
Whoa
Uh
Oscar. Nice to
see you again
It was lovely
And don't forget to call. Okay
Thanks so
much for coming
Why does this always
happen to me? Ahh!
I just feel so
bad for Angela
Apparently, there were some silly
rumors going around tonight
We are very much in love
Very much in love
So it just goes on under
here like this?
That's right
Oh, God. Yeah, you never
get used to that.
Hey, just wanted to check in
to see how you're doing.
He's great.
We're all great
Twelve dogs
This is my life now
I'm a dog nurse
Look at that one,
though. He's smiling
Yeah, he should be It's his
first day without a muzzle
This is the greatest thing
that has ever happened to me.
Absolutely, it's
Yes
Awesome.
I'm sorry
Are you guys nuts?
He's not doing great
He was fired
This is terrible
This is literally the worst thing
that has ever happened to you
Not the best
You're right
He's right. I am a mess
This whole night I've been trying
to convince you guys that I'm fine.
I guess I thought that if I could
convince you that I'm fine, maybe
Maybe you would
think it, too.
I'm sorry,
it's just, I
in a lot of human
conversations, so
Okay. Well, Andy, listen it's okay
if you don't feel totally settled.
This is all very fresh
Yeah, I mean, admitting that you
need help is the first step.
Yes, and also focusing
on the positive.
Like, I got a lot of good
things going on.
Yeah, like that
rock opera.
You could always
do that, right?
Yeah, I do. I have that
Yeah
You're going
to be all right
No. No, he's not
Yes, I am
Thank you, Kev
You're welcome
Sometimes I feel like everyone
I work with is an idiot.
And by sometimes
I mean all times.
All the times
Every of the time
So, some of us ended up
adopting those elderly dogs
It's been great
Pepper's been getting me out
of the house Going on runs
My dog Ruby
doesn't do anything
She just lays
there all day
She's so chill
What do you
feed her?
Well, I put out Pro Bow Wow
but she barely touches it
She's so dainty
Is she sick?
How are her poops?
Doesn't really poop
It's perfect
Nothing to pick up
She just kind of lies there
all day like a good girl.
But I have to prop her eyes
open so she can see it.
Does she smell?
She smells horrible
It's unbelievable
But I don't want to
put her in the bath
'Cause I'm afraid
that she'll drown
People seem awful
interested in you, Ruby
Guess they're
just jealous, right?
Yeah, that a girl
That a girl
Man, that stinks