Ho-ho
Look who's back reporting
for duty Hey, guys
Hey
Hi
Pam! Ha
Look what I can do now that
she's no longer pregnant
Bam! Bam! Bam! Pam
Are you glad
to be back?
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I could have
used another week, or three
You still had eight
weeks more than we did.
Well, it's not
exactly a vacation
Hello, everyone! Remember?
Little old me. Hi
What are you doing here?
You just had our baby.
Our collective Dunder Mifflin
family baby four days ago.
I wanted to come
back to work.
Not everybody needs some long,
luxurious, Parisian maternity leave
Damn, girl! Your body!
What?
Angela, you
look amazing
Really? I feel like
this big rhinoceros
Anyway, I wanted to thank you guys for
covering for me, so I made some treats
I've got brownies
and magic cookie bars
Mm-mm-mm
Angela, those brownies have walnuts in them
and I think Kevin's allergic to walnuts.
You're allergic to
walnuts right, Kevin?
Extremely, but I'm going
to fight through it
It's okay, Angela. I have mommy brain, too
what that is, Pam
special for you,
Kevin. Right here.
When did you find time
to do all this?
Babies sleep a lot, Pam
if you feed them enough
Brownie, Pam?
Thank you
Oh, my gosh
It's really good
I'm watching my weight
Say, guys, you know what's an even
more useful treat is cash. So
Nope. It's over. No. Okay
We wanted to say thank you
Dwight, I have exciting
news for you What?
Going to like it
You can't tantalize me
Oh, maybe I can
I got an e-mail
from corporate
that told me
Okay.
...that you got
a promotion
Right? I mean, that's not the kind of thing
you want to read quietly at your desk
If you make me head of sales
one more time, I swear
No. This is legit
You will be assembling a team to
go to Tallahassee for three weeks
to develop and launch
a chain of Sabre stores
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah
Yeah! Yeah!
The Schrutes
have a word for when
everything in a man's life
comes together perfectly
"Perfektenschlag.'
Right now, I'm in it
I finally get a chance to
prove myself to corporate
a competent team
I am likely a father
I am so deep inside of
perfektenschlag right now
And just to be clear,
there is a second definition
"perfect pork anus, '
which I don't mean
And here's
the fax for you
some facts for you
Did you know frogs can
hear with their lungs?
And that flamingos can have
orgasms that last 30 minutes
Love to learn. Yeah, it's weird
that I said that last one.
So
Yeah, look at that
We're pin twins.
Pin twins
This is a gift from Jessica
Kind of a gag gift, really
Real gifts come later
Yeah. That's cute
When I saw it at CVS
it made me gag, too. Just
For a while there, I thought
something would change, but nope.
Andy's still with Jessica
They even carpool
together most days.
I don't know.
I wouldn't mind carpooling
every day with Andy,
but I wouldn't want to spend
that much time with Jessica
What do we have here?
Val knit me a beanie.
But I can't tell if it's a
"We're just friends" beanie
or a "I'm hot, you're hot,
let's get it popping" beanie
So I'm going
to up the ante
Give her a clearly
romantic gift.
And we'll get to the
meaning of the beanie.
Pam, pack up your
post-natal swimwear
make it a one piece or
this offer is rescinded
and join me for a fantastic barbeque one
week from today in Tallahassee, Florida
where I'm going to be living
for the next three weeks.
Really?
Mm-hmm
I'll fly anywhere
for some good barbeque
Ooh, me three
No plus ones. This is for
competent workers only.
And don't worry about the cost.
Sabre is footing the bill
Does this have anything to do with
what you were talking to Andy about?
God, you're
such a spy.
Notice anything
different about me?
You're wearing the beanie.
You like it?
Super comfortable Like
sweatpants for my head.
It's really itchy
uh, but to be fair, my
head is constantly itching
so I can't really
peg it on the hat
Wow. It's like the Nation
of Islam down here.
Don't hate.
Who's that for?
Oh. This is a gift for
my man Nate here.
What?
Yeah
Darryl, you
shouldn't have
Can I open it? No, no,
no maybe just later
Ah, I can't wait I'm sorry.
I'm too excited.
Darryl
Wow. Those
are really nice
They're so elegant
Cashmere
How did you know?
Just a hunch
Your gift is on the way
Can't wait
"I'm glad you're in my life
Happy Valentine's Day."
Darryl, I am glad
to be in your life, too
Your card is more
beautiful than the gloves
My first task as special project
manager Dwight Schrute,
assembling a crack team.
I need people who are loyal,
people who will help me get an inroad
with the gay Hispanic community.
People who won't be missed.
We don't need idiots.
Good for nothings.
Meth heads.
Or...
What's your name?
Cathy
Cathy.
I just got a text from
Robert California that says
"Bring your clubs
to Florida."
Why? Does he think you're
going to Florida?
I hope not. Because
I am not going.
Two question marks?
No, just do one. Two question
marks is kind of aggressive
You know, it's like
"Well, what?"
Just do one
You want to take Darryl Phyllis,
Toby, Angela and Oscar?
Yes
Can I interest you
in someone less essential?
Like a Creed or a
Meredith perhaps?
Oh, my God They're not
expendable exactly
I can't think of the word
I'm trying to find
Are you kidding me?
I'm supposed to get on an
airplane with those nincompoops?
We'd never make it
off the runway
All right, look, I got to keep
this office functioning somehow
so I have put
together a list
Here's your team
Darryl and Phyllis
you can have
You're also taking Cathy
Kelly and Kevin.
Oh, God.
You have your team
Kevin? Kelly? Cathy?
Andy just gave me a chain
with three weak links
Have you ever tried to use a chain
with three weak links? I have
And now I no longer
own an Arctic Wolf
Well, let's hear it
"Robert, hey,"
exclamation point I like it so far
"Got your text
Awesome idea
"Let's hit the links the next
time you're in PA. -J.H.'
It's perfect. You emphasize the
golf, completely omit the Florida
Yeah, it's a golf text
Total golf text. Send it
Done. Wait, I just feel weird
I should just call him
You want to call someone that texted you?
Do you want to drive them away? I mean
This is Darryl
Sorry, I asked for
the main shipment number.
I just need the address
for the warehouse.
My girlfriend
some flowers.
Your girlfriend?
Is your girlfriend Val?
Yeah. Do you know her?
We're friends
Cool. So can I get
that address or...
Yeah, yeah. Sorry I'm
just looking for a pen
Why do you
need a pen?
Back off I got my reasons
May I have your
attention, please?
Could Cathy, Phyllis,
Darryl, Kevin and Kelly
please join me in the
conference room immediately?
Why?
No big deal
It's just that you five have been
deemed most deserving of a three-week
all expenses paid business
trip to Tallahassee, Florida
Hell, yeah
What?
I'm sorry, Stanley. I can't
share any more details with you
You see
Andy rejected you
Wait
Cathy gets to go?
Why does she even still work here?
Pam is back.
It just feels like
a slap in the face
I can understand your pain.
And your rage.
But you know what?
Andy is an honorable man
Let us not question his choices.
I'm sure he had his reasons.
We're not questioning his reasons.
I just want to know what they are
I know. You and me
both, brother.
It seemed kind
of random to me
but he was pretty clear on who he thought
truly deserved this boondoggle of a lifetime.
Well, he nailed it because
I do deserve a vacation
Sometimes Batman's
got to take off his cape
Good point. But we're going to be
working pretty hard until 5:00 p.m
After that, it's going to be beach
volleyball trips to Cape Canaveral
and sea kayaking
with Gloria Estefan
What were the
criteria for going?
It might be innate goodness
versus innate badness
But there's an easy
way to find out
Oh, Andy, got a few
questions for you
Moshi moshi.
Uh, the Florida
picks got out,
and people were just kind of curious
as to why they weren't picked,
and maybe you
could just clarify
Uh.
Well, the deliberations were confidential,
so I feel like we should respect that.
Respect it? You're
trying to tell me
Kevin Malone deserves more
than Stanley Hudson?
Hey
Okay, it's obvious
that Andy picked the people that
are least important to the office.
Important? Because you and
your enormous monster baby
are so important
to the branch?
My baby is
not a monster
Hey, be proud of your
enormous monster baby
an enormous
monster baby
Guys! Guys! Guys
Come on, seriously, we cannot let this
trip cause this kind of rift, guys
Stop calling us "guys"
when I'm nervous, guys
Guys, guys, guys. Guys.
- Stop it
Stop! Stop it! Andy
Dudes
The dudes who are going to Florida
were picked by Dwight and me
Okay, hey, I
specifically remember
that there were a lot of other people
I thought should be considered.
Uh.
If anybody's going to
Florida, it should be me.
Every shirt that I have that isn't
a work shirt is a Tommy Bahama.
I'm the only person in this
office who watches Burn Notice.
Okay. I did not realize that so
many of you wanted to go so badly
so if you feel like you have a
very good reason to go to Florida,
I'm happy to hear you out.
Great idea
So why doesn't everyone just
take the next five to six hours
come up with a statement on why you
feel you deserve to go to Florida,
and Andy and I
will listen to it.
No, that is a ridiculous waste of time.
For you maybe
Five to six hours?
Three to four hours
No, no, no, no. No.
Just two to three hours
Come up with a statement
over the next hour.
Thirty minutes
I'm out
Okay, read it
back to me
"Robert, great offer. Wish I could
hit the links with you in Florida,
"but a father of a newborn really should be
helping out his wife any chance he gets.'
Good. Doesn't sound pushy
You're just stating a fact
Absolutely
Works for me
Okay. Sending.
Well done. And we managed
to kill the entire morning
We really did
He responded, "L.O.L.'
I am already...
I already picked my team, Darryl,
Oscar, Angela, Phyllis and Toby.
And that is the team
that I am taking.
What's that? It's not up to me?
I only have influence?
Well, that's all
Baltzer Glattfuelder had
and now no one eats
owls for Thanksgiving
You have two young dynamic
people in this office
who know trends
who know youth.
That's myself and Kelly Kapoor
you need one of us there
Or both? Not both. Just one. Me
Or if not me, Kelly
Ideally me
Again, youth knowledge
that's what you get when you put Ryan
Howard on your special project team
Or Kelly Kapoor.
Again, not both. Thanks
Very impressive
He put a lot of work into that.
Mm-hmm
PowerPoints are the peacocks
of the business world
All show, no meat
Because I feel like that I am in
a place with my gambling rehab
that I can finally start
going to dog racing again
You know, just sitting
watching, enjoying the sport
Maybe putting down a few dollars if there's
like a crazy mismatch or something
Okay. Thank you Kevin,
we'll let you know.
Thank you.
When do we leave?
Thank you
It really has been
a long, lonely winter
Wow. Seasonal affective
disorder, a.k.a. SAD.
That sounds like
a very real thing, Toby
It is real. Thank you
for saying that
Yeah, wow,
it's almost like
we're not all experiencing
the same winter
Florida Stanley smiles Florida
Stanley is happy to go to work
Florida Stanley is who you
want on your Florida team
It's still... Well
...she does here
Hey, guys.
Any spots left?
Erin, you want to go
to Tallahassee?
I think it would be a
nice way to clear my head
You know, I don't think it's a good
idea for you to clear your head
any more than it
has been already
a workplace where
the burdens of everyday life
keep you tethered to reality
Either or
But if you can find someone to
fill in, I would love to go
Well, it wouldn't be hard
to find someone to fill in
Really? Oh, great. Good
Now, is it too dark to say that
Cece's having an operation?
I think you need
to go to Florida.
It's only for three weeks
You know, with my mom and
sister at the house, it'll be
A total nightmare
because I'll have
all the help I need
Yeah, that's what I'm saying
They're incredibly helpful.
You're lucky
to have them
With them there, you probably
won't even know I'm gone
Exactly
Well
No. No! Absolutely not You are not going!
Over my dead body, no. Andy
Toons, I'm really sorry
You're too essential to the
operation here I can't let you go.
I wouldn't say that
That's a bit much
You know, Dwight if you
didn't want me to go
the smart move would be to tell Andy that
I actually am essential to the operation
That way, I couldn't go
Jim is essential Hold on. I
just want to get it on camera.
Andy, Jim is just too
Essential
This is stupid! Cut
All right. I'm going
to pack my trunks
He doesn't even
want to go.
Well, I got a text
from R.C.
inviting me to come down so I think
that's going to make us roommates.
Oh, my God
Hey, quick question, do you shower at
night? Or do you shower in the morning?
Because I want to shower when
you're showering to save some water
Okay, listen up, everyone
Here's who's going to Florida
Cathy
What?
Stanley.
No
Ryan.
Erin.
And Jim
You got to be *
kidding me. Okay
Okay
Florida group,
welcome to the team
Let's go
Step it up, you runts.
You infants. Let's move
Why is it so
hot in here?
Hot? What are you talking about? This
is a nice, temperate Florida morning
Eighty-five degrees
73% humidity.
This is the exact environment
that you will be facing
for the next three
weeks of your life.
Welcome to Special
Projects orientation.
The next three weeks
of your life
are going to be the most
miserable you've ever faced.
They're going to be hard
They're going to be dirty
You're going to
wish you were dead
But?
"But?" There's no "buts.'
That's it. You'll wish you were dead.
You seem a little disturbed
Do you want to stay here?
No. No. I want to go.
Because if any of you
would prefer to stay here
all you need to do
is ring this bell
Is that the buzzer
from Taboo?
Shut up, maggot
It is.
You don't want to go
ring the be
Ring it. Ring it
How many of you have seen the
documentary Deliverance?
How did a mosquito
get in here?
I released 300 mosquitoes
into the conference room.
Just temporarily
When I'm done, the frogs will
take care of the mosquitoes.
Yes. And then he brushes
your soft supple cheeks
with his worn leathery
hands and says
"I'm going to make you
the seventh Mrs. Rosenblat!'
Unless you ring
the bell. Ring it
No.
Ring the bell
You want to spend the rest of your life
changing your husband's colostomy bags?
Huh? Do you? Ring it
What? Ah.
What was that?
Mosquito
Orientation's over
Darryl, hey
Hey, what's up?
You called?
Yeah, you know,
I felt really terrible
that you got me these lovely gloves,
and I didn't get you anything
It's cool, really
No, it's anything
but cool.
Now, I haven't really had time to
go out and buy you anything, but
here goes
"This coupon entitles you to one
free tickle monster attack."
Yeah. They're Nate coupons or
Nate-pons And they're all different
Cash that one in and I will
bring you a stick of gum
any time, any place
I'll find you.
Thanks
Nice flowers
Thanks. They're
from my mom.
Your mom?
Yeah
Oh
So I guess that was your mom who called
me earlier looking for the address.
Real deep-voiced woman
Yeah, that's her
She said her name
was Brandon, I think
Your mom's name
is Brandon?
Yeah, Darryl. My mom's
name is Brandon
out where I stand
This is a love beanie
Okay, Florida team
let's reconvene.
I'm going to Florida
And I'm not coming back
So Sabre has set up a conference room
for our use while we're at corporate.
So what is this
special project?
Basically, Sabre has
tasked us with
helping them branch into
the retail market place
They want to set up their own
version of an Apple store.
That sounds awesome
It did. It did
You know what
might be great?
Is if instead of a genius
bar, we have a lounge area
where people can ask
questions about the product
with other customers
who liked it
Yeah, and they should have a place where
people can check their computers or printers
before they see you, so you don't
have to carry it around like a dope
Like a coat check
Oh, don't write it down
unless you like it
Oh, I like it
It seems to me that the Apple
store is kind of like a party
so I think our question is how
do we make this a better party?
No. We sell business tools and
the stores need to reflect that.
They need to be all business Let all the
other stores look like a toy store.
Right. Think different
From Apple.
Dwight, is now a good time to
go over what you expect of us?
Yes
What are my expectations
for the group?
I have been given the responsibility
to manage Stanley, a solid player.
Ryan, who is capable
of surprises.
Erin, an excellent
follower.
And Cathy, a probably not
totally useless enigma.
And, well, Jim.
Under the right manager
that's not a bad team.
Perfektenschlag
I'm going to live here
without you
Me neither. Hey, will you
put this coat on my chair?
I just realized I'm not
going to need it down there
Yes, I will take
your coat.
And I will keep it
with me
and I will sleep with it
because it smells like you
No, no, no, no, no.
Just put it on my chair
All right
Bye
Bye. Call me when
you land I will.
Safe travels
Goodbye for a very
very long time.
Okay
It's only three weeks
All expenses paid
Yeah. Jim's going
to be there.
That marriage is not good
Nobody knows better than me
Definitely, we will
It's three weeks in Tallahassee.
What else is there to do?