Val, I need the space
All right
guys, clear out
Everybody out
Promise me you're
going to clean up.
What I'm going
to do or not do
Promise me
Obviously
I'm going to clean up
Stress is like the uptight
mayor of a town who's saying
"Hey, we're uptight
You can't dance."
And then, you have to be like "Oh,
yeah, Mayor Stress? Well, watch this.'
And then, we dance.
Oh, how we dance.
Sex also works
Hey, Jim's back
from jury duty.
Hey! Tuna
He's back
Hey
Oh, look at this
Tuna wrap
Okay
Hand roll
How was jury duty?
Pretty uneventful
actually.
Let someone like you
serve on a jury
Makes me question
the whole judicial system
What was the case?
A hit and run
Ooh! The case of the hit and run.
That's exciting.
Did you send him
to the slammer?
No. Not guilty
Of course you
found him not guilty
He apologized And I just really
want him to like me. Mmm!
We're best friends
actually.
We're going wine tasting next
weekend if you want to come
Not coming
Have plans.
Okay
I did get called
into jury duty
And they
released me around noon
so I didn't
think it was worth it
to come back to work
for a half day.
And then the next morning, Pam was
a little overwhelmed with the kids
so I took an extra day
to help out.
And then
three other days happened
Ah
Angela had the baby
Is it black? Because
that would be hilarious
Why?
You know
Would it be more hilarious than
Angela having a Chinese baby?
A little bit. Yeah.
Right, guys? Back me up
Maybe a little bit
Oh. Did I win the pool?
Uh, no Right month wrong year.
No one won the pool Angela
wasn't due for another month.
We should all go to
the hospital and visit her
Oh, I'd love to, but
Oh, man, I would, but I
can't miss any more work
Well, Kevin and I have to go because
accounting is its own little family.
Yeah, Oscar's the dad I'm Oscar's
dad and Angela's my mom.
Everyone,
our very own Angela
We all got the e-mail Some
of us are going to go visit
Oh, I am so in
It's the perfect blend
of love and horror
Things can go so
wrong or so right
Come on, Judge Judy tell us your case.
What were the deets?
It was actually
a pretty boring case
How could it be boring? You were
there for five days Titillate us
Yeah, you owe us. I had to stay
until 6:00 twice to cover for you.
My wife got to
the TV first.
I had to sit through damn
Rizzoli & damn Isles.
Yeah. My car got smashed
visiting one of your clients
and I had to have it detailed
and they took my meter change
Wow. I'm really sorry
Yeah
I never considered
that my week off
would make everyone
else's job harder
The least I could do
was give them a good story
So Phyllis
he was here and then
the car came and
it was like that.
Yeah, so it had to be a
double backflip, actually
You know when I was on
J-duties strangler case,
we used to recreate the various
stranglings with empanadas from Ernesto's
Oh, man, Ernesto's
That was our
favorite restaurant, too
You mean food truck
Ernesto's was a food truck
Toby, shut your hole
about the empanadas
Nobody cares
I was in Los Angeles
last year
Jim tricked me into thinking I'd
won a walk-on part on NCIS,
but that's not important
While I was being kicked off the
lot, I saw food trucks everywhere
Everyone in Los Angeles
eats from them
and nobody calls
them restaurants
Guys, I don't know how
many of you have seen
Gabe, bring it in
how many of you have seen
a premature baby before.
It's going to be really tiny so
please don't say anything offensive
Got that, bimbo?
Got it, bimbo
Yes?
Knock, knock.
Hi.
- Uh
I don't want What are
you guys doing here?
We wanted to say hi to the
newest little Dunder Mifflinite
Well, meet our not-so-little bundle
of joy Philip Halsted Lipton
Philip is so fat
Kevin
You warned me not to say
anything if it was tiny, Oscar
You didn't prepare me
for a big, giant, fat baby
Yes, he's substantial
Hey
He's more than substantial
He's a monster.
So this whole
hit and run thing
there's this one part
I can't figure out.
You said it was
at a four-way stop?
Mmm-hmm
And the victim rode his bicycle
into the left-hand turn lane
but the perp was already in
the left-hand turn lane?
Mmm-hmm
See, that's what I'm having
trouble with, because the fact is
you never said he
was on a bicycle.
Busted, Halpert! Yes
Wait. No
Andy, get out here
was on a bicycle
wasn't listening to you
a citizen's arrest
You have the right
to remain silent.
to beg for mercy.
You have the right to request
judgment by combat Dwight's rights
What's up, gangsters?
Jim was lying
about jury duty
He was lying the whole time so he
could go do yoga or go canoeing,
I don't know what this pervert likes.
Fire him!
Dwight, not everything
is a conspiracy theory
saying that the victim...
Dwight I have me on the record
saying to you take a
chill pill all right?
I don't need to
take a chill pill
Here, right there
Down the hatch
I really don't want
to take a chill pill.
That a boy, good
Now, chill.
Okay, okay
But let's just say that Jim
was lying about jury duty
you would have to
fire him, right?
Yeah, sure. Of course.
I'd fire him to Timbuktu
Ha-ha
Good enough for me
Ah
And Pam was just going crazy
trying to take care of Philip
because Cece has been
out of control recently.
Look, Andy, it doesn't matter The truth
is I just feel terrible lying to you.
Getting lied to
No one's ever
lied to me before
Okay
I think the best
thing to do right now
is just come clean
and tell everybody
No. Not after what I told
Dwight about firing you. No
Here's what
we're going to do
We're going to have ourselves
a good old fashioned cover-up
You ever heard of a
Connecticut cover up? No
You know why you
never heard of it?
Covered it up
Are you sure you can
keep this under wraps?
They used to
call me King Tut
because I'm so good at
keeping things under wraps
My nickname was
actually King Butt
because I had
a king-sized butt
Where do you
want it parked?
Okay, everybody
Gather round.
Got a real special
surprise for you
Ernesto
Hola, Toby!
Uh, I'm going to say "I"
when I'm talking for Ernesto
so instead of,
"He says blah, blah, blah, '
I'm going to say, "I say blah,
blah, blah, ' but that's for him.
Anyway, it was something
like he remembers Toby.
"I remember Toby.'
Oh, Jim. Hey, this
guy look familiar?
It's the empanada guy
The empanada guy
Holy *. Damn it, Toby
No, I wasn't asking you.
Ask him if he
remembers Jim
No
He says no
He says no. Boom
Yeah, but who remembers
all their customers?
I mean, I can name
like three of our clients
He remembers Toby the most
forgettable man in the known world
He doesn't want
any trouble.
He sees lots of people
they come from all around to eat
his delicious meat pockets.
Uh, you guys are going to love
these, so empanadas on me
You guys got to try them
Usually I'm a burrito guy but if you
won't tell, I won't. Wink, wink.
Great And while we're enjoying
these delicious empanadas
Jim, why don't you
tell us your story again?
Why? Everybody's heard it
Walk us through it
What time would you get
there every morning?
Hey, Murder, She Wrote,
how about we drop the whole
Murder, She Wrote thing, okay?
Jim was at the courthouse
for jury duty every morning
How do I know?
Because I drove him there
Why?
Because my car broke down
His car broke down
so he called me
because I live
near the courthouse
Wait, wait,
you live by the courthouse
You drove from near the
courthouse out to Jim's house
and then back to
the courthouse?
Thirty minutes out 30
minutes back easy hour.
And I would watch
that cute, little tooshy
scurry up those courthouse
stairs every morning
and that was that
I'm sorry, do you have
any American Mexican food?
We're getting
buried out there
What was that stuff about
the car breaking down?
Well, I think you
handled it pretty well
I'm not Rumpelstiltskin, Jim, I can't
keep spinning gold out of your *
Okay, listen, all right?
Dwight's onto us. He's going
to figure it out really soon
So let's just get ahead of it.
Let's tell the truth
I don't even know what
the truth is anymore.
Wow, it's so
healthy
I'm going to call
him Little Kevin
No, you will not
Is he really five pounds? Because
I squat with five pounds
This
Yeah, this feels like
more than that
No, no, no he's nine
pounds seven ounces.
Nine pounds? Really?
I thought you said five You know what?
I was under so many drugs
a James Taylor concert
or something
So, what did you bring?
Oh, yeah, I don't know
if it's right, but...
Well, if it's anything like
that gorgeous wrapping paper
you hit it
out of the park
Oh
Preemie pajamas
Again, it may not be
the right size, I can
No, I think he came early
just so he could wear these
Thank you
Call of Duty.
This baby is
clearly not premature
They're lying about
the date it was conceived
It's very interesting
And her husband's gay I don't
even know which thread to follow.
Uh, excuse me, can I have
everyone's attention for a second?
First off, I just want to
say that I'm really sorry
I didn't know that
my absence last week
would have been
a burden on any of you
Because, though I did
have jury duty last week,
they did dismiss me
early on Monday.
And I think you're going to
find this pretty hilarious.
I kind of, well
maybe took the week off
What?
Funny? No? Nobody laughed
You're screwed
Oh! It's happening.
It's really happening
What the hell, Jim I
covered for your bony butt
Pam really needed some help
with the kids, so...
I promise my
intentions were good
Your clients,
they're all mine
Jim, I got my ass chewed out because
one of your orders got messed up.
And Andy, you said you drove
him to the courthouse
Uh, I did
Every morning And if I
didn't then I hope I die
All right, well, let's get this
show on the road, shall we?
Allow me to give you
a hand Here we are.
So long, clump mate
I'm going to miss you
Truth be told,
I never thought that this
was how it was going to end
I was going to
defeat you somehow
but you've
defeated yourself
Dwight, cut it out
I'm not firing Jim.
No, no, no, no
you said...
ANDY
I know what I said
Jim, you're in deep
doo-doo you understand?
And I have one
thing to say to you
and I'm going to say it in
front of this whole office
Look me in the eye
That's it?
This is crap
You've reached Gabe Lewis.
I'm currently indisposed.
Leave me a message. Ciao.
Gabe, it's Dwight again
Highest priority
triple urgent.
Call me immediately
That means ASAP
I'm going to find Gabe
tell him what Jim did
and let the little stickler
do what he does best, stickle
Honestly, I can return
this for a larger size
It's fine Pajamas aren't
supposed to be baggy, right?
It's not the barrio
The only premature baby in this
room is the baby this baby ate
Little Kevin
Really?
Angela
Fine. God
Philip was conceived
nine months ago.
The Senator and I
wanted to wait
but we had just seen Thor,
and there was way too much
wine in my chicken piccata
Chicken marsala
Right
And, the point is, Philip was
conceived out of wedlock
Hmm
And now you all know
but you can never tell
I'm serious
Dwight
Hey
Oh. Hey, have you
seen Gabe?
He went to the car or
something but he'll be back.
Okay
Don't you want
to see the baby?
Why? I know what Angela
and the Senator look like
I can mash that up
in my head right now
wouldn't tell
So don't
Angela got pregnant
before the wedding.
What?
She got pregnant
before the wedding
How long before?
A month
You didn't hear it
from me
Yes, I did
Dwight?
Dwight.
Well, Angela will make you cut
your fingernails It's not worth it
Oh
Yes
What a beautiful child Prominent
forehead, short arms, tiny nose.
You will lead millions
willingly or as slaves
That baby is a Schrute, and
unless somebody taught Mose sex
that baby is mine
He's hungry
Oh, that's my cue
to leave.
No, you don't have to I'm
going to wear this cover.
Still
You won't be seeing
Do you want the giraffe?
Yes, I am bringing my kids in to
help me get out of this hole.
And you all remember
my beautiful wife, Pam
Hi
Wow, I really thought I'd
be more excited to be here
Whoa, whoa, whoa Game face, baby.
Game face
Oh, right. Okay
Hey, Stanley
it's great to see you
No, that's overdoing it I think.
Hi, Stanley.
Split the difference
Jim.
Okay. Let's go
Hi
Hi, everybody
What?
Oh, hi
How about
a little visit?
Wow. What a surprise
That's crazy
You guys get to meet
the little heck raisers
Hey, Angela's back
with her baby.
Yes, well, you guys
all know Cece,
but we wanted to introduce
you to baby Philip.
You guys
He's licking on my finger
just like my cat does.
Let me have a turn
No, it's
the pacifier's turn
All right
Did you say
something about
this one bringing in
something for these people?
Yes. Cece wanted
to thank everybody
for letting her daddy stay home
with her all last week and play
so she brought
you a little treat
Oh, cookies?
No. But that would have
been a really good idea
That would have
been really good
No, she
brought you drawings
Oh, my goodness,
let's take a look at these
They're usually amazing so let's see.
Yep, they are
Uncle Andy
Oh
Aunt Phyllis
Wow. These are incredible
Cece, did you do these?
No
She says no to everything. You
know, she thinks my name is "No.'
Cece, do you want
some broccoli?
Yes
No
It's crazy
Why am I shorter than the table
that I'm standing next to?
ANDY There is crosshatching
in some of these
That's kind of advanced
for a 2-year-old.
Cece, this is your
big sister, Kelly
Did you color
this pretty picture?
No
So then this
means nothing to you?
Hey, Cece
why don't you draw another picture
for us exactly like this one
or at least in
the exact same style?
You know what? I don't think you
need to do things on command.
That's very weird Just take that.
Thank you.
I think we should just wrap
up the show kiddos, right?
Else we can do here
Okay. All right
It's okay, sweetie
All right
All right. Okay
It's okay
Shh
Angela, this child is definitely mine.
He looks just like me
Every baby
looks just like you
Your face kind of
looks like a baby
Need I remind you that we were
together a month before the wedding?
That is completely untrue
Completely true
No
Remember?
You said that Robert
was not fulfilling you
And I said that I
could fulfill you
and you said
"I'd like to see you try.'
And then I kissed you with the
force of a thousand waterfalls
That didn't happen
Then I inserted my
penis into your...
No! Stop it! Dwight
...vagina and
And even if it did,
it's just a coincidence
Admit that there is a chance.
I will not
Admit it
It's not
All done?
Yes
Yes. He's sleeping
Before I go, may I?
Sure
Watch the head
Nurse! You know that baby in there?
Baby Philip?
Cancel the circumcision
Who are you?
What that means
We're going to
circumcise him
Cece, want to come?
No
Want to come play?
Oh, bud, I know.
Do you have a pacifier?
Yeah. I'm looking I'm
looking for the pacifier.
Cece
Okay, we're going
We got to go All right,
we're going home
I know
You gotta grab her
I'll go grab her. Okay
Okay. Here we go
Here we go.
Okay, I'm just going to go down to
the car, and I'm going to put her
in her seat and
I'll be right back up
We'll see you tomorrow
No, no, it's okay
I'll be right back.
No, just go home
It's all good
We got this.
Last week
Jim at home
that was no vacation
Jim, just go
Hey, we'll be just fine
Thanks, guys
All right, here we go
Let's go
Oh!
Phew
Dwight, what the hell?
You can't smoke in here
Oh, all right
Ah
The office looks
different now Mmm
Smaller
Maybe I just feel bigger
Hello, Gabe
You had something
important to tell me?
Oh. You know, I did but now it
seems infinitely insignificant
Jim? Oh, right
No, forget it.
He was doing it for
his kids I get it
Kids drive us dads crazy.
Sometimes I feel
like they're raising us.
Am I right?