Morning, Dwight.
Who are you?
Who am I? I'm Jim. We've been
working together for 12 years.
Weird joke, Dwight.
You're not Jim.
Jim's not Asian.
You seriously never noticed? Hey,
hats off to you for not seeing race.
All right then, Jim.
Why don't you tell me
about that sale that
you made yesterday?
Uh... Wellington Systems? Sold them
10 cases of 24-pound letter stock.
Or were you talking
about Krieger-Murphy?
Because I didn't
close that one yet,
but I'm hoping
I've got a voice-mail
from Paul Krieger
waiting for me.
Please enter your password.
You have one new message.
How did you know?
No, no.
That is sensitive information,
only for employees, not outsiders!
Dwight, cut it out.
I'm trying to work.
You don't work here!
You're not Jim!
Jim, I got us that dinner reservation.
Grico's, 7:30.
Oh! Great. Can't wait.
Jim's at the dentist
this morning,
and Steve is
an actor friend of ours.
I don't know who you are, but
you are not Jim! This is Jim!
Um...
Oh, dear.
How did...
Hey! Study buddies!
Oh! Okay_
Oh!
Getting Things Done.
Awesome!
It's all about finding ways to
make yourself more efficient.
Life hacking, baby.
This morning,
I brushed my
teeth in the shower.
Saved myself 90 seconds, which I
just used to explain this to you.
Damn it.
Since Andy promoted me to
assistant regional manager,
I've been trying to step my game
up, you know, be more productive.
In fact, you know what?
Let's knock out a few more of these
sound bites while we're here.
Whoa. That person
has really gotten
him or herself
into quite a predicament.
Ah, French. It's a great language
if you're a chain-smoking acrobat.
I'm just trying to fit in
better with Andy's family.
They all speak more than one
language, usually when I'm there.
You want to learn a really impressive
second language, try Dothraki.
Win over any man in my guild.
Dothraki is the native tongue
of the nomadic, war-mongering
horse lords of Essos,
as featured in the superb
Home Box Office series
Game of Thrones.
It has a lot of nudity,
which I fast forward through to
get to the chopped-off heads.
I could teach you if you want.
It's a lot easier than French.
Yeah. Let's do it!
Oh!
It means, "Excellent."
And we have begun.
Is everything okay?
Mmm.
Oh. Oh. Yeah, yeah.
Fine, fine. I mean I...
I just don't want to
burden you with my
massive stress freakout.
Great.
It's just that I am taking my
driver's license test in two days,
and I need to practice with an
experienced driver in the car.
But I've had no time to do
that, thanks to "DemAndy."
I just want to hit the
open road and drive, man!
But in whose car?
ANDY; Nellie!
Get your wrinkly
old balls in here!
Nellie, I could practice with
you in my car at lunchtime.
Oh, Pam, thank you!
You are my savior!
0h, my gosh! Oh!
I'm sorry, I'm leaving
you alone for lunch.
Don't worry about it.
I have a thing,
a thing of soup, which
I've been wanting to try.
This is my research into how we
might produce childproof paper
that doesn't
give you papercuts.
We can't.
And here is a printout of your genealogy
from ThislsYourFamilyTree.com.
Executive-summary me.
Hit the highlights.
Well, it turns out you are a distant
blood relative of Michelle Obama.
As in?
Wife of Barack,
loves gardening,
wants to wipe
out fat children.
Wow.
This is super flattering. She's the
most popular person in America.
This is a big
day for both of us.
My fellow Americans!
I have a feeling
my approval rating
is about to go
through the roof.
It turns out I am
related to Michelle Obama.
I was intimidated by
Andy's family before,
and now I have to see
the First Lady at holidays?
She's going to be like, "What's
your stance on politics?"
Or, "What is the best war to
do?" And I will just be like...
Duh...
All right, we've got to get
rid of all this junk food.
Get fit, America. Not sure if the
buzz has reached the annex yet,
but I'm related
to Michelle Obama.
Yeah, we noticed early on that Andy
really appreciates enthusiasm.
CLARK". So we decided the best way to get
ahead here is to be his cheerleaders.
Whoa!
It's starting to have
this reverse effect, though,
where I really do think
the stuff he does is awesome.
PETE".
Yeah, me, too. It's weird.
Hard to remember
what's real at this point.
Just clap
through it, man.
You log in sales at
10 different times.
If you log them all at once, you'd save
a lot of time. It's called batching.
This is really good, Darryl.
Life hacking, man.
There he is!
Andy, you've got to check this out.
He just showed me what...
Right now I
need canned tuna, okay?
Darryl, guess which
talented individual,
who also has
a killer singing voice,
is related
to the First Lady.
Tracee Ellis Ross, daughter of the
First Lady of Motown, Diana Ross.
It's me. I'm related
to Michelle Obama.
What? Really?
I mean,
it's distant, but...
That's cool, man.
Right?
Darryl said, "Cool, man."
He called me a cool man.
You know, I really do
think it'd be worth it to
pull over and just
take 10 minutes to eat.
The thing is, Pam, I'm going to
be eating while I'm driving,
so I might
as well get good at it.
Brake lights. Brake lights!
Brake lights! Brake lights!
Whoo!
I'm just saying, what does
it imply, in this country,
when a white person shares an
ancestor with a black person?
You think that Andy's
family owned slaves?
Well, somebody
owned somebody.
And I don't think anybody
would buy an Andy.
"I throat-rip."
"You throat-rip."
"He/she/it throat-rips."
More of a barbaric growl.
Loudefl You're shouting it
from the back of a horse!
Pretty crazy about
Andy and Michelle Obama, huh?
Yeah.
It's almost unbelievable.
What?
Well, you know
how Andy has been
really salting
my onions lately?
Sure.
Well, when he asked me to
look up his ancestry online,
I remembered that
news story about
Michelle Obama
having white relatives,
and I just knew he
would eat that up.
So, he's not related
to Michelle Obama?
Pam, I barely know
how to turn on my computer.
Nellie's pretty fearless,
and I think she might
be maybe even
almost sort of fun.
Pam!
Well, if there's
another explanation,
I don't really see
what it could possibly be.
What's going on here? I'm related
to the First Lady, okay?
Get over it.
I still need weekly status
reports from most of you.
So, can we get
back to work, please?
Get back to work.
Andy? Andy, no! I would
be very polite today.
Why? Is it Employees'
Day or something?
I cannot keep track
of these BS holidays.
Your connection
to Michelle Obama
has certain
negative connotations.
Most likely, your
family were slave owners.
Does anyone else think it's possible
that I come from slave owners?
Whoa. That person
has really gotten
him or herself into
quite a predicament.
Hey, Mom, it's Andy. Give me a
call when you get a chance,
got a quick
question for you.
No big deal, it's just about America's
national shame. Thanks, bye.
Where were we?
Yes, okay,
your productivity thing.
Yes, yes, yes.
Great. Ooh!
Spreadsheets. Yum, yum.
I included some
time-saving ideas.
Uh-huh, uh-huh. Look,
I'm not going to lie to you.
I'm a teensy bit
distracted right now.
Look, Andy, even if your
ancestors did own slaves,
it wouldn't
be your fault.
This is only weird
if you make it weird.
Right on, brother. Word dat.
Does anyone here have
fermented mare's milk?
Hey, Erin.
Oh. Okay. Sorry.
Aw, still, it must be great to have
something else going on outside of work.
Yeah. Turn signal. It's exciting
to be painting again.
Those are the wipers.
So, it's just, there you go.
Yeah.
Yeah, things get so busy
with the kids, red light,
that it's nice to
have a creative outlet.
Red light! Red light! Red! Red!
That is brilliant, Pam! I would
love to see some of your work.
Well, since we're
stopped at a light,
here is the mural
I did for Angela's baby.
That is amazing, Pam. Oh, I
love the lion in the tuxedo.
Angela insisted that all
the animals be fully clothed.
Hey, has anyone turned in
their status reports up here?
So, no?
Do you think maybe you
could remind people?
I'm trying to downplay the
whole bossy boss thing today.
Because of your slaves. Yep.
Not my slaves, my ancestors' maybe.
Probably not.
Oh. Well, if it makes
you feel any better,
the Dothraki word
for slavemaster...
...is a term of respect.
I'm learning how to speak Dothraki!
Color you impressed.
That you're learning a made-up
language from HBO's Game of Thrones?
I have a lot going on today,
but this was a great nerd-out.
Dwight! You didn't tell me you
were teaching me a fake language.
People laughed at Klingon at first,
and now you can major in it.
Hi, guys.
Hey, boss, I am so thirsty.
Can I have a scoop of water?
Yeah, you don't have to ask me.
Okay, great.
Very funny, I get it.
Just because my
ancestors happen to be...
Very funny, Kevin. Change my ringtone.
Very funny.
I liked the original song on my
ringtone, which you may remember,
was Diamonds on the Soles of
Her Shoes, by Paul Simon,
featuring Ladysmith,
African American Mambazo.
Good. Very good.
Oh! No!
Here, it's a text
from Andy.
"New special proj. Need fam.
tree for evbody.
"Really dig up dirt ASAP."
And then in parentheses, he wrote
out, "As soon as possible."
Oh, God.
Looks like it's
pretendy time again.
Write back,
"Looking for dirt."
Oh. Can I help? We could say someone
is related to, um, Tonya Harding?
Pam, I'm related
to Tonya Harding.
Oh, gee, I'm...
No, I'm just practicing
my lying.
I love it!
Brilliant.
What should
we say about Jim?
Um, oh! I'll say he's related to
Richard Nixon! It's an inside joke.
He looks really
Nixon-y when he wakes up.
My ex behaved like Nixon. All of the
lying, none of the sexual charisma.
I just made a joke then.
I'm sorry. lt'sjust, um,
I actually do have this weird feeling that
there's something Jim isn't telling me.
Oh, no. An affair,
it is always an affair.
Jim? No.
How can you be sure?
Because he just
loves me too much.
You're a cocky little
thing, aren't you, Pam?
I've done a little genealogy
research of my own.
Turns out I'm not the only
one with a few skeletons
in the old family closet.
For example, Phyllis'
great-great-grandmother was
responsible for spreading
cholera to the United States.
ANGELA; Ew.
Kevin is related to both John Wayne
Gacy and John Wayne Bobbitt.
And John Wayne?
No, not that I see here.
Wayne Johnson? The Rock?
You mean Dwayne, and no.
What about Jim Halpert?
Uh-oh! Turns out, distant relative
of the reviled Richard Nixon.
Pam always says
I look like Nixon.
That's crazy, right?
I mean, there's nothing there.
True.
Oh, no.
Dwight's grandfather...
Was a member
of the Bund,
which is not technically
the same thing
asthe
Nazi party. So...
I was going
to say he was a tax evader.
Oh.
I was joking about that whole Bund thing.
The look on your faces.
And Meredith is a blood
relative of Lizzie Borden.
Cool.
Stop it! Stop it!
You're frightening me.
Andy, did you
call this meeting
just to talk junk
about our families?
Yeah, that, you're
being really mean.
Stop it, Andy.
No, I'm proving
a point, okay?
We all have ancestors who may have
done horrible things in the past,
but it's in the past,
and it's not our fault,
so we don't have
to talk about it.
The difference is, Andy,
that you're the only one
here still benefitting
from the terrible things
your ancestors did.
Might have done,
and how do you figure?
Your family is rich.
I have to believe that a big
part of the Bernard fortune
was earned
on the backs of slaves.
You know, there's nothing wrong with
being successful in America, Oscar.
I'm not going to apologize
for my family's wealth.
That wealth could one day
benefit society,
if capital gains are ever taxed at
the same rate as earned income.
Okay, Kevin did that.
I do not wish I was in Dixie.
Hey, Mom.
How are you?
Did any Bernards ever own a
plantation in the South?
She said, "No." Take that!
Follow-up question, did any Bernards
ever make money in an unsavory way?
I just asked you... Why
didn't you just say that?
Okay, stop. Stop.
Stop talking! Stop talking! That's...
No, I don't want to know that.
Okay. You're interrupting a meeting.
I have to go. Love you. Bye.
Well, it turns out the Bernards
of yore did not own slaves.
Really?
We merely transported them, which
at worst makes us amoral middlemen.
Yo, D-Dog. I need your help.
I'm trying to think of things I
can say that make it sound like
I had a more difficult
childhood than I actually had.
You're going to po' mouth.
Exactly! Help me
"po' mouth," Darryl.
Actually, Andy,
you promised me five minutes
to talk about
productivity suggestions.
What if I said
that my dad beat me,
and I just left out
the croquet of it all?
Or I could just go all the way and
say I grew up in an apartment.
Or is that too crazy?
That could work.
You know, Darryl,
this is textbook
assistant regional manager
stuff here, and I feel like
I'm doing all
the heavy lifting.
I'm coming up with
all the ideas here.
I'm going for a walk.
Okay-
Good, good, and...
You doing
all right, man?
I'm done. I got to
get out of here.
Yeah, not the easiest day to
be assistant regional manager.
It's not just today,
it's every day.
Seems like the better title I
have, the stupider my job gets.
Well, come on. It can
always get better, right?
Hmm. Yeah, right.
No, I'm serious. There's
always something better.
Like what?
Like, hypothetically,
if I said that there was anotherjob
that you and I could both have.
What kind ofjob?
Something cool,
like sports marketing, or...
Does that sound like
something you'd be into?
Hell, yeah.
Right?
That sounds awesome.
Okay. But wait,
what if I told you
that it was in Philly?
So you'd have to...
I love Philly.
Right?
That's not
even a thought.
Not even a thought.
It's not even that far away.
I could still commute.
Exactly. Exactly!
All right.
What? Wait, wait, wait!
So what, is this happening?
Oh, it's happening. Let's just keep
it between you and me for right now.
Yeah. For sure, for sure, for sure.
Man. And Pam's into it?
Yeah, we haven't talked
about it, but I think
that she's...
I think she understands.
Aw, come on, man.
Ithoughtyou
had something real.
What? No, no, no.
Come on.
This is real.
It's not real until
your wife is on board.
So what did you
want to show me?
That is quite
an ugly wall, isn't it?
Yeah.
It's really ugly.
It needs something, doesn't it?
I'm thinking a mural.
You mean me?
Yes, you! You are so talented. It's
going to be my next special project,
hiring Scranton's most
dangerous young muralist
to paint
the warehouse wall.
Oh, my God, I love it.
Nellie, this is brilliant!
Hey!
Hey. Can I talk to
you for a second?
Anything you have to say
to her, you can say to me.
She never loved you!
What? No, I... I got this.
It's okay.
This is his fault.
It is not your fault.
I'm going to find you
someone better and rich.
And Filipino, but we'll
break that to her later.
You know what
this is all about?
Yeah. You, too, huh?
Yeah.
Go on, spill it!
Tell her all the gory
details, you snake!
Hey, he deserves this, and he
said I could get in on it, too.
Yeah.
Oh, Pam, no! Oh,
I can't bear to watch this.
I don't know what
I was so worried about.
I have the best
wife in the world.
I still can't believe
he didn't tell me.
I was helping
Nellie drive, and...
Do not care.
I like that guy. We should
hook him up with Meredith.
Ooh.