Hold it!
New glasses.
Dwight, what a ridiculous,
fancy clown you are.
I am dressed according to the
Schrute codes of mourning.
My Aunt Shirley has died.
Oh! Dwight, I'm so sorry.
Were you guys close?
I would say
that she raised me,
but let's not kid each other.
I raised myself.
She was, however, the closest
thing I had to a mother.
My actual mother was
very cold and distant.
I'd say she was the closest
thing I had to an aunt.
My condolences.
- Keep them!
- Okay.
Now, what do we got
in these two pails?
In keeping with
Schrute custom,
I will either invite you
to Saturday's funeral
by sprinkling red, fertile
dirt in your face,
or I will ask you to keep a respectful
distance during my time of grief
with a dusting of black,
slightly acidic soil.
What color is it?
It looks pretty black.
Yep. Acidic all right.
Oh, thank God.
Excuse me?
I'm so sorry, Dwight.
And if you want me to be
there, of course I will go.
It's just, I have a
personal training session.
Okay, that's not...
I just can't...
I get red dirt.
Nobody is getting red dirt.
I should've kept
my mouth shut.
We're not even that close.
I've only known
Dwight 12 years.
Twelve years.
Time is a son of a bitch.
I'm sure
she's in a better place.
I really hope so.
Okay, now this is crazy.
You can't make a dirtball...
I miss her so much.
Okay.
You know?
There's a bright
golden haze on the meadow
A bright golden
haze on the meadow
Zeke's here. Zeke!
Hey, Dwight.
Mose, Mom says hi.
Hi to Mom.
You going?
Will there be
ghosts there?
Get in the sidecar.
Get in the sidecar. Get...
You get in the sidecar.
What are you
doing here?
You invited me. You threw
the red dirt in my face.
Oh, yeah.
Who is that?
Jeb, my brother.
You have a brother? Mmm-hmm.
I didn't really see
a better parking spot.
Oh!
LOOK what I did.
It's a rental.
You wanna go in? No, you do!
You wanna go in?
I'll put you in there.
Okay, I'll put you.
Here we go.
Uncle! Uncle! Uncle!
Uncle! Uncle!
Oh, gosh.
Hey, moon face.
Nice to see those shiny
little Chinese eyes of yours.
Who's this guy?
Bad.
Hi, all!
Why are you here, Todd?
Okay, let's get
right to it, I guess.
My name is Todd Packer,
and I am in recovery.
I'm working the steps. I'm on step
eight of Alcoholics Anonymous,
step nine of
Narcotics Anonymous.
I'm here
to make amends.
I've been hard to deal
with over the past years.
Kind of a jerk.
I know it.
I don't need you
to accept my apology,
but I'd love it
if you did.
Packer, we accept.
Actually, they have a specific
way I need to do this,
and I have to go through
examples of stuff.
Okay, where to begin? Hey.
Pam Pam and her pampams.
Well, I have said some
crude things about those.
But they are beautiful,
and I guess that's
why I acted out.
Pam, I'm sorry
I objectified you
and personified
your breasts.
Sorry, guys-
Oh, boy. I have
not been nice to you.
Phylly, I'm sorry for the
things I said about your size
to your face,
behind your back,
and in the form
of drawings.
Actually, that goes to all you double XLs.
Stanley, Kevin,
this kid
in a few years.
Todd, you're just saying insults
in the form of an apology.
Why can't I just be nice?
Truth is, I really like
you guys. I really do.
Okay, the apology's
just half of it.
The big thing
is making amends,
and that's why
I brought these.
I went out to
the Steamtown mall,
and I got you all cupcakes
from that place Nipples.
- Think it's called Nibbles.
- Ha!
The mind sees
what it wants to, huh?
Hmm. Oh.
There you go.
Hey, hey. guys. Wait.
Before we accept
these cupcakes,
I think we need to
have a conversation privately
in the conference room.
Don't eat the cupcake.
We are here today to join
this woman and the ground.
Man is born of woman, and his
life is full of turmoil.
It's crap soil. Nothing's
gonna grow here.
It doesn't matter.
It's a cemetery.
Yeah, well, I'm saying
it's garbage soil, that's all.
Well, the only thing we're
planting here is dead bodies.
That's fine, 'cause
they're not gonna grow.
Well, I thank God
they're not,
because we don't
wanna make zombies.
Good. I agree. Don't worry about it.
You won't get any.
Would the family
care to say something?
You had black hair
and then gray hair.
You were the aunt
to my cousins.
Most of your life,
you were 5'4".
At the end,
you were 5'1".
They're a descriptive people.
I see you
started without me.
You were late,
so... What am I
supposed to do?
Hi, Fanny. How are you? Hey.
Who is that?
Dwight's sister.
Dwight has a sister? Yeah.
She's beautiful.
Blech.
Hello, little man. Haven't
seen you in a few years.
What is this?
Oh, God.
Just...
Whatdid you...
Henry.
Dwight.
I see
Esther's back in town.
Hi, Dwight.
Hi, Esther.
Nice of you
to come today.
This was on the way.
We're going into town after.
I need yarn.
Well, if you can snap two chicken
necks with a single motion,
why use two motions
to slaughter those chickens?
We're at a funeral. There's
a funeral going on here.
Okay-
Anyone mention
her height?
Yep-
Land size?
Shirley, at 1,600 acres, you have
the largest farm in the area,
sharing borders
with six other farms,
including my own farm
and your nephew Dwight's.
Okay-
So, let's get it going.
Would you want
to do the honors?
Oh, right, uh,
you know, I don't think
we have to do this.
We Schrutes don't need
some Harvard doctor
to tell us who's alive
and who's dead.
But there was
an unlucky streak
of burying some
heavy sleepers.
And when grave robbers
discovered some scratch marks
on the inside
of some of the coffins,
we decided to make
sure that our dead
were completely dead,
out of kindness.
That's it for me.
I don't think we should
eat Packer's cupcakes.
We can't give him the satisfaction.
I agree.
Even though that place has a
way of making those cupcakes
so they're dense but
they're also really fluffy.
We can't let him buy our
forgiveness with cupcakes.
He was awful to us.
And he still is.
How much
is a cupcake, $2.50?
Is that the price
of our dignity?
$3.75 a cupcake actually,
$3.67 if you buy a dozen.
I never forget a number. Names,
in one ear and out the other.
Places, nope.
Faces, that's rich.
But numbers,
I have a gift.
I guess that's why
I'm an accountant.
Hey, man, I don't think
we've met. I'm Clark.
Oh. I'm Todd. Sorry for calling
you a fat little runt earlier.
You didn't
actually say that.
No?
No.
Wow! I'm in this mode now
where I'm apologizing
for thoughts
that are in my head.
Hmm.
Hey!
I have a crazy feeling that you
are really gonna like this.
Maybe we should
eat the cupcakes.
Haven't we done
enough to Packer?
I mean, we've sent him down
to Florida on a prank,
and you did fire him.
I did. I did, yes.
And it was purely political.
He did nothing wrong.
Would any of you be
saying any of this
if the cupcakes
were from Supermart?
Do they even have
a bakery anymore?
They do. It's awful!
And it's getting
worse every day.
So, it really is just
about the cupcakes.
Wow, you're right. It is
just about the cupcakes.
So, we're all agreed no one
touches those cupcakes?
Okay-
Packer can go to hell.
Thank you for coming
to my funeral.
As I gaze
at life's big sunset,
I can't help but wonder
where it all went wrong.
You've all
disappointed me greatly.
Fanny, a single mama
in the city.
Thank you.
Jeb, a street pusher.
After I left the army,
I bought a 9-acre worm
farm from a Californian.
Turns out "worm" means
something else out there,
and I am now in
the business of
pain management.
Or the smoking of
I can't stand the fact
that Jeb is a pot farmer.
He could've
grown anything.
Anything in the world.
He used to talk about growing
a peanut-grape hybrid.
One plant,
one sandwich.
We can't just sit by
and watch
our family farm disappear.
So, here are my terms.
Dwight, Fanny, Jeb,
if you come back home,
I will leave you my farm.
So, there you have it.
Is she crazy?
FANNYI Dwight?
JEBI Dwight? Buddy?
- No, no, no.
- Snap out of it.
JEBI Dwight!
Let's do this. Let's run
Aunt Shirley's farm.
I'm in. Boom!
No, no, no.
I'm not moving back here.
Are you crazy?
Of course you are.
Look, I don't wanna
be mean, or insulting.
I know that
you like it here.
But, Dwight,
it's just that farm life
lacks a certain sort
of sophistication...
Oh, my God.
...that Cammie and I
are drawn to.
I don't know,
the men are just...
It's almost like
there's a willing ignorance.
Yes, I... Thank you
for asking me.
I actually have written a little
bit of poetry. That's crazy.
And I was recently published.
Which is just...
Maybe I have... Yep, I do.
Here it is, from the
hartfordwomens litquarterly.com.
"A Willing ignorance"
by Fanny Schrute.
Totally. Yep.
The people here are like
a fart.
You know what I'm saying?
Like a fart.
You know what? Let's take a
couple of nights and stay here
and think about
Aunt Shirley's offer.
Couple of nights
couldn't hurt.
Somehow I think a couple
of nights could hurt.
You will say yes
on one.
Five, four, three, two...
Get ready to say yes. One!
Yes!
Absolutely!
Growing up with Dwight
and Mose was not easy.
Dwight was obviously the cool
one, and Mose was the visionary,
which left me to
be the comedian.
That doesn't work
on me...
Okay... by the way. It's not...
Very clever. Okay.
Oui!
Oui.
Oh, my goodness.
When we
arrive, sons and daughters
We'll make
our homes on the water
We'll build our...
People underestimate
the power of nostalgia.
If baseball can use it
to get people to care about
that worthless sport,
then I can use it to get my
siblings to care about the farm.
Nostalgia is truly one of
the great human weaknesses.
Second only to the neck.
When we
arrive, sons and daughters
We'll make our
homes on the water
We'll build
our walls aluminum
We'll fill our mouths
with cinnamon now
So, I forgot about
this old custom.
If a man is interested
in courting a woman,
he may throw
the beaks of a crow at her.
And then if she's interested
in accepting the courtship,
she has to destroy the beaks.
When we
arrive, sons and daughters
We'll make our
homes on the water
We'll build
our walls aluminum
We'll fill our mouths
with cinnamon...
Hey, uhm...
I just wanna say
I'm sorry for screwing you.
I'm not sorry
about it.
I am.
It was my rock bottom.
Kevin, you can do this.
You don't know that.
Kevin, let's think of
something to distract us.
Like the movie Skyfall.
You loved the movie
Skyfall, right?
Mmm-hmm.
James Bond was a spy.
Yes, he was a good spy.
Yeah. He was the best.
James Bond would
love this cupcake.
Hey, you know what, it was
great to see you all again.
Take care.
I am going through
a 12-step program.
I'm currently
on step zero,
which is have
a load of fun.
I spent six hours
carefully removing
the frosting
and then layering in a variety
of drugs, some legal, some not,
some laxative,
some constipating.
You don't fire The Packman and
expect to get away with it.
Guys, I'm proud of us.
Ithinkwe did
the right thing. Hey!
What, Pam?
Wait!
He's gone. It's just
a cupcake now.
No, no! It's the
principle of the thing.
Oh, my God. lforgive
him so much.
- Whoa, is he choking?
- Kevin?
That was fantastic.
Is it dangerous to take the
eggs in front of them?
Yes, very. You really
need to stand back.
'Cause these are
killer chickens.
I was just asking you
something I didn't know.
Which is fine,
and you learned something.
But it was kind of
a stupid question,
so you're gonna get
made fun of a little bit.
Are we gonna
eat these today?
If you want.
Is that a guillotine?
This? No.
That'd be cool though.
It's for milking.
That's a cow?
Did you just ask me
if this was a cow?
What are you
doing now?
Come here. Come on.
Grab a teat with each hand.
Sit down.
There you go. Squeeze
from top to bottom.
Really pull, use some muscle.
Draw the milk out.
All right,
going all right?
I don't know.
Well, is the udder hot?
ls the milk clumpy?
I don't know
any of that.
Okay, you suck at this.
Gimme those teats.
Didn't your father
teach you anything?
I never met him.
Good morning, Erin.
Hey.
Hey, everybody. I decided
to eat my cupcake.
I thought about it
last night.
I talked to Jim,
I talked to my sister,
and I think that as long as Todd
Packer doesn't know, it's okay.
I don't care what you do, Pam,
just please stop making noise.
Phyllis!
Packer laced the cupcakes.
No!
Did you get diarrhea
or were you stoned?
Some of us got both.
Oh, my God!
ls everyone okay?
Last night, I got out
all of my old dolls
and played with them
on the living room floor.
Then I ordered 10 American
Girl outfits online.
It was thousands
of dollars.
VVeH, count
yourself lucky, Phyllis.
I got the toilet.
Me too.
I went Christmas caroling,
in March,
and I fertilized some
bushes along the way.
So, not my best night.
But not my worst night.
Oh!
What did you do, Andy?
Last night! Oh, God.
I don't know. Nothing, really.
Kevin? KEVIN:
Why would you ask me?
I'm not...
I just... I don't know.
No.
Gosh, actually,
it is hard to recall.
Pretty normal night.
My night was just like that.
Yup-
Okay-
Meaning normal.
Yeah, I didn't see
you last night at all.
Nope,
I did not see you either.
Wow! He is officially
the worst human being.
Uh...
But, Kevin, that's...
Yeah, no, I understand, Pam.
I understand.
No. Oh.
So, that's it. I just wanted
to make amends.
That's big of you, man.
Takes a lot of courage.
Ooh.
Red velvet.
I should apologize too.
It's okay.
I'm over it.
This is no
9-acre worm farm.
This is a beast.
Whoever's managing this thing
is gonna have a hell of a job.
Not it.
It.
If your kid doesn't put in some farm
time, he's gonna stay like that.
All right, fine.