This year I decided to really
get into the spirit of Halloween.
It may have been the costliest
decision I've ever made.
My greased-up head went into
the pumpkin no problem, but...
it won't budge!
I can't get it out.
Try again.
I mean, I could try
destroying the pumpkin.
No! No! No!
But as Jim and I discovered...
No!
Any blow to the pumpkin itself
could prove fatal to me.
At first, I drove
myself crazy thinking
about the things I should've
done differently. Yes, Dwight.
I never should've
played that joke on Erin.
I never should
have hollowed out
this damned pumpkin
in the first place.
But then I realized
I was being silly.
I mean, the pumpkin should rot off
of my head in a month or two.
Right?
', 9W5-
Hey!
Pam, what are you?
I'm Dr. Cinderella.
Cece's really
into princesses now,
so we decided to turn them into
positive female role models.
I'm an oncologist.
And you are a dog.
I'm a PUPPY-
Dang it, I was
worried that would happen.
It's okay.
Jim, you're not
dressed up at all.
Sure I am. lam
one of the
Men in Black guys.
Can I have
your sunglasses?
Jim, come on. I thought
we were past this.
So the sports
marketing business
that Jim told everyone
about except for me...
There's a big
investment lunch today,
so I decided to
skip the costume.
Unless he has a secret costume that
he told everyone about except for me.
Getting a lot of mileage
out of this, aren't you?
Yeah, well, get
used to it, bud.
Jitterbug.
You guys look great!
Just a reminder, the party
is right after lunch,
so make sure you get all your work
done before that or throw it out.
Any questions?
The Senator will
be joining us later.
Not a question.
No, it wasn't.
Excellent. That reminds me,
has anyone seen treble?
Anyone? I could have sworn
I saw some treble somewhere.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Here Comes Treble!
I'm a man without conviction
You come and go
Karma, karma, karma, karma,
karma chameleon
You come and go
Loving would be easy if your
colors were like my dreams
Red, gold, and green
Karma, come on!
Ah!
So good.
What lab did these
little clones escape from?
My Cornell
a cappella group.
You were in an a
cappella group?
You went to Cornell?
Yeah! Okay.
But you have no
idea how lucky you are,
because HCT is doing a set
at our Halloween party.
Ugh. I don't want to sit through
a whole concert of that.
I do! I love the
boss' interests.
Attaboy, Clark.
Where you boys staying?
How does it work in the rooms?
You get a privacy partition?
No. No, no, no.
Stay away.
You know what
I just realized?
They might actually call me up to
solo on George Michael's Faith.
That was one of
my signature songs.
Oh, man.
That would be insane.
I'm so not prepared.
Are you sure you're okay with
me putting in this much money?
Yeah. I mean, listen,
if we're going to do this thing,
then we should do it right.
You're the best.
I kind of am. It's crazy.
- Okay, I'll see you in a little bit.
- Okay.
Jim, look, I'm eating you.
Shut up.
Hey, Erin, look.
These are Nerds.
I'm eating Jims.
Must eat more Jims!
Stop it! Stop it!
I'm spilling Jims!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it!
Hello, little pill.
What do you do?
Dumatril is licensed
to treat anxiety symptoms
such as panic attacks,
excessive worrying and fear.
Translation?
There's a madman
in our midst.
Okay, I give up.
What are you?
I'm sexy Toby.
Gross! I love it.
Dumaflm
Something wrong, Dwight?
Dumaflfl
Yes?
This is a pill I
found here in the office.
But it's not for worms or
eczema, like any normal pill.
It's not for any
disorder of the body.
It's for
a disorder of the mind.
The mind is part
of the body.
Okay, this is a pill
that combats insanity.
Okay? Whoever is taking
it is not only insane,
they are now off their meds.
Dwight, our co-workers'
heafihissues
are really none
of our business.
Why are you trying so hard
to bury this thing, huh?
What's going on, Nellie?
Talk to me. Hmm?
It's my pill. I have an anxiety
issue, and I'm not ashamed of that,
but I'm not loving the idea of
Dwight having that information.
I once saw him yell at
Phyllis for sneezing wrong.
Yeah, you're right. This man
needs to be apprehended.
I'll get my
apprehension kit.
Dudes! What's up?
I know it's pathetic to relive your
college years, but cut me some slack,
okay, because I was a freaking
rock star in college.
When I joined Here Comes Treble,
that's when I became somebody.
When I got the nickname Boner
Champ, that is when I became me.
You didn't come here
to sit in a room, right?
You came here for some
intergenerational bro time!
Well, now's your
chance! I'm here!
You got Q's,
I got A's.
Did you say
you've got AIDS?
No, I don't have AIDS. That's
not what I said. Next question.
You don't have any questions
about the old days?
You at least want to know
why they call me Boner Champ?
I thought Broccoli Rob
was the Boner Champ.
I'm sorry. What?
I just thought Broccoli Rob
was the Boner Champ.
Broccoli Rob was
Broccoli Rob.
Andy Bernard is
the Boner Champ.
I didn't realize that everybody
here dresses up every year.
Me neither.
It's Halloween.
That is really,
really good timing.
I was just talking to
some of the actives,
and they think that
you're Boner Champ.
I'm so sorry. I don't know
how that could've happened.
Did you maybe tell
them that? Or...
I just started
yapping about the old days,
and I guess the wine
coolers were flowing,
and you know, somehow
things just got hinky.
Could you call them
and just tell them the truth?
Because I know
it's really stupid,
but it's also really,
really, really important.
Will do.
I love you, Andy.
Love you too.
So the workspace
looks awesome.
And the graphic
designer is gonna be
sending us in some of
the logo treatments.
Can't wait to see them.
You guys rock.
Rocking.
There you go.
I've also been running the
numbers, and between our backers
and our own investments, we're looking
great for a full year on this.
Is it too late to get in?
Jim, I explained everything,
so you're all set.
Oh, no, I actually talked to my
wife, and we'd really like to,
you know, invest, get
in on the ground floor.
Wow, well, what level of investment
were you thinking about?
We were thinking somewhere
between $5,000, $10,000.
I can do the full $10,000.
We should just... All in.
All right,
welcome aboard.
All right.
Awesome, cool.
Hey, Darryl. I'm just here to smear
some peanut butter on my forehead.
You know,
to protect his brain
from the nanobots that the government
put in the air conditioning.
That makes
sense to you, right?
Or does it sound crazy?
I can't really picture it.
Can you get it on there?
Yeah.
Maybe get the cheeks.
So this makes sense then?
Or is it crazy?
Get under your chin
first, yeah, yeah.
Is that where the
nanobots like to come in?
Get all the way up
to your lip, yeah.
Okay-
Is that how they
like to get in?
Yeah. That's crazy.
I don't know.
I just don't know.
Yo! Bad boys
of a cappella!
Hey.
Heard any good stories lately
or new twists on old stories?
Yeah, I got a call
from Broccoli Rob.
I guess you really
are the Boner Champ.
Did he tell you
how I got the name?
No.
Spring Sing '95, we got
completely ripped on Bud Drys,
I had sex with a snowman.
I just went
at that thing.
The cold would've
stopped most people,
but I stayed
locked in, you know?
I took the face off. Just
seemed easier that way.
And I told Phyllis not to put
it out, but she insisted.
So, anyway, hi.
Oscar, you remember
my husband, the Senator.
Senator Lipton.
Nice to see you.
Nice to see you, Oscar.
Wait a second.
Who designed this spread?
The sweets and savories
are all mixed together.
This is mayhem.
So, Oscar, you're
a dinosaur?
Actually, I'm the
electoral college.
Ouch. Right on target.
You know what? This is outrageous.
I have to find Phyllis.
You two talk, okay?
Sorry, babe.
Okay.
Phyllis!
God, it's just so
good to see you.
All having this wonderful
Halloween gathering.
Excuse me, is that punch?
They didn't know
about the snowman story.
And when I told them,
they were not impressed.
What is with these turkeys?
Right?
Hey. You better
do Faith. You get me?
We don't know it.
So learn it. You all go to Cornell.
You're, like, eight Rain Men.
Just learn the fricking song.
Look, I know it was big
with the old guys, but...
Butts are for pooping.
Okay, make it work. You have
to, or Andy will flip out.
And make it
a surprise, please.
This isn't stupid.
What?
Hey-
Hey, Toby.
Are you me?
Yeah.
Oh, my goodness,
look at this.
Yeah.
Look at me.
Being you.
I know! Look at you.
It's funny, right?
All right, all right,
just stay focused on the pill.
Okay, look. Dwight, let's
just call this thing off.
I mean, it's just an anxiety pill.
Lots of people have anxiety.
You think I don't have anxiety?
I have anxiety all the time!
Every waking moment of my
life is sheer torture!
I have land disputes to settle,
and idiot cousins to protect,
and ne'er-do-well
siblings to take care of.
And I don't need some stupid
pill to get me through all this.
Cool, free upper.
Ah-ha! The jig is up,
PSYChOpathl
Yeah!
What the hell?
Don't dog catch me!
Gotcha! Yeah!
Let's see you
get out of this web.
The pill is mine!
What the...
What?
Get her out.
Stop banging my head!
Dwight, look! It's just
a pill, all right?
It's for anxiety. I take it every
day, and it makes me feel better.
And maybe it
could help you too.
Hey! How'd it go?
Hey!
Man, it was great.
They were great.
Did you end up investing?
I did, yeah.
How much?
Uh...
By the end, I guess
it was about 10.
About 10? Ten. it
was the full 10.
Wow.
Yeah.
You know, it's a good thing
we talked about it, though,
because we had to.
Yeah, yeah. I know.
Yeah.
So did everybody end up
investing $10,000?
Um... Man, I don't
actually know.
What?
They weren't really talking
that much about money.
They just said, "We're good
with investing," and then I...
Ladies and gentlemen.
Here Comes Treble.
They said they were
done with the investing,
and then you
volunteered $10,000?
No, lhadto. I needed to look
like a team player, Pam.
So you invested $10,000
to look like a team player?
You weren't there.
It was very clear
that $10,000 is
what we had to do.
We'll talk about it later.
No, I want to talk
about it now!
Jim, that was most
of our savings.
And I'll be better
when I'm older
I'll be the greatest fan
of your life
Wait.
Wait, hold on.
Where's the band?
'Cause there's no way you
guys are making this magic
with just your mouths!
That's what she said.
Why, am I overdoing it?
No. No.
We said some.
We'll talk
about it later.
We said "part.".
And I'll be
your crying shoulder
Get your car washed today
Ba-da-bah
Fill up and you don't
have to pay
Ba-da-bah
Come on and give us a play
Get a wash
Right away
Car wash, yeah!
Yes!
Oh, man.
That's how you do that!
Thank you.
Show some pride.
This is crap.
I agree. Yes, crap.
Confinue.
Now, folks, by
special request,
we're going to take
it a little old school.
There is a former
Trebler in this room.
Who?
It's Mr. Andy Bernard.
No, do not sing that.
Do not... Oh, man.
He reminded us today
of how much he means to us,
and we certainly seem
to mean a lot to him.
So, without any further ado,
here's an old Treble classic.
Dank, dank, dank, dank
dank, dank, dank, dank, dank
Well, I guess
it would be nice
If I could touch your body
I know not everybody
Has got a body like you
Whoa! Whoa!
What the hell is
Broccoli Rob doing here?
She said you
wanted to hear Faith.
That's Broccoli
Rob's signature song.
Oh, but I need
some time off...
That's my signature song.
I really didn't
know that, man.
I just thought you
wanted to hear it.
Russell, I'm dressed
like George Michael.
Ithoughtyou were Adam Lambert.
The more I hear about
all this a cappella drama,
the more I think
it's kind of pathetic.
But when you're with someone,
you put up with the stuff
that makes you lose respect
for them, and that is love.
Are you okay?
He's still mad.
Okay.
Shut up, Broccoli!
Champ, I feel awful
about this whole thing.
Russell called me up,
and they said they needed 20
cc's of George Michael, stat.
So, just wham! I sprang into action.
You know me.
I assumed you wanted to hear
me do your signature number.
You thought I wanted to sit in the
audience like some slutty Treb rat?
A man's signature solo
is his for life, okay?
That's group policy,
and you know it.
Look, it's not my fault
I still live near campus.
And it's my duty as an alum to
be friendly to the young guys,
and stop in two,
three times a week.
Just don't do
the song anymore.
I tell you what. We'll
have a sing-off for it.
You pick 12
alums from any year
to back you up,
and I'll do the same.
And I'm so confident that I'll
win, I won't even warm up.
Fine, go ahead,
thrash your pipes.
My pipes are primo, Champ!
Why don't you ask Trey
Anastasio about my pipes?
I knew you would go there,
you son of a bitch!
He said, and I quote, "Hey, Rob,
nice pipes-" That happened!
Okay. Fine, yeah.
That's real!
That's one guy's opinion.
That'll never change!
Okay!
Doesn't mean you're the
best singer ever. Dick!
I thought that concert
was pretty great.
Oh, yeah, I decided
acapelco music is awesome.
They lost me when
they sang Monster Mash.
That song obviously
glorifies the occult.
Angela, it's Halloween.
You have to sing Monster Mash.
You have to, Jim?
You literally have to?
Uh...
No, I'm just... I'm saying what would
happen if they didn't sing it?
Would they go to jail?
Would they be shot?
Okay. We'll
just forget it.
No, no! I'm interested.
I mean, I think everybody's interested
in why they have to sing it.
Because it is Halloween.
So if you're going
to sing a concert,
it's a good idea to
throw that one in.
Yeah, yeah. No, no, it's a
good idea to brush your teeth,
but you have to, um, feed your children.
Send them to school.
You know,
all things you can't do
if you just keep
singing Monster Mash.
It turns out Pam really,
really hates Monster Mash.
I mean, like, never bring
that song up in front of her.
Even though Jim was making great
points, like, in favor of the song,
Pam was like, "No!
Hate it! Stupid!"
This is all so
silly, right?
What am I going to do,
move back to Cornell?
Yeah.
I mean, what
if we did that?
Like, we gotjobs, and we
were happy all the time?
Oh. Well, Andy, we're
not moving to Cornell.
Duh, I know. That would be insane.
Yeah.
It could totally
work, though.
I don't know
why we wouldn't.
Oh, my God,
are we doing this?
Oy. Andy,
what is going on?
If I am not Boner Champ,
I don't know who I am.
Well, you know, maybe
you're the wise old guy
that the new B-O-N-E-R
Champ looks up to.
You know, you could just...
Make a donation.
Well, I was going
to say, be a mentor.
Yes.
I'm going to
make a donation.
And it just so
happens I know someone
who works at the Bernard
Family Foundation.
Her name is Mom.
Oh.
I want some of those pills.
Well, good for you.
I mean, you'll need
a prescription.
Oh, no, no,
they're not for me.
They're for my cousin, Mose.
He's just having a tough
time, being wifeless,
and a high-pressure job,
and his crazy cousin Mose.
Other cousin Mose.
Mmm.
Got it.
Well, you tell Mose
that he's a good man,
and I hope
he feels better.
Which one?
Mose, or the real Mose?
The real Mose.
He says thank you.
Mom? I had this
really charitable idea
to set up a scholarship for
a cappella kids at Cornell,
and just need to wire
some money over there.
What?
Far above the busy humming
of the bustling town
Reared against
the arch of heaven
What's wrong?
Looks she proudly down
My parents are broke.
Lift the chorus,
speed it onward
Loud her praises tell
Hail to thee,
our alma mater
Hail, all hall, Cornell!