The documentary series
finished airing ages ago.
Why is PBS
sending another crew?
We're getting
bonus footage for the DVD.
Nobody buys DVDs anymore.
It'll be a pledge gift.
PBS. The propaganda wing
of Bill and Melinda Gates,
and viewers like you.
In the past year,
I've consolidated
the entire
Scranton paper market.
We regained the White Pages,
the School District,
Lackawanna County,
we supply them all.
I'm getting married
tomorrow afternoon.
And in the morning,
there's a mini-reunion,
a kind of a where-are-they-now?
panel at a local theater.
It will be nice to see everyone again.
I haven't seen Kevin
since we let him go.
Today marks several
important milestones.
Stanley, as you know,
is retiring.
Ah!
I've been looking forward to this
day since I was 18 years old.
Speech!
No.
And our next and most
thickly frosted cake
is for Kevin.
Yes!
Wait, why?
Go ahead and just
read the frosting.
"Get out"?
What does that mean?
It's a colloquial way of
saying you're fired, Kevin.
- Which you are.
- What?
Dwight,
you can't do that.
The cake has
spoken, Pam. Sorry.
Well, if anyone here can make
a case for Kevin staying...
Based on his merit.
Oh.
Um...
I'm good.
Well,
Toby will stop it.
Any time anyone's ever been
fired, Toby's blocked it, so...
Yeah. Yeah,
I don't think...
Toby, wait, wait.
Hold that thought.
Here's your cake.
Bye, bye, TOW-
At least I got chocolate.
I bike to work now.
It saves on gas, it's
cheaper than a vasectomy,
and, oh, yeah, it's good
for the environment, too.
Pam and I are great.
She just recently finished her mural
for the Irish Cultural Center.
Can you clap?
Can you clap for Mommy?
And Dwight is imitating
Japanese business practices,
for reasons he
explained to us in Japanese.
Angela, are you
ready for the wedding?
Yes.
My heart is so open.
I'm so at peace.
Ugh. Look at Meredith.
She's disgusting.
Those feet. They're like
the paws of an orangutan.
I think she looks good.
Now that she's
wearing sports bras,
we don't see
her boobs as much.
That is all.
Have a good morning.
Thank you.
What was that for?
To remind you that our Wedding's
going to be wonderful.
Oh, I know.
It just feels so empty with
so many of the old gang gone.
D, it's going to be perfect.
The only people that need
to be there are you and me.
Oh, and the old man to
feed us the cheese
that he's been fermenting
since the day of my birth.
You keep forgetting
about him.
I don't know why.
I brought in some
new faces, and one old.
I always liked Devon.
I hired him back after
Creed faked his own death
in the baler the day
after the doc aired.
The only person he fooled was Kevin.
Then the police showed up.
Turns out Creed was in the band
The Grass Roots, in the 1960s.
During that time,
the police say he sold drugs.
And trafficked in
endangered species meat.
And stole weapons-grade
LSD from the military.
Some fudge?
Oh, thanks.
I love your fudge.
Mmm!
I think I've gained a couple
of pounds since I got here.
You can afford it.
After 16 years,
it's strange sitting across
from somebody
who isn't Stanley.
But
he'll get there.
Okay, the limo's going to
be here at 5:00.
I need everybody to be ready,
because I want to pack in a lot.
Party time,
whorehouse.
No. No whorehouse.
This is Dwight's night. Okay?
Well, you're
the bestisch Mensch.
Dwight has made me
his bestisch Mensch,
which is Schrute
for "best man."
He is putting himself
entirely in my hands tonight,
and I know, for over 12 years, I've
done nothing but trick and prank him.
But tonight?
Only good surprises.
"Guten pranken . "
Oh, hey, Jim, I forgot
to mention, often times
in Hollywood portrayals of bachelor
parties, there are accidental murders.
That won't be
necessary tonight.
Great, now we've got
three hours to fill.
Okay, hold on. Are you sure
Mose isn't going to show up?
Ever since
Angela moved in,
and Mose had to stop sleeping
at the foot of my bed,
he's been acting pretty weird
about this whole wedding thing.
Mose has been weird?
That's so unlike him.
Yeah, sure, I'll talk about it.
Why not?
America's Next A Cappella
Sensation aired my audition,
and when I started
sobbing uncontrollably,
apparently, that struck a chord
with quite a lot of people.
Not a very
compassionate chord.
The clip went viral,
as they say.
You can't just
sit here and cry.
I can so just
sit here and cry!
Two million hits in the first week,
and then the parodies started.
One from the Philippines
got 12 million hits.
And the late night comedy guys
had a field day with it.
Aw, come on, Baby Wawa.
Don't be such a baby.
Oh, no.
It's going to be all right.
For Weekend Update, I'm Seth Meyers!
That's Baby Wawa! Good night!
After my clip blew up, I actually got
a call from the Double Rainbow guy
and the fat Star Wars kid.
Turns out they
have a support group.
Not really my scene.
Years ago,
the senator promised
a left-turn
lane by the Arby's.
So I want to know where in the
name of horsey-sauce is it?
Well, yeah, you...
Hold on.
Hi. I keep seeing this symbol
in the accounts from last year.
It's all over the place.
I don't know what it means.
That's the reason
Kevin got fired.
It's his magic number. He used to
use it to balance his accounts.
He used to call
it a "keleven."
He told Dwight, "A mistake plus
keleven gets you home by 7:00."
He was home
by 4:45 that day.
Oh, I live in Poland now.
The Scranton of the EU.
Thank you for flying me
out here for the weekend.
I'm looking forward
to the reunion panel tomorrow.
Can't wait to see everyone.
Well, almost everyone.
Hello! Hello!
Oh.
Hi! Oh.
No.
How did you know
my plane had arrived?
How long have you
been stalking me?
No, no, no. My flight just
got in from New York.
Are you still
with Pyotr?
No, and I thought
I unfriended you.
Anyone can follow
a Twitter feed.
Want to share a cab?
After Dwight fired me,
I moved to New York
to write
the Great American Novel.
I have six roommates,
which are better
than friends, you know,
because they have to give you one
month's notice before they leave.
Hey-o!
Andy?
You're back?
Yeah.
That's Baby Wawa, right?
Oh, my God.
Hey, man,
good to see you.
Thank you. Yeah.
HSy_ Andy“.
Aw. A bear hug from
my favorite mama grizzly.
Andy, I've been worried about you.
How are you?
Little warm.
Poor, poor Andy.
Aw. Thank you, Phyllis.
Hello, hello.
Hey!
Darryl!
Hey, what's up?
Didn't I just see you at the
airport, jumping into a limo?
What? Must've been another devilishly
handsome debonair individual.
Hey, man.
How you doing?
I didn't call 'cause I figured
you changed your number.
No, I didn't change the number.
All good, though.
Phone never rings.
What? AW.
Surprise!
Ithoughtyou
guys couldn't come!
Yeah, but then they moved the
panel to the same weekend
and the doc crew paid to fly us in.
It was kismet.
Kismet?
Yeah, right. Pam and I came up with
excuses for every other weekend.
You remember my two
Lap-Band surgeries, right?
Neither do I.
Guten prank number one.
You ready for tonight?
We going to tear up the town?
Uh, you better ask Jim.
And Jim
will say nothing.
Darryl! Andy!
Hey, Pam!
How are you?
We're fine.
Yeah!
And I'm sure that you guys are fine,
too, because why wouldn't you be?
Mmm-hmm.
Darryl, oh, my gosh,
how is Austin?
Tell me everything.
How's the merger?
I feel like I read
aboutAthlead all the time.
I love it. And it's Athleap now.
And the city is amazing.
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
It's hot,
the music is awesome,
and the tacos are for real.
Wow.
That sounds incredible.
Oh, guys, the limo's here.
Let's do this.
Change if you need to.
Okay, you guys,
have fun!
You, too, Andy.
Whoa!
Oh, ho!
Haven't been in one
of these in forever.
They wanted me to go to the
bachelorette party with the girls.
Really? Such a cliché.
I'm a man.
So, I'm going to the bachelor
party with the boys.
I just have to remember how
I acted before I came out.
VVazzup!
Hey, why are we stopping? Jim,
this isn't on the itinerary.
Jim?
Get out!
Come on!
What, are you
going to whack me, Jim?
No, Dwight.
You'll be doing
the whacking.
A bazooka.
You remembered.
Of course I did.
Get out of my way.
Whoa!
Guten prank number two.
Private room!
Yeah, brocephus!
Amazing!
Enjoy, eHJOY-
Hey, I know you. You going
to sit here and cry?
Okay, man. Easy.
Hey, dude, leave him alone.
What are you doing?
Jim, it's fine.
He'll just get you on his cell
phone and then that will go viral.
That happens a lot?
Yeah, I guess, but things
are going well, actually.
I spoke at Cornell
during Commencement week.
Well, I mean, the seniors invited me
as a joke, but it was a huge success.
Well, I bet
it was a smash.
That's how I got my new job
in the Admissions Office.
Is that
a volunteer program, or...
No, it's a job.
Things are going great!
Let's get
a drink in you, huh?
Yes!
Whoo-hoo!
Let's get this party started!
Where's my angel?
This is my big sister,
Rachael.
No, this is my
big sister, Angela.
We're very close. We even have
our own special language.
ANGELA". People love it.
They do.
Man, how long have
we been sitting here?
Hi. boys!
Here we go!
Oh, thank God.
We are famished.
Hey, did somebody
order the chef's special?
Right there.
Right here.
No, we haven't
ordered anything.
No one's even
taken our drinks.
Uh, what is the chef's special?
I bet you boys
have a big appetite.
Oh, we do.
So we'll have an onion loaf
for the table, please.
And tell us about
your heartiest soups.
Ooh, I know what you want.
I know exactly what you want.
Yes, an onion loaf for the table.
But that's not all.
Now the chef's special sounded
good, what is it exactly?
Shh.
Wait,
what are you doing?
Are you giving me a taste
of the chef's special?
Mmm.
Mmm?
It tastes like cigarettes.
That won't work.
That's no good.
Whoo!
What?
Hey, oh, boy!
Oh.
Heard you guys needed some pipes
fixed, or cleaned, or whatever?
Angela, special
repairman is here!
What is this?
Shut up! Jakey?
Mom?
Wait, Wait. What?
Oh, man.
No, no, no. Just do your work.
Pretend Mom's not here.
Uh, that seems
inappropriate.
Give them a good show,
my little entrepreneur.
- Okay.
- Take it off.
Yeah!
Good song choice, Jakey!
Stripper's only
as good as his song.
Whoa! Oh!
Oh.
Oh, wowy-wow.
Okay...
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Go, Meredith's
stripper son.
Rachael, are you all right?
I don't know!
Oh, my God!
Be gentle,
Jakey, genfle!
Just one second,
just one second.
If anything,
this is rougher!
Stop it, Meredith!
Sorry! My bad.
Go ahead, Jakey.
Uh, it's okay.
Thank you.
You know what?
You don't have to...
No, no, it's okay.
Now for the last time, I'd like
a side salad with balsamic.
Dwight, for the last time,
she's not a waitress.
You're telling me!
If you want her to leave,
just tip her.
What for? We haven't
even gotten bread yet!
Does anyone want to split
a twice-baked potato?
Do you have those? Those
aren't deep fried, right?
That was interesting.
What was that?
It's just the wind.
Will you lock the door?
Okay.
It's just the wind, see?
Nothing.
All right, you know? You don't
have to leave the door wide open.
We get it. It's the wind.
Just come and shut the...
Oh, my God!
- Phyllis?
- What's happening?
Oh, man! I never
thought I'd say this
but I think I ate too much bone marrow.
Oh, it's the girls.
Hey, Pam.
What?
Angela's been kidnapped.
Phyllis left the door open
and some freak came
and grabbed her and fled.
Good old Mose!
They think it was Mose.
Oh, great! He's getting into
the spirit of the festivities.
Fantastic! He just
pulled off a Braut entfUhrt.
What is that?
A ceremonial
bridal kidnapping.
He will take the bride
and hide her at a local pub.
And when I find the place,
I have to buy everyone drinks.
Oh, all right!
Oh, Mose!
Wait a minute.
You said the tradition
is for the groom
to search for her,
and it ends at a pub.
So, how about the last pub you'd
ever set foot in in this town?
Great,
which one is that?
Mmm. Hey, driver, why don't
you take us to 3030 Adams?
Is that Mose?
Yes, it is!
I am here
for my bride.
Well, first,
buy us a drink!
If you want your
bride, buy us a drink!
If you want your bride,
buy us a drink!
Very well, drinks on me!
Bartender.
Well, well,
well, well, well.
That's six "wells".
Did I get that
number right, Dwight?
I heard you
bought a bar, Kevin.
Yes, I did. This one.
Now, get out.
Why did you
pick this place?
Oh.
You? You did this as a prank.
My own bestisch Mensch.
Nope, not a prank.
I think it's time for you
to bury the hatchet.
Waste of a good hatchet.
Okay, just talk.
Well...
I heard you say
"well" the first time.
I know Dwight
misses Kevin.
I saw him making his portrait
out of a Wooly Willy.
Tomorrow's
his wedding day.
You can't be anything but
happy on your wedding day.
It was nothing personal. It's just
that you were terrible at your job.
You're just saying that
to make me feel better.
No, really.
You were terrible at math,
and organization, time
management, personal hygiene.
Your Internet
searches were so filthy
we had to throw
out your computer.
Is that all it Was?
That's it.
Come here.
I missed you, Kevin.
I missed you!
Guten prank.
Yes, Mose.
Guten prank
number three.
You've had your drink.
Now, where's my bride?
Mose? What?
Oh, Mose!
What the is
your problem, you?
- Hey, is Angela coming, or...
- No.
We can't see each other
on our wedding day.
And her legs are still numb
from being in the trunk.
- Right.
- Hey, guys!
Stanley!
How's Florida?
Oh, great.
Yes, I'm living
in Florida now,
little town
called Florida City,
just on the edge
of the Everglades.
The man who delivered my divorce
papers came by fan boat,
which was kind of fun.
I sit on my porch
all day carving birds.
Am I the only one that's nervous?
How are you doing with this?
Should we have bailed?
No, no. I'm fine.
Doesn't seem like anyone
cares about us anyway.
I guess this was worth being
filmed nonstop for nine years.
I'm sorry, guys.
This is probably on me.
I got hated on pretty hard when
that auto-tune went viral.
Just sit here and cry
Oh, I can so
just sit here and cry
You guys are really mean
It can't end like this
You know
Slept in my car last night
Quit my job
Burned all my bridges
And I did unspeakable things
You're just not good
Are you insane?
Chill out
Just sit here and cry
People actually
dance to this.
It's in my jukebox.
None of the money
goes to Andy, though.
Yeah, people hate you.
I'll go talk to the manager.
Maybe we should just go home.
Hey,
it's Andy Bernard.
How did it feel to see your
lives played out on TV?
It's like seeing a documentary
about how your food is made.
It's kind of disgusting.
You learn a lot, but I didn't
want to know any of it.
With today's modern
surveillance technology,
we are in a constant
state of being watched,
whether it's our government or the
government of other countries,
a.k.a. Google.
You guys are being filmed
way more than we ever were.
Uh, no one recognizes me, but now
all my friends call me Plop.
So, thanks, PBS.
Uh, Jim, that DVD in the last
episode was so romantic.
And I think we'd
all love to know,
Pam, what romantic
thing did you do
to pay Jim back
for leaving Athlead?
Well, I mean, how do you pay back
someone for something like that?
But I don't know.
I'm working on something.
She pays me back every day
just by being my wife,
so, that's fine.
Aw...
Okay-
AH I can say is,
if I had Jim,
he'd have a free pass
to do anything.
I mean if! lucked into that,
he could do anything.
Anything.
I'm sorry,
is there a question?
Uh... No.
Pam, what was
in the teapot letter?
Oh, um, well, you know, I think I
would rather keep that private.
If you've been filmed
for nine years of your life,
there'd be some things that you
just want to keep to yourself.
I hear you.
What did it say?
We're going to move on.
Next question, please.
Do you find that your
life feels pointless
now that nobody's actually
filming you anymore?
Yes.
I want to know how everyone
felt they were portrayed.
Was it accurate?
I've got
a beef with that.
For the first seven years I was
getting my PhD in school psychology
and they didn't show it.
Yes, I was getting hammered,
but, hey, it was college.
I have a question
for Jim and Pam.
Everyone watching sees
how much you love each other
and how you're soul mates.
So, Pam,
how could you doubt that
when Jim moved
to Philadelphia?
Uh, you know what? I actually didn't
handle that move very gracefully,
from not communicating
to being a little selfish...
Listen, um,
I was scared.
You know, I loved what I had
and I didn't want to risk it.
And I think that maybe I did
doubt him a little, too.
Which was wrong because he's
shown me time and again.
But when the documentary
started airing,
people in the street told me that
I had this fairytale romance.
But there were
a lot of times last year
when it did not
feel like a fairytale.
But then it got deeper,
and it got stronger,
and now it's better
than a fairytale.
It's like a long book
that you never want to end,
and you're fine with that because you
just never, ever want to leave it.
Aw...
Like Harry Potter?
Yeah.
Like Harry Potter.
I have
a question for Erin.
Really?
Yes, um, the thing I found most
compelling about the documentary
was your search
for your birth mother.
Thank you.
So, my question is,
um, don't you hate her?
I mean,
I would just imagine
that you are so angry at her
that you would hate her.
Maybe sometimes.
But not like hate-hate.
More just like,
"Mom, I hate you,"
and then she would say,
"Go to your room, young lady,"
and I'd stamp my foot
and run upstairs.
And I have a room,
which is really cool.
And then we'd just
have dinner together.
But I don't know,
I'd have to meet her.
Thanks.
Erin?
Yes?
Um, oh.
Erin.
Yes, is there
a follow up question?
Mom?
Aw...
Erin, same question,
but about your dad?
Well, this feels
like a good place to stop.
Let's thank all our
wonderful panelists
for being here on this
wonderful panel today.
Next week at
the Scranton Cultural Center,
don't forget, Irish
step dancing semi-finals.
Winning team to Mid-Atlantic.
Where is the basket
for gifts?
Right there, sir.
Okay.
Hi. I'm Dakota.
Jeff Bomondo.
I sell ceramic tile
out of Newark.
My wife's name
is Kathryn.
I can show you my social
security card if it helps.
Ugh!
Look at this mud.
Can you imagine
if I'd worn my Jimmy Choos?
I just saved you
600 bucks, mister.
Thanks for helping out, sweetie.
Mmm-hmm.
Kelly? You're here.
Hey, Ryan!
Hey.
Whose baby is this? Oh, are
you, like, a manny now?
No, this little
guy is mine.
So, I was
dating this girl,
and one day she went out to get a
new charger for her e-cigarette.
Never came back.
Oldest story in the book.
Say hi, Drake.
Drake is your baby's name?
Yeah.
That is an amazing name.
I am obsessed with Drake.
His last album,
it just touched me...
No, Kelly, he is not named after
a hip-hop artist from 2011.
It's Drake, like a mix
of Drew and Blake.
Cool.
Well, he is so cute.
Ravi, check out
this cute baby.
I'm obsessed with him.
Hello.
Ravi's a pediatrician, and some
of his patients are total uggos.
Uh, they're called
premature, sweetie.
Yeah. It's good to
see you again, Ryan.
Can you help me up?
Thanks.
Ooh. Oh!
Oh, boy. Maybe your
heels are too high.
No, my heels
aren't too high.
It's because I spent three
hours in a car trunk.
Thanks for not locking the door
when I asked you to, Phyllis!
Sorry, Phyllis.
You didn't know.
As long as I can
get to the altar.
Oh, I'm going to get
you to that altar.
You can take
that to the bank.
You ready?
You kidding?
I was born ready.
Dwight. Dwight. Dwight.
Um...
I don't know how
to tell you this,
but we have
a little bit of a problem.
Oh, no. What?
The ministerjust told
me that it's tradition
for the bestisch Mensch
to be older than the groom.
Oh, come on. I've never
heard of such a thing.
I haven't heard
of it, obviously.
But I'm out, because I'm
significantly younger than you.
Not, significant
is a big word.
I think...
Well, okay, either way.
Teeny“.
Either way, Dwight,
I can't
be there for you.
I'm sorry.
Jim...
I just really wish there
was something I could do.
Michael.
I can't believe
you came!
That's what she said.
Best prank ever.
Yeah!
As is traditional
to the Schrutes,
the lovers are standing
in their own graves,
as a reminder
that this is the only escape
from what they
are about to do.
See, I get what
they're trying to do,
but why are
the graves so shallow?
"Arise, my love,
my fair one, and come away.
"For lo,
the winter is past,
"the rain is over and gone.
"The time of singing has come,
"and the voice of the turtledove
is heard in our land.
"Let me see your face,
"let me hear your voice,
for your voice is sweet,
"and your face is comely."
I now pronounce
you man and wife.
Release the doves!
Oh.
That's...
That's not...
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you so much for coming!
Now, please take your
hay bales to the reception.
They'll be
used for seating.
Complimentary hay hooks
are placed along the aisles.
Just stab them on in there.
Everybody!
See, now you
don't owe me anything.
Raw? Raw?
Drake has a bit
of a rash and he's hot.
Oh, no!
I was wondering, could you maybe
examine him for a second?
Oh, yeah. You're not feeling well,
little guy?
Okay, sure.
Um, shall we go inside?
Actually, could you go inside?
I'm feeling a little dehydrated.
I could really use a little
break, have some water.
Are you sure you
don't want to go in?
Ravi, just do it! This baby is burning up!
Isn't this what you live for?
Just, go, go!
Thank you, Ram.
Thank you so much.
This is great for me and for Drake.
Thank you.
I don't know, Ryan. Baby
Drake didn't look so good.
He'll be fine. I let
him suck on a strawberry.
He's allergic,
but he'll get over it fast.
I had to talk to you.
You gave your baby an allergic
reaction just to talk to me?
Michael has so many
pictures of his kids,
he had to get two phones with two
numbers, and he pays two bills.
He's just so happy
to have a family plan.
Where did you learn
to dance like that?
I don't know, I've just always
been really good at dancing.
Is it me?
Is it Nellie?
It's everything.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
Lots of people think that Stanley
Hudson's a mean old grump.
But
would a grump make this?
It's me.
I love you.
I love you, too!
We're going
to be together forever.
We're running
off into the sunset!
I've finally
mastered commitment!
Rules and stuff?
Has anyone seen Ryan?
Or Kelly?
Ooh. Yes. Uh, they left
together a little while ago.
Kelly was hoping that
you would keep the baby
so they can start
a new life together.
Oh, that's it. Here.
Call Child Services
and report an abandoned baby.
They'll find a better parent
than Ryan in no time.
Oh, I don't know.
Um, Kevin, oh,
I can help you with that.
Yeah.
I mean, I can find
someone who will...
Who will love that beautiful
little boy the way he deserves.
Okay. This is better.
Yes, it is.
Hi.
Oh, yes.
Hey.
Yes, it is.
Oh, yes, it is.
If Ryan wants his baby back,
please tell him where to find me.
We'll be
somewhere in Europe.
Won't we?
I feel like all
my kids grew up
and then they
married each other.
It's every parent's dream!
Thank you so much.
Good night.
Good luck.
Really fun.
The doc crew is throwing a big after
party in the warehouse tonight.
Yeah, I heard. It sounds kind of lame.
No offense.
You going, Toby?
Oh, I don't know.
I might turn in early.
It's only 6:00.
Come on, everybody's going.
You have to go, Toby!
Yeah, come on, Tobes!
Come on, Toby.
Yeah, I'll stop by.
There he is.
I need to get
out of this dress.
I got to get
Oh, I'm sorry, Pam.
What's going on?
Why are you
still here?
I'm so sorry,
they were an hour late.
No, really,
what's going on?
Okay, Okay-
So this past year
has been really great,
and you've been great,
and I know that you
had to make this choice,
and you had to give
something up for me.
But I never want you to have
to give up anything.
I just thought if I
could get us an offer,
then there wouldn't be
anything standing in our way
and I could come to you
with this big Jim gesture,
and show you all at once
just how much I love you,
and how much I really do
believe in your future.
Sorry, how long have you
been showing the house?
About two months.
That's why
it's so clean.
Yeah.
I mean, you were going
to do this without me?
Well, you bought the house
without telling me,
so I thought I could sell it
without telling you.
Oh, okay.
Where would we go?
Austin, maybe?
I promise you, you don't
have to do this for me.
I'm doing it for us.
- The last...
- Okay, we'll take it.
Hold on one second.
The last few months have
meant the world to me,
and all I care about...
Hold on a second.
Wait, what did
you just say?
We want to
buy your house.
You want to do this?
I want to do this.
You really
want to do this?
I really
want to do this!
Oh, my God!
Hey, Darryl.
What?
Yeah!
All right!
We're so excited.
Cool.
Oh, that's for PBS
executives only.
I had to pledge $50 to my local
PBS station just to get this.
I think your ideas
are fantastic, Oscar.
I'd love to contribute
to your campaign.
Thank you, David.
Uh, could I please
have your attention?
So, a year ago, I got
my first art commission
to paint a mural
for Dunder Mifflin.
And I decided to paint
the history of paper,
which was just
some trees and stuff.
And then someone spray-painted
a bunch of butts on it
and I had to start
from the beginning.
But it all worked
out for the best,
because I think that I've
painted the perfect thing,
which is the history
of us, all of us.
And this is
for you, Jim.
And go ahead!
Everyone, let's take our
picture in front of the mural.
Oh, um, I kind of meant just
everybody from the office.
Very nice.
Just a couple dozen more.
Smiles, everybody, smiles!
All right, that's great. I got enough.
Thank you, everybody.
Let's go.
Okay, I need a drink.
Yeah, we all
need a drink.
What the...
There's only dandelion tea
and raisins in here.
Hey, bottom drawer.
Yes.
Dunder Mifflin,
this is Pam.
Oh, I'm sorry. Jim Halpert
doesn't work here anymore.
I didn't watch
the whole documentary.
After a few episodes,
it was too painful.
I kept wanting
to scream at Pam.
It took me so long to do
so many important things.
It's just hard to accept that I spent
so many years being less happy
than I could have been.
Jim was five feet from my desk and
it took me four years to get to him.
It'd be great if people saw this
documentary and learned from my mistakes.
Not that I'm a tragic person. I'm
really happy now.
But, it would just
make my heart soar
if someone out there saw this
and she said to herself,
"Be strong, trust yourself, love
yourself, conquer your fears.
"Just go after what you want.
"And act fast, because life
just isn't that long."
If there is one thing that I've learned
through this whole experience,
it's that if you film
anybody long enough,
they're going to do
something stupid.
It's only human natural.
Hey, guys.
What about
the honeymoon?
Oh, the honeymoon
can wait until tomorrow.
We wanted to
hang out with you guys.
I mean, when are we all going
to be here together again?
Aw, J, P and D,
the three amigos.
It warms my heart.
Hey, what do you say when I
get back from our honeymoon,
the three of us have a conference
room meeting just for fun?
What is that
meaningful look?
You know what?
Maybe we should talk.
Hey, come here!
You guys need to see this.
What is it?
You're
probably sitting there wondering
what will be your mark?
What will you be known for?
It might surprise you
to learn. ..
I finally feel ready.
Athlead is growing.
Athleap.
And Jim can jump back in
without skipping a beat.
We'll come back to visit, but I think
it's time for us to officially...
No, don't say it. You're fired.
You're both fired.
Dwight, come on.
Don't end on a bad note.
Don't be an idiot.
It's for the severance.
The best that
I can do is one month
for every year
you've been here,
that's the max.
Thanks, Dwight.
And, hey,
if you're ever in Austin...
Oh, right, for what? The art? The music?
The incredible night life?
No, thank you.
But if you're
ever in the area,
you'll always
have a place to stay,
in my barn.
There it is.
Do I get along
with my co-workers?
Well, first of all, I don't
have co-workers anymore.
I have subordinates.
So, have I gotten along
with my subordinates?
Let's see.
My supplier relations rep,
Meredith Palmer,
is the only person I
know who knows how to
properly head bang to Motdrhead.
Oscar Martinez, my accountant,
is now godfather to my son.
Angela Schrute, my former
accountant, is now my wife.
My top salesman, Jim Halpert,
was best man at my wedding,
and office administrator Pamela
Beesly-Halpert is my best friend.
So, yes.
I'd say I have gotten along
with my subordinates.
You might feel sorry for me,
but I actually
feel sorry for you,
because you're about
to leave Cornell!
So say it with me.
Oh, I can so just
sit here and cry!
on, yes!
You did good. Real good.
Thanks, Dad“.
Darryl.
I spent so much of my
time here at Dunder Mifflin
thinking about my old pals,
my college a cappella group.
The weird thing is,
now I'm exactly
where I want to be,
I got my dream
job at Cornell,
and I'm still just thinking
about my old pals,
only now, they're the
ones I made here.
I wish there was a way to know
you're in the good old days
before you've
actually left them.
Someone should
write a song about that.
You take something ordinary,
like a piece of paper.
It's not much.
But if you see
it the right way,
and that's what you did
with this documentary.
But seriously, you made
a nine-year documentary
and you couldn't once
show me doing my origami?
Uh, oh!
I saw a friend today
And it had been a while
And we forgot
each other's names
But it didn't matter
Because deep inside
The feelings still
remained the same
Imagine going back and
watching a tape of your life.
You could see
yourself change
and make mistakes
and grow up.
You could watch
yourself fall in love.
Watch yourself
become a husband.
Become a father.
You guys
gave that to me.
And that's
an amazing gift.
Hey, Jim, remember Flonkerton
when you did Office Olympics?
It was awesome.
Thanks, Phyll.
I still have
my medal from that.
Do you even
have a mattress?
No, but I still
have my medal from that.
Oscar? Oscar?
I think I'm gay.
Why do you say that?
It's just that
I'm so emotional.
You're not gay.
No, but,
maybe the reason...
You're not gay.
Now the faces that I know
Have that same familiar glow
I think I must have known
them Somewhere once before
How did you do it?
How did you capture
what it was really like?
How we felt, and how we
made each other laugh,
and how we got through the day.
How did you do it?
Also how do cameras work?
Every day when I came to work,
all I wanted to do was leave.
So why in the world does it feel
so hard to leave right now?
It all seems
so very arbitrary.
Iapphed for a job at this company
because they were hiring.
I took a desk at the back
because it was empty.
But no matter how you
get there or where you end up,
human beings have this miraculous
gift to make that place home.
Let's do this.
I just feel lucky that I got a
chance to share my crummy story
with anyone out
there who thinks
they're the only one to take
a dump in a paper shredder.
You're not alone, sister.
Let's get a beer sometime.
I'm happy that
this was all filmed,
so I can remember everyone
and what we did.
I worked for a paper
company all these years,
and I never
wrote anything down.
I sold paper at this
company for 12 years.
My job was to speak
to clients on the phone
aboutquanfifies
and types of copier paper.
Even if I didn't love
every minute of it,
everything I have,
I owe to this job.
This stupid,
wonderful, boring,
amazing job.
I thought it was weird when you
picked us to make a documentary,
but all in all,
I think an ordinary paper
company like Dunder Mifflin
was a great subject
for a documentary.
There's a lot of beauty
in ordinary things.
Isn't that kind of the point?