Uh-oh.
She's doing it again.
Phyllis has gotten
into audio books.
And lately she's been listening
to Fifty Shades Of Grey,
which, if you don't know what
it is, it's a book about, um...
It's porn.
Yeah.
Seriously?
This is unacceptable.
It's officially
a hostile work environment.
Why'?
Somebodyjust needs
to get her attention,
tell her it's not okay
to do this in public.
Be careful. I pulled
my mom's dog
off a pillow once,
and I got bit.
Just ignore her. Sooner
or later, she'll finish.
Oh, Meredith! Good lord.
What?
Phyllis is masturbating.
In the office
right now as we speak.
Can we skip
the color commentary
and just have Andy go
out there and fire her?
He can't do that.
Turns out she's allowed to have
feelings of sexual arousal.
Doesn't become a violation till
she physically acts on it.
- How do you propose that...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Why is Phyllis so aroused?
She's listening to
Fifty Shades Of Grey.
Well, there you go.
That's muy caliente.
Okay, you are useless.
I'll take care of this.
What the hell?
It's okay, guys.
She's no longer horny.
Excuse me,
dirty birdie.
What?
You can have this back
at the end of the day.
Okay-
Clark, I need
your advice.
I'm having
some lady troubles.
What's her name?
Esther Brueger.
Sweet.
Lives on the neighboring
farm. 85 acres.
Yeah. Keep talking.
Well, we've been out three times.
There has been physicality.
The thing is,
we were hanging out
with her father
the other night,
looking at a farm catalogue,
next thing I know
he wants to lease
a tractor with me.
Oh!
What do you think?
The same thing
that you think.
Long-term tractor leases can put
pressure on a relationship.
God, a lot of my buddies are going
through the same thing right now.
Something in the air.
Here you go.
And good
for you, Dwight.
I'm so glad
you found someone.
I bet she's got
kind eyes.
Dwight is dating a Brussels
sprout farmer named Esther.
She's coming here this
afternoon with her father.
Who knows? Maybe she'll be
pulling the horse cart.
Cece has been calling me Pamela.
Like, four times this week.
Oh, man!
I wonder if she'll
start calling you Jim.
Oh, boy!
Please don't.
I know.
Let's not
let that happen.
Um...
What was I gonna...
What was I gonna say?
You know,
your assistant told me
that you have a big
pitch meeting today.
With Ryan Howard.
How did that happen?
Not that Ryan Howard.
The Phillies' first baseman.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, yeah.
Exactly.
Oh.
Um...
Okay. Well...
Yeah. So, I'll talk
to you later?
Yeah, sounds good. Okay.
Yup. Okay, great.
Bye.
What's going on? Did Gangnam
Style put out a new song?
There's a promo for the
documentary on the web.
Play it again.
The boss.
There's Michael.
The workers.
The lives.
The loves.
The people.
The paper.
The Office:
An American Workplace.
Coming soon on WVIA.
You go to the bathroom for 45
minutes, and everything changes.
This is a documentary?
Oh!
I always thought we were, like,
specimens in a human zoo.
Did you see this?
Your screen is all black. You
just unplugged your computer.
Oh, my God. Is that you and Jim?
Uh-huh.
Jeez!
You fell in love
with that hair? Really?
Yikes!
That is awful.
It wasn't so bad.
Guys, are you reading
the online comments?
Somebody commented
on my banjo playing.
"Banjo at 0:19 is a'ight."
Internet, calm down!
I must have really
connected with this guy.
I mean, that's a guy's name, right?
Chobblegobbler?
Hey, man, how you doing?
Jim Halpert.
Nice to meet you.
Eat fresh.
Hey, man. Darryl.
Hey, man. Ryan.
Nice to meet you.
Eat fresh. Eat fresh.
Let's go to
the conference room.
Esther's on her way up.
I wonder if she wants a snack.
Let me see. I know she
likes apples and carrots.
I bet she does.
I bet she'll eat 'em right out of your
hand with those big, strong teeth.
Did I tell you
about her teeth?
Hey, Dwight,
you have some guests.
I think they're from the forest
where we harvest our paper.
Yes.
Ah!
The Brueger family. Welcome.
Fine office you have here.
Sturdy walls.
Yes. Esther. You look
radiant as always.
Thank you.
I guess men find
Esther attractive.
I mean, if there are
chubby chasers,
then there are men
that like that thing.
Weird to see how we used
to look in those promos.
Some of us have
changed so much.
We've all changed.
With our firm,
you'll be building equity
for long after they
retire your number.
And we all know baseball
does not last forever.
I look at these actors
on TV, and I think,
"Come on. I can do that."
Right?
Watch this. Eat fresh.
Now, what does that
make you think of?
Subway sandwiches.
Yeah.
How? I didn't say,
"Subway sandwiches."
It's called
playing the subtext.
Wow.
I actually wrote
a screenplay.
It's called The Big Piece.
Based on his nickname.
I like it already.
Let me guess,
it's autobiographical.
Half biopic,
half superhero movie.
The mild-mannered
professional baseball player
Ryan Howard
hits a home run...
Okay.
...into outer space.
Ball comes back
with space dust on it,
which transforms him
into the Big Piece.
Big Piece. The
space dust doesit
Space dust.
Okay.
I actually brought
some copies of my script,
if you guys want
to read it together.
Sure, yeah. Hollywood.
All right. Yeah,
we're gonna read it.
Okay, great.
Andy, are there
documentary groupies?
Of course there are.
Of course.
A little ironic that I'm
gonna be kind of a TV star,
because my last
Chad Flenderman novel
was based on
a murdered TV star.
The Small Scream.
I don't care.
Hey, guys, I just
found another promo.
- It's in Danish.
- Danish?
I guess it's gonna start
airing in Denmark.
Oh, my God.
What was that
word they said
when they showed me?
Skrald mand?
What's that mean
in Danish?
IICOOI guy“?
"Dumpster man."
Cool. Superhero.
What about me'?
Cloken tre pige.
Tre pige. "3:00 p.m. girl."
What? Why would they...
Wait a second. Wait a second.
What was that?
I didn't know
they were filming then.
It looks like the cameraman was
hiding behind the shelves.
Wait, so they were
filming all the time,
even when we didn't
know it?
Oh, my God.
There is much more secret
filming than I expected.
But I am fine with it,
I mean it. lam.
Are you kidding me? It's like
half the show is secret footage.
I am a very
private person.
I show 'em when I
want to show 'em.
Who wants a taste?
Boob sauce!
Meredith!
Oh, my God. Do they film us
at night when we're sleeping?
Yes, Erin. They film us at
night when we're sleeping
'cause that
makes great TV.
Hey. Oscar.
I'm sorry, sweetie. This whole
thing is just freaking me out.
I have been very
honest with you guys,
in a way that could
seriously impact
the political career of a
very good friend of mine.
You're not gonna use
any of that, are you?
People, relax.
We are killing it online.
Have you guys
checked the comments?
Smokethatskinwagon says,
"You guys are killing it."
I mean, we're Internet
sensations, guys.
I think we need to figure
out what's going on.
I mightjust
take a little walk.
Yes, a little walk
sounds like a good idea.
Okay-
Okay, everyone,
turn off your mikes.
We need to know more.
Did those shots have sound?
What exactly did
they get on tape?
Isneezed into my hands
without using Purell
and then dipped
into the candyjar.
Did they film that?
My first week here, I sneezed
directly into the candyjar
becauselthought I'd get more
screen time as a villain.
Okay, Pam, why don't
you visit your buddy,
the crew guy that got fired,
find out what they got?
- Bflan?
- Yeah
Yeah, I guess I could.
Hurry, Pam. I need to know how much
hellfire is gonna rain down on me.
I thought Teri
knew about Cynthia.
She does, but neither of
them know about Lydia.
Oh.
Whoa!
Okay, so what's
this lever do?
That manipulates
the secondary shaft.
The secondary shaft.
Mmm-hmm.
The lift capacity's up to 2,000 pounds.
That's a lot of beets.
Let's talk terms.
If you agree to a 40:60
split on this tractor,
I'll store it in
one of my barns.
Mr. Brueger, are you trying
to take advantage of me
because I'm interested
in your daughter?
50:50 split,
or no deal.
Esther, get in the truck.
No, wait, okay, wait.
You win.
Let's get
the paperwork started.
We should buy
an auger together.
Oh.
Yeah. Yeah,
we should do that.
You would be a great one
to buy an auger with.
Hello, honey, I just spoke
to the TV repairman,
and he says we need to
keep our TVs turned off
for a couple
of months.
Something about
the wiring.
Oh! Seven new comments.
"The guy at 0:19 is hawt."
"Hi, bongripper, it's me,
Andy, the guy from 0:19.
"I'm glad that you enjoyed
my work in that promo.
"I really enjoyed
your comment.
"Going to read some more comments now.
Have a great day!"
"He's not hawt.
He's gay."
"Dear JasonJasonJason, it's me, Andy.
Nice name. Not!
"Guess what? I'm not gay.
So, you're an idiot.
"And I am hawt, according to people
on this site who have a brain.
"Never comment on
this page ever again."
"He is hawt." See? Thank you.
That's more like it.
"He is butt."
Damn it!
I'm about to lose
my freaking mind!
Screw you, TexasPoonTappa.
Oh.
Security deposit.
That's been...
Standard.
Right. Standard.
Hey, can I talk to you for one second?
Not now.
Just one second.
No. No.
I'm closing a deal on a
tractor with the father
of a woman
I plan to inseminate.
Don't do it.
What?
Don't you cap
that pen.
Do not cap
that pen! Do not!
You capped it!
Wow. You are serious. Okay,
you've got two minutes.
Then the cap comes off.
Dude, we're
being conned.
Go on.
These chicks are way
too hot to be into us.
Esther's just pretending
to like you,
so that you'll buy her
daddy a new tractor.
No.
Yeah, the sister's
trying to seduce me
into buying
an auger with her.
What? Has the warranty expired
on the auger you have now?
I don't even know
what an auger is.
No woman would
ever want a man
who doesn't know
what an auger is.
Hey. You ready to sign?
I just need a moment
to consider your offer.
Excuse me.
Oh, hey.
Hey.
Hi.
I'm sorry. Do you have a minute?
Is this a bad time?
No, no. Please, yeah.
Come on in.
Good to see you. Sorry. My
place is usually not this...
Oh, my gosh,
please, don't.
Actually, it's always
like this.
You want to go outside? It's a
little less cluttered out there.
Sure. Yeah.
Yeah?
Let me grab a couple drinks.
Okay.
Wow. You have
a nice view.
All right.
That's for you.
Thank you.
Cheers.
All right. How much have
you revealed on camera
about your relationship
with the Senator?
They caught us
kissing on Halloween.
He was dressed
like Ronald Reagan!
God.
Ow! Angela!
Well, he kissed
like Jack Kennedy. Oh.
Stop it.
Stop kissing him.
Someone needs to call and warn him.
This could ruin his career.
Idon%Hke
giving him bad news.
Call him!
You call him!
Call him! Call him!
Stop hitting me! No!
So...
What brings you by?
Well, the promo for the
documentary aired today.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
It's kind of crazy. It is.
See all this,
like, old stuff.
I know.
There's that shot of Jim
and I up on the roof.
Yeah, that was
a good moment.
Yeah, wasn't that neat?
Yeah, that was cool.
Yeah.
And there's this one
when we were listening
to music,
and it's like,
it's like
we were in love,
we didn't even know
we were in love.
But do you think
Jim's changed?
Um...
I'm sorry. Did that... But
that was out of the blue.
I just mean,
because you know us,
and you've observed
us for 10 years,
and I feel like he's...
I just feel like he's so into
his work right now, and...
I don't know.
Am I crazy?
No, you're not crazy.
Well, I wish
that made me feel better.
Listen, so, everybody
saw the promos,
and they're kind
of freaking out.
'Cause it seems like you got a
lot of private stuff on camera.
Yeah.
Stuff people didn't intend
for everyone to see,
and they kind of
want to know how much.
They want to know
how much what?
How much stuff you got.
Pretty much everything.
Well, yeah, but what if we
turn off our mike packs?
They've got parabolic mikes. They
can pick you up 100 yards away.
So, no, if you were
around there, they got you.
So, we basically had no
privacy for 10 years.
That's not really true.
I mean...
Um...
Yeah, I gotta go.
No, hang on a second.
Pam, I'm sorry.
I can explain this
so much better.
No, I think
you explained it.
Look, if you give me
a chance, I can... Pam...
"Together we will win
this baseball game
"against the Evil
Space Yankees. Eat fresh."
That'll pay for
the exploding helicopter.
Smart.
Mmm-hmm.
"Suddenly, the evil thugs
break into the stadium.
"The Big Piece hits baseballs
at the evil thugs."
"Buy me some peanuts
and crackerjacks."
Come on, man. Sell it.
Yeah, Jim.
"Buy me some peanuts
and crackerjacks!"
Yeah, that's better.
"A bunch of hot women
go, 'Oh, yeah!"'
"Megan, I was too shy
to tell you this
"when I was just a normal
professional baseball player,
"but I love you."
"They kiss. It is super emotional.
Like in Toy Story."
Wow.
I tell you what.
It's really strong.
Can't wait to read the rest
of it later, see how it ends.
It's so strong.
Keep reading then.
"Gotta go. Darth Vader's
launching a huge attack."
Um, another thing.
I'm gonna need you
to get me the rights
to Darth Vader.
I don't know how we'd go
about doing that, but...
We can look into it.
We'll look into it.
We need Darth.
We gotta get him.
Go after Darth then.
We're gonna go get him.
That's what
we're gonna do.
We're gonna go
get him.
Maybe you're right.
Esther's a 10,
and the best I've
ever done is Angela,
who's a nine,
and she rejected me.
A Scranton nine,
but, yeah, point taken.
Hey, let's go out tonight and just
score a couple of fours, huh?
I mean, there are
no games with fours.
Who needs a new
tractor anyway?
Maybe we're the kind of guys
who end up with a tractor
that's already been rode
hard and put away muddy.
Screw new tractors.
Guys like us,
we got to plant
our seed a different way.
By hand.
Dwight. We need to talk.
I don't know that
there's anything
left for us to
talk about, Esther.
Look, we're gonna
have the tractor
for the same amount
of work days,
but my dad is planning
on leasing it
to the Vanderkirk
brothers on the weekends.
No.
So, you're gonna be
paying more,
but he's putting on
10 times the miles,
and he's pocketing
a profit behind your back.
Thatsnake!
You need to tell him you
want a deal based on miles,
or he can just stick that tractor
where the sun don't shine.
That shady grove
out by Willard's Pond.
So, you're fine with me
not leasing the tractor?
I mean, our courtship can proceed?
Of course.
You didn't think I was just
tractor bait, did you?
No.
Yeah.
Hey, Dwight.
What's an auger used for?
Post hole digging.
You've reached Senator
Robert Lipton. Please leave a message.
', honey.
Go. No, go ahead.
No, you go.
Hi, honey.
Hey, Robert.
It's Angela and Oscar.
Hey.
Just a few quick things.
The documentary's going
to be airing soon,
and you look great
in the promos.
You look so handsome.
Very presidential.
Very much so. Absolutely. Yeah.
Hey, I get the sense you're
gonna be outed as gay.
Yes, and I cheated
on you with Dwight.
It looks like they got it on film.
I didn't tell you about it.
I think that's it.
I think we're good.
Done. Okay.
Bye. Love you.
Hey, TexasPoonTappa
and JasonJasonJason
and all the rest of you haters
out there, check this out.
Good night, Andy.
Yeah. See ya.
Oh!
What?
I hope you got sound on everything.
I'd love a DVD of that.