Uh, what else? I've seen
Dirty Dancing like, ten times...
- Breaks my heart every time, you know?
- Whoa!
Andy!
That Swayze sure
can dance dirty.
Don't you have
any sunblock?
No, Walter J's
been hoarding it.
If you want to worry about a part
of my body, worry about my eyes.
They're like two flaming
meatballs in my skull.
Last week, Andy set sail for the
Bahamas to sell his family's boat.
And he took his
brother but not me.
I was kind of sad at first, but then
I remembered that Bob Marley song,
"No, woman. No cry!"
Check this out.
Keeps my hair
out of my stare.
Also helps me
combat the Glare Bear.
That's what I
call the sun now.
Andy, it's Darryl. Take
your drawers off your head.
What else can I show you?
Damn it!
Oh, Andy, was that
your drinking water?
Yeah, it was. That's okay, though.
I've got this cool
desalinator device.
It sucks up sea water through this
hose and pumps out fresh water.
See? Check it out.
Ow!
That's not good.
I'd better sign off.
I need to get going.
I mean, these Skype sessions
are, like, the only thing
that keep me sane
out here, you know?
He's been
sailing for two days.
I'll leave you with this, the
image of a man and his boat!
Burn this into your brains!
Yeah.
No.No, No!
Andy? Andy? Andy? Andy?
Dwight Schrute.
Well, hi there,
David Wallace.
Why would you ever call me when
the manager is out of town?
Well, I have some
very exciting news.
And you didn't call Jim.
That seems significant.
Hi, David! Jim, good. You
should hear this, too.
No, he shouldn't!
What? Jim!
Go ahead, David.
I'm listening.
I... Okay, David, I want
to take you off speaker.
But I don't know
where I'd put you.
Guys, listen.
This is big news.
The Scranton White Pages just
got in contact with my office.
They have apparently dropped their
supplier for the last ten years.
The White Pages.
Do you want it? No.
Do you use it? No.
Does it inexplicably show up on
your doorstep three times a year?
Yes, yes and yes.
There is a reason we
in the paper industry
call this thing
the White Whale.
Look at all
that sweet blubber.
Look, we need our
top salesman
running point on this,
and Dwight, that is you.
I'm going to need to
put you on hold for a second.
Yeah! Whoo!
Eat it, Jim!
Eat it, Phyllis! Eat...
Where's Stanley?
He's in the bathroom.
Will you run into the bathroom
and tell him to eat it?
Of course.
Yeah! Okay.
Hey, David, I'm back.
Eat it, Stanley!
So, last I remember Tom Peterman
was in charge of that account?
No, my assistant spoke to the
receptionist over there.
It's someone new but she
didn't catch her name.
Her name?
No. Hey, Dwight shouldn't...
Thanks, David! Thank you so
much for calling me today.
Good luck!
Good luck to you.
Dwight, you can't go.
You have a problem with women.
You can't sell to them.
That's a damnable lie.
I love women.
Gina Rogers at Apex Technology
said you called her "Jine-a"
for your entire meeting.
NELLIEI EW.
That's not good.
Yeah, she said she
corrected him five times.
"Jine-a" said that?
Guys, we can't let
Dwight blow this!
An account this size
could double our gross!
That means raises, bonuses.
Pizza Friday could come back.
Hey, remember that week in
the '90s when we got bagels?
I miss Clinton.
Can you go instead?
Can't. I have the thing.
I have this conference call
today with this company
in Philly
that I'm helping start.
First board meeting.
Also the first time I've ever
been excited about work,
so, that feels
wrong.
Okay, calm down, it's
just me, not Tom Selleck.
Nice.
Toby got us all to
participate in Movember.
It's a charity
for prostate cancer.
You pledge money and
then you grow a mustache
for the month of November.
So, this is how
we look now.
I hope you like being
turned on all the time.
Damn!
Just keeps on coming, huh?
I have very
fertile hair glands.
I am so glad I got all of
the dudes to do Movember.
We have the dopest
time back in the annex.
God.
We even go to lunch,
pick up babes.
Smile if you love
men's prostates!
Hi.
Spring cleaning?
More like fall cleaning.
I think the Senator
is having an affair.
This doesn't...
I'm sorry, what?
I think the Senator
is having an affair.
I literally have nightmares in
which what just happened happens.
I wake up in a sweat,
and then I make Angela's
husband spoon me back to bed.
When he comes home
in the morning,
he has this
secret little smile.
Aww...
I'm sure that's nothing.
And he's always
at the yoga studio.
He never misses
the noon class.
Hot Yoga with Blake.
Angela,
Blake is also a guy's name,
so he may be spending his
afternoons with a guy named Blake,
so nothing to worry about.
Huh.
Blake. Who's Blake?
I don't know.
I've just never heard
about the Senator and yoga.
Right.
From you.
I'm sure it's
probably nothing.
But what's with
the yoga already?
Right?
And Blake?
Right! All right,
Angela, calm down.
We need to go and check this out.
What?
Angela, I'll go with you.
So, show us how you'd normally
sell to a female client.
Okay, with pleasure.
Time to learn a few
new tricks, old dog.
You got this, Schrute.
You've just walked
into her office and begin.
Hello.
May I please
speak to your boss?
No, she is the boss.
I am?
Yes.
Hi, I'm Mr. Hannon,
how can I help you?
Okay, this isn't
working for me,
because no one would ever believe
that she would be a boss.
He's absolutely right,
I'm really struggling here.
I'll be the buyer.
Okay-
Hello, Mr. Schrute, nice to see you.
Please have a seat.
I never sit down
during sales meetings.
I want to appear
aggressive and imposing.
I am going to sell to
you in 12 minutes.
No, actually, she'd like to take
her time discussing her needs.
I will tell her what her needs
are and then fill them.
This is going to
work out best for you
if you just relax
and do nothing.
And once I'm finished,
it's over.
Okay, let's stop here.
Anyone have any thoughts?
I thought it went great.
I have written down
a few questions.
One, have you ever
killed a woman?
How many women
have you killed?
Please sir,
will you not kill me?
Okay,
let's get started.
Okay, cool. Are we all on?
Well, you're the only one
"on." We're all here.
Right.
Okay, over the next
three months, I...
That's the winter season,
three months.
I had some ideas actually...
Are you at your
office right now?
Yeah. Trust me, I would
rather be with you guys.
Okay. Yeah,
it's sounding kind of
spooky-sexy
over here, Halpert.
Oh.
Sorry. I was
saying that you should probably...
Whoa.
I think there's... I think
there's been a mistake.
We're trying to reach Jim
Halpert, not Batman.
You know what?
I should have just had...
I should have just had you
call me on my cell.
Yeah. I'll... I'm going to
try a different spot. Okay?
Okay, yeah. Okay. I'll
call you right back.
Cool. What's happening
in three months?
Okay, when you're
selling to women,
it is crucial that
you listen, Dwight.
Also, you want to
respect their...
Are you listening now?
Yes.
Okay, well,
you have to show us.
That's impossible. Listening happens
in the ear and in the brain.
I mean, some organisms
have external hairs
that vibrate to
indicate auditory stimulation,
but unfortunately our external
hairs don't vibrate at all.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
What are you doing?
A little smile and a nod shows
that I hear you. Got it?
Kind of.
Nellie,
why don't you tell Dwight
what we were
doing earlier today,
and Dwight, you show us
that you're listening.
Well, we were in the warehouse
where we were discussing the mural
that I've commissioned
Pam to paint there.
We were talking about
the color schemes
and the major themes
we want to hit.
Children of the world
coming together,
cutting down trees
to make paper,
but not in
a child labor-y way.
It's just up and down, just a
regular nod, like a person.
I am a person.
Yes. Yeah.
Of course. You're a person.
We can do this. All right?
And then we thought we'd...
I can't. I just, I can't carry
on with that face. Look at it.
I'm going to get
nightmares with that face.
I mean, he looks like
he's laboring over
a stool having just
eaten human flesh.
That's a bit extreme.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but that is true.
He's screwed! The meeting
is in less than an hour.
All right, God, Dwight, just
ignore every instinct you have.
It's all garbage. Okay?
You're the woman,
I'm the salesman.
Watch what I do
and try to learn.
Okay, I'm the woman. I'm a woman. Good?
No.
Ms. Thomas!
So good to see you.
Hello.
Are those your kids?
They're so cute.
They could be models.
Thank you.
I'm so proud of them.
I carried each one of them for
nine months inside of my torso
and then pushed
them out of my vagina.
Boo. Weird.
Okay, well, this is a lost cause.
He's hopeless.
Ten years ago I didn't care if Dwight got
married or died a beet farming bachelor.
But having kids
makes you so soft.
I used to watch Pulp Fiction
and laugh, and now I'm like,
that poor Gimp
is somebody's child.
You know, I think there
could be a lot of benefits
if you could learn to
get along with women.
I have no problem with women.
It's business women
and their...
Their power suits
and their shoulder pads.
Don't lie about
your shoulders!
Dwight, listen to me.
Business women are just normal,
nice, reasonable people.
Who's a nice, reasonable
person, in your experience?
I had a barber once who used
to comb my hair gently.
Okay. So, when you're
selling to this woman,
just imagine she's that nice,
reasonable barber.
Okay. I can do that.
Good. Baby steps.
He used to fight dogs.
Like, he used to make dogs fight,
or he actually fought dogs?
Little of this,
little of that.
Which one is
the instructor?
They're all fatties.
Angela. Angela.
What? Where?
The stairs,
the stairs.
Oh, my God.
So wait, Blake is a her.
Oh, my God!
She's so stunningly tiny.
She's like a petite double
zero, for sure. For sure.
Holy cow,
look at what they're doing.
She's repositioning his hips
for Downward Facing Dog.
I've heard of this.
D°9 Style!
Wait! Look, Oscar!
Thumbelina has a boyfriend.
And he has a ponytail. Ew.
I'd like to see
that run for office.
Oscar, you were right, I had
nothing to be worried about.
Thank you.
Let's go, let's go.
Shut up. Hold on. Hold on.
Hold on. Just, sorry.
Look.
This is fun.
You know?
I mean, this is fun.
What I was saying
is the genius of
Air Jordan was not in
the market saturation,
it was...
It was what?
Sorry...
Jim we're having a lot
of trouble hearing you.
The... What I was saying is, the real
genius was in the...
Hey! Are those
skateboarders back?
Jim? Jim, are you there?
Where are they?
The little punks!
It was in
the authentic design, right?
So, I mean,
you really felt like
Michael Jordan was wearing
these shoes for...
Jim, who's messing with my van?
Nobody.
Jordan wore them for nobody?
No, no. We're not
following you, Halpert.
This ends now!
Have a seat.
She will be right in.
Great. I'm sorry, do you
mind telling me her name?
I realize we don't have it.
Uh, she'll be right in.
Okay, great.
She'll...
Okay-
Just a little off the top,
and then a nice combing.
Yeah. Just comb it.
Oh, my God.
It's Jan.
Dear God in heaven.
Jan used to be
one of my superiors,
and she is one of
the most erratic
and terrifying people
I have ever met.
You son of a bitch! You're firing me?
I answered you...
Where the hell do you get off?
Jim and I are pretty sure she had
an affair with her ex-assistant, Hunter.
He was 17.
But she looks great!
If she asks, will you
tell her I said that?
Forget
everything we taught you!
Hey, Jan!
It's so great to see you.
Where's Wallace?
What?
I was under the impression
David Wallace would be coming.
He bought back
Dunder Mifflin, correct?
Hey!
Your daughter could
be a bubble bath model.
I could just
bite her head off.
Sorry.
David is in Vermont.
Did you speak with him?
He sent Dwight instead.
Molly!
David Wallace
is in Vermont.
Oh, my God.
I talked to his assistant,
and I guess it did
get a little confusing
because you said not
to tell anyone your name.
And then also, these Bluetooths
are very hard to hear with.
I know you love
the way they look,
but Tom never had
us use them, so...
Molly? I am not Tom. lam Jan.
I'm so sorry, Jan.
Anyway-
Thought it would be fun to
have a little chat with
David Wallace
after all these years.
Oh, Well.
What are you doing?
Listening.
- Stop.
- Sorry.
Stop that.
Okay.
So, this was all just a trick? You don't
really have any business to give?
No, I do.
But not to us.
Insightful, Pam.
You did good, Dwight. It's okay.
Seriously, Jan's not normal.
Let's just go. She's not
going to sell to us.
Yes, she is.
Now, I may not have
any instincts with women,
butlhave
an instinct for sales.
You keep her occupied,
I'll be right back.
What?
Pam.
Yeah?
I'm a very
busy woman, so...
Yeah, do you have any
other pictures of Astrid?
Fine, I will show you
one slideshow.
Erin, did this call come...
Sorry. I just...
I saw your face.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
It's for the thing.
I know. That's great.
It just, it makes it look
like there's an eyebrow
in the middle of your face.
Wow.
A handsome eyebrow! But it makes
your mouth look like an eye socket.
Which isn't bad!
Uh-huh. Butyoulook
like a cyclops
whose eye fell out.
Which is great.
It's such a great cause.
Yeah.
Mommy, you're a princess
Mommy, you're a superstar
Mommy, you're the greatest
How can I ever
fill your shoes?
Your voice is
as lovely as ever.
Oh...
And it is so cute
how she signs her name.
That was... That was me, too.
Okay. It's just, that's how Cece
does it, with the backwards Es.
Cece can't spell her name?
Actually, she can.
Well, it's not really much
of a comparison, is it?
I mean, "Cece" is two
letters, and "Astrid" is...
I mean, there's even some
adults who can't spell it.
Of course.
Can you spell it?
Try to spell it, Pam.
Um...
"A,"
"X"? I don't...
You got me.
Don't patronize me.
I'm so sorry. I hate this.
You're better.
Okay, we should go now.
Let's go.
Wait, just... Just
waitjust a minute. Just watch.
Wait, why are you... Oh. Are you
getting yourjollies right now?
Can't get enough
of the show?
Yourjollies
are all on fire.
Please! It's Robert
who's enjoying it!
What?
This could be the affair
that you're scared of.
Politicians are
wonderful liars.
You never know
who they really are.
But he's probably not gay.
He's straight.
He's straight, so...
Excuse me, could I get
some more water? No.
Jan, you thought I had no
more cards left to play.
Well, I've got one.
Man-Boy!
The Ace of Babes.
Oh, my God.
Where's the Quiznos?
You're the Quiznos.
Jan, may I introduce
to you,
your own personal
Dunder Mifflin liaison,
devoted to servicing this account
with total client satisfaction.
I sense that Molly
wasn't quite
meeting your needs.
Nothing like
your old assistant.
Hunter,
was that his name?
I... I don't recall.
And yes, Molly is crap.
Okay, you do not
have to do this.
Do what? Get into sales?
That's what I want.
He's been growing
that mustache for weeks.
Best he can do.
So young.
Will you...
You. Can you
turn around for me, please?
Dwight, you can go. I will
call you in a week or so
and let you know whether
I want your business.
Thank you.
Very good.
Do you have
a valid passport?
Jim Halpert.
Hey, it's Colin.
Hey, man.
lam so sorry about that.
No, don't worry about it.
It's just,
it's not totally working.
Yeah, no, I know. This whole
telecommuting thing, not ideal.
But don't worry,
I'll figure it out.
Yeah, it's not just not ideal.
I mean, with you there,
I don't know how
we're going to do this.
What does...
What does that mean?
Oscar, what is
happening here?
Why would you say you think
the Senator might be gay?
I don't know, Angela.
I'm dehydrated.
Maybe you heard me wrong.
We should just go.
Look, look, here he comes! Here he comes.
He's coming, he's coming.
What is he doing? He's
making a phone call.
Hey, Molly.
You should just quit.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Oh, and Molly?
I know it can't be easy working for Jan.
Good luck with your feelings.
Dwight!
That was really nice.
You should ask
for her number.
I got her number.
Four-one-five-Y-C-L.
That's a license number?
That's all you need.
And when I have curried favor
with her, I will let you know.
Why me?
Because you are my friend
and you are a woman.
And women love gossip.
It's like air to you people.
Ugh. God!