All right, everybody,
great season of softball.
I'm super proud
of you guys,
and I think you're
going to like this
little highlight reel
that I've put together.
GROUP". Dunder Mifflin!
ANDY". Andy Bernard presents,
"Summer Softball Epic Fails!"
Fail.
Fail!
That's me!
Fail. Is this like
a blooper reel?
A blooper reel?
What is this, 2005?
Do I look like
Bob Saget? Fail!
Who's this guy?
♪ Meow, meow, meow, meow.
Look at him dance!
Fail!
Fail.
I deserved that.
Do-dee-do-dee-do
That was a triple.
Can't take the fail?
Get out of the fail video!
My pleasure.
Hi, I'm Pete!
Puberty is such a drag, man.
And I'm Clark, I like to
eat toilet paper. We fail!
I'd like to take a solemn
moment to remember
Jerry in the warehouse,
who passed away this year.
Well, that's all, folks!
Ski you later, everybody! Thanks for
a great season.
What was that? That was just normal
video with you making vulgar noises.
Well, I worked with
what I had, Oscar.
Next time do more
fail-ier stuff, okay?
What happened to
that video I sent you?
Oh, that wasn't... That didn't work.
That was not the right...
I think
I've got it right here.
No.
Oh!
That was not a fail!
Fail! Fail! Fail!
That was actually
a serious accident
that could have resulted
in severe bodily harm.
Fail! Fail! Fail!
You're all failing right now.
Congratulations on your epic fail
of the use of the word "fail!"
Oh, God.
What's going on?
Nothing!
Nothing is going on.
Keep moving, please.
What's he measuring?
Okay, excuse me,
lam the landlord.
This is between me and the
management, no one else. Please.
It's an EMF hotspot.
Oh, my God!
It stands for
electromagnetic field,
generally caused
by a concentration
of wiring in one area,
especially if
poorly insulated, Dwight.
Um.
Okay, I'm just
walking in to this.
Am I to understand there's
a beehive in the wall?
You think I have a machine
for measuring beehives?
I was just asking
a question, Toby.
How are you not
murdered every hour?
Well, I'm not getting paid
to work in a microwave oven.
Okay, listen.
Everything here is up to code.
"Oh, the wires
need insulation."
It's a wire, people.
I'm not buying it a fur coat.
Thank you.
You got it.
Last week, I finally told Pam
about the other job I took in Philly,
the side job, and she was so
incredibly cool about it.
And now I just want to do
something huge for her.
Like if we were
in some biker bar
and she mouthed
off to some bikers
and they came lumbering over
and I was like... Wham!
"You've got to go
through me first!"
Andy, could I have
a word, please?
It won't take a moment,
it's extremely important,
and it really
has to happen now.
Fine. I will
give you one minute.
Oh, please don't
use the hourglass.
You have one minute
and your minute has begun,
and no time will
be added at the end,
even to accommodate
this sentence,
with all of its
baroque dependent clauses
and cascading
turns of phrase.
I'm trying
to adopt a baby.
A baby what?
A human?
And the agency requires a character
reference from my employer.
Oh.
You wouldn't have to do anything.
I'd write the letter myself.
You'd just simply
sign it. So...
Okay-
And fall right into your
plagiarism entrapment scheme?
I don't think so.
It's... No, it's...
And I happen to notice you're
down to about 30 seconds here.
If I could just
convince you that you...
And those sand grains are
tumbling with
fury down the side...
It's not entrapment
if I'm writing...
...of the hourglass.
Time's up!
Fine.
Sure, I'll read
her letter.
And if she tells the truth
about how evil and unfit
to be a mother she is, then,
yeah, I'll sign that.
"Statistical correlations
exist between EMF
"radiation and
various health hazards,
"but mainstream
studies are inconclusive."
That means you
can't make me do squat.
You better fix this!
I already ditched my uterus, and I
ain't losing any more good parts!
You people don't
realize what you're asking.
I'd have to rip
open the walls.
We'd have to shut this
place down for a week.
A week off,
that'd be great.
Hey, if you don't want to teach
me the PowerPoint, just say so.
I don't want to
teach you PowerPoint.
Come on.
Just show me the PowerPoint.
Just do the tutorial!
You're the tutorial.
No, dude, I'm not.
I'm not the tutorial.
You could be.
Mmm-mmm.
What are you doing?
Getting my wife
a week off from work.
You popped one kernel.
Awesome, right?
So Creed is that
dude's stepdad?
Correct.
Well, I don't know about the rest of
you, but I'm just going to say it.
I'm nervous.
I have no idea what
health problems this
is all going to cause.
What? Come on.
I'm sorry.
I'm not growing a third arm.
I know what Jim
is trying to do.
He's trying to
get Big Bad Dwight
to shell out for
a huge repairjob
while lucky Jimbo
gets a paid vacation.
Well, sorry, lucky Jimbo.
I can live very
happily in a magnetic field.
Most of my childhood heroes
got their powers that way.
"Side effects of EMF
include headaches."
Had them all my life.
"Breast pain."
No knobbies, no probbies.
Nice try, Jim.
O01'. "infertility."
Yeah, right.
Ah.
There's my popcorn.
Can you just grab that for me?
Keep your snacks on
your side, Jim, idiot.
What the...
What?
Some of these
kernels have crowned.
That's impossible, becausethafs
a brand-new bag...
Oh, my God.
Andy!
I'm going to drive
you up to the lake.
Give you a whole week on the
water, just you, me and the kids.
Can we stop by that
pie stand on the way?
You mean Laverne's Pies Tires Fixed Also?
Yes, we will be doing that.
We'll be getting a dozen.
A dozen different pies?
'Cause that means rhubarb.
Why would you say that? I meant
four apple, four blueberry,
two cherry, one peach, one chocolate.
I thought that was implied.
Yeah, okay, then.
Ladies and gentlemen!
I have heard your complaints
and we reached
a settlement.
So, we will be leaving the
office for one whole week.
Nice job.
In my contract
it is stipulated
that I provide
a temporary workspace.
It will arrive in one hour.
What?
What's this?
Whoa. What?
Bring it in.
Roll into
the future with Work Bus.
Say goodbye to
wasteful buildings.
These days a mobile office
isn'tjust for hotshot politicians.
Now anyone can
rent a work bus.
If you've got a parking lot, a work
space is just a phone call away.
In this age of belt-tightening
and less empowered workers,
a work bus is how tomorrow
gets things done.
They're a hundred pack...
No six pack for me.
Six. Yes.
Sorry.
Oh, my God!
Ah! Sorry.
Lose weight!
I'm trying, sorry.
Oh, The Pennsylvania Department of
Public Welfare Pre-Adoption Standard.
Oh, of course,
you were adopted.
I wish!
No, I made some short lists,
I had a couple of sleepovers,
but I never
managed to get
in the end zone.
I don't know what it was.
Not loveable, maybe.
Oh, well.
Listen, I'm really
struggling with this form.
But as you know the system, do
you think maybe you could...
Absolutely. I know exactly
what they want to hear.
I would love to help.
Oh, thank you so much!
Just, don't tell Andy,
because“.
He hates me.
Thinks I'm a monster.
Should go back to Loch Ness.
Stretch. All right.
How many times do you
need to take a stroll?
I... My legs cramp up, okay?
It's a circulation issue.
Boy, I will hammerspank
your rear.
All right, all right, gang.
Let's just settle down.
You're yelling in her face.
It's a medical thing.
Just... We good?
I'm good! All right?
I'm so sorry
for all of this.
It's okay. You know what they say,
a change is as good as a rest.
I need to get
to the paper, please.
Oh, God!
Oh!
Ah! Oh, my God!
Are you okay?
All right,
I'll get you a napkin.
Can someone get
napkins, please?
You know what? It's fine. It's fine.
Let me just... It's fine.
Pam, I'm really sorry.
I just...
I'm... I'm really
sorry about all that.
Really? Smirking?
What can I say?
I love justice.
You forced me to spend money
on needless repairs.
And now you're
locked in a prison bus
and your woman
drips with beverage.
Hey, Dwight, I was trying to
do something nice for Pam.
Can you just help me out?
Can we maybe take
this thing somewhere?
Or do something to not make
this the worst day ever?
It's not my responsibility to
solve your marriage problems
by spending my money on gas.
Andy!
Yo, Toonces.
You're the boss.
Don't you think
we'd all be
a lot more productive
if while we were doing work,
we looked up and saw
the best rural pie
stand in Pennsylvania?
I know
I'd be more productive.
As would I.
No question.
No, no,
this is a work bus.
The wheels are
for transporting
the work space to
and from the work site.
What are you talking about?
You're not the boss.
Andy is. Andy?
Pies!
Pies! Pies! Pies! Pies! Pies!
All right!
The fat people have spoken!
Dwight,
get this bus moving.
Next stop, Laverne's
Pies Tires Fixed Also!
Oh, yes!
So it looks like this work bus was
a pretty good idea after all, huh?
Get your foot
behind the yellow line.
You got it.
Stop.
Come back.
Too late.
Hmm.
Shabooya roll call! Shabooya
yaya, shabooya roll call!
My name is Pam
Yeah?
I like to paint
You think you're better?
Yeah?
Oh, no, you ain't!
Roll call!
Shabooya yaya
Shabooya roll call!
My name is Kevin
Yeah?
That is my name
They call me Kevin
Yeah?
'Cause that's my name
Roll call!
Shabooya yaya
Shabooya roll call!
Thanks. Playing a little
hookey from work today.
Oh, my God!
Dunder Mifflin
road trip 2012!
Okay, now a serious one.
Hey, where's Dwight?
He should be a part of this.
Has he been acting kind
of weird to you lately?
If by lately you mean
for the last 12 years, yeah.
No, I mean he's sulking.
That's not like him.
He's just mad that
we're all having fun.
Then why isn't he scheming?
Or preparing to avenge?
He's fine.
He's indestructible.
Always say that
a child is "placed"
for adoption,
never "surrendered."
We're not hostages.
Although, I have
considered kidnapping one.
And never say that.
I am so excited thinking about this
child that you're going to adopt.
I wish I could just
wave a magic wand and
make you a parentless
five-year-old again.
I would snap you up.
Oh.
Next stop, pies.
Let's go, driver.
Laverne packs up
the pie wagon at 5:00, so...
At 5:00? That's only
20 minutes from now.
The pie shop
is 13 miles away.
So at 55 miles an hour, that just
gives us five minutes to spare!
So, wait.
When pies are involved
you can suddenly do
math in your head?
Well...
Hold on, Kevin,
how much is 19,154 pies
divided by 61 pies?
Three hundred
and fourteen pies.
What if it were salads?
Well, it's the...
Carry the four...
In the...
It doesn't work.
I'm sorry to spoil Jim's
fantastic voyage, everyone.
But we're
almost out of gas.
Okay, well, I saw a station about
a mile back, so chop-chop.
That name brand place?
No, forget about it, sorry.
The tanks are so big on this
thing, five cents a gallon extra?
It really adds up.
Are you kidding me?
Dwight, come on!
Hey, honey? I don't think
we should push him.
No, I'm going to push him.
You know why?
Because you're getting a pie.
Why? Because you deserve it!
And what is he doing? He's trying to
drive us all around the countryside
looking for gas, because he
knows we won't get there.
- Is that what we want?
- No!
Stop ordering
me around, Jim!
- What do we want?
- Pies!
- When do we want it?
Okay, fine!
You win, Jim! You win.
We have been battling for a
long time, but you know what?
You win, because you are the winner.
You are the alpha male.
There you go. Alpha male,
go buy your wife a pie.
Go buy the whole
world a pie!
That's impossible.
Dwight!
What are you doing?
What the hell?
Dwight!
Well, now I don't
even feel like pie.
Wait.
No, it's back.
Oh, just drive away. Just...
Phyllis, that's not safe.
Guys, we only have
18 minutes left.
At 61 miles an hour, we're
just going to barely make it.
Go up and check on him.
He's upset.
You know he's doing
all this on purpose.
Please just make
sure he's okay.
And hurry it up,
for God's sake!
They're going to be
out of banana cream.
Banana cream is
the first to go.
We'll be lucky to get
pumpkin at this point.
What?
Dwight?
Why are you such a jerk?
I'm trying to do
something for my wife,
and you keep derailing...
I'm barren, Jim.
What? My trouser hives
are void of honey.
I had congress with Angela,
and the child that she bore
did not issue
from my loins.
I thought I would be a father
and instead I am a eunuch,
neutered by my own building.
Is this about the popcorn,
or the X on the ceiling?
Dwight,
that was a prank.
You mean you flooded my building
with dangerous electromagnetic
radiation as a prank?
No.
That's genius. That's the
best prank you've ever done.
Ru take it.
Andy?
Who is it?
Um, is this a good time?
Yeah.
Perfect time, right in the
middle of a rooftop crisis.
Fine, let me read it.
What do we have here?
Okay.
You've made this very easy for me.
It's unsignable.
Oh.
Well, is there something...
It's inaccurate, dishonest,
and in a word, dong water.
Oh, well, perhaps I could
reword some of it to...
Here's the thing. You asked
me to do you a favor.
I did it. I read it.
Thank you very much
to me for my time.
Good luck with
your impossible dream.
All right then.
Dwight, sometimes it takes
couples years to get pregnant.
Really? How long did it take
you and Pam to conceive?
That doesn't matter. What
position did you use to conceive?
Okay, I'm not
talking about that.
Regular or
lady-on-her-back?
You used lady-on-her-back,
didn't you, freak?
Yuck, gross.
Never mind, Jim.
British women, famously
over-emotional, am I right?
I don't think that's Nellie.
What?
NELLIEI Oh.
Oh, no, no. Look, it's all right, really.
It isn't your fault.
No, no.
You were so kind,
and it isn't
anything to do with you.
Did you ever think that
because you own the building,
everyone in it, we're all
kind of like your children?
You know there's a phrase about
that in German, bildenkinder,
used almost
exclusively by childless
landlords to
console themselves.
But now I really
understand it.
Well, now you have a bus full
of real bildenkinder.
Bildenkinder. Okay, and
they're all dangerously close
to not getting pie.
And there's only one
guy who can save them.
It's not me.
I agree.
Oh.
Hey, how did it go?
It was pretty good, actually.
We bonded, we got to talk...
Oh. Wait, wait, wait!
That's what happens when
you don't get out of the way.
Out of the way!
You feel okay now?
Better than okay.
And you know what, honey?
I'm going to get
you that rhubarb pie.
Well, actually, rhubarb is...
Don't.
...the one pie that I...
Everybody, hang on!
Oh!
Whoa!
Pie! Pie! Pie! Pie! Pie!
Oh.
I changed my mind.
Oh, you signed it?
Yeah.
Not as is, obviously.
I made a couple of changes, added
some sentences at the end.
Trust me, it needed it.
But, yeah, whatever.
"She's tough in business, but tender
with the people she cares about.
"She'll make a wonderful
mother to any child
"who can
overlook weird accents."
I insult you, Oscar!
What?
I insult you,
to your face!
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Then why don't you
do something about it?
Kevin, are you
trying to get me
to hit you in
the face with my pie?
You don't have the guts,
you stupid,
dumb do-do face.
Yes!
Oh, my God,
I'm getting so stuffed.
We did it.
You did it.
My name is Andy!
Yeah?
I don't do drugs
Now check the style
Yeah?
Of Flatt and Scruggs!
Yeah
Roll call
What?